<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2022-08-11T06:28:02.048Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic On This Day – 11th August – David Potter’s Celtic Diary]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-on-this-day-11th-august-david-potters-celtic-diary/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-on-this-day-11th-august-david-potters-celtic-diary/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-11T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 11 of Celtic Historian David Potter’s new diary  on The Celtic Star  which will run throughout the new season and will highlight key Celtic related events relevant to each day, today covering 11 August…SATURDAY 11 AUGUST 1928Now minus Tommy McInally and Adam McLean, Celtic begin the new campaign with a fine 1-0 win over Dundee Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Jota's Celtic rise to stardom as Benfica mentor reveals what's set him apart from day one - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEKtGumYM7kQn_x-EFjbhVEsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/inside-jotas-celtic-rise-stardom-27708145"/>
        <updated>2022-08-11T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Jota's Celtic rise to stardom as Benfica mentor reveals what's set him apart from day one  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: BIG YOGI AND LISBON: THE TRUTH (Part Five)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-big-yogi-and-lisbon-the-truth-part-five/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-big-yogi-and-lisbon-the-truth-part-five/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-11T04:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE name of John Hughes was missing when Jock Stein named his Celtic line-up for the European Cup Final against Inter Milan in Lisbon on May 25 1967. The giant forward, lovingly known as ‘Yogi’ to his legions of fans, had played in five of the club’s eight ties during their great adventure to propel [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mat Ryan completes Copenhagen move one year after Celtic links]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/mat-ryan-completes-copenhagen-move-one-year-after-celtic-links/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/mat-ryan-completes-copenhagen-move-one-year-after-celtic-links/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T22:25:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australian goalkeeper Mat Ryan has completed a move to Copenhagen one year after he was linked with a move to Celtic. The goalkeeper signed for La Liga side Real Sociedad on a permanent deal after it became clear that he would be a second choice at Brighton under Graham Potter. Although the move to Spain Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Nope’, Croatian journalist reacts to Juranovic Manchester United link]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/nope-croatian-journalist-reacts-to-juranovic-manchester-united-link/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/nope-croatian-journalist-reacts-to-juranovic-manchester-united-link/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T22:11:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Croatian journalist Ižak Ante Sučić has weighed in on the story that Manchester United are interested in signing Josip Juranovic from Celtic. The full-back joined from Legia Warsaw last summer and has been an integral part of Ange Postecoglou’s team, helping win the League Cup and League last season.However, his form has resulted in potential Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ross County defender suffers broken leg after tackle against Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/ross-county-defender-suffers-broken-leg-after-tackle-against-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/ross-county-defender-suffers-broken-leg-after-tackle-against-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T21:58:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ross County have confirmed that defender Connor Randall has suffered a broken leg as a result of a tackle against Celtic on Saturday. The ex-Liverpool youngster was forced from the field after 71 minutes as he tackled Celtic’s Jota.The Staggies took to Twitter to confirm that Randall had fractured a bone in his leg during Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend set to face Chelsea legend in English League Cup]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-legend-set-to-face-chelsea-legend-in-english-league-cup/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-legend-set-to-face-chelsea-legend-in-english-league-cup/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T21:45:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend Scott Brown will face up against Chelsea legend Frank Lampard in the English League Cup. The two midfield generals-turned-managers will face off with their respective clubs, Fleetwood Town and Everton on either August 23rd or August 24th at the home of the EFL League One side.The two midfield legends will face up in Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tackle on Celtic's Jota results in broken leg for Ross County player]]></title>
        <id>3801204</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/tackle-on-celtics-jota-results-in-broken-leg-for-ross-county-player-3801204"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T21:26:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ross County defender Connor Randall will be out for “a significant period of time” after fracturing his leg in the 3-1 defeat by Celtic on Saturday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Elder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reported Celtic target Alex Collado in talks with La Liga outfit]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/reported-celtic-target-alex-collado-in-talks-with-la-liga-outfit/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/reported-celtic-target-alex-collado-in-talks-with-la-liga-outfit/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T21:23:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reported Celtic target Alex Collado is in talks with Elche with a view to completing a loan move this month. The Spaniard is a product of Barca’s legendary La Masia but openings with the Camp Nou outfit appear to be extremely limited, especially due to the influx of new talent this summer.Reports have stated that Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart issued VAR warning over Celtic vs Ross County incident]]></title>
        <id>1622d5265c091e7518903c73d412fb1d</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20619423.joe-hart-issued-var-warning-celtic-vs-ross-county-incident/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T20:45:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART has been warned he will "need to be careful" when VAR comes into force in Scotland after an incident in the win over Ross County.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Green Brigade Footage Makes Cameo Appearance in Mick Lynch Video]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/green-brigade-footage-makes-cameo-appearance-in-mick-lynch-video/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/green-brigade-footage-makes-cameo-appearance-in-mick-lynch-video/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T20:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE GREEN BRIGADE kicked off the season with an incredible pre-match flag day tifo that encompassed the entirety of Celtic Park. During the game, the group also displayed solidarity with the RMT and their decision to strike while directing a very catchy chant at the Conservative Government. It was something that didn’t go unnoticed on […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bamba Dieng transfer latest as Celtic 'target' gets ominous message from Marseille chief - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEKqLA-R0mWuI9EQJUP1VuHYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-transfer-news/bamba-dieng-transfer-latest-celtic-27710615"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T19:49:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bamba Dieng transfer latest as Celtic 'target' gets ominous message from Marseille chief  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kilmarnock vs Celtic: TV channel, live stream & kick-off time]]></title>
        <id>04fcc1ef7a59120898e1995dbbe85522</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20619390.kilmarnock-vs-celtic-tv-channel-live-stream-kick-off-time/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T19:33:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC continue their Scottish Premiership defence this weekend with a trip to Ayrshire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One More Ange Signing; Celtic Trio Hold Key – Opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/one-more-ange-signing-celtic-trio-hold-key-opinion/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/one-more-ange-signing-celtic-trio-hold-key-opinion/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T18:53:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have done phenomenally well to make the two signings The Hoops support craved at the beginning of this transfer window. Signing both Jota and CCV seemed unimaginable to those who follow Celtic closely. Incomings have been great, but now Celtic must show their ability to offload unwanted players as we approach the end of […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: JOHN ‘YOGI’ HUGHES FUNERAL ARRANGEMENTS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-john-yogi-hughes-funeral-arrangements/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-john-yogi-hughes-funeral-arrangements/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T18:44:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE funeral of Cetic great John ‘Yogi’ Hughes will take place on Friday. The cortege will pass Celtic Park following the Requiem Mass which will be held at St Mary’s, in the Calton district of Glasgow, at 12.30pm. Following the service, the cortege will then make its way to Celtic Park at approximately 1:45pm. The club [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Jota-Kent Comparison Has Celtic Fans Laughing At Barry Ferguson.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/the-jota-kent-comparison-has-celtic-fans-laughing-at-barry-ferguson/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/the-jota-kent-comparison-has-celtic-fans-laughing-at-barry-ferguson/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T18:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve got to love it when an on-form Celtic player is compared to one at Ibrox who isn’t kicking his own backside. It was a matter of time before someone on their side of the street pointed to Ryan Kent as their own version of Jota. It was always going to be hilarious, because anyone […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou brilliantly details key reason behind Celtic signing success]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-brilliantly-details-key-reason-behind-celtic-signing-success/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-brilliantly-details-key-reason-behind-celtic-signing-success/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou has explained how the environment of his current Hoops squad allows new signings to settle in quickly at Parkhead. The 56-year-old is currently amidst his third transfer window as the manager at Celtic Park. During that time, he has racked up a total of 24 new additions to his first team ...
The post Ange Postecoglou brilliantly details key reason behind Celtic signing success appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic confirm funeral arrangements for late Parkhead legend John 'Yogi' Hughes]]></title>
        <id>aeb568c4c12b723a1215bca454c91e1b</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20619284.celtic-confirm-funeral-arrangements-late-parkhead-legend-john-yogi-hughes/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T17:40:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have confirmed the funeral arrangements for late Parkhead legend John 'Yogi' Hughes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic defender backs summer signing to kick on after earning teammates&#039; respect]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-defender-backs-summer-signing-to-kick-on-after-earning-teammates-respect/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-defender-backs-summer-signing-to-kick-on-after-earning-teammates-respect/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic defender Alan Stubbs has backed Hoops summer recruit Moritz Jenz to kick on after scoring his first goal for the club on Saturday. The 23-year-old arrived at Parkhead in July, joining on a season-long loan deal with an option to buy from French side Lorient. On Saturday, the German defender made his first ...
The post Former Celtic defender backs summer signing to kick on after earning teammates&#039; respect appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scouts watching: Celtic eyeing up the &#039;new Sadio Mane&#039; for Ange - report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-bamba-dieng-alex-collado-transfer-gossip-news-updates/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-bamba-dieng-alex-collado-transfer-gossip-news-updates/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T17:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are among a host of clubs to have sent scouts to check out Marseille attacker Bamba Dieng, according to a report from the Daily Mail.  The lowdown: Wanted man Signed for just £360,000 from Senegalese outfit Diambars FC following a successful loan spell, Dieng has enjoyed a rapid rise to prominence in France, directly […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Taylor says he has improved ‘insane amounts’ at Celtic as he notices doubts from fans turning to praise]]></title>
        <id>b90fda750ddb7458c234dd98951f93a9</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20619113.greg-taylor-says-improved-insane-amounts-celtic-notices-doubts-fans-turning-praise/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T17:04:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT may be fair to say that Greg Taylor had a bit to do to win over the Celtic fans upon his arrival from Kilmarnock three years ago. Whether it was the unfashionable club he was signed from, his slight build and lack of height, or the fact he was tasked with filling the boots of Kieran Tierney, the left-back wasn’t instantly taken to the hearts of many supporters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warning: Scam Attempts To Steal Funds From Celtic Fans’ Mental Health Charity]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/__trashed-7/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/__trashed-7/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T16:44:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A disgusting scam has been launched today, which aims to profit from donations that are intended for the Mental Health Walk and Talk charity group. Do NOT be fooled by it!In 2020, Celtic fan Andy Pingu launched a Mental Health Walk and Talk group for fellow supporters, and fans of other clubs/none, going through a Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Journo Sets Record Straight Over Celtic Rumour]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/top-journo-sets-record-straight-over-celtic-rumour/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/top-journo-sets-record-straight-over-celtic-rumour/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T16:23:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been paying attention to the online rumour mill and twittersphere this summer, the hit rate of Mark Hendry from Football Scotland has been phenomenal when it comes to nailing Celtic rumours. The journalist clearly has the ear of someone very high up within the ranks of the club who puts out information via […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Last Season, Celtic Proved That “Fortress Ibrox” Is A Myth. Why Do Others Believe In It?]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/last-season-celtic-proved-that-fortress-ibrox-is-a-myth-why-do-others-believe-in-it/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/last-season-celtic-proved-that-fortress-ibrox-is-a-myth-why-do-others-believe-in-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T16:20:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last night, in the aftermath of the Ibrox club’s European win, I read, with incredulity, the opposition coach say that he thought the tie was won in the first leg because his team didn’t score enough times at home to make up for what he expected in the return leg. As defeatist attitudes go, this […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic supporters set for first glimpse of innovative Champions League VAR technology]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-supporters-to-receive-first-glimpse-of-innovative-champions-league-var-technology/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-supporters-to-receive-first-glimpse-of-innovative-champions-league-var-technology/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T16:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic supporters will get their first glimpse at the new VAR technology being utilised in this season’s Champions League later this evening. After lifting the Scottish Premiership title last campaign, Ange Postecoglou’s side were rewarded with direct entry into the group stages of the UCL. The Hoops will be taking part in Europe’s most prestigious ...
The post Celtic supporters set for first glimpse of innovative Champions League VAR technology appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Willie Wallace At The Derby Double, On This Day]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/video-willie-wallace-at-the-derby-double-on-this-day/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-willie-wallace-at-the-derby-double-on-this-day/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T16:14:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this day in 1968, Celtic faced Rangers at Ibrox in the League Cup. The match resulted in a 2-0 victory for the Celts, who earned an early season boost with a magnificent performance on the afternoon.Goals for the Hoops came through Lisbon Lion Willie Wallace; the first when he latched onto a loose ball Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Willie Wallace At The Derby Double, On This Day - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEE3knxeGetQdRYLyeSkgvfMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-willie-wallace-at-the-derby-double-on-this-day/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T16:14:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Willie Wallace At The Derby Double, On This Day  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Of The Day: Roddie MacDonald Up For The Header]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/photo-of-the-day-roddie-macdonald-up-for-the-header/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/photo-of-the-day-roddie-macdonald-up-for-the-header/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T16:04:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The return of the photo of the day feature this afternoon is something of a random rewind. The chosen image dates back to March 1978 when Celtic beat Rangers 2-0 Paradise in the Scottish Premier Division.Roddie MacDonald was one of the goalscorers that day, adding to Ronnie Glavin’s earlier strike.Here, Roddie is pictured leaping up Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Of The Day: Roddie MacDonald Up For The Header - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEEAzuGjsUZcC3cBbM-D6TukqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/photo-of-the-day-roddie-macdonald-up-for-the-header/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T16:04:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Of The Day: Roddie MacDonald Up For The Header  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Josip Juranovic Celtic to Chelsea transfer slapped with a big 'nope' in Croatia - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>1527569893</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-transfer-news/josip-juranovic-celtic-chelsea-transfer-27709245"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T15:59:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Josip Juranovic Celtic to Chelsea transfer slapped with a big 'nope' in Croatia  Daily Record
Reliable source shuts down ‘farfetched’ link as Celtic continue active transfer approach  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News
Transfer News: Manchester United monitoring 26-year-old star playing in Scotland  We All Follow United
‘Nope’, Croatian journalist reacts to Juranovic Manchester United link  The Celtic Star
Interesting Dele Alli to Celtic transfer rumour emerges  The Celtic Bhoys
View Full coverage on Google News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Insane Amounts’ – Greg Taylor Explains Life Under Ange Postecoglou]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/insane-amounts-greg-taylor-explains-life-under-ange-postecoglou/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/insane-amounts-greg-taylor-explains-life-under-ange-postecoglou/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T15:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Taylor is no stranger to the Rugby Park surface having spent three years at the club before making the switch to Celtic and has opened up about his start to the season and role within the team.  The fullback has been absolutely outstanding since the arrival of Ange Postecoglou to the club last summer […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christopher Jullien&#039;s future latest as Celtic defender fails to attract &#039;serious&#039; interest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/christopher-julliens-future-latest-as-celtic-defender-fails-to-attract-interest/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/christopher-julliens-future-latest-as-celtic-defender-fails-to-attract-interest/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Christopher Jullien is still hopeful of finding a new club as we approach the end of the 2022 summer window. However, according to the latest report from Football Scotland, the Frenchman is failing to attract any serious interest, which could see him remain at Parkhead. The 29-year-old looked all set to depart the ...
The post Christopher Jullien&#039;s future latest as Celtic defender fails to attract &#039;serious&#039; interest appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christopher Jullien transfer latest with Celtic defender facing frozen out spell]]></title>
        <id>326beae4405e7e4ead4016a93a4db530</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20618386.christopher-jullien-transfer-latest-celtic-defender-facing-frozen-spell/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T15:43:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CHRISTOPHER JULLIEN faces being frozen out at Celtic until January after failing to attract fresh transfer interest, according to reports.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's set to miss out on Alex Collado as La Liga side in 'advanced talks' with Barcelona star]]></title>
        <id>ebddc8c10d129fb47ef3d82b1b32da60</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20618270.celtics-set-miss-alex-collado-la-liga-side-advanced-talks-barcelona-star/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T15:28:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou's side had enquired about a move for the 23-year-old Barcelona starlet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Josip Juranovic Rumours; Latest]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/josip-juranovic-rumours-latest/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/josip-juranovic-rumours-latest/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T15:17:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Croatian journalist Izak Ange Sucic hasn’t wasted any time in letting his social media followers know the Josip Juranovic rumours aren’t true. We reported earlier today Graeme Bailey was pushing a story surrounding Josip being chased by both Chelsea and Manchester Utd. Izak, who will have his sources close to Juranovic and Croatian football has […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manchester United want Celtic defender Josip Juranovic?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sportsmole.co.uk/football/man-utd/transfer-talk/news/manchester-united-want-celtic-defender-juranovic_491949.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.sportsmole.co.uk/football/man-utd/transfer-talk/news/manchester-united-want-celtic-defender-juranovic_491949.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T15:13:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manchester United are reportedly considering a move for Celtic right-back Josip Juranovic, who joined the Scottish Champions last summer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Greg Taylor reckons extended pre-season will pay dividends after title triumph]]></title>
        <id>56fd5b3e1c74a725f8db95222e5cae34</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20618092.celtic-defender-greg-taylor-reckons-extended-pre-season-will-pay-dividends-last-seasons-title-triumph/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T15:06:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taylor's featured in previous qualifiers and believes advancing straight into the group stages could be crucial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: La Liga side in advanced talks to sign Celtic target Alex Collado]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/report-la-liga-side-best-placed-to-sign-celtic-target-alex-collado/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/report-la-liga-side-best-placed-to-sign-celtic-target-alex-collado/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spanish La Liga side Elche are reportedly ‘best placed’ to sign Barcelona winger and Celtic target Alex Collado. On Tuesday afternoon, the 23-year-old was linked with a move away from the European giants, seeking more regular game time. According to Sky Sports, both Celtic and Greek side Olympiacos had enquired about a potential move for ...
The post Report: La Liga side in advanced talks to sign Celtic target Alex Collado appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic credited with interest in Senegalese star dubbed 'the next Sadio Mane']]></title>
        <id>3800795</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-credited-with-interest-in-senegalese-star-dubbed-the-next-sadio-mane-3800795"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T14:34:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are among a host of clubs credited with showing an interest in Marseille striker Bamba Dieng.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angus Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Rangers out of reach but Aberdeen the ones to watch, says Kris Boyd - Sky Sports]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEE-5XNTEdMdF8E8PGSctNAsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow2LCYCzDvurADMI6l0AY</id>
        <link href="https://www.skysports.com/football/news/36621/12669839/celtic-and-rangers-out-of-reach-but-aberdeen-the-ones-to-watch-says-kris-boyd"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T14:24:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Rangers out of reach but Aberdeen the ones to watch, says Kris Boyd  Sky Sports]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgos Giakoumakis reveals Celtic warning he got from Giorgos Samaras before joining – ‘don’t take it’]]></title>
        <id>3800761</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/giorgos-giakoumakis-reveals-celtic-warning-he-got-from-giorgos-samaras-before-joining-dont-take-it-3800761"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T14:19:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgos Giakoumakis has revealed the warning he received before signing at Celtic over taking on the club’s number nine shirt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Oliver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s Link To Barca Winger Seems Real. But Do We Really Need This Guy?]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/celtics-link-to-barca-winger-seems-real-but-do-we-really-need-this-guy/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/celtics-link-to-barca-winger-seems-real-but-do-we-really-need-this-guy/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T14:10:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reports from Sky and elsewhere today say that they can confirm that Celtic have made an offer for the Barcelona winger Alex Collado. This is on the same day that rumours continue to link us with the Marseille striker Bamba Dieng, which some sources have denied. Collado has a year left on his deal. But […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chelsea considering bid for Celtic defender Josip Juranovic?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sportsmole.co.uk/football/chelsea/transfer-talk/news/chelsea-considering-bid-for-celtic-defender-juranovic_491944.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.sportsmole.co.uk/football/chelsea/transfer-talk/news/chelsea-considering-bid-for-celtic-defender-juranovic_491944.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T14:01:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chelsea are reportedly giving consideration to making an approach for Celtic defender Josip Juranovic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic teenager secures 'dream' transfer to Newcastle United]]></title>
        <id>31e5d4e60b8413b9e7ad0b1488b16e33</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20617455.former-celtic-teenager-secures-dream-transfer-newcastle-united/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T13:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The keeper was released by the Hoops last year but has completed a sensational career turnaround]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Rangers could be impacted by new automated offside technology]]></title>
        <id>7d2ce00c40fe06f518983fd2d80915a8</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20617201.celtic-rangers-impacted-new-automated-offside-technology/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T13:25:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER referee Des Roache has revealed how new automated offside technology could impact both Celtic and Rangers in Scottish football.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Taylor on ‘insane amounts’ of improvement and the manager’s mantra]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/greg-taylor-on-insane-amounts-of-improvement-and-the-managers-mantra/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/greg-taylor-on-insane-amounts-of-improvement-and-the-managers-mantra/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T12:48:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Taylor is perhaps the most improved player from the crop that Ange Postecoglou inherited last summer and in that time the left-back has gone from a regular whipping Bhoy of the more critical element within the online Celtic support to a firm fans favourite. And there can be no doubt that even his hardest Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Taylor on ‘insane amounts’ of improvement and the manager’s mantra - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEOj5qPucjqgcGQVIMzhJL5gqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/greg-taylor-on-insane-amounts-of-improvement-and-the-managers-mantra/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T12:48:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Taylor on ‘insane amounts’ of improvement and the manager’s mantra  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Taylor becomes latest Celtic star to express the positives of valuable summer luxury]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/greg-taylor-becomes-latest-celtic-star-to-express-the-positives-of-valuable-summer-luxury/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/greg-taylor-becomes-latest-celtic-star-to-express-the-positives-of-valuable-summer-luxury/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Greg Taylor is hopeful that the Hoops extended pre-season schedule will make a big difference for Ange Postecoglou’s side this campaign. It has been a changed summer for the Bhoys, who spent their pre-season preparations working hard in Austria and at Lennoxtown. Celtic’s regular new season schedule would usually consist of European qualifiers ...
The post Greg Taylor becomes latest Celtic star to express the positives of valuable summer luxury appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic cult hero reckons Aaron Mooy can fill Scott Brown void]]></title>
        <id>b3aa2437d0983ff09d543e52128b281c</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20616828.celtic-cult-hero-reckons-aaron-mooy-can-fill-scott-brown-void/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T12:34:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic cult hero believes Mooy's a shrewd piece of business by the Hoops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[St Johnstone Fans Are Tasting Only What Celtic Fans Have Put Up With For Years.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/st-johnstone-fans-are-tasting-only-what-celtic-fans-have-put-up-with-for-years/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/st-johnstone-fans-are-tasting-only-what-celtic-fans-have-put-up-with-for-years/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T12:20:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First up, I think St Johnstone fans are 100% right to complain about excessive ticket prices, especially at the current time, and it is something that a lot of our fans will be saying to Celtic if the Champions League prices are not set at a reasonable level. I have, and we should all have, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic cup clash was a good lesson for us but we're disappointed to lose, says Rovers boss - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEDiUTxijGOwJV1kUjBYCMiIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/local-sport/celtic-cup-clash-good-lesson-27705993"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T11:54:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic cup clash was a good lesson for us but we're disappointed to lose, says Rovers boss  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The reason Josip Juranovic may think twice about Celtic summer exit amidst Chelsea interest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-reason-josip-juranovic-may-think-twice-about-celtic-summer-exit-amidst-chelsea-interest/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-reason-josip-juranovic-may-think-twice-about-celtic-summer-exit-amidst-chelsea-interest/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T11:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier today, reports suggested that Celtic defender Josip Juranovic was attracting interest from English Premier League side Chelsea. Having only spent one season in Glasgow, the right-back is already being eyed up by some of the biggest club’s in the world, with Atletico Madrid also watching the Croatian closely this summer window. There is no ...
The post The reason Josip Juranovic may think twice about Celtic summer exit amidst Chelsea interest appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contact made: Celtic make move to sign &#039;spectacular&#039; midfielder for Ange - journalist]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-alex-collado-transfer-gossip-news-updates/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-alex-collado-transfer-gossip-news-updates/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T11:40:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have reportedly ‘made an enquiry’ regarding Barcelona midfielder Alex Collado, according to Sky Sports journalists Anthony Joseph and Lyall Thomas. The lowdown: Hot prospect Part of the famous La Masia academy following a switch from Espanyol as a fledgeling youngster, Collado has come through the ranks at the Camp Nou, amassing 34 direct goal […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mikey Johnston Celtic transfer latest as Ange Postecoglou gives loan exit approval]]></title>
        <id>78f264e3002cff5a0d2b467026bd113f</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20616302.mikey-johnston-celtic-transfer-latest-postecoglou-gives-loan-exit-approval/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T11:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 23-year-old's looking to kickstart his career after an injury-plagued few years]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers fans blast St Johnstone over ticket boycott row - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEP5SrCdD0Sh2tMwuZTsMnAkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/celtic-rangers-fans-blast-st-27705022"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T11:14:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers fans blast St Johnstone over ticket boycott row  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer Latest: Celtic star Josip Juranovic linked with Chelsea and Manchester United]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/transfer-latest-celtic-star-josip-juranovic-linked-with-chelsea-and-manchester-united/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/transfer-latest-celtic-star-josip-juranovic-linked-with-chelsea-and-manchester-united/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T11:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Josip Juranovic has today been linked with a move to both Chelsea and Manchester United, via a report on 90min.comThe main focus of the report centres around interest in signing the Celtic right-back from Chelsea and they merely state that ‘they understand’ that the London club, which has already spent almost £100m this summer on Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Taylor explains how Celtic are preparing for trip to tricky Kilmarnock surface]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/we-are-all-ready-greg-taylor-explains-how-celtic-are-preparing-for-tricky-killie-surface/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/we-are-all-ready-greg-taylor-explains-how-celtic-are-preparing-for-tricky-killie-surface/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Greg Taylor has insisted another full week of training will stand Ange Postecoglou’s side in good stead for this weekend’s trip to Rugby Park. It has been a positive start to the 2022/23 season, with the Bhoys kicking proceedings off by picking up six points from their first two games. Potentially tricky fixtures ...
The post Greg Taylor explains how Celtic are preparing for trip to tricky Kilmarnock surface appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More warning signs for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/more-warning-signs-for-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/more-warning-signs-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T11:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fair play to Newco, a 3-0 win after a 2-0 defeat is an achievement.  Anyone who things this season will be easy has not been paying attention.  Whatever they do in the Champions League playoff round, they will arrive at Celtic Park three weeks on Saturday battle ready. The circa £5m they earned last night [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgos Giakoumakis reveals his Celtic fan chant is dressing room favourite as Parkhead pals at the wind up - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEPmYqGSpI2X8_YGq4YYrTVYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/giorgos-giakoumakis-reveals-celtic-fan-27704897"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T10:51:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgos Giakoumakis reveals his Celtic fan chant is dressing room favourite as Parkhead pals at the wind up  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic boss Neil Lennon would be a 'major coup' for SPFL club insists pundit]]></title>
        <id>849a4046045058e610ad67e80a8c9cd0</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20616032.former-celtic-boss-neil-lennon-major-coup-motherwell-insists-pundit/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T10:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lennon's currently at the helm at Omonia Nicosia in Cyprus]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“It’s Ange’s methodology you’re studying,” Celtic cult hero Albert Kidd on Australian coaching]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/its-anges-methodology-youre-studying-celtic-cult-hero-albert-kidd-on-australian-coaching/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/its-anges-methodology-youre-studying-celtic-cult-hero-albert-kidd-on-australian-coaching/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T10:41:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Albert Kidd visited Lennoxtown this week, met up with his old pal Ange Postecoglou and spent some tome with Harry Kewell, who he regards as probably Australia’s best ever player. Kidd himself will always be a Celtic cult-hero after his heroics playing for Dundee against title favourites Hearts on 3 May, 1986.Hearts just needed a Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou’s Massive Impact Beyond Celtic; Hoops Cult Hero Reveals]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/ange-postecoglous-massive-impact-beyond-celtic-hoops-cult-hero-reveals/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/ange-postecoglous-massive-impact-beyond-celtic-hoops-cult-hero-reveals/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T10:39:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Albert Kidd is a name known to Celtic fans across generations and upon his return to Scotland the former Dundee striker was given an access all areas tour of Lennoxtown. Kidd famously wrote his name into the history books when he scored two goals on the final day of the season in 1986 against Hearts […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC CULT HERO IN CLUB SEARCH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-cult-hero-in-club-search/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-cult-hero-in-club-search/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T10:37:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic star Efe Ambrose is still in the hunt for a new club after leaving St Johnstone in the summer. The 33-year-old Nigerian international became a cult hero with the Hoops fans during his five years after Neil Lennon bought him from Israel top-flight club FC Ashdod for around £800,000 in August 2012. He [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here We Go Again With Another Round Of Juranovic Transfer Bollocks.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/here-we-go-again-with-another-round-of-juranovic-transfer-bollocks/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/here-we-go-again-with-another-round-of-juranovic-transfer-bollocks/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T10:35:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ll bet you were relieved when the Juranovic story seemed to have died away, eah? Not because you were worried about the prospect of us selling a guy who is happy at the club and has been here for less than a year, but because frankly the story had become a crippling bore and the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alex Collado and the mixed Barcelona messages as Celtic loan target sparks Xavi transfer U-turn - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEDQ-z-XZG9z7lA4ge_o3BCAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/alex-collado-mixed-barcelona-messages-27704223"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T10:35:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alex Collado and the mixed Barcelona messages as Celtic loan target sparks Xavi transfer U-turn  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chelsea Weighing Up Juranovic Deal – Report]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/chelsea-weighing-up-juranovic-deal-report/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/chelsea-weighing-up-juranovic-deal-report/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T10:20:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star Josip Juranovic is reported to be attracting from English Premier League sides with Chelsea and Manchester United reportedly interested in the fullback [90 Min].  The Croatian defender has already been subject to previous transfer rumours during this window as he was linked to Spanish outfit Atletico Madrid. Both sides are in need of […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Brown Gets First Major Win as Fleetwood Boss]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/scott-brown-gets-first-major-win-as-fleetwood-boss/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/scott-brown-gets-first-major-win-as-fleetwood-boss/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T10:10:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic captain Scott Brown’s Fleetwood Town defeated Championship side Wigan Athletic in the Caraboa Cup last night. This was Brown’s second win in a row as Fleetwood boss having managed his first competitive win at the weekend against Plymouth Argyle with former derby rival Joe Garner bagging the winning goal. It was a different […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: EPL giants &#039;considering&#039; move for wanted Celtic star Josip Juranovic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/report-english-premier-league-giants-considering-a-move-for-celtic-star-josip-juranovic/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/report-english-premier-league-giants-considering-a-move-for-celtic-star-josip-juranovic/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T10:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[English Premier League side Chelsea are reportedly interested in a move for Celtic right-back Josip Juranovic. The 26-year-old enjoyed an outstanding first campaign at Parkhead, joining from Polish side Legia Warsaw as part of Ange Postecoglou’s recruitment drive. Juranovic played a key role in helping the Bhoys to a league and cup double whilst also ...
The post Report: EPL giants &#039;considering&#039; move for wanted Celtic star Josip Juranovic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: The Giakoumakis song everyone’s talking about]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/video-the-giakoumakis-song-everyones-talking-about/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-the-giakoumakis-song-everyones-talking-about/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T09:56:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgos Giakoumakis officially endorsed his new song yesterday afternoon on the first Celtic View Podcast of the new season and revealed that his teammates are now singing it themselves. The Greece international striker is a firm fans favourite and as Celtic edged ever closer towards the title last season this wee song emerged from the Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's Josip Juranovic a 'target' for Premier League Chelsea]]></title>
        <id>f19fff47f856d50b5d2947c017a90166</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20615593.celtics-josip-juranovic-target-premier-league-chelsea/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T09:55:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 26-year-old has already been subject to transfer speculation this summer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If Chris Jullien Did His Talking On The Park And Not Instagram He Might Get Games.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/if-chris-jullien-did-his-talking-on-the-park-and-not-instagram-he-might-get-games/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/if-chris-jullien-did-his-talking-on-the-park-and-not-instagram-he-might-get-games/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T09:49:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The saga of Chris Jullien continues today, with his latest lengthy Instagram post where he seems to be suggesting that he “struggles alone.” I’ve got to be honest; reading any professional footballer writing about his struggles right now seems just wrong to me when ordinary people are going through 99 kinds of Hell worrying about […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero Efe Ambrose training with Scottish Championship club as signing chances confirmed - Glasgow Live]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEPVGrbryQa3sfrMeccVtew8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow96D9CjDOy_QCMKzp0wU</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowlive.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/celtic-hero-efe-ambrose-training-24717662"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T09:34:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero Efe Ambrose training with Scottish Championship club as signing chances confirmed  Glasgow Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic B complete impressive cup comeback against Scottish League Two opposition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/celtic-b-complete-impressive-cup-comeback-against-scottish-league-two-opposition/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/celtic-b-complete-impressive-cup-comeback-against-scottish-league-two-opposition/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic B completed an impressive comeback on Tuesday evening, defeating Scottish League Two side Albion Rovers 3-2. The young Celts took a break from league action this midweek, playing in the first round of the Challenge Cup, otherwise known as the SPFL Trust Trophy. Darren O’Dea and Stephen McManus would have been looking to take ...
The post Celtic B complete impressive cup comeback against Scottish League Two opposition appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic hero ISN'T signing for Hamilton Accies, insists boss - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEDBO_gfOHfVGx1upKnuYuqwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/local-sport/ex-celtic-hero-isnt-signing-27703548"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T09:06:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic hero ISN'T signing for Hamilton Accies, insists boss  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic star weighing up transfer options as he prepares for summer loan exit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/report-mikey-johnston-weighing-up-transfer-options-as-winger-prepares-for-celtic-loan-exit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/report-mikey-johnston-weighing-up-transfer-options-as-winger-prepares-for-celtic-loan-exit/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic winger Mikey Johnston is reportedly weighing up a number of options as he prepares to depart on loan this summer. The 23-year-old first broke through into the first team under Brendan Rodgers in 2017, making his debut against St Johnstone. However, it was Neil Lennon’s second tenure as boss, which was when the academy ...
The post Report: Celtic star weighing up transfer options as he prepares for summer loan exit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Mikey Johnston ‘weighing up’ transfer options as winger prepares for Celtic loan exit - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEEHhNxw_TITxLdKcGYScTAwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMLbFpgY</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/report-mikey-johnston-weighing-up-transfer-options-as-winger-prepares-for-celtic-loan-exit/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Mikey Johnston ‘weighing up’ transfer options as winger prepares for Celtic loan exit  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“We are really big on having a strong mindset, about the football we want to play,” Ange Postecoglou]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/we-are-really-big-on-having-a-strong-mindset-about-the-football-we-want-to-play-ange-postecoglou/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/we-are-really-big-on-having-a-strong-mindset-about-the-football-we-want-to-play-ange-postecoglou/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T08:39:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That new interview with Ange Postecoglou we told you about yesterday should be dropping today on the club’s You Tube Channel, so if you don’t have a subscription to Celtic TV that’s the place to watch it. In the meantime here’s what the Celtic manager has been saying over at Lennoxtown following his side’s impressive Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“We are really big on having a strong mindset, about the football we want to play,” Ange Postecoglou - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEIYD_S0X5tG90t1qta5ZC-kqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/we-are-really-big-on-having-a-strong-mindset-about-the-football-we-want-to-play-ange-postecoglou/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T08:39:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“We are really big on having a strong mindset, about the football we want to play,” Ange Postecoglou  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘RESPECT,’ CELTIC HERO BACKS NEW BHOY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/respect-celtic-hero-backs-new-bhoy/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/respect-celtic-hero-backs-new-bhoy/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T08:17:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ALAN STUBBS was a record signing for Celtic when Tommy Burns shelled out £3.5million to buy him from Bolton in August 1996. The Englishman is well aware of the importance of making a favourable first impression. Unfortunately, for the centre-back, he saw red on his Premier League debut when the Hoops, who had been leading [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pundit touts Celtic legend Neil Lennon for Motherwell vacancy]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/pundit-touts-celtic-legend-neil-lennon-for-motherwell-vacancy/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/pundit-touts-celtic-legend-neil-lennon-for-motherwell-vacancy/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T07:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Motherwell should appoint Celtic legend Neil Lennon as their new manager, according to pundit Stephen Craigan. The former Fir Park defender has said that the Irishman who has won ten Scottish Premiership titles as both a player and as a manager would be top of his list but questions whether The Steelmen would be able Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic On This Day – 10th August – David Potter’s Celtic Diary]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-on-this-day-10th-august-david-potters-celtic-diary/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-on-this-day-10th-august-david-potters-celtic-diary/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T07:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 10 of Celtic Historian David Potter’s new diary  on The Celtic Star  which will run throughout the new season and will highlight key Celtic related events relevant to each day, today covering 10 August…SATURDAY 10 AUGUST 1929Celtic’s new stand on the London Road side of the ground is officially opened today. It sees a fine Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mikey Johnston Celtic Exit Latest]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/mikey-johnston-celtic-exit-latest/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/mikey-johnston-celtic-exit-latest/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T07:37:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic winger Mikey Johnston is believed to be weighing up his options as he is expected to go out on loan during this window [Football Scotland].  Ange Postecoglou is keen for the 23-year old to get much needed game time which he simply cannot guarantee at Celtic. With this is mind, it is believed that […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Postecoglou must now ditch £20k-p/w Celtic “shocker”, Parkhead doesn't need him - opinion - msnNOW]]></title>
        <id>CBMinwFodHRwczovL3d3dy5tc24uY29tL2VuLWdiL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL3Bvc3RlY29nbG91LW11c3Qtbm93LWRpdGNoLSVDMiVBMzIway1wLXctY2VsdGljLSVFMiU4MCU5Q3Nob2NrZXIlRTIlODAlOUQtcGFya2hlYWQtZG9lc250LW5lZWQtaGltLW9waW5pb24vYXItQUExMHVQMzTSAQA</id>
        <link href="https://www.msn.com/en-gb/sport/football/postecoglou-must-now-ditch-%C2%A320k-p-w-celtic-%E2%80%9Cshocker%E2%80%9D-parkhead-doesnt-need-him-opinion/ar-AA10uP34"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T07:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Postecoglou must now ditch £20k-p/w Celtic “shocker”, Parkhead doesn't need him - opinion  msnNOW]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic tipped to capitalise on Barca’s financial situation with move for attacker]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-tipped-to-capitalise-on-barcas-financial-situation-with-move-for-attacker/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-tipped-to-capitalise-on-barcas-financial-situation-with-move-for-attacker/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T07:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic could look to capitalise on Barcelona’s precarious financial position by signing Alex Collado. Ange Postecoglou may be able to offer the Spaniard the opportunity to play Champions League football, something that could sway a deal.As reported by The Sun, Barca legend Xavi is willing to sanction a move this summer. Collado is a versatile attacking Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PLAYING FAVOURITES WITH ON-SONG GIAKOUMAKIS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/playing-favourites-with-on-song-giakoumakis/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/playing-favourites-with-on-song-giakoumakis/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T07:04:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GIORGOS GIAKOUMAKIS sealed Celtic’s tenth title in 11 years when he rose to an Anthony Ralston cross to head in powerfully from eight yards in the 1-1 draw with Dundee United at Tannadice on May 11. Two months earlier, the Greek striker had stuck two into the same rigging as Ange Postecoglou’s men overcame their [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alan Stubbs on the two things Moritz Jenz achieved on his dream Celtic debut and what the German must do now]]></title>
        <id>f6f06f20f6057db09cf9ef38ed69736a</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20614964.alan-stubbs-two-things-moritz-jenz-achieved-dream-celtic-debut-german-must-now/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T06:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT took a long time, probably well over a season, for Alan Stubbs to come good at Celtic, perform at his very best on a consistent basis and justify the record £3.5m transfer fee which it took to land him.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alan Stubbs on the two things Moritz Jenz achieved on his dream Celtic debut and what the German must do now - Celtic Way]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEKswZj62f3hto_mkPJ8SIQwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsJStCzC9n8UDMNeMswc</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticway.co.uk/news/20614964.alan-stubbs-two-things-moritz-jenz-achieved-dream-celtic-debut-german-must-now/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T06:45:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alan Stubbs on the two things Moritz Jenz achieved on his dream Celtic debut and what the German must do now  Celtic Way]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pundit Hails ‘Outstanding’ Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/pundit-hails-outstanding-celtic-star/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/pundit-hails-outstanding-celtic-star/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T05:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jota has had a terrific start to the season with the Portuguese winger on one goal and three assists after the first two games of the season.  The 23-year old scored a stunning goal against Aberdeen on the opening day and helped Ange Postecoglou’s side to three points at the weekend as he set up […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘More Levels to Come’ – Ange Postecoglou Praises Greg Taylor]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/more-levels-to-come-ange-postecoglou-praises-greg-taylor/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/more-levels-to-come-ange-postecoglou-praises-greg-taylor/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T05:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Taylor’s form hasn’t gone unnoticed by the manager. He’s been superb ever since he returned from his shoulder injury last season and has come on leaps and bounds as a player under Postecoglou’s guidance. With competition arriving in the summer, Taylor looks to be unfazed as he carries on performing well. He’s adapted to […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leeds and Newcastle joined by Celtic in transfer race for 'the new Sadio Mane' - Express]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEL5aPm7afpmgSvGiC4TUAKAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow9935CjCe0eYCMNHmzAU</id>
        <link href="https://www.express.co.uk/sport/football/1652989/Leeds-transfer-news-Newcastle-Celtic-Sadio-Mane-Premier-League-gossip"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T04:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leeds and Newcastle joined by Celtic in transfer race for 'the new Sadio Mane'  Express]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: BIG YOGI AND LISBON: THE TRUTH (Part Four)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-big-yogi-and-lisbon-the-truth-part-four/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-big-yogi-and-lisbon-the-truth-part-four/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-10T04:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOHN ‘YOGI’ HUGHES played in five of Celtic’s eight ties during their great adventure that took Jock Stein’s team to the European Cup Final against Inter Milan in Lisbon on the unforgettable date of May 25 1967. The non-appearance of the iconic Hoops forward has been the subject of conjecture ever since. The goalscoring winger, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic ‘in’ for Collado - Sky Reports]]></title>
        <id>https://www.jerseydoesntshrink.com/2022/8/9/23298797/celtic-in-for-collado-sky-reports</id>
        <link href="https://www.jerseydoesntshrink.com/2022/8/9/23298797/celtic-in-for-collado-sky-reports"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T22:13:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Jose Breton/Pics Action/NurPhoto via Getty Images
  

 Well, it’s a midfielder we’re linked with again, albeit another attacking one and not the defensive king. 
Indeed, reports suggest Celtic are interested in Barcelona’s Alex Collado. 


☘️Celtic have made an enquiry for Barcelona attacking midfielder Alex Collado — Sky Sports Scotland (@ScotlandSky) August 9, 2022




There may very well be ‘something’ to this, but let’s not get too excited and go ‘all in’ on it like we did with that Vinicius Souza nonsense, only to all get disappointed and in some cases, a few people looked really stupid.
Furthermore, it would suggest Ange is keen to add more creativity to the squad, and may very well not be fully happy with the current attacking players in the side.
Here’s some stats on Collado: 


 Celtic Transfer Link: Stats Report  Álex Collado12 p90s in La Liga - mostly central/att mid but also some games on right wing. Overall, a roughly average data output - Granada relegated so team quality influence some numbers.High dribble volume and effective tackler. pic.twitter.com/NrCtzpExAE— The Cynic (@90MinuteCynic) August 9, 2022



And no article would be complete without a youtube compilation and various readers declaring him the new Toni Kroos or De Bruyne so here we are:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic must learn key lesson from another Rangers comeback - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEDfxBn-wMhYlrBIc02l914gqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4KKJCzCv9JoDMICkoAY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2022/08/09/celtic-key-lesson-rangers-comeback/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic must learn key lesson from another Rangers comeback  The Celtic Bhoys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers Is Excellent At Finding Points Of Friction With His Employers.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/articles/brendan-rodgers-is-excellent-at-finding-points-of-friction-with-his-employers/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/articles/brendan-rodgers-is-excellent-at-finding-points-of-friction-with-his-employers/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T20:45:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no doubt whatsoever that Brendan Rodgers had issues at Celtic. But he was very good at provoking issues, and he has been for the whole of his managerial career. We know that in the summer of his departure he used alleged interest from China to leverage himself a better salary. He then confirmed […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou Explains ‘Really Important’ Summer Signing]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/ange-postecoglou-explains-really-important-summer-signing/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/ange-postecoglou-explains-really-important-summer-signing/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T20:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Celtic Announced the signing of Alexandro Bernabei, many assumed Ange Postecoglou had brought in a player ready to go straight into the starting eleven, but that’s not been the case. After playing a few times in pre-season, it was thought that he’d at least feature in the first two games of Celtic’s domestic campaign. […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been handed Alex Collado transfer boost - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEBUU3nCAg422b8vCA_D777IqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4KKJCzCv9JoDMICkoAY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2022/08/09/celtic-handed-alex-collado-transfer-boost/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T20:03:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been handed Alex Collado transfer boost  The Celtic Bhoys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic star completes shock move to Australian club - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>CAIiED-j00WvkYHaE3DqXkiWanAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4KKJCzCv9JoDMICkoAY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2022/08/09/former-celtic-star-australian-club/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T19:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic star completes shock move to Australian club  The Celtic Bhoys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic&#039;s big Alex Collado advantage as Barcelona receive contact from more teams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtics-alex-collado-advantage-as-barcelona-receive-contact-from-more-teams/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtics-alex-collado-advantage-as-barcelona-receive-contact-from-more-teams/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T18:46:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s participation in the UEFA Champions League looks to be a key advantage in the transfer chase for Alex Collado. As we discussed earlier today, Sky Sports have reported that the Bhoys have made contact with Barcelona about the attacking midfielder’s situation. However, Ange Postecoglou isn’t the only manager in Europe eyeing his signature, with ...
The post Celtic&#039;s big Alex Collado advantage as Barcelona receive contact from more teams appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon touted for Motherwell job as ex Celtic boss deserves 'boat pushed out' - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEKhNi--nM1AqK4ASZKxf2hAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPPfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/neil-lennon-touted-motherwell-job-24714908"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T18:39:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon touted for Motherwell job as ex Celtic boss deserves 'boat pushed out'  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Kennedy in Celtic exit dilemma as FC Midtjylland linked coach told 'it's right time to go' - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEHqYqW1jN5G5c7rqTgIxCKUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPLfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/john-kennedy-celtic-exit-dilemma-24714926"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T18:08:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Kennedy in Celtic exit dilemma as FC Midtjylland linked coach told 'it's right time to go'  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Today the Celtic family remembers Thomas ‘Kidso’ Reilly]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/today-the-celtic-family-remembers-thomas-kidso-reilly/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/today-the-celtic-family-remembers-thomas-kidso-reilly/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T17:50:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘Through the barricades,’ Thomas ‘Kidso’ Reilly’s tragic story… In loving memory of Celtic fanatic Thomas ‘kidso’ Reilly. Murdered in cold blood by a British soldier, Pte Ian Thain on August 9th 1983. Always remembered by his friends and relatives in Éire Go Brách CSC Hail hail kidso, you’ll never walk alone pic.twitter.com/mqgnS4VuU5 — Éire Go Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgos Giakoumakis reveals brutal Benji Siegrist Celtic initiation and his own training ground trolling]]></title>
        <id>1b83ac06e17783f357ddf030f3f3f291</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20614120.giorgos-giakoumakis-reveals-brutal-benji-siegrist-celtic-initiation-training-ground-trolling/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T17:40:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GIORGOS GIAKOUMAKIS is thrilled to have been given his own song by the Celtic support - however he revealed he's less excited to hear his team-mates singing it in training.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SPFL transfer news LIVE as Jack Simpson leaves Rangers and Griffiths seals move - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEF6kmvbIOvQ_B2_gv6PnJm4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPLfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/spfl-transfer-news-live-celtic-24696594"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T17:06:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SPFL transfer news LIVE as Jack Simpson leaves Rangers and Griffiths seals move  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable journalist provides significant update on Celtic links to &#039;very dangerous&#039; PL man]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-spl-ross-barkley-transfer-news-updates/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-spl-ross-barkley-transfer-news-updates/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T16:41:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are not interested in signing Chelsea midfielder Ross Barkley this summer despite rumours suggesting otherwise, according to journalist Mark Hendry. The Lowdown: Barkley rumour emerges The Hoops have made an ideal start to their Scottish Premiership title defence, winning their opening two matches against Aberdeen and Ross County. That’s not to say that Ange […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I Love It’ – Giakoumakis Reveals Why Teammates Make Fun of Him]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/i-love-it-giakoumakis-reveals-why-teammates-make-fun-of-him/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/i-love-it-giakoumakis-reveals-why-teammates-make-fun-of-him/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T16:25:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgos Giakoumakis was a hugely influential player towards the end of last season and has opened on life in Glasgow.  The Greek striker scored 17 goals for the Hoops during Ange Postecoglou’s maiden season at Celtic and will be hopeful of bettering his goals tally during this campaign. Majority of the Greek forwards goals came […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgos Giakoumakis responds to hearing his Celtic song in the stands; squad reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/giorgos-giakoumakis-responds-to-hearing-his-celtic-song-in-the-stands-squad-reaction/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/giorgos-giakoumakis-responds-to-hearing-his-celtic-song-in-the-stands-squad-reaction/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T16:24:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgos Giakoumakis had a difficult start to life at Celtic but has firmly become a hero of the supporter after his goalscoring exploits in the second half of last season. Arriving with injury and fitness issues, we didn’t see the best of the Greek international until the turn of the year but he played a ...
The post Giorgos Giakoumakis responds to hearing his Celtic song in the stands; squad reaction appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“We will be hard to stop,” Ange Postecoglou’s “brand of football” message]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/we-will-be-hard-to-stop-ange-postecoglous-brand-of-football-message/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/we-will-be-hard-to-stop-ange-postecoglous-brand-of-football-message/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T16:16:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has been speaking to Celtic TV today and that interview is now available to view to subscribers. For everyone else it will be a day or two before it’s available on the club’s You Tube channel in a day or two.I’ve just watched the interview and there are a few interesting points worth Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic showed they are best team but Rangers rivalry 'back to what it should be', claims pundit]]></title>
        <id>71143c7924ab5deca681334013b0d327</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20613485.celtic-showed-best-team-rangers-rivalry-back-be-claims-pundit/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T16:05:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOHN BARNES insists the Celtic and Rangers rivalry is "back to what it should be" but insists Celtic proved they are the best team in Scotland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIFFERENT BALL GAME FOR ANGE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/different-ball-game-for-ange/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/different-ball-game-for-ange/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T16:03:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JAMES McCARTHY and the Celtic fringe players face some serious work-outs to get them up to match fitness for the rigours that lie ahead. The Republic of Ireland midfielder has yet to kick a ball in competitive action after two Premiership games against Aberdeen and Ross County while Mikey Johnston, Christopher Jullien and Albian Ajeti [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer machine begins to move again with latest Sky Sports update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/the-celtic-transfer-machine-begins-to-move-again-with-sky-sports-update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/the-celtic-transfer-machine-begins-to-move-again-with-sky-sports-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T15:52:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have made an enquiry to Barcelona regarding attacking midfield talent Alex Collado, Sky Sports journalists Anthony Joseph and Lyall Thomas have reported this afternoon. Collado’s name surfaced in Spanish and Greek reports earlier in the day with Olympiacos also said to be keen on his services. The 23-year-old is unlikely to get game time ...
The post Celtic transfer machine begins to move again with latest Sky Sports update appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Leigh Griffiths chose Mandurah City transfer as ex Celtic star heads Down Under 'for a holiday' - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEFNUKoRwdSjekRYNT8-LtI8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/leigh-griffiths-chose-mandurah-city-27698587"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T15:37:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why Leigh Griffiths chose Mandurah City transfer as ex Celtic star heads Down Under 'for a holiday'  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers and Celtic could be freed to leave Scottish league after landmark court ruling - Daily Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEGXsSGHDEK3ulSE6hssjibYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowjKT8CjCc44gDMN2jzQU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailystar.co.uk/sport/football/celtic-rangers-leave-scottish-premiership-27698324"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T15:33:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers and Celtic could be freed to leave Scottish league after landmark court ruling  Daily Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Maybe in the Past; John Barnes Makes Brilliant Celtic Assesment]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/maybe-in-the-past-john-barnes-makes-brilliant-celtic-assesment/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/maybe-in-the-past-john-barnes-makes-brilliant-celtic-assesment/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T15:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic manager John Barnes believes that there isn’t an over reliance on any of the players in the current Celtic team with there being a strong collective in the group.  There has been many standout players which Ange Postecoglou has recruited since his arrival at the club last summer with Jota and Kyogo receiving […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TWO YEARS ON: CELTS BACK IN CHASE FOR COLLADO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/two-years-on-celts-back-in-chase-for-collado/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/two-years-on-celts-back-in-chase-for-collado/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T15:20:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC are back on the trail of Barcelona forward Alex Collado – TWO YEARS after CQN reported their original interest. Ange Postecoglou has been alerted to the news the versatile 23-year-old raider will be allowed to leave the Nou Camp on loan before the August 31 deadline, according to the Scottish Sun. Greek outfit Olympiakos [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop Jota And You Stop Celtic, Right? Wrong. So, So Wrong.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/stop-jota-and-you-stop-celtic-right-wrong-so-so-wrong/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/stop-jota-and-you-stop-celtic-right-wrong-so-so-wrong/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T14:53:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three assists and one goal in two games. That’s Jota, that’s our player, that’s the guy who has such quality that the press is raving about him and the Ibrox illiterati are grumbling that he’s over-rated. Whatever gets them through the night. The new school of thought amongst them – and I daresay amongst some […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A wonderful, magical Celtic Star is born at Tynecastle]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/a-wonderful-magical-celtic-star-is-born-at-tynecastle/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/a-wonderful-magical-celtic-star-is-born-at-tynecastle/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T14:41:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the midst of the qualification process for the Champions League, Brendan Rodgers had faced his first domestic challenges as manager of Celtic.The quest for six-in-a-row began in Edinburgh, the opening League fixture seeing the Hoops travel to Tynecastle on Sunday, 7 August 2016, four days after Moussa Dembele’s late winner against Astana. The big Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou references dodgy Kilmarnock pitch ahead of Sunday Celtic visit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-references-dodgy-kilmarnock-pitch-but-insists-celtic-must-find-sunday-answers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-references-dodgy-kilmarnock-pitch-but-insists-celtic-must-find-sunday-answers/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T14:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou has been speaking about the difficulties of travelling to Rugby Park this weekend as the Bhoys look to make it three wins from three at the start of the season. Postecoglou’s side face recently promoted Kilmarnock on one of the dodgier playing surfaces in the division – an artificial effort that ...
The post Ange Postecoglou references dodgy Kilmarnock pitch ahead of Sunday Celtic visit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Champions League schedule preparation detailed by Ange Postecoglou]]></title>
        <id>71ced080e1df6bc702059409044d3f36</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20612631.celtic-champions-league-schedule-preparation-detailed-ange-postecoglou/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T14:18:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU has revealed Celtic will play bounce games as part of their preparation for their upcoming Champions League schedule.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou confirms plan for Celtic fringe players]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-confirms-plan-for-celtic-fringe-players/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-confirms-plan-for-celtic-fringe-players/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has confirmed bounce games have been arranged for the Celtic players not currently getting minutes in his first-team. Celtic have a relatively easy schedule at the moment compared to what’s coming later in the season, meaning the manager can stick to a pretty consistent starting eleven every week, with no Tuesday, Wednesday or ...
The post Ange Postecoglou confirms plan for Celtic fringe players appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic organised bounce games to help with Champions League preparation as club get bumper ticket boost]]></title>
        <id>3799210</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-organised-bounce-games-to-help-with-champions-league-preparation-as-club-get-bumper-ticket-boost-3799210"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T14:07:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou has revealed the club have organised bounce games to ensure fringe players are fit and ready to play when called upon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Reveals Early Season Edge Helping Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/ange-reveals-early-season-edge-helping-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/ange-reveals-early-season-edge-helping-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T14:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With no European qualifiers to play Ange Postecoglou has detailed the ways in which the time between games is being managed.  Celtic have started off the season well with two victories against Aberdeen and Ross County with Hoops fans having to once again wait till the weekend to watch their side. At times during both […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top-flight club confirm reversal of trend that was impacting Celtic support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/premiership-club-delivers-welcome-ticket-news-to-celtic-supporters/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/premiership-club-delivers-welcome-ticket-news-to-celtic-supporters/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T13:37:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ross County have confirmed they will be offering more away tickets to Celtic for the upcoming Scottish League Cup clash in Dingwall than the usual allocation. Less than 2,000 Celtic supporters were allowed into the Staggies’ ground at the weekend, as Ange Postecoglou’s side secured a 3-1 victory. Having sold less home tickets than they ...
The post Top-flight club confirm reversal of trend that was impacting Celtic support appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harry Hood and Big Yogi the stand-outs as the 1969-70 season kicks off]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/harry-hood-and-big-yogi-the-stand-outs-as-the-1969-70-season-kicks-off/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/harry-hood-and-big-yogi-the-stand-outs-as-the-1969-70-season-kicks-off/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T13:24:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harry and Yogi the stand-outs as the season kicks off…Harry Hood would start his first full season as a Celt by featuring in three very different friendly matches. First of those was against St Etienne, on Wednesday, 30 July 1969, the French champions memorably defeated by the Bhoys in the previous European Cup campaign.Celtic’s return Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Kennedy Has Shown Astonishing Commitment To Celtic. It May Be Time To Go.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/john-kennedy-has-shown-astonishing-commitment-to-celtic-it-may-be-time-to-go/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/john-kennedy-has-shown-astonishing-commitment-to-celtic-it-may-be-time-to-go/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T13:20:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you had told me even twelve months ago that I would be writing an article about John Kennedy possibly leaving this club, and that I would be writing it with regret and in this tone, I would have flatly refused to believe it. This time last year I wanted him gone. It seemed like […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Every word from Ange Postecoglou as Celtic boss reveals bounce game plan amid vital Champions League prep - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEIKIyjWwe_FyJtXpdfnbaf4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/every-word-ange-postecoglou-celtic-27696180"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T13:02:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every word from Ange Postecoglou as Celtic boss reveals bounce game plan amid vital Champions League prep  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic May Yet Have The Last Laugh In The Strange Case Of Jack Hendry.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/blogs/celtic-may-yet-have-the-last-laugh-in-the-strange-case-of-jack-hendry/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/blogs/celtic-may-yet-have-the-last-laugh-in-the-strange-case-of-jack-hendry/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T12:10:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There was an odd story on the websites last night, and I’m assured that it is true. The story is about Jack Hendry, who has been told, after one season at Brugge, that he is no longer in their first team plans and is free to find a club. I thought we had been grafted […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alex Collado: Celtic one of four clubs linked with move for Barcelona winger - one factor could be crucial]]></title>
        <id>3798922</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/alex-collado-celtic-one-of-four-clubs-linked-with-move-for-barcelona-winger-one-factor-could-be-crucial-3798922"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T12:05:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been credited with an interest in Barcelona winger Alex Collado.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ross McLeish</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alex Collado 'wanted' for Celtic loan as Barcelona set to let attacker leave - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiECq-flyr_pMhZsbJbg-6JZQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-transfer-news/alex-collado-wanted-celtic-loan-27695766"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T11:52:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alex Collado 'wanted' for Celtic loan as Barcelona set to let attacker leave  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Make Move for Barcelona Midfielder Alex Collado – Report]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-make-move-for-barcelona-midfielder-alex-collado-report/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-make-move-for-barcelona-midfielder-alex-collado-report/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T11:39:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Spanish journalist Albert Roge, Celtic have made a move for the highly rated Barcelona midfielder Alex Collado. Collado has come through the ranks at Barcelona, playing for the B side and moving to the main squad last year. Alex then went out on loan to Granada last season but has since returned to […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hanger on can sling his hook as Jota, Robbie Neilson and Hibs catering get it tight - Hotline - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiECP8sUAwuTuiJqUZ234LhJwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/celtic-hanger-can-sling-hook-27694544"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T11:22:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hanger on can sling his hook as Jota, Robbie Neilson and Hibs catering get it tight - Hotline  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ross County to trial increased Celtic allocation after empty seats on Saturday]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/ross-county-to-trial-increased-celtic-allocation-after-empty-seats-on-saturday/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/ross-county-to-trial-increased-celtic-allocation-after-empty-seats-on-saturday/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T11:17:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ross County should be applauded today for taking action to increase the away ticket allocation ahead of the next visit from Celtic at the end of the month in the Premier Sports League Cup tie.Despite the Highlands club maximising the seating available for their own support for their first home match of the season on Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic transfer misfit could be set to link up with Ronaldo]]></title>
        <id>056c0056f9cfc438edbb5eb2f1e40e7a</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20611224.former-celtic-defenders-future-belgium-scotland-international-frozen/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T11:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Hendry has been linked with Real Valladolid after failing to impress Brugge boss Carl Hoefkens]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CL millions floating across Glasgow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/cl-millions-floating-across-glasgow/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/cl-millions-floating-across-glasgow/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T11:04:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tonight, we see the conclusion of the first of two ties that don’t involve Celtic but have a significant bearing on our income and domestic competitive stance.  Union Saint-Gilloise take a 2-0 lead to Ibrox, a result that in earlier times brought an 80% success rate.  Without the away goals rule, the advantage is reduced, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic star Leigh Griffiths in shock move to Australian third tier for final 4 games]]></title>
        <id>3798733</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/ex-celtic-star-leigh-griffiths-in-shock-move-to-australian-third-tier-for-final-4-games-3798733"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T10:41:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leigh Griffiths has made a shock short-term move to Australia joining third tier side Mandurah City.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stick or twist: Every year John Kennedy gets linked with Celtic departure - is now the time?]]></title>
        <id>3798737</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/stick-or-twist-every-year-john-kennedy-gets-linked-with-celtic-departure-is-now-the-time-3798737"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T10:41:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whenever a top managerial vacancy comes up in Scottish football, one name features prominently on the bookmakers’ odds list: John Kennedy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leigh Griffiths signs for Australian minnows Mandurah City]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/leigh-griffiths-signs-for-australian-minnows-mandurah-city/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/leigh-griffiths-signs-for-australian-minnows-mandurah-city/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T10:39:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker Leigh Griffiths has at last found himself a new club and has had to go to the other side of the world to achieve his target to continue playing football this season. His destination is Australia but not to one of the top club’s in the A-League but instead to minnows Mandurah Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic land bumper away-day allocation for League Cup clash]]></title>
        <id>08465cc71c18a2395f856e2af7aa02ae</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20610768.celtic-given-bumper-away-day-allocation-premier-sports-cup-clash/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dingwall's going to be a little busier than usual on August 31]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome To Celtic And Scotland Moritz, Where The Press Tries To Get You Banned.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/welcome-to-celtic-and-scotland-moritz-where-the-press-tries-to-get-you-banned/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/welcome-to-celtic-and-scotland-moritz-where-the-press-tries-to-get-you-banned/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T10:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What a weekend it has been for Moritz Jenz. He has made his full debut for Celtic and scored a critical goal in it. This was a guy whose dream move to France turned into a nightmare last season, and who is enjoying his football again. What a response he’s had from our fans. Instant […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers and Celtic get Super League call from Serie A chief]]></title>
        <id>ebbb43d612217ea2a3cba67647039594</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20610696.rangers-celtic-get-super-league-call-serie-chief/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T10:20:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A failed breakaway didn't include Scotland's big two, but Adriano Galliani feels a rival to the Premier League is the only way to go.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Great News For Celtic Fans]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/great-news-for-celtic-fans/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/great-news-for-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T10:15:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ross County has taken a U-turn on their decision to decrease travelling supporters for their upcoming Premier Sports Cup clash. Celtic travel to the highlands on the 31st of August to take on the side they’ve already defeated 3-1 this month. Celtic has been given two full stands for the match for their fans. County […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Taylor Report – “Greg is nothing like me. He is a much better player than I ever was,” Ange Postecoglou]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/the-taylor-report-greg-is-nothing-like-me-he-is-a-much-better-player-than-i-ever-was-ange-postecoglou/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/the-taylor-report-greg-is-nothing-like-me-he-is-a-much-better-player-than-i-ever-was-ange-postecoglou/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T10:12:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou was asked at his media conference on Friday afternoon ahead of the trip to Dingwall about the improvement in Greg Taylor’s game as Celtic’s left back and also the arrival of Argentinian left-back Alexandro Bernabei in the summer to provide additional back-up at that side of the Celtic defence.Postecoglou was of course a Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leigh Griffiths joins Mandurah City as former Celtic striker takes on Australian adventure - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEFYw-Uo1tZ0Zbzo6w99HnfkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-transfer-news/leigh-griffiths-join-mandurah-city-27693769"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T10:07:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leigh Griffiths joins Mandurah City as former Celtic striker takes on Australian adventure  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GRIFF COMEBACK – WITH AUSSIE SECOND-TIER CLUB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/griff-comeback-with-aussie-second-tier-club/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/griff-comeback-with-aussie-second-tier-club/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T10:03:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic striker Leigh Griffiths is poised for a shock return to football – with Australian SECOND Division side Mandurah City. The former Scotland international had his contract scrapped by the champions at the turn of the year after he had been returned by Dundee early from his original season-long loan agreement. Griffiths, who will [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic star Leigh Griffiths back in football as he makes huge career change with Australia switch - Glasgow Live]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEK3w-g-jzTN-y3npB-5JirwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow96D9CjDOy_QCMPvp0wU</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowlive.co.uk/sport/ex-celtic-star-leigh-griffiths-24707620"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T09:56:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic star Leigh Griffiths back in football as he makes huge career change with Australia switch  Glasgow Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leigh Griffiths joins Australian side - Scottish Daily Express]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEOirpLX7ie5TFzgcRKOPF5cqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowi76vCzCYyccDMK3zuAc</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottishdailyexpress.co.uk/sport/football/leigh-griffiths-seals-australian-move-27693667"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T09:48:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leigh Griffiths joins Australian side  Scottish Daily Express]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leigh Griffiths Finds New Club]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/leigh-griffiths-finds-new-club/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/leigh-griffiths-finds-new-club/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T09:46:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LEIGH GRIFFITHS has found a new club after he was released from Falkirk when his contract expired in June. The former Celtic player has signed for Australian third division side Mandurah City FC. It’s a funny one; Griffiths will feature in two home games with four games remaining in the season. These home games will […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Immortals, Two Nines and Other Celtic Stories]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/the-immortals-two-nines-and-other-celtic-stories/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/the-immortals-two-nines-and-other-celtic-stories/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T09:32:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Immortals is a passionate love letter to Celtic FC, by turns ecstatic and distressed, angry and joyous, but always obsessed. After the disappointment in 2021 of failing to complete the fabled ten-in-a-row league titles, the author took solace in researching causes for celebration from Celtic’s proud past.His starting point was the rallying cry that Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Drop More Adidas Gear]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-drop-more-adidas-gear/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-drop-more-adidas-gear/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T09:08:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adidas has dropped some more training gear after some stunning collections have surfaced over the past few years. It was always going to be hard for the company to beat last year’s range, but the effort is pretty impressive. THE BOSS 😍🍀 Kitted out in the newest drop of adidas trainingwear 22/23, pre-order yours now! […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic could be on verge of suffering massive blow - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>CAIiECVOQ6MXb7NhOnNkZkaMXrsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4KKJCzCv9JoDMICkoAY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2022/08/09/celtic-verge-suffering-massive-blow/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T09:02:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic could be on verge of suffering massive blow  The Celtic Bhoys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic transfer target on move again after just a year with new club | Celtic Way - Celtic Way]]></title>
        <id>CBMiW2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmNlbHRpY3dheS5jby51ay9uZXdzLzIwNjEwMDYxLmZvcm1lci1jZWx0aWMtdHJhbnNmZXItdGFyZ2V0LWJlY29tZXMtZnJlZS1hZ2VudC_SAQA</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticway.co.uk/news/20610061.former-celtic-transfer-target-becomes-free-agent/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T08:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic transfer target on move again after just a year with new club | Celtic Way  Celtic Way]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic transfer target on move again after just a year with new club]]></title>
        <id>a1803dee21c0ff0abc336754b51bfb36</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20610061.former-celtic-transfer-target-becomes-free-agent/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T08:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former Celtic target is on the move again after a disappointing spell in San Sebastian]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charlie Nicholas highlights Rangers' 'scary problem' posed by Celtic]]></title>
        <id>978cb0d95c1456d7c58bd7a4131d8981</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20610086.charlie-nicholas-highlights-rangers-scary-problem-posed-celtic/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T08:27:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RANGERS face Union Saint-Gilloise tonight in a do-or-die Champions League qualifier.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BACKS TO THE FUTURE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/backs-to-the-future/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/backs-to-the-future/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T08:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU admits Celtic were short in the full-back department last season. Greg Taylor was the only recognised No.3 and the manager was forced to switch Josip Juranovic from right to left when the Scotland international was unavailable through his shoulder injury. Postecoglou was quick to add another left-sided back-four performer in Argentinian Alexandro Bernabei [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Scary problem for Rangers' outlined regarding Celtic's 'financial muscle' ahead of Champions League qualifier]]></title>
        <id>3798395</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/rangers/scary-problem-for-rangers-outlined-regarding-celtics-financial-muscle-ahead-of-champions-league-qualifier-3798395"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T08:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers could allow Celtic to “flex their financial muscle again” if they fail to qualify for the Champions League, according to Charlie Nicholas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic assistant John Kennedy 'could be on verge' of FC Midtjylland move]]></title>
        <id>36c9686d7cc6fec03e1fbbb915adbcb8</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20610011.celtic-assistant-john-kennedy-could-verge-fc-midtjylland-move/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T07:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC assistant manager John Kennedy could be on the verge of his way out of the club, it has been reported.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Kennedy Exit Latest]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/john-kennedy-exit-latest/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/john-kennedy-exit-latest/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T07:56:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Kennedy has been linked to a few Hoops exits over the past few months, but his most recent one is starting to bear fruit. It’s now emerged that Celtic are expecting Midtjylland to make an approach for the Celtic assistant manager as they look to replace Bo Henriksen. [Football Scotland] The former defender hasn’t […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEEING RED: THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN JENZ, BROONY AND VENNEGOOR OF HESSELINK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/seeing-red-the-difference-between-jenz-broony-and-vennegoor-of-hesselink/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/seeing-red-the-difference-between-jenz-broony-and-vennegoor-of-hesselink/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T06:16:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MORITZ JENZ escaped seeing red and joining Celtic stars such as Scott Brown and Jan Vennegoor of Hesselink who have been banished for celebrating a goal with the fans. The towering German shared the joy with the travelling support after heading in a superb second goal in the 3-1 win over Ross County in Dingwall [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Taylor Appreciation Post]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/greg-taylor-appreciation-post/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/greg-taylor-appreciation-post/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T06:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Taylor was one of the standout performers for Celtic last season and so far is continuing his high level of performance.  With the arrival of Alexandro Bernabei from Lanús many questioned what it meant for the left-back position at Celtic. It was a position which badly needed depth with players such as Liam Scales […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic On This Day – 9th August – David Potter’s Celtic Diary]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-on-this-day-9th-august-david-potters-celtic-diary/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-on-this-day-9th-august-david-potters-celtic-diary/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 9 of Celtic Historian David Potter’s new diary  on The Celtic Star  which will run throughout the new season and will highlight key Celtic related events relevant to each day, today covering 9 August…SATURDAY 9 AUGUST 1941Celtic’s war time woes continue with a dreadful 0-3 opening day defeat at Tynecastle in front of a surprisingly Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liel Abada Brilliant Response to Ange Question]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/liel-abada-brilliant-response-to-ange-question/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/liel-abada-brilliant-response-to-ange-question/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIEL ABADA was a vital player for Celtic last season, particularly during the first half of the season. He was expected to provide cover to James Forrest, but after injuries to the winger and exceptional performances from Abada, he found himself starting most games. His numbers were excellent at the end of last season, but […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charlie Nicholas fears Rangers 'scary problem' as he predicts shock transfer and Euro chances - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEG9Bu5jb1setLCBOXAOQwm8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/charlie-nicholas-fears-rangers-scary-27691739"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T05:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Charlie Nicholas fears Rangers 'scary problem' as he predicts shock transfer and Euro chances  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC No.2 IN DEMAND]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-no-2-in-demand/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-no-2-in-demand/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T05:34:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC assistant boss John Kennedy has emerged as a shock candidate for the manager’s job at FC Midtjylland. The Danish club, who knocked the Hoops out of the Champions League at the qualifying stage last July, are looking for a new boss to replace Bo Henriksen who has been sacked after only 14 months in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Celtic Have Got Away With One’ – Former Ref’s Red Card Verdict]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-have-got-away-with-one-former-refs-red-card-verdict/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-have-got-away-with-one-former-refs-red-card-verdict/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC Defender Moritz Jenz should have been sent off in the aftermath of his debut goal for the Hoops against Ross County, according to former referee Des Roache. The German defender put Celtic back in the lead with six minutes of regulation time remaining. The defender was so delighted with his goal he ran straight […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Taylor can reach higher Celtic levels as boss debunks Bernabei assumption - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiELdYOQEHtXrf06fCh1862QkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/greg-taylor-set-celtic-levels-27688945"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Taylor can reach higher Celtic levels as boss debunks Bernabei assumption  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: BIG YOGI AND LISBON: THE TRUTH (Part Three)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-big-yogi-and-lisbon-the-truth-part-three/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-big-yogi-and-lisbon-the-truth-part-three/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-09T04:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC great John ‘Yogi’ Hughes was missing from Jock Stein’s Lisbon line-up for the history-making triumph on May 25 1967. The non-appearance of the iconic Hoops forward has been the subject of conjecture ever since. Hughes played in five of the eight games leading up to the European Cup Final, but the nearest he got [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moritz Jenz escaped Celtic suspension with Ross County celebration deserving of caution, says ex-ref]]></title>
        <id>756b1852553408c01f0167c7b9a7442c</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20609724.moritz-jenz-escaped-celtic-suspension-ross-county-celebration-deserving-caution-says-ex-ref/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T21:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC defender Moritz Jenz should have been sent off after netting his first goal for the club against Ross County, a former ref has said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou makes bold Greg Taylor prediction and outlines Alexandro Bernabei dynamic]]></title>
        <id>c6dc43ac0dbe32e29104612741434d6a</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20609631.celtic-manager-ange-postecoglou-makes-bold-greg-taylor-prediction-outlines-alexandro-bernabei-dynamic/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T21:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WHEN Celtic signed Alexandro Bernabei from Lanus in his native Argentina for a cool £3.75m back in June, it was unclear what the future held for Greg Taylor at Parkhead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou makes Greg Taylor quip as Celtic boss out to 'eliminate' the 'most overrated position on the field']]></title>
        <id>3798246</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/ange-postecoglou-makes-greg-taylor-quip-as-celtic-boss-out-to-eliminate-the-most-overrated-position-on-the-field-3798246"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a growing appreciation of Celtic’s Greg Taylor in the inverted full-back role that proves a crucial component of Ange Postecoglou’s attack-accented system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero slams Kris Boyd claim over Alfredo Morelos and insists he doesn’t come near Jota - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEMrC7prEZ7_K6Lk0E9x59ZIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/celtic-hero-slams-kris-boyd-27689926"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero slams Kris Boyd claim over Alfredo Morelos and insists he doesn’t come near Jota  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Journalist Makes Interesting Celtic Transfer Admission]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/journalist-makes-interesting-celtic-transfer-admission/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/journalist-makes-interesting-celtic-transfer-admission/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T20:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is still plenty of time left in the transfer window but journalist Pete O’Rourke has admitted that Celtic were interested in signing German defender Malick Thiaw from Schalke.  Ange Postecoglou confirmed during his pre-match press conference before the match against Ross County that the Hoops were still active in the market. So far, the […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Journalist Makes Interesting Celtic Transfer Admission - CeltsAreHere]]></title>
        <id>CBMiUGh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9qb3VybmFsaXN0LW1ha2VzLWludGVyZXN0aW5nLWNlbHRpYy10cmFuc2Zlci1hZG1pc3Npb24v0gFUaHR0cHM6Ly9jZWx0c2FyZWhlcmUuY29tL2pvdXJuYWxpc3QtbWFrZXMtaW50ZXJlc3RpbmctY2VsdGljLXRyYW5zZmVyLWFkbWlzc2lvbi9hbXAv</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/journalist-makes-interesting-celtic-transfer-admission/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T20:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Journalist Makes Interesting Celtic Transfer Admission  CeltsAreHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moritz Jenz Celtic ban escape as ex-ref Des Roache says defender should have seen red for Dingwall celebration - Scottish Daily Express]]></title>
        <id>1523624142</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottishdailyexpress.co.uk/sport/football/moritz-jenz-celtic-ban-escape-27690630"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T20:34:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moritz Jenz Celtic ban escape as ex-ref Des Roache says defender should have seen red for Dingwall celebration  Scottish Daily Express
Class Joe Hart Celtic moment in Dingwall shouldn’t go overlooked  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News
Ross County vs Celtic Player Ratings; Two Celtic Standouts  CeltsAreHere
Daizen Maeda Celtic injury latest as Ange Postecoglou discusses Ross County knock  Football Scotland
Liel Abada says Ange Postecoglou's detailed planning is behind unbeaten run  Daily Record
View Full coverage on Google News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers pace, Jota class, Aberdeen star, Hibs-Hearts, huge win for St Johnstone - watch Premiership review]]></title>
        <id>3798249</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/rangers-pace-jota-class-aberdeen-star-hibs-hearts-huge-win-for-st-johnstone-watch-premiership-review-3798249"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T19:23:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second weekend of Scottish Premiership action produced 17 goals and plenty of drama and talking points.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I’m told…’ - BBC journalist reveals Celtic ‘interest’ in ‘quality’ 28 y/o; loan deal possible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-hoops-ross-barkley-transfer-news-latest-rumours/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-hoops-ross-barkley-transfer-news-latest-rumours/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T19:10:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are interested in signing Chelsea midfielder Ross Barkley this summer, according to BBC journalist Fraser Fletcher. The Lowdown: Barkley’s absence In recent years, the 28-year-old has been largely absent from the Chelsea team at Stamford Bridge. The former England international has played just 14 times for the Blues under current boss Thomas Tuchel, making […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic&#039;s ideal opportunity to reintroduce Hoops star returning from injury]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/celtics-ideal-opportunity-to-reintroduce-returning-defender/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/celtics-ideal-opportunity-to-reintroduce-returning-defender/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Saturday afternoon, Celtic fans were delighted to see the return of defender Carl Starfelt from injury. The 27-year-old arrived at Parkhead last summer to join Ange Postecoglou’s new-look Hoops squad, who underwent a huge rebuild. After signing from Russian side Rubin Kazan, the central defender was thrust straight into the starting 11 and faced ...
The post Celtic&#039;s ideal opportunity to reintroduce Hoops star returning from injury appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ibrox’s Whingeing About The Belgian’s “Disrespect” Is The Act Of A Pitiful Club.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/ibroxs-whingeing-about-the-belgians-disrespect-is-the-act-of-a-pitiful-club/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/ibroxs-whingeing-about-the-belgians-disrespect-is-the-act-of-a-pitiful-club/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T19:05:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What a pathetic, contemptible press conference they had at Ibrox today, full of blubbering bitchery about the Belgians and their after-match celebrations. Ibrox really plays the victim card for all its worth, don’t they? And their demands for “respect” sound ridiculous when delivered by a club which doesn’t have the least bit of it for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scottish football fan behaviour: Pyros, pitch invasions, sick chants and players pelted by missiles - the deterrent is not enough]]></title>
        <id>3798239</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/scottish-football-fan-behaviour-pyros-pitch-invasions-sick-chants-and-players-pelted-by-missiles-the-deterrent-is-not-enough-3798239"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T18:37:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The announcement over the Tannoy at Easter Road was loud, clear and precise. On a Sabbath at shortly before midday, it had a sermon-like quality in its promise of hellfire for transgressors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alan Pattullo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Repellent' Super Trouper chant by mindless Celtic minority under fire from club's own fans - Scottish Daily Express]]></title>
        <id>CAIiELip8sMUafcttfH4q1T14RYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowi76vCzCYyccDMKzzuAc</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottishdailyexpress.co.uk/news/scottish-news/repellent-super-trouper-chant-mindless-27689464"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T18:17:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA['Repellent' Super Trouper chant by mindless Celtic minority under fire from club's own fans  Scottish Daily Express]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Embarrassed. Pride’s hurt. We let ourselves down. We let the club down,” Dean Gibson]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/embarrassed-prides-hurt-we-let-ourselves-down-we-let-the-club-down-dean-gibson/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/embarrassed-prides-hurt-we-let-ourselves-down-we-let-the-club-down-dean-gibson/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T17:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dean Gibson, the coach of the Hibernian Women side thrashed 9-0 by Fran Alonso’s rampant Celtic side in the SWPL1 opener at Airdrie, has admitted that his team embarrassed the Easter Road club yesterday.Hat-tricks for Cal-Jac (Clarissa Larisey and Jacynta), a double from former Hibs star Amy Gallacher and an own goal all added up Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Miller in BBC Sportscene Celtic Admission]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/kenny-miller-in-bbc-sportscene-celtic-admission/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/kenny-miller-in-bbc-sportscene-celtic-admission/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T17:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Miller who played for both Glasgow clubs has admitted that Celtic so far look the better of the two teams from what he’s watched already this season.  Although the former Scotland internationalist will be remembered more for his time at Ibrox, he did win the double under Gordon Strachan in 2006/07. The former striker […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Miller in BBC Sportscene Celtic Admission - CeltsAreHere]]></title>
        <id>CBMiSWh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9rZW5ueS1taWxsZXItaW4tYmJjLXNwb3J0c2NlbmUtY2VsdGljLWFkbWlzc2lvbi_SAU1odHRwczovL2NlbHRzYXJlaGVyZS5jb20va2VubnktbWlsbGVyLWluLWJiYy1zcG9ydHNjZW5lLWNlbHRpYy1hZG1pc3Npb24vYW1wLw</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/kenny-miller-in-bbc-sportscene-celtic-admission/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T17:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Miller in BBC Sportscene Celtic Admission  CeltsAreHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s Start Has Been Excellent, Hence Some In The Media’s Negativity Around It.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/celtics-start-has-been-excellent-hence-some-in-the-medias-negativity-around-it/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/celtics-start-has-been-excellent-hence-some-in-the-medias-negativity-around-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T17:37:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This season is only just underway, but still it has rocked the perceptions of a lot of people who thought they had it figured out before it began. They never expected Ange to succeed last year. So of course, they had to explain it away as some kind of one off. As a movie buff, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic duo leaving could cause Champions League problem - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEEMIcEs5RWotfjA_M0XSUCkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4KKJCzCv9JoDMICkoAY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2022/08/08/celtic-duo-champions-league-problem/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T17:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic duo leaving could cause Champions League problem  The Celtic Bhoys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The exciting Celtic change against Ross County that we could see more of this season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-exciting-celtic-change-against-ross-county-that-we-could-see-more-of-this-season/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-exciting-celtic-change-against-ross-county-that-we-could-see-more-of-this-season/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there is one thing that Ange Postecoglou’s Celtic side currently has in abundance, it is attacking talent. The 56-year-old prides himself on his attacking style of play, which was on display right from the off upon his arrival last summer. During his first 12 months at the club, Postecoglou oversaw a dramatic rebuild, which ...
The post The exciting Celtic change against Ross County that we could see more of this season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Kennedy’s Potential Job Opportunity]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/?p=88978</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/?p=88978"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Kennedy has been linked with a move to Danish side FC Midtjylland to take over the role as manager.  The former Celtic defender has worked under four different Celtic managers and has a wealth of experience with a very impressive honours list. FC Midtjylland are on the hunt for a new boss after Bo […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Pools – Helping create winners on and off the pitch]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-pools-helping-create-winners-on-and-off-the-pitch/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-pools-helping-create-winners-on-and-off-the-pitch/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T15:59:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Pools – Helping create winners on and off the pitch – 2021/22 year in review…For almost sixty years, Celtic Pools has been the Club’s official lottery operator, gifting millions of pounds worth of prizes to supporters and providing a vital source of support to youth development at Celtic.Thanks to your support, Celtic Pools have Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Pools – Helping create winners on and off the pitch - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEA7EtpBjECWkr1-pVA0XhIwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-pools-helping-create-winners-on-and-off-the-pitch/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T15:59:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Pools – Helping create winners on and off the pitch  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Impressive Celtic performers are already showcasing the effects of Ange&#039;s pre-season work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/impressive-celtic-performers-are-already-showcasing-the-effects-of-anges-pre-season-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/impressive-celtic-performers-are-already-showcasing-the-effects-of-anges-pre-season-work/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been a strong start to the season for Celtic, picking up two victories to kick off the Scottish Premiership campaign. The Bhoys faced two potentially tricky fixtures to start their push for a second title under Ange Postecoglou, with Aberdeen travelling to Glasgow before a trip to Ross County. However, Postecoglou’s side came ...
The post Impressive Celtic performers are already showcasing the effects of Ange&#039;s pre-season work appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise And Rise Of Celtic’s New Unsung Hero Greg Taylor.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/the-rise-and-rise-of-celtics-new-unsung-hero-greg-taylor/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/the-rise-and-rise-of-celtics-new-unsung-hero-greg-taylor/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T15:32:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is great to watch Celtic at the moment, and in particular to watch how the players are coming into their own after one year with Ange Postecoglou in charge. We can see the improvements in guys who we’ve brought to the club in the last year, of course, but in my opinion the real […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Groundhog day for Brendan Rodgers]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/groundhog-day-for-brendan-rodgers/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/groundhog-day-for-brendan-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T14:13:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been over three years since Brendan Rodgers left Celtic and now he is left facing a situation which he knows all too well.  Although Rodgers departed Celtic a long while ago now, time is yet to be too great a healer for the former Hoops boss who left the Hoops in February 2019 before […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable source shuts down &#039;farfetched&#039; link as Celtic continue active transfer approach]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/reliable-source-shuts-down-farfetched-link-as-celtic-continue-active-transfer-approach/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/reliable-source-shuts-down-farfetched-link-as-celtic-continue-active-transfer-approach/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s links to Chelsea midfielder Ross Barkley have been short-lived after reliable transfer source Mark Hendry described the rumours as ‘farfetched’ [Football Scotland]. On Sunday afternoon, a report from Givemesport stated that Ange Postecoglou’s side were among the clubs interested in bringing the midfielder in on loan. The Hoops were quoted alongside the likes of ...
The post Reliable source shuts down &#039;farfetched&#039; link as Celtic continue active transfer approach appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable source shuts down ‘farfetched’ link as Celtic continue active transfer approach - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>1527569893</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/reliable-source-shuts-down-farfetched-link-as-celtic-continue-active-transfer-approach/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable source shuts down ‘farfetched’ link as Celtic continue active transfer approach  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News
Ross Barkley 'interesting' Celtic as Chelsea try to offload midfield misfit  Daily Record
Massive Ross Barkley to Celtic transfer news emerges  The Celtic Bhoys
Celtic in heavyweight transfer 'battle' as they tussle with West Ham for Premier League maestro  Glasgow Live
Celtic Credited With Ross Barkley Interest  CeltsAreHere
View Full coverage on Google News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic No.2 John Kennedy 'under consideration' for FC Midtjylland job]]></title>
        <id>9a6ed2abe60df037a4020a276fdc230e</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20608730.celtic-no-2-john-kennedy-under-consideration-fc-midtjylland-job/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T14:06:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC No.2 John Kennedy is reportedly under consideration for a managerial job on the continent, according to a report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic linked midfielder 'on trial' with Reading FC as Paul Ince eyes free agent to bolster side - Berkshire Live]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEO9RKYVkbpL7P__Aj6MEfUAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowiKD9CjD-yvQCMIrp0wU</id>
        <link href="https://www.getreading.co.uk/sport/football/transfer-news/celtic-reading-free-agent-midfielder-24701430"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T13:51:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic linked midfielder 'on trial' with Reading FC as Paul Ince eyes free agent to bolster side  Berkshire Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ross Barkley and The Celtic Speculation]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/ross-barkley-and-the-celtic-speculation/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/ross-barkley-and-the-celtic-speculation/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T13:33:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During a transfer window there is all sorts of speculation and links with players but is has been confirmed that Ross Barkley is not on Celtic’s radar. [Football Scotland]. Mark Hendry from Football Scotland has been near enough spot on with Celtic’s transfer targets this summer. The 28-year old Chelsea midfield looks set to leave […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Kennedy faces potential Celtic exit as Midtjylland eye Ange Postecoglou’s right hand man - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEJ5Xq1j2CcB2Xn2Ixo7n4ugqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/john-kennedy-faces-potential-celtic-27687093"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T13:29:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Kennedy faces potential Celtic exit as Midtjylland eye Ange Postecoglou’s right hand man  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic FC Women Get Off To A Great Start. - Vital Celtic]]></title>
        <id>CBMiTGh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdGljLnZpdGFsZm9vdGJhbGwuY28udWsvY2VsdGljLWZjLXdvbWVuLWdldC1vZmYtdG8tYS1ncmVhdC1zdGFydC_SAVBodHRwczovL2NlbHRpYy52aXRhbGZvb3RiYWxsLmNvLnVrL2NlbHRpYy1mYy13b21lbi1nZXQtb2ZmLXRvLWEtZ3JlYXQtc3RhcnQvYW1wLw</id>
        <link href="https://celtic.vitalfootball.co.uk/celtic-fc-women-get-off-to-a-great-start/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic FC Women Get Off To A Great Start.  Vital Celtic]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SPFL transfer news LIVE as Celtic Barkley links and Rangers flop nears £25 move - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEFKyfPLwMv5ulxsVLBrSficqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPTfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/transfer-news/spfl-transfer-blog-live-celtic-24696594"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T12:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SPFL transfer news LIVE as Celtic Barkley links and Rangers flop nears £25 move  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liel Abada Is One Of Celtic’s “Good Soldiers” On And Off The Pitch.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/liel-abada-is-one-of-celtics-good-soldiers-on-and-off-the-pitch/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/liel-abada-is-one-of-celtics-good-soldiers-on-and-off-the-pitch/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T12:48:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love Liel Abada as a footballer, but he’s also got to be a good person because those are the only type of people Ange brings to Celtic. In the aftermath of the game at the weekend he has spoken to the media. Everything he said was focussed on the team. Abada didn’t start at […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: European side considering surprise managerial move for Celtic coach]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/report-fc-midtjylland-considering-surprise-managerial-move-for-celtic-coach/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/report-fc-midtjylland-considering-surprise-managerial-move-for-celtic-coach/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[European side FC Midtjylland are reportedly considering a potential surprise managerial move for Celtic coach John Kennedy. The 38-year-old is currently part of Ange Postecoglou’s backroom staff, alongside fellow first-team coaches Harry Kewell and Gavin Strachan. Kennedy has previously held several different roles at Parkhead after bringing his playing career to an end early, including ...
The post Report: European side considering surprise managerial move for Celtic coach appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: FC Midtjylland considering surprise managerial move for Celtic coach - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CBMibGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL25ld3MvcmVwb3J0LWZjLW1pZHRqeWxsYW5kLWNvbnNpZGVyaW5nLXN1cnByaXNlLW1hbmFnZXJpYWwtbW92ZS1mb3ItY2VsdGljLWNvYWNoL9IBcGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL25ld3MvcmVwb3J0LWZjLW1pZHRqeWxsYW5kLWNvbnNpZGVyaW5nLXN1cnByaXNlLW1hbmFnZXJpYWwtbW92ZS1mb3ItY2VsdGljLWNvYWNoLz9hbXA</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/report-fc-midtjylland-considering-surprise-managerial-move-for-celtic-coach/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Report: FC Midtjylland considering surprise managerial move for Celtic coach  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simon Jordan gets tough on Rangers over Champions League reality - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEL1Ti1vagzg8LiFD3ZcKCwAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/simon-jordan-gets-tough-rangers-27686212"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T12:34:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Simon Jordan gets tough on Rangers over Champions League reality  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The potential Celtic selection headache Ange Postecoglou will love to have]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-potential-celtic-selection-headache-ange-postecoglou-will-love-to-have/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-potential-celtic-selection-headache-ange-postecoglou-will-love-to-have/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What a difference a year makes. Last summer, Celtic were in the middle of a dramatic rebuild as Ange Postecoglou looked to build his squad for the season ahead. The 56-year-old brought 12 new faces to the club as his new-look side went on to lift the Scottish Premiership and Premier Sports cup. Of course, ...
The post The potential Celtic selection headache Ange Postecoglou will love to have appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Burchill Buzzing After Daughter’s Celtic Debut]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/mark-burchill-buzzing-after-daughters-celtic-debut/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/mark-burchill-buzzing-after-daughters-celtic-debut/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T11:56:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker Mark Burchill’s daughter Tiree followed in the footsteps of her Dad by making her first start for the Celtic Women’s team on Sunday.  It was a great day for Fran Alonso’s side as they kicked the season off in style as they emphatically defeated Hibs 9-0 at the Excelsior stadium. This was […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nine goals then perfect 10/10 player ratings from Fran Alonso]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/nine-goals-then-perfect-10-10-player-ratings-from-fran-alonso/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/nine-goals-then-perfect-10-10-player-ratings-from-fran-alonso/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T11:54:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summarising his thoughts after that sensational 90 minutes of football from his Celtic side yesterday afternoon, in the 9-0 season opener against Hibs, a delighted Fran Alonso said, ‘in one word, it would be pride. I am so proud of the Ghirls. We had a game-plan and they had been outstanding all week in training, Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glasgow grandad facing football banning order for lighting flare before Old Firm game]]></title>
        <id>3a61ced82e694092c3838e1e099b69ac</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20608207.glasgow-grandad-facing-football-banning-order-lighting-flare-old-firm-game/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T11:46:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Archibald Smith, 58, sparked the pyrotechnic close to Celtic Park on February 2, 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic defender in limbo as manager pulls no punches over situation that 'should be clear']]></title>
        <id>67307d9a855032b4e7e02b59a47fd95d</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20608182.ex-celtic-defender-limbo-faces-frozen-current-club/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T11:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic defender Jack Hendry is facing the prospect of having to leave Club Brugge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's transfer business not finished yet amid 'interest' in Ross Barkley]]></title>
        <id>64aaa0ce7a282e69943532d682f85b1d</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20608056.celtics-transfer-business-not-finished-yet-amid-interest-premier-league-star/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T11:12:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are reportedly 'interested' in Chelsea midfielder Ross Barkley, according to reports.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALL OVER FOR CELTIC’S ‘LOST BHOY’?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/all-over-for-celtics-lost-bhoy/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/all-over-for-celtics-lost-bhoy/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T11:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CHRISTOPHER JULLIEN’S Celtic career is surely over. That’s the only conclusion that can be drawn from the fact the French centre-back was overlooked for Ange Postecoglou’s matchday squad for the second successive Premiership game. There was no sign of Jullien, who cost £7million when Neil Lennon signed him from Toulouse in June 2019, in the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jota needs to hide effectively too]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/jota-needs-to-hide-effectively-too/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/jota-needs-to-hide-effectively-too/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T11:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With four assists and a goal in the opening two fixtures of the campaign, Jota is getting himself noticed.  We have seen this before with players on a prodigious streak.  Opposition teams scout Celtic, record where the danger comes from, then spend 90 minutes trying to inhibit the player. We are inevitably going to see [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Hendry in Club Brugge limbo as ex Celtic star and Burnley transfer target dealt with major blow - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEMB9pb1OYm9udF_KJtQp_QwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPLfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/jack-hendry-club-brugge-limbo-24698534"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T10:54:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Hendry in Club Brugge limbo as ex Celtic star and Burnley transfer target dealt with major blow  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic interested in outcast £10m rated international striker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/report-celtic-interested-in-international-ligue-1-striker-bamba-dieng/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/report-celtic-interested-in-international-ligue-1-striker-bamba-dieng/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T10:47:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are reportedly interested in outcast Marseille striker Bamba Dieng, who looks set for a move away from the Ligue 1 side this summer. The 22-year-old has made 42 appearances for his current side, scoring nine goals and providing a further three assists during that time. Dieng joined Marseille in 2020 after a successful first ...
The post Report: Celtic interested in outcast £10m rated international striker appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kieran Tierney's injuries 'becoming a problem' as Celtic legend given brutal live Sky Sports assessment]]></title>
        <id>4dc8a204427fe74e619c9a3ca2882b8c</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20607943.former-celtic-hero-receives-injury-warning-jamie-carragher/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T10:46:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic defender Kieran Tierney has had his fitness questioned by Liverpool legend Jamie Carragher.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sensational Unique Angle – Watch all nine Celtic goals against Hibs]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/sensational-unique-angle-watch-all-nine-celtic-goals-against-hibs/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/sensational-unique-angle-watch-all-nine-celtic-goals-against-hibs/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T10:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sit back and enjoy the Unique Angle goals from Celtic TV from yesterday’s SWPL opener when Celtic sent out a message to theRangers, Glasgow City and of course Hibernian Women that Fran Alonso’s team are serious about winning the league this season.There’s so much to enjoy in this video, watch your Tiree Burchill inside the Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Interest in Senegalese International – French Report]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-interest-in-senegalese-international-french-report/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-interest-in-senegalese-international-french-report/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T10:42:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic wants to sign Senegalese international Bamba Dieng, according to French outlet Homme du Match. The 22-year-old striker can be deployed on both wings. Currently, he plays with Olympique Marseille in the French top division. Dieng played 25 games last season in Ligue 1, netting the ball seven times and assisting a further three goals. […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bamba Dieng 'courted' for Celtic transfer as Marseille keen to offload Newcastle United target - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEBAzvXOuS2XCK8M4k2DmGMYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-transfer-news/bamba-dieng-courted-celtic-transfer-27684291"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T10:17:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bamba Dieng 'courted' for Celtic transfer as Marseille keen to offload Newcastle United target  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Amazing to be honest,” Patsy Gallacher’s great grand-daughter Amy’s scoring debut]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/amazing-to-be-honest-patsy-gallachers-great-grand-daughter-amys-scoring-debut/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/amazing-to-be-honest-patsy-gallachers-great-grand-daughter-amys-scoring-debut/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T10:16:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[She’s the great grand-daughter of Celtic legend Patsy Gallacher and yesterday afternoon, after her summer move across the M8 she finally got the chance to wear the Hoops after going Celtic from Hibs.And the Edinburgh side were on the wrong end of Gallacher’s first two goals for Celtic, rubbing salt into their wounds after hat-tricks Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Hendry Looking for New Club]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/jack-hendry-looking-for-new-club/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/jack-hendry-looking-for-new-club/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T10:11:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Hendry’s fairytale has come to an end. After leaving Celtic, he excelled on loan with Oostende before sealing a big-money move to Club Brugge, but after just a season with the club, he’s looking for his next destination. [Daily Record] The former Celtic player is not part of the plans and has been left […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star sends important squad message after impressive Ross County showing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/liel-abada-sends-important-celtic-message-after-impressive-ross-county-showing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/liel-abada-sends-important-celtic-message-after-impressive-ross-county-showing/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic winger Liel Abada has stated that squad rotation is bound to take place, with Ange Postecoglou’s side facing another long season ahead. The 20-year-old scored his first goal of the new campaign on Saturday, coming off the bench to replace the injured Daizen Maeda at the break. Abada’s strike was one of the highlights ...
The post Celtic star sends important squad message after impressive Ross County showing appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer update as club 'interested' in exiled Ligue 1 forward]]></title>
        <id>c2131e03e3428cc6edefa256df1faef2</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20607679.celtic-transfer-update-club-interested-exiled-ligue-1-forward/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T09:43:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are interested in Marseille forward Bamba Dieng, according to reports from French outlet Homme Du Match.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic "embarrass" Hibs, as Rangers and Glasgow City hand out thrashings - SWPL round-up]]></title>
        <id>3797071</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-embarrass-hibs-as-rangers-and-glasgow-city-hand-out-thrashings-swpl-round-up-3797071"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T09:28:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opening day in the Scottish Women’s Premier League (SWPL) saw Fran Alonso’s Celtic destroy Hibs, Rangers hit double figures, Glasgow City down Spartans and a Hearts summer signing hit a dream hat-trick on debut.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Graham Falk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic star&#039;s delight as daughter makes impressive first start]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/mark-burchills-delight-as-daughter-makes-first-celtic-start/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/mark-burchills-delight-as-daughter-makes-first-celtic-start/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T09:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic player Mark Burchill has reacted to his daughter making her first start for the Hoops Women’s team on Sunday. After a busy pre-season of friendly fixtures, Fran Alonso’s side got the competitive action underway last weekend, taking on Hibernian in the league opener. The Ghirls ran out comprehensive winners over the Edinburgh side, ...
The post Former Celtic star&#039;s delight as daughter makes impressive first start appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Burchill’s delight as daughter makes first Celtic start - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CBMiZ2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL2NlbHRpYy1mYy13b21lbi9tYXJrLWJ1cmNoaWxscy1kZWxpZ2h0LWFzLWRhdWdodGVyLW1ha2VzLWZpcnN0LWNlbHRpYy1zdGFydC_SAWtodHRwczovL3d3dy42N2hhaWxoYWlsLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtZmMtd29tZW4vbWFyay1idXJjaGlsbHMtZGVsaWdodC1hcy1kYXVnaHRlci1tYWtlcy1maXJzdC1jZWx0aWMtc3RhcnQvP2FtcA</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/mark-burchills-delight-as-daughter-makes-first-celtic-start/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T09:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Burchill’s delight as daughter makes first Celtic start  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s hat-trick Ghirls Cal-Jac show off their signed match-day balls]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtics-hat-trick-ghirls-cal-jac-show-off-their-signed-match-day-balls/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtics-hat-trick-ghirls-cal-jac-show-off-their-signed-match-day-balls/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T09:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best way to make the support forget all about losing a 40 goal a season striker is for the team to go out, hit the back of the net and prove a point that there’s plenty of other players who can do that job for Celtic.After a difficult summer with the Scottish Cup winning Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s hat-trick Ghirls Cal-Jac show off their signed match-day balls - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEO4Gl7ZCgZZXoLZchzfEixgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtics-hat-trick-ghirls-cal-jac-show-off-their-signed-match-day-balls/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T09:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s hat-trick Ghirls Cal-Jac show off their signed match-day balls  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic spark that means they have started title chase better than Rangers]]></title>
        <id>efbbbed9a9b34ca6cd96fd5b1170f9f2</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20607537.former-celtic-player-exciting-going-forward-claim-explains-hoops-started-better-rangers/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T09:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic striker Kenny Miller has praised his former clubs start to the domestic season and explained how they have kicked off slightly stronger than their Glasgow rivals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer rumours: Coady to Everton, Barkley to Celtic, Lirola to Southampton]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sportsmole.co.uk/football/man-utd/transfer-talk/feature/transfer-rumours-coady-to-everton-barkley-to-celtic-lirola-to-southampton_491796.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.sportsmole.co.uk/football/man-utd/transfer-talk/feature/transfer-rumours-coady-to-everton-barkley-to-celtic-lirola-to-southampton_491796.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T08:47:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sports Mole rounds up the latest transfer rumours, including Conor Coady to Everton, Ross Barkley to Celtic and Pol Lirola to Southampton.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liel Abada explains the crucial Postecoglou factor helping extend Celtic’s long unbeaten run]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/liel-abada-explains-the-crucial-postecoglou-factor-helping-extend-celtics-long-unbeaten-run/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/liel-abada-explains-the-crucial-postecoglou-factor-helping-extend-celtics-long-unbeaten-run/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic winger Liel Abada has explained one of the key parts of Ange Postecoglou’s preparation that has helped the Hoops stretch their unbeaten run to 34 games. The Bhoys travelled to Dingwall last weekend, looking to continue their perfect start to the Scottish Premiership by picking up six points from six. Three second-half goals helped ...
The post Liel Abada explains the crucial Postecoglou factor helping extend Celtic’s long unbeaten run appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“I knew the yellow card was coming,” Liel Abada]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/i-knew-the-yellow-card-was-coming-liel-abada/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/i-knew-the-yellow-card-was-coming-liel-abada/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T08:31:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liel Abada’s celebration at Dingwall – taking his shirt off – was always going to get him a yellow card – and although he reckons it was worth it, these things can come back to haunt you later in the season. Ange might have a quiet word, or simply regard it as an emotional reaction Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mikey Johnston’s Late Night Post]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/mikey-johnstons-late-night-post/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/mikey-johnstons-late-night-post/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T07:25:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mikey Johnston has been linked with a move away from Celtic for a week now, but reports haven’t suggested he’s edging closer to a Parkhead exit. Late on Sunday night, Mikey Johnston posted a picture of him from pre-season. It showed him playing for the Hoops without a caption. Many fans are wondering the same […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boruc Names Current and Former Celtic Stars in All Time Best XI]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/boruc-names-current-and-former-celtic-stars-in-all-time-best-xi/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/boruc-names-current-and-former-celtic-stars-in-all-time-best-xi/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T07:13:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ARTUR BORUC has hung up his boots, ending an action-packed career. Throughout his playing days, he played alongside some top talents, but he’s managed to narrow them down to just eleven. The Polish keeper has selected ten other players to create the best XI he’s ever played with. Josip Juranovic has been sensational since he […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers delivers doomsday Leicester City scenario as ex Celtic boss left with hands tied - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEBzLyf--be4C9if1sdvJdqcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPPfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/brendan-rodgers-delivers-doomsday-leicester-24696306"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T07:10:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers delivers doomsday Leicester City scenario as ex Celtic boss left with hands tied  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero Kris Commons makes Rangers Champions League prediction]]></title>
        <id>685bea932ad5baca47bf60dcce207ae0</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20607246.celtic-hero-kris-commons-makes-rangers-champions-league-prediction/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T06:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE opening half-an-hour of Rangers' second-leg Champions League qualifier against Union Saint-Gilloise will be pivotal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer news LIVE as Celtic and Rangers plus Aberdeen, Hearts and Hibs make signings - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CBMibmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLXRyYW5zZmVyLW5ld3MvdHJhbnNmZXItbmV3cy1saXZlLWNlbHRpYy1yYW5nZXJzLTI3NjgyMjc10gFyaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZGFpbHlyZWNvcmQuY28udWsvc3BvcnQvZm9vdGJhbGwvZm9vdGJhbGwtdHJhbnNmZXItbmV3cy90cmFuc2Zlci1uZXdzLWxpdmUtY2VsdGljLXJhbmdlcnMtMjc2ODIyNzUuYW1w</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-transfer-news/transfer-news-live-celtic-rangers-27682275"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T06:52:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer news LIVE as Celtic and Rangers plus Aberdeen, Hearts and Hibs make signings  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kris Commons in Rangers Champions League prediction as he points to Celtic blueprint - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEI8dBSuHJRfdsA4lRfOxhGcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/kris-commons-rangers-champions-league-27682336"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T06:28:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kris Commons in Rangers Champions League prediction as he points to Celtic blueprint  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S ‘NON-STARTER’ READY FOR MARATHON]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtics-non-starter-ready-for-marathon/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtics-non-starter-ready-for-marathon/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T06:16:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIEL ABADA has been a non-starter in the first two games of Celtic’s Premiership defence – but the goalscoring winger WILL play a vital role in the season’s marathon. The Israeli international came off the substitutes’ bench for the wins over Aberdeen, 2-0 at Parkhead, and Ross County, 3-1 in Dingwall, and made an impact [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic final word: Jota catching eye of scouts with this trajectory already - and can Moritz Jenz win his own battle?]]></title>
        <id>3796682</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-final-word-jota-catching-eye-of-scouts-with-this-trajectory-already-and-can-moritz-jenz-win-his-own-battle-3796682"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are only two games into the 2022/23 cinch Premiership season and already a favourite for player of the year has emerged.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic On This Day – 8th August – David Potter’s Celtic Diary]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-on-this-day-8th-august-david-potters-celtic-diary/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-on-this-day-8th-august-david-potters-celtic-diary/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 8 of Celtic Historian David Potter’s new diary  on The Celtic Star  which will run throughout the new season and will highlight key Celtic related events relevant to each day, today covering 8 August…SATURDAY 8 AUGUST 1931Celtic open the new season with a trip to Marine Gardens, Leith where they beat Leith Athletic 3-0 with Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Ronny Deila Roars for New Club]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/video-ronny-deila-roars-for-new-club/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/video-ronny-deila-roars-for-new-club/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T05:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RONNY DEILA brought his famous ‘Ronny Roar’ to the Jupiler Pro League at the weekend after registering his first victory as boss of Standard Liege. The former Celtic manager took over the Belgian side in the summer, leaving New York City FC after a successful spell in the States. Ronny is tasked with improving Standard […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: BIG YOGI AND LISBON: THE TRUTH (Part Two)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/95034-2/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/95034-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T05:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MYSTERY has surrounded the non-appearance of Celtic great John ‘Yogi’ Hughes from Jock Stein’s Lisbon line-up ever since that memorable, history-making day in the Portuguese capital on May 25 1967. The iconic Hoops star played in five of the eight games leading up to the European Cup Final, but the nearest he got to the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major Ross County Flashpoint Flies Under Radar]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/major-ross-county-flashpoint-flies-under-radar/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/major-ross-county-flashpoint-flies-under-radar/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC dominated the game in Dingwall on Saturday as expected but it took a little later to make certain of all three points in the end. County were set up to frustrate from the off and be as robust as possible when dealing with the Hoops players. It’s something we’ve grown accustomed to in the […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Rangers complete Champions League salvage job and should Celtic let James McCarthy leave? Monday Jury - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEAluMJwH8vEuxs4XCuPn2xsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/rangers-complete-champions-league-salvage-27680518"/>
        <updated>2022-08-08T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will Rangers complete Champions League salvage job and should Celtic let James McCarthy leave? Monday Jury  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ross County 1-3 Celtic and 3pm blackout rule nonsense - reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.jerseydoesntshrink.com/2022/8/7/23296063/ross-county-1-3-celtic-and-3pm-blackout-rule-nonsense-reaction</id>
        <link href="https://www.jerseydoesntshrink.com/2022/8/7/23296063/ross-county-1-3-celtic-and-3pm-blackout-rule-nonsense-reaction"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T23:21:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Craig Williamson/SNS Group via Getty Images
  

 The latest GIGPOD covering yesterdays game is now live and available everywhere you listen to your podcasts! It’s episode 123 - and there’s no Spunkphone - good news for everyone! 


 NEW PODCAST ⚪️ GIGPOD EPISODE 123: THIS IS ABADA ON THE RIGHT  Reidzo & Stevie discuss three well earned points on the road and this IDIOTIC no football on tv in Scotland at 3pm crap which has to go Spotify: https://t.co/okZG1K2rTc& everywhere else as per pic.twitter.com/qZgxHKB67I— GIGPOD ⚪️ (@gigpod) August 7, 2022



Discussing: 
A hard fought win up in the highlands
Jota’s brilliance, again
This ridiculous 3pm blackout farce which really has to go after Saturday’s debacle
And most importantly, the new feature where YOU decide the music on the show. Interactive legends ? It’s a yes from us.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artur Boruc selects Celtic star in his career XI along with mercurial teammates]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/artur-boruc-selects-celtic-star-in-his-career-xi-along-with-mercurial-teammates/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/artur-boruc-selects-celtic-star-in-his-career-xi-along-with-mercurial-teammates/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T22:18:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artur Boruc has named Celtic’s Josip Juranovic in his best XI from across his career. Celtic were in Warsaw last month to play a game against Legia in honour of the great career that the big goalkeeper had. However, in the weeks following his retirement, Boruc has compiled a list of his best teammates across Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liel Abada makes Celtic squad selection claim as winger vows to make impact every time he's involved]]></title>
        <id>0b681b3620a366f72b51a4690e4e0462</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20606526.liel-abada-makes-celtic-squad-selection-claim-winger-vows-make-impact-every-time-involved/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIEL ABADA concedes that he might not play every game for Celtic this season – but the winger insists he will be ready to make an impact whenever he is brought onto the park.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Miller in Celtic 'better than Rangers' admission but Ibrox hero predicts Champions League turnaround - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEKPEwzhsU4LoJc3sU033ISoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/kenny-miller-celtic-better-rangers-27681405"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T20:21:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Miller in Celtic 'better than Rangers' admission but Ibrox hero predicts Champions League turnaround  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[David Martindale in pointed ‘Mr Montano’ jibe after Celtic and Rangers fan row - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiELLtu2MLP4e8YLYRkiWbxuQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPPfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/david-martindale-pointed-mr-montano-24695614"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T19:58:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Martindale in pointed ‘Mr Montano’ jibe after Celtic and Rangers fan row  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quiet on Celtic’s outgoings as Jullien, Ajeti and McCarthy are linked away]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/quiet-on-celtics-outgoings-as-jullien-ajeti-and-mccarthy-are-linked-away/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/quiet-on-celtics-outgoings-as-jullien-ajeti-and-mccarthy-are-linked-away/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T19:26:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic recorded their second win of the Premiership season on the road against Ross County. Late goals from Moritz Jenz and Liel Abada gave Ange Postecoglou’s side the three points to travel back down from the Highlands. While Ange Postecoglou confirmed that the Scottish Champions will look to strengthen in the next few weeks of Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Must Price Their Champions League Package With The Cost Of Living Crisis In Mind.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/celtic-must-price-their-champions-league-package-with-the-cost-of-living-crisis-in-mind/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/celtic-must-price-their-champions-league-package-with-the-cost-of-living-crisis-in-mind/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T19:23:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a club, Celtic might have been founded on charitable foundations but we’re a business first and foremost now, and a business that does very well. This is very likely to be an exceptional year in terms of turnover and profitability. The Champions League is going to net us a small fortune. When those games […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ryan Christie makes huge claim about why he left Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEPe0vEUi-cXrQCJhRyc9Sz0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4KKJCzCv9JoDMICkoAY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2022/08/07/ryan-christie-huge-claim-left-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T19:03:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ryan Christie makes huge claim about why he left Celtic  The Celtic Bhoys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Brendan Rodgers signing scores stunning winner in MLS]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/video-brendan-rodgers-signing-scores-stunning-winner-in-mls/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-brendan-rodgers-signing-scores-stunning-winner-in-mls/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T18:39:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic full-back Andrew Gutman has scored a stunning last-minute winner for Atlanta United. The 25-year-old struck a sweet left-footed effort into the back of the net to settle the game against Seattle. OMG! ANDREW GUTMAN GAME-WINNER IN STOPPAGE TIME! 😱 pic.twitter.com/DGUAds4na2 — Major League Soccer (@MLS) August 6, 2022 It is a tidy finish Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Match Report: Celtic 9-0 Hibs – My word. That was impressive]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/match-report-celtic-9-0-hibs-my-word-that-was-impressive/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/match-report-celtic-9-0-hibs-my-word-that-was-impressive/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T18:37:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic FC Women kicked of the new SWPL season with a devastating and relentless nine goal demolition of Hibs, which saw Jacynta and Clarissa Larisey both score hat-tricks and new signing Amy Gallacher brab a brace, as pre-season anguish as to how Celtic might replace the forty goals Charlie Wellings scored last season answered by Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Match Report: Celtic 9-0 Hibs – My word. That was impressive - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEGj6pE7uGWXgZzqACIrDET0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/match-report-celtic-9-0-hibs-my-word-that-was-impressive/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T18:37:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Match Report: Celtic 9-0 Hibs – My word. That was impressive  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliving Paul Lambert’s Derby Day screamer against Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/reliving-paul-lamberts-derby-day-screamer-against-rangers/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/reliving-paul-lamberts-derby-day-screamer-against-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T18:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Lambert celebrates his 53rd Birthday today and it gives us a chance to look at one of his greatest goals for Celtic. The central midfielder signed for Wim Jansen’s side in 1997 from Borussia Dortmund. Lambert would go on to become an integral part of the team that stopped 10IAR. In the 1997/98 season, Lambert Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic youngster set to improve greatly this season; shouldn&#039;t be undervalued]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-next-steps-for-liel-abada-and-his-exceptional-instincts-at-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-next-steps-for-liel-abada-and-his-exceptional-instincts-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T18:28:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s victory over Ross County in Dingwall yesterday felt like a statement of intent for the champions. Without ever truly being at their best, it was a game they largely controlled, and even after Alex Iacovitti’s equaliser on the hour, it never felt like a game in which Celtic wouldn’t find a way to win, ...
The post The Celtic youngster set to improve greatly this season; shouldn&#039;t be undervalued appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On This Day: Scott Sinclair scores late winner on debut at Tynecastle]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/on-this-day-scott-sinclair-scores-late-winner-on-debut-at-tynecastle/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/on-this-day-scott-sinclair-scores-late-winner-on-debut-at-tynecastle/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T18:25:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On This Day in 2016, Scott Sinclair made a dream start to life as a Celt. The winger, signed from Aston Villa, joined Celtic in the morning and was named straight away on the bench for the game against Hearts at Tynecastle later that day. The game was Brendan Rodgers’ first in the league and Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Irish outfit confirm signing of promising attacker following Celtic release]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/irish-outfit-confirm-signing-of-promising-attacker-following-celtic-release/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/irish-outfit-confirm-signing-of-promising-attacker-following-celtic-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T18:18:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic youngster Jonathan Afolabi has signed for Irish side Bohemians following his release from the Scottish Champions. Afolabi, 22, joined Celtic in 2019 from Southampton but failed to make a first-team appearance during that time.The FAI outfit announced the arrival of the Irish youth Internationalist on Friday as he looks to kick on after Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sandman’s Definitive Ratings Nonsense – Celtic at Hadley’s Hope]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/sandmans-definitive-ratings-nonsense-celtic-at-hadleys-hope/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/sandmans-definitive-ratings-nonsense-celtic-at-hadleys-hope/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T18:13:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANDMAN’S DEFINITIVE RATINGS NONSENSE: CELTIC @ HADLEY’S HOPE… “Stupid names and utter drivel. Utter nonsense of the highest order. Seems like some would be arsy studenttrying to be clever. Not the sort of type who’d be welcome in our golf club, that’s for sure.” – Patterson & Lapping, Facebook’s interchangeable vocab comedy twins. Or lovers… “I like nonsense; it Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s Contribution To The Co-Efficient Is A European Cup. That’s All That Matters.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/celtics-contribution-to-the-co-efficient-is-a-european-cup-thats-all-that-matters/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/celtics-contribution-to-the-co-efficient-is-a-european-cup-thats-all-that-matters/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T18:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Daily Record is having some fun tonight, and Sevconia is united in joy, at the “news” that the Ibrox has made a greater contribution to Scottish football’s co-efficient than Celtic since the 50’s. Where in God’s name do they get this crap? Why do they assume that any of it matters to us or […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full-time Report: Celtic 9-0 Hibs – Larisey gets her hat-trick then a Gallacher double]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/full-time-report-celtic-9-0-hibs-larisey-gets-her-hat-trick-then-a-gallacher-double/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/full-time-report-celtic-9-0-hibs-larisey-gets-her-hat-trick-then-a-gallacher-double/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T17:32:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic blew Hibs away in a sensational first 45 minutes at the SWPL1 opener at the Penny cars Stadium this afternoon as Fran Alonso’s side swept aside the visitors and any doubters within the Celtic support that the team had been weakened after the historic double cup winning campaign last season.We have already covered the Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic thrash Hibs with remarkable 9-0 Sunday show]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/celtic-thrash-hibs-with-remarkable-9-0-sunday-show/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/celtic-thrash-hibs-with-remarkable-9-0-sunday-show/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T17:04:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic FC Women impressively started the SWPL 1 season this afternoon, destroying Hibernian 9-0 at home. Hat-tricks from Jacynta and Clarissa Larisey, as well as an unfortunate Hibs own goal and Amy Gallacher efforts all contributed to the massive scoreline, delighting Fran Alonso and the attending fans. There has been some concern about Celtic Women ...
The post Celtic thrash Hibs with remarkable 9-0 Sunday show appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic thrash Hibs with remarkable 9-0 Sunday show - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CBMiXmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL2NlbHRpYy1mYy13b21lbi9jZWx0aWMtdGhyYXNoLWhpYnMtd2l0aC1yZW1hcmthYmxlLTktMC1zdW5kYXktc2hvdy_SAWJodHRwczovL3d3dy42N2hhaWxoYWlsLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtZmMtd29tZW4vY2VsdGljLXRocmFzaC1oaWJzLXdpdGgtcmVtYXJrYWJsZS05LTAtc3VuZGF5LXNob3cvP2FtcA</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/celtic-thrash-hibs-with-remarkable-9-0-sunday-show/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T17:04:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic thrash Hibs with remarkable 9-0 Sunday show  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers top Celtic in all-time coefficient hit list as four Scottish clubs make UEFA's top 100 - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEGfX81rBsVEQap9Slcg_uaQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/rangers-top-celtic-time-coefficient-27680526"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T16:54:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers top Celtic in all-time coefficient hit list as four Scottish clubs make UEFA's top 100  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Postecoglou hails "first class" Celtic reaction from Ross County win]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-dismisses-december-comparison-with-first-class-celtic-verdict/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-dismisses-december-comparison-with-first-class-celtic-verdict/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T16:43:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou has hailed his side’s “first class” reaction in the second half of yesterday’s win over Ross County in Dingwall. The champions took the lead early in the second half through Kyogo’s first goal of the season, but were pegged back on the hour by Alex Iacovitti’s equaliser, before Mortiz Jenz and ...
The post Postecoglou hails "first class" Celtic reaction from Ross County win appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Watch the Celtic Goals as Hoops hit Hibs for six in sensational first half]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/video-watch-the-celtic-goals-as-hoops-hit-hibs-for-six-in-sensational-first-half/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-watch-the-celtic-goals-as-hoops-hit-hibs-for-six-in-sensational-first-half/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T16:36:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two from Clarissa Larisey, a hat-trick from Jacynta and an OG that’s the story of the first half at Airdrie’s Penny Cars Stadium as Fran Alonso’s new;look Celtic side look every inch the title challengers that the Celtic manager wants them to be.Sit back and enjoy the six Celtic goals and remember these are against Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Journalist: Celtic could ‘resurrect’ move for £8.5m youngster with ‘great potential’ – report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-transfer-rumours/celtic-hoops-malick-thiaw-transfer-news-latest-rumours/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-transfer-rumours/celtic-hoops-malick-thiaw-transfer-news-latest-rumours/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T16:35:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic could ‘resurrect’ their interest in signing Schalke 04 defender Malick Thiaw this summer, according to journalist Pete O’Rourke. The Lowdown: Previous links In June, Italian outlet Calciomercato reported that the Hoops were ‘in talks’ with the 20-year-old ahead over a potential move to Parkhead. At the same time, Serie A giants AC Milan were also […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Half-time Report: Celtic 6-0 Hibs – Jacynta and Larisey, putting on a show]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/half-time-report-celtic-6-0-hibs-jacynta-and-larisey-putting-on-a-show/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/half-time-report-celtic-6-0-hibs-jacynta-and-larisey-putting-on-a-show/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T16:21:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Where were the goals for Celtic going to come from after the news during the week that last season’s top goalscorer Charlie Wellings had joined Reading for an undisclosed fee? Welling bagged 40 goals in just 34 games for Fran Alonso’s side so in today’s SWPL1 season opener against Hibs, all eyes were on the Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Season’s Just Started, But Celtic Fans Are Right To Be Thrilled By Jota.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/the-seasons-just-started-but-celtic-fans-are-right-to-be-thrilled-by-jota/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/the-seasons-just-started-but-celtic-fans-are-right-to-be-thrilled-by-jota/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T16:17:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last season, Ryan Kent, the Ibrox poster-boy, in one of his better years at the club, got 11 assists in the SPFL. It is worth pointing that out, for a little context, before we start. He played 24 times and created a goal every second game. Good job he was creating them, because he only […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch: The Ronny Roar returns to Europe as former Celtic boss picks up first win in Belgium]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/watch-the-ronny-roar-returns-to-europe-as-former-celtic-boss-picks-up-first-win-in-belgium/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/watch-the-ronny-roar-returns-to-europe-as-former-celtic-boss-picks-up-first-win-in-belgium/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T16:11:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic manager Ronny Deila has celebrated his first win as Standard Liege manager in a fashion that will be instantly familiar to all Hoops supporters. Deila replaced Neil Lennon as Celtic manager in 2014, leading the Hoops to back-to-back league titles and a league cup, before stints at Valerenga in his homeland, and New ...
The post Watch: The Ronny Roar returns to Europe as former Celtic boss picks up first win in Belgium appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch: The Ronny Roar returns to Europe as former Celtic boss picks up first win in Belgium - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEAmkNK0CdGmwqNH0j5j07NgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMLbFpgY</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/watch-the-ronny-roar-returns-to-europe-as-former-celtic-boss-picks-up-first-win-in-belgium/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T16:11:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Watch: The Ronny Roar returns to Europe as former Celtic boss picks up first win in Belgium  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Stewart delivers verdict on Moritz Jenz Celtic debut]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/michael-stewart-delivers-verdict-on-moritz-jenz-celtic-debut/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/michael-stewart-delivers-verdict-on-moritz-jenz-celtic-debut/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T15:40:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BBC Sportsound pundit Michael Stewart has offered his thoughts on the debut performance of new Celtic defender Moritz Jenz, after he scored a vital 84th-minute winner for Celtic over Ross County yesterday. The German came into the starting lineup for the first time in Celtic colours in Stephen Welsh’s absence through illness, and his intervention ...
The post Michael Stewart delivers verdict on Moritz Jenz Celtic debut appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mikey Johnston and Celtic teammate tipped to seal exit after Saturday development – pundit - Football Insider]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEJOSV8v1X7IMKN27yltf3cMqMwgEKioIACIQnJ4k3aT29tENAyPF0QESjSoUCAoiEJyeJN2k9vbRDQMjxdEBEo0w4IzKBg</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballinsider247.com/mikey-johnston-and-celtic-teammate-tipped-to-seal-exit-after-saturday-development-pundit/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T15:17:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mikey Johnston and Celtic teammate tipped to seal exit after Saturday development – pundit  Football Insider]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Credited With Ross Barkley Interest]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-credited-with-ross-barkley-interest/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-credited-with-ross-barkley-interest/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T15:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic aren’t done in the transfer market, Ange Postecoglou has made it clear if the club sees a deal worth doing, they’re flexible enough to go out and get it done. The manager has spoken about outgoings also, we don’t know for sure how much getting players out the door will impact on who can […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and taking the knee as English Premier League agree to a new strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/celtic-and-taking-the-knee-as-english-premier-league-agree-to-a-new-strategy/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/celtic-and-taking-the-knee-as-english-premier-league-agree-to-a-new-strategy/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T15:15:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taking the knee before kick-off has become customary in British football since its return after the outbreak of the COVID-19 pandemic and subsequent initial lockdown. The murder of George Floyd at the hands of Derek Chauvin [The Independent] and subsequent reinvigoration of the Black Lives Matter movement inspired football and other sports to adopt the ...
The post Celtic and taking the knee as English Premier League agree to a new strategy appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou's Celtic selection dilemmas, 'we don't stop' rallying call and best transfer business - Five Things]]></title>
        <id>3ab9d934a46535905f8c0d1ffeeef241</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20606770.ange-postecoglous-selection-dilemmas-we-dont-stop-rallying-call-best-transfer-business---five-things/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T14:48:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC ensured it was six points from six from their opening two Scottish Premiership games on Saturday as they edged past Ross County in Dingwall.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ross Barkley 'interesting' Celtic as Chelsea try to offload midfield misfit - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiELec-z9C-iG_tmllAsg40BQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/ross-barkley-interesting-celtic-chelsea-27679862"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T14:46:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ross Barkley 'interesting' Celtic as Chelsea try to offload midfield misfit  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The solution to Saturday&#039;s Celtic broadcast farce]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-solution-to-saturdays-celtic-broadcast-farce/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-solution-to-saturdays-celtic-broadcast-farce/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T14:41:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The issue of Scottish Premiership broadcast rights is a thorny subject and, at times, emotive. There’s a lot of anger flying about amongst supporters with regards to Sky Sports, the SPFL, clubs and the SFA – some of it deserved and much of it less so. Ultimately the way forward requires discussion and compromise rather ...
The post The solution to Saturday&#039;s Celtic broadcast farce appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BBC Scotland’s Anti-Celtic Bias Summed Up In Two Different Pictures And Reports.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/bbc-scotlands-anti-celtic-bias-summed-up-in-two-different-pictures-and-reports/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/bbc-scotlands-anti-celtic-bias-summed-up-in-two-different-pictures-and-reports/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T14:37:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange was quite snappy yesterday when he stood in front of the BBC’s interviewer, and no wonder considering the ridiculous nature of the questioning. Were we lucky? Were we wasteful? Was he worried? All of which Ange answered emphatically in the negative. We were none of those things. We won and we thoroughly deserved to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BBC Scotland’s Anti-Celtic Bias Summed Up In Two Different Pictures And Reports. - TheCelticBlog.com]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEHorMnNu4TrbOCwvf7gesMkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowne-jCzDg-bsDMLnLhQc</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/bbc-scotlands-anti-celtic-bias-summed-up-in-two-different-pictures-and-reports/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T14:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BBC Scotland’s Anti-Celtic Bias Summed Up In Two Different Pictures And Reports.  TheCelticBlog.com]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Team’s Up – Burchill starts, Larisey and Jacynta up front]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/teams-up-burchill-starts-larisey-and-jacynta-up-front/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/teams-up-burchill-starts-larisey-and-jacynta-up-front/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T14:27:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fran Alonso has named his Celtic side to take on Hibs this afternoon in the SWPL1 season opener at the Penny Cars Stadium in the sunshine of Airdrie.Rachael Johnstone is in goals and the back three is the tried and tested, highly experienced trio of Chloe Craig, the captain Kelly Clark and Caitlin Hayes, all Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hibs launch probe into fan behaviour as Hearts boss Robbie Neilson slams 'unacceptable' Easter Road incidents - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CBMiY2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvaGlicy1sYXVuY2gtcHJvYmUtZmFuLWJlaGF2aW91ci0yNzY3OTc1NtIBAA</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/hibs-launch-probe-fan-behaviour-27679756"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T14:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hibs launch probe into fan behaviour as Hearts boss Robbie Neilson slams 'unacceptable' Easter Road incidents  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Call for Celtic Park tunnel to be renamed in honour of Lisbon Lions legend - Celtic Way]]></title>
        <id>CAIiENQ_iCHO0jtl21dMzd3WQgoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsJStCzC9n8UDMNiMswc</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticway.co.uk/news/20606627.call-celtic-park-tunnel-renamed-honour-lisbon-lions-legend/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T13:17:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Call for Celtic Park tunnel to be renamed in honour of Lisbon Lions legend  Celtic Way]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Idiotic Clickbait Nonsense Links Celtic With Former Everton Wonderkid.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/idiotic-clickbait-nonsense-links-celtic-with-former-everton-wonderkid/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/idiotic-clickbait-nonsense-links-celtic-with-former-everton-wonderkid/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T13:06:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been on the increasingly atrocious Newsnow Celtic aggregator today, you’ll have seen a piece so ridiculous that it beggars belief. It’s a piece “linking” Celtic – but only, it appears, in the mind of the writer – with a move for “£100,000 a week” Ross Barkley, now at Chelsea but who made his […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The spectre of "Old Firm Inc." and why it refuses to die - Read Celtic]]></title>
        <id>CBMiWGh0dHBzOi8vcmVhZGNlbHRpYy5jb20vMjAyMi8wOC8wNy90aGUtc3BlY3RyZS1vZi1vbGQtZmlybS1pbmMtYW5kLXdoeS1pdC1yZWZ1c2VzLXRvLWRpZS_SAQA</id>
        <link href="https://readceltic.com/2022/08/07/the-spectre-of-old-firm-inc-and-why-it-refuses-to-die/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T12:45:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The spectre of "Old Firm Inc." and why it refuses to die  Read Celtic]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic v Hibs Preview: Alonso targets “historic achievement” of SWPL title triumph]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-v-hibs-preview-alonso-targets-historic-achievement-of-swpl-title-triumph/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-v-hibs-preview-alonso-targets-historic-achievement-of-swpl-title-triumph/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T12:12:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the beginning of a new era for the women’s game in Scotland today when the new season kicks off with the return of the SWPL under the SPFL umbrella. That’s an aside really but it’s certainly worth mentioning as it’s something that the clubs hope will lead to a new standard of professionalism in Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic v Hibs Preview: Alonso targets “historic achievement” of SWPL title triumph - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiENW1tto3hlJlqOgP7q7xkbwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-v-hibs-preview-alonso-targets-historic-achievement-of-swpl-title-triumph/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T12:12:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic v Hibs Preview: Alonso targets “historic achievement” of SWPL title triumph  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou talks up Celtic performer who is earning plaudits "the right way"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-singles-out-real-special-celtic-performer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-singles-out-real-special-celtic-performer/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T12:10:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou has singled out Jota for praise after the winger’s inspired performance led the Hoops to victory in Dingwall yesterday. The 23-year-old helped himself to a hat-trick of assists and another man-of-the-match award in the highlands following last week’s stunning strike against Aberdeen at Celtic Park. As reported by The Scottish Sun, ...
The post Ange Postecoglou talks up Celtic performer who is earning plaudits "the right way" appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic callers won't let Rangers fan off the hook as Jota dig ages terribly - Hotline - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiELsKX96cwfBQjzGr8gKmWs8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/celtic-callers-wont-rangers-fan-27679077"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T12:03:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic callers won't let Rangers fan off the hook as Jota dig ages terribly - Hotline  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blinkered Boyd’s Incredible Jota Retort; Live on Air]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/blinkered-boyds-incredible-jota-retort-live-on-air/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/blinkered-boyds-incredible-jota-retort-live-on-air/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T12:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER CELTIC midfielder Scott Allan told Sky Sports live on air he believes Jota is the best player in the league after the winger grabbed three assists in Dingwall. The Portuguese star was in scintillating form six days after his incredible strike against Aberdeen. We have spoken to so many Benfica supporters who are irate […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Only going to get better"; Sky Sports pundit left in awe of Celtic star]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-best-in-the-league-big-sky-sports-praise-for-celtic-hero/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-best-in-the-league-big-sky-sports-praise-for-celtic-hero/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T11:46:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic midfielder Scott Allan has branded current star Jota the best player in Scotland. The 30-year-old was speaking before today’s Edinburgh derby live on Sky Sports, after been released by Hibs in the summer at the conclusion of his contract, also having spent four frustrating years in Paradise from 2015-2019, making very few appearances ...
The post "Only going to get better"; Sky Sports pundit left in awe of Celtic star appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boyd Is Right. Jota Isn’t The League’s Best Player. He’s Not Even Celtic’s Best Player.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/boyd-is-right-jota-isnt-the-leagues-best-player-hes-not-even-celtics-best-player/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/boyd-is-right-jota-isnt-the-leagues-best-player-hes-not-even-celtics-best-player/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T11:29:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kris Boyd has it right for once. But he’s also wrong. Of course. What kind of world would it be if we had Kris Boyd being right in it? Whatever next? Hugh Keevins making a prediction that’s actually on the money? The planet would stop spinning on its axis. Scott Allan (remember him?) was on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["This was why I left Celtic"; Former star speaks out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/this-was-why-i-left-celtic-ryan-christie-speaks-about-move-to-england/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/this-was-why-i-left-celtic-ryan-christie-speaks-about-move-to-england/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T11:15:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic midfielder Ryan Christie has opened up on his exit from Paradise a year on from making the move south to Bournemouth. The 27-year-old left the Hoops on deadline day last summer after 5 years at the club, and will star in the Premier League this season following the Cherries’ promotion, with tough fixtures ...
The post "This was why I left Celtic"; Former star speaks out appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“This was why I left Celtic”; Ryan Christie speaks about move to England - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEGAbxVRc1V5HQxAufE-uraEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMLbFpgY</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/this-was-why-i-left-celtic-ryan-christie-speaks-about-move-to-england/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T11:15:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“This was why I left Celtic”; Ryan Christie speaks about move to England  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Fans Receive Sunday Boost]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-fans-receive-sunday-boost/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-fans-receive-sunday-boost/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The only Celtic fans inside the UK and Ireland able to watch the Ross County game legitimately on Saturday were the supporters inside the stadium. Sky Sports opted not to air the game, and the archaic 3pm TV kick off agreement the SPFL sign up to every season proves it’s not fit for purpose. Celtic […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Season opener 2022-23]]></title>
        <id>http://celticunderground.net/season-opener/</id>
        <link href="http://celticunderground.net/season-opener/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T10:40:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last Sunday (31st July) saw the flag day season opener of the 2022-23 campaign.   Here’s some pics:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top-flight boss in bizarre Celtic praise as he claims to spot tactic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/hibs-boss-johnson-in-bizarre-celtic-praise-as-he-singles-out-champions-secret-weapon/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/hibs-boss-johnson-in-bizarre-celtic-praise-as-he-singles-out-champions-secret-weapon/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hibernian boss Lee Johnson has suggested that Celtic have a secret weapon which gives them an advantage over other Premiership sides – the ball boys. Johnson has endured an acrimonious start as Hibs boss after his side’s Premier Sports Cup exit, and despite beating St Johnstone in Perth last weekend, faces a daunting task against ...
The post Top-flight boss in bizarre Celtic praise as he claims to spot tactic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hibs boss Johnson in bizarre Celtic praise as he singles out champions’ secret weapon - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEDVpni20s2YgKWhngkNf-2IqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMLbFpgY</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/hibs-boss-johnson-in-bizarre-celtic-praise-as-he-singles-out-champions-secret-weapon/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hibs boss Johnson in bizarre Celtic praise as he singles out champions’ secret weapon  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Allan labels Celtic star 'the best player in Scotland' as Rangers legend Kris Boyd bites back - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiECSDL54NkHlrPZCaUIWEPXoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPLfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/scott-allan-labels-celtic-star-24692931"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T10:36:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Allan labels Celtic star 'the best player in Scotland' as Rangers legend Kris Boyd bites back  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tifo or Tifno…?]]></title>
        <id>http://celticunderground.net/6409-2/</id>
        <link href="http://celticunderground.net/6409-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T10:24:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tifo or Tifno…? Sometimes the title doesn’t really give an insight into the real content of the podcast but I’ve got to write something and I quite liked this so, there you go. Anyway, this week the middle aged podcast by middle aged fans for EVERYONE returns (have we mentioned we are the world’s longest […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Star Fails to Make First Two Competitive Celtic Squads]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-star-fails-to-make-first-two-competitive-celtic-squads/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-star-fails-to-make-first-two-competitive-celtic-squads/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T10:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s no doubt about it, Christopher Jullien’s Celtic career looks to be over. Ange Postecoglou has named two competitive squads this season, the Frenchman hasn’t featured in either of them. Even when Stephen Welsh was out with an illness, the Celtic manager opted to put Carl Starfelt on the bench despite not having any sort […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing left stunned by away support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/new-celtic-hero-moritz-jenz-left-buzzing-with-away-support/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/new-celtic-hero-moritz-jenz-left-buzzing-with-away-support/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T10:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Moritz Jenz spoke of his joy after a dream debut saw him score a dramatic late winner for the Hoops against Ross County in Dingwall yesterday. The champions took the lead shortly after half-time after Kyogo Furuhashi swept home Jota’s pinpoint pass, but were pegged back by Ross County’s equaliser on the hour ...
The post New Celtic signing left stunned by away support appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So just who were the Class of ‘55? Matt McVittie’s Celtic Story]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/so-just-who-were-the-class-of-55-matt-mcvitties-celtic-story/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/so-just-who-were-the-class-of-55-matt-mcvitties-celtic-story/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T09:56:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last Wednesday’s article in The Celtic Star featuring photos provided by Peter Goldie, Celtic’s oldest-living player, provoked a lot of interest and discussion.One photo in particular generated quite a few queries. It was a photoshoot taken at the annual pre-season trial match played at Celtic Park on Tuesday, 9 August 1955. Some of the players, Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pre-season rival claims Celtic interest after completing Serie A move]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/defender-claims-celtic-interest-after-completing-serie-a-move/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/defender-claims-celtic-interest-after-completing-serie-a-move/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T09:48:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Cremonese defender Emanuel Aiwu has claimed that Celtic were interested in signing him before his transfer to Serie A. The 21 year old Austrian this week completed a move from Rapid Vienna to the newly promoted Italian side for £3.5million upon his announcement that the Hoops were amongst several clubs vying for his signature. ...
The post Pre-season rival claims Celtic interest after completing Serie A move appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BROONY THANKS TO EX-IBROX STAR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/broony-thanks-to-ex-ibrox-star/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/broony-thanks-to-ex-ibrox-star/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T09:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Scott Brown had an ex-Ibrox striker to thank for his first win as manager of Fleetwood Town. The former Hoops skipper, who took over the English third-tier side in the summer, saw his team level at 1-1 with Plymouth Argyle and only two minutes to play in his second League One outing. Joe [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['It's genius!': Rival boss praises Celtic's clever ball-boys strategy]]></title>
        <id>6e047421b9555b0e4abb4f927548d5bc</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20606355.its-genius--rival-boss-praises-celtics-clever-ball-boys-strategy/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T09:11:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Easter Road manager reckons the Hoops lead the league in an underrated way]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pleasing Celtic Trend Continues]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/pleasing-celtic-trend-continues/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/pleasing-celtic-trend-continues/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Signs that a full pre-season with Ange Postecoglou is starting to show through the Celtic team, with small parts of Celtic’s game becoming better. Something that has been worked on on the training pitch is attacking set pieces, particularly corners. Last week, on the season’s opening day, Stephen Welsh scored from a corner just minutes […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defender in post Celtic exuberance as he sparks wild scenes with last gasp goal - Glasgow Live]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEAaA8GrJ1dfMcN_r3IrVIMoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow96D9CjDOy_QCMKzp0wU</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowlive.co.uk/sport/defender-post-celtic-exuberance-sparks-24692358"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T08:52:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Defender in post Celtic exuberance as he sparks wild scenes with last gasp goal  Glasgow Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ryan Christie opens up on Celtic exit, twitter trolls and coping in 'tough' Premier League]]></title>
        <id>f1732b45f0812dd74175d50a9ed6762e</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20606339.ryan-christie-opens-celtic-exit-twitter-trolls-coping-tough-premier-league/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T08:49:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former Hoops midfielder made his English top-flight bow at the weekend]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE ON ABADA: ‘I THOUGHT HE COULD MAKE AN IMPACT’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ange-on-abada-i-thought-he-could-make-an-impact/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ange-on-abada-i-thought-he-could-make-an-impact/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T08:48:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIEL ABADA has missed out on Ange Postecoglou’s starting line-ups for the two Premiership games against Aberdeen and Ross County. The Celtic boss has given the nod to Daizen Maeda on both occasions before introducing the Israeli touchline ace. Abada had to wait until the 66th minute before he replaced the Japanese speedster in the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Postecoglou Not Concerned About Liel Abada Situation]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/postecoglou-not-concerned-about-liel-abada-situation/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/postecoglou-not-concerned-about-liel-abada-situation/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Liel Abada arrived at Celtic, Nir Bitton took the then-teenager under his wing and helped him settle in in his new surroundings. However, news of Bitton’s departure had seemed to affect Abada, tearing up in a recent interview where he discussed how much he missed his ‘big brother’ but revealed the pair are in […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE ON JENZ: ‘DID HIMSELF PROUD’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ange-on-jenz-did-himself-proud/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ange-on-jenz-did-himself-proud/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T08:29:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MORITZ JENZ rose to the challenge in more ways than one during his Celtic debut in the 3-1 win over Ross County in Dingwall. The German defender, who joined the champions on a season-long loan from French top-flight outfit Lorient last month, was pitched in for a surprising baptism after Stephen Welsh had taken ill [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE ON JOTA: ‘HE WANTS TO BE THE BEST HE CAN BE’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ange-on-jota-he-wants-to-be-the-best-he-can-be/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ange-on-jota-he-wants-to-be-the-best-he-can-be/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T08:01:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FILIPE JOTA played a major role in Celtic’s 3-1 win over Ross County with three assists in a no-holds-barred confrontation in Dingwall. The flamboyant Portuguese ace set up Kyogo Furuhashi, Moritz Jenz and Liel Abada for the crucial strikes for three more points from a difficult venue in tricky conditions. Jota also made certain of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda Injury Update]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/daizen-maeda-injury-update/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/daizen-maeda-injury-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU was forced to take Daizen Maeda off at half-time after the winger picked up a self-inflicted knock during the first half. The manager has confirmed it’s nothing serious, and there is no cause for concern, meaning at the moment, he’s not ruled out of Celtic’s trip to Killie next weekend. Speaking to The […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Hughes Tribute – Celtic did what Muhammad Ali had done and “shook up the world”]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/john-hughes-tribute-celtic-did-what-muhammad-ali-had-done-and-shook-up-the-world/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/john-hughes-tribute-celtic-did-what-muhammad-ali-had-done-and-shook-up-the-world/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T07:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To the entire Hughes family, after much thought and a considerable amount of procrastination, I decided I would write a tribute to a Celtic great but more importantly, a husband, father and grandfather. To hear of the passing of John ‘Yogi’ Hughes was poignant as it is sad for me; for I had lost my Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Hughes Tribute – Celtic did what Muhammad Ali had done and “shook up the world” - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEMOinOOC_-BjgSif2l7soFoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/john-hughes-tribute-celtic-did-what-muhammad-ali-had-done-and-shook-up-the-world/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T07:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Hughes Tribute – Celtic did what Muhammad Ali had done and “shook up the world”  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Brown brings Celtic mentality to Fleetwood as he gains first boss win with last gasp goal - Glasgow Live]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEGlSVx_2NYhhu7Oowtf_JKYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow96D9CjDOy_QCMKzp0wU</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowlive.co.uk/sport/scott-brown-brings-celtic-mentality-24692078"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T07:56:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Brown brings Celtic mentality to Fleetwood as he gains first boss win with last gasp goal  Glasgow Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One in One Out; Celtic Women’s Latest Transfer Business]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/one-in-one-out-celtic-womens-latest-transfer-business/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/one-in-one-out-celtic-womens-latest-transfer-business/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Women have been busy in the transfer market this window, but concerningly there have been more outgoings than incomings. The summer window was expected to be a tough one for Celtic, but the arrivals were expected to come thick and fast. However, that’s not been the case. The club announced that top-scorer Charlie Wellings […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘DREAM COME TRUE’: JOY BHOY JENZ AND THE CELTIC CUDDLE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/dream-come-true-joy-bhoy-jenz-and-the-celtic-cuddle/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/dream-come-true-joy-bhoy-jenz-and-the-celtic-cuddle/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T07:26:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MORITZ JENZ revealed it was a dream come true to score on his Celtic debut – and then go and take a running jump! The on-loan German centre-back headed in the second goal to propel the champions to a 3-1 victory over Ross County in Dingwall yesterday. There were only six minutes left on the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Desperate’ Greg Taylor verdict issued after what pundit has seen at Celtic - Football Insider]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEBlpDGHTdnVp73zRK-yVD7UqMwgEKioIACIQnJ4k3aT29tENAyPF0QESjSoUCAoiEJyeJN2k9vbRDQMjxdEBEo0w4IzKBg</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballinsider247.com/desperate-greg-taylor-verdict-issued-after-what-pundit-has-seen-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T07:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘Desperate’ Greg Taylor verdict issued after what pundit has seen at Celtic  Football Insider]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Celtic Fans Catch Brilliant Jota Moment]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/video-celtic-fans-catch-brilliant-jota-moment/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/video-celtic-fans-catch-brilliant-jota-moment/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC made it two wins out of two in the SPFL after a 3-1 victory against Ross County in Dingwall. Goals from Kyogo, Jenz and Abada delivered the three points on Saturday afternoon after a slight scare when County levelled the game against the run of play. It was testament to the team’s resolve on […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jota’s the Special One – Ange Postecoglou hails Celtic’s hard working Superstar from Portugal]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/jotas-the-special-one-ange-postecoglou-hails-celtics-hard-working-superstar-from-portugal/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/jotas-the-special-one-ange-postecoglou-hails-celtics-hard-working-superstar-from-portugal/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T06:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou hailed our Superstar from Portugal after Jota’s second Man of the Match performance of the season up in Dingwall which featured a hat-trick of assists for the Celtic winger.“Jota is earning the assists in the right way, he’s working hard,” Ange told the mainstream media after the match, as reported by Scottish Sun. “He Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE PRAISES CELTIC’S ‘SPIRIT’ AND ‘BELIEF’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ange-praises-celtics-spirit-and-belief/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ange-praises-celtics-spirit-and-belief/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T06:45:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU hailed the Celtic spirit in a gritty 3-1 victory over rugged Ross County in Dingwall yesterday. The champions were forced dig deep into their resources to come back from the shock of losing an equalising goal when it looked as though they were going to make unhindered progress in their quest for a [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic reaction: Truly toxic chants sour afternoon as first-timer displays finery and talisman earns boost]]></title>
        <id>3796417</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-reaction-truly-toxic-chants-sour-afternoon-as-first-timer-displays-finery-and-talisman-earns-boost-3796417"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There was no escaping the vile and repellent element of the afternoon as Celtic won 3-1 away at Ross County.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treatment of fans: Time has come to crank up the pressure, increase the noise - enough is enough with tickets]]></title>
        <id>3796059</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/sport-opinion/treatment-of-fans-time-has-come-to-crank-up-the-pressure-increase-the-noise-enough-is-enough-with-tickets-3796059"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here we are, a week into the new league season. Clubs have been welcoming back sell-out crowds, season ticket holders and big away followings with wide, open arms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not an add on, flourish without SPFL, what Nicola Sturgeon can do, we want to be there - Henry McLeish on women's football in Scotland]]></title>
        <id>3796051</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/not-an-add-on-flourish-without-spfl-what-nicola-sturgeon-can-do-we-want-to-be-there-henry-mcleish-on-womens-football-in-scotland-3796051"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was as happy as anyone when England’s women footballers lifted the Euro 2022 crown last Sunday. It was a tremendous performance, a well-earned success and something to genuinely celebrate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henry McLeish</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic On This Day – 7th August – David Potter’s Celtic Diary]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-on-this-day-7th-august-david-potters-celtic-diary/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-on-this-day-7th-august-david-potters-celtic-diary/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Day 7 of Celtic Historian David Potter’s new diary  on The Celtic Star  which will run throughout the new season and will highlight key Celtic related events relevant to each day, today covering 7 August…SATURDAY 7 AUGUST 1965Celtic thrash Sunderland 5-0 at Roker Park in a pre-season friendly. This is a clear indication of what Jock Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: BIG YOGI AND LISBON: THE TRUTH (Part One)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-big-yogi-and-lisbon-the-truth-part-one/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-big-yogi-and-lisbon-the-truth-part-one/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T05:55:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CONJECTURE still surrounds Celtic great John Hughes and the reason he did not feature in Jock Stein’s line-up for the European Cup Final against Inter Milan in Lisbon on May 25 1967. Teams were only allowed a back-up keeper as a substitute back then and the man known as ‘Big Yogi’ to his legion of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘ETERNALLY GRATEFUL,’ HUGHES FAMILY THANK CELTIC FANS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/eternally-grateful-hughes-family-thank-celtic-fans/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/eternally-grateful-hughes-family-thank-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-07T05:12:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE family of John ‘Yogi’ Hughes, who passed away on Monday at the age of 79, have expressed their eternal gratitude to the Celtic support. A huge banner was unfurled before the 3-1 Premiership win over Ross County in Dingwall yesterday which proclaimed: ‘YOGI – A CELTIC MAN, REST IN PEACE’. The thoughtful gesture was appreciated and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video – It’s Unique Angle Time starring Kyogo, Mercedes Jenz and Abada]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/video-its-unique-angle-time-starring-kyogo-mercedes-jenz-and-abada/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-its-unique-angle-time-starring-kyogo-mercedes-jenz-and-abada/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-06T22:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Watch the Unique Angle from Celtic TV from today’s match at Dingwall. The Celtic goals in a very satisfying 3-1 win were all classy and Jota claims an assist for them all. The celebrations after big Mercedes Jenz put Celtic 2-1 up with time running out were almost Ralstonesque and it was all a bit Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Former Celtic man scores ridiculous MLS stoppage-time winner]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/video-former-celtic-man-scores-ridiculous-mls-stoppage-time-winner/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/video-former-celtic-man-scores-ridiculous-mls-stoppage-time-winner/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-06T21:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remember Andrew Gutman? He was the Celtic signing from America who never managed to make a single appearance for the club due to work visa issues. The defender eventually made a permanent switch to Atlanta United after a couple of loan moves to teams in the USA, and it’s there he has popped up on ...
The post Video: Former Celtic man scores ridiculous MLS stoppage-time winner appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Former Celtic man scores ridiculous MLS stoppage-time winner - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEBePWn3IiBh0pF2e21Ap0WoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMLbFpgY</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/video-former-celtic-man-scores-ridiculous-mls-stoppage-time-winner/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-06T21:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Former Celtic man scores ridiculous MLS stoppage-time winner  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moritz Jenz opens up on his Celtic dream and explains crowd celebrations - 'there's no stopping']]></title>
        <id>3796305</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/moritz-jenz-opens-up-on-his-celtic-dream-and-explains-crowd-celebrations-theres-no-stopping-3796305"/>
        <updated>2022-08-06T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As debuts go, Moritz Jenz’s was not a bad one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Dream come true' for Moritz Jenz as debut goal sparks Celtic win]]></title>
        <id>cbeba366c4d3fb2cb7b1d9e308e69885</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20606033.dream-come-true-moritz-jenz-debut-goal-sparks-celtic-win/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-08-06T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MORITZ JENZ says it was a dream come true to score on his Celtic debut as he lapped up his side’s celebrations with their huge travelling support in Dingwall.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Highlights from Dingwall, table topping Celtic unbeaten in 34 league games]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/video-highlights-from-dingwall-table-topping-celtic-unbeaten-in-34-league-games/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-highlights-from-dingwall-table-topping-celtic-unbeaten-in-34-league-games/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-06T20:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enjoy the highlights from Celtic’s 3-1 win over Ross County in Dingwall this afternoon, or if you were watching on Celtic TV, the 3-0 win… Celtic tv going full North Korea by cutting off the stream so we can’t see that we have conceded. — The Resistance Review (@T_Rreview) August 6, 2022 Goals from Kyogo, Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["It’s going for 95 minutes"; Relentless Celtic leave impression on opponent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/match/its-going-for-95-minutes-relentless-celtic-leave-impression-on-ross-county/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/its-going-for-95-minutes-relentless-celtic-leave-impression-on-ross-county/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-06T20:14:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ross County boss Malky Mackay has admitted it’s been a difficult week for his team preparing for the intense test against Celtic this weekend. The Staggies gave a good account of themselves in today’s Scottish Premiership clash in Dingwall but succumbed to two late goals after periods of dominance for the Bhoys in the 3-1 ...
The post "It’s going for 95 minutes"; Relentless Celtic leave impression on opponent appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Outstanding Joe Hart Flash Point at Dingwall]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/video-outstanding-joe-hart-flash-point-at-dingwall/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/video-outstanding-joe-hart-flash-point-at-dingwall/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-06T20:03:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re a regular reader of the site, you’ll know by now we’re all Joe Hart fan bhoys! The Celtic goalkeeper has been superb since signing for the club for around £1m. The Englishman helped the Hoops to a title win last season with his heroics in goals and his leadership in the dressing room. […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Broadcast blackout – A state of affairs that cannot be allowed to continue]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/broadcast-blackout-a-state-of-affairs-that-cannot-be-allowed-to-continue/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/broadcast-blackout-a-state-of-affairs-that-cannot-be-allowed-to-continue/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-06T20:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like so many others of the Celtic supporting community, I was actually prevented from watching my team playing this afternoon by a combination of some woolly thinking from Ross County who seem quite happy to have empty seats when there are thousands of people wanting it buy one (other than football, is there any other Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Absolute adrenaline"; Joe Hart, Moritz Jenz and Kyogo take to Instagram after Celtic win]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/match/absolute-adrenaline-joe-hart-moritz-jenz-and-kyogo-take-to-instagram-after-celtic-win/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/absolute-adrenaline-joe-hart-moritz-jenz-and-kyogo-take-to-instagram-after-celtic-win/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-06T19:40:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic players have taken to Instagram this evening to share their delight with a 3-1 victory over Ross County in Dingwall. The Bhoys have made it six points from six at the start of the Scottish Premiership campaign, winning in intense and difficult circumstances up in the Highlands. Goals from Kyogo Furuhashi, Moritz Jenz and ...
The post "Absolute adrenaline"; Joe Hart, Moritz Jenz and Kyogo take to Instagram after Celtic win appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Class Joe Hart Celtic moment in Dingwall shouldn&#039;t go overlooked]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/match/class-joe-hart-celtic-moment-in-dingwall-shouldnt-go-overlooked/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/class-joe-hart-celtic-moment-in-dingwall-shouldnt-go-overlooked/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-06T19:15:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although the headlines will belong to Jota, Moritz Jenz and Liel Abada after their brilliant attacking contributions in the Celtic win over Ross County, Joe Hart’s big moment shouldn’t go overlooked. The Bhoys goalkeeper made a brilliant low save to his left from a powerful Owura Edwards free-kick with the game deadlocked at 1-1, just ...
The post Class Joe Hart Celtic moment in Dingwall shouldn&#039;t go overlooked appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Class Joe Hart Celtic moment in Dingwall shouldn’t go overlooked - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEBl2jROrwmmnmViXXq5V88cqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMI7NpgY</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/class-joe-hart-celtic-moment-in-dingwall-shouldnt-go-overlooked/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-06T19:15:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Class Joe Hart Celtic moment in Dingwall shouldn’t go overlooked  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The “Celtic In Hopes To Join English Setup One Day” Nonsense Rears Its Head Again.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/the-celtic-in-hopes-to-join-english-setup-one-day-nonsense-rears-its-head-again/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/08/articles-and-features/the-celtic-in-hopes-to-join-english-setup-one-day-nonsense-rears-its-head-again/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-06T19:07:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, a story from UEFA which will spark excitement in some quarters over the “prospect” of Celtic and our city rivals joining the English league setup. A case has been filed against UEFA by a club which currently plays in Luxembourg. The idea behind the case is to force open the door for clubs in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Big Mercedes Jenz” – “Winning up the Highlands when it matters isn’t for all Teams”]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/big-mercedes-jenz-winning-up-the-highlands-when-it-matters-isnt-for-all-teams/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/big-mercedes-jenz-winning-up-the-highlands-when-it-matters-isnt-for-all-teams/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-06T18:55:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well that was certainly a perfect starting debut for Celtic’s new Bhoy Moritz Jenz, who stepped in to cover for Stephen Welsh, who dropped out with an illness, up at Dingwall this afternoon.The German centre-back got the nod ahead of Carl Starfelt, who Ange told us at yesterday’s media conference, wasn’t ready to play as Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delight for Celtic icon Scott Brown as former Rangers star helps him to first win as a manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/delight-for-celtic-icon-scott-brown-as-joe-garner-helps-him-to-first-managerial-win/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/delight-for-celtic-icon-scott-brown-as-joe-garner-helps-him-to-first-managerial-win/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-06T18:45:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic captain Scott Brown picked up his first competitive victory as a manager this afternoon after a Fleetwood Town winner from former Rangers player Joe Garner. Brown enjoyed dominance over Garner in the 2016/17 season as part of the Celtic Invincibles team but is now in charge of the former Ibrox man. Fleetwood Town ...
The post Delight for Celtic icon Scott Brown as former Rangers star helps him to first win as a manager appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I wouldn’t say that’ – Ange Gets Fed Up of Lazy BBC Questions]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/i-wouldnt-say-that-ange-gets-fed-up-of-lazy-bbc-questions/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/i-wouldnt-say-that-ange-gets-fed-up-of-lazy-bbc-questions/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-06T18:29:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou expressed his frustrations with the BBC’s angle of questioning after his side left Dingwall 3-1 winners. It was a great display from the Hoops, who were dominant throughout the match. Yet, somehow, the BBC managed to ask the Celtic boss some negative questions. As usual, Postecoglou didn’t have any of it and was […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>