<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2024-01-03T18:13:19.156Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[’Things haven’t’: Chris Sutton names Celtic star who struggled despite 3-0 win over St Mirren]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185175</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/chris-suttons-brutally-honest-verdict-on-luis-palma-despite-celtics-3-0-win-at-st-mirren/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton thinks Luis Palma struggled to put in a strong showing despite Celtic’s 3-0 win over St Mirren on Tuesday. The 23-year-old started the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[’This is unreal’: James McFadden blown away by Celtic duo against St Mirren]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185159</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/james-mcfadden-delivers-verdict-on-celtic-duo-matt-oriley-and-paulo-bernardo-after-st-mirren-win/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What a way to start 2024 for Celtic. A comprehensive 3-0 win at St Mirren. Paulo Bernardo is having the time of his life because...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['They played long': Rod Stewart shuts down Simon Jordan’s claim about Celtic's win over Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185121</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/rod-stewart-shuts-down-simon-jordans-claim-about-celtics-recent-win-over-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic-mad Rod Stewart was sure to defend the quality of the Glasgow derby over the weekend and the manner of the Bhoys’ victory. Brendan Rodgers’...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘RUTHLESS,’ CENTURY BHOY PINPOINTS REASON FOR REVIVAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116175</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ruthless-century-bhoy-pinpoints-reason-for-revival/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T12:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY celebrated becoming a Century Bhoy by going into double figures with a neat goal in the 3-0 win over St Mirren in Paisley. The on-fire midfielder claimed a meagre four last season, but he has wasted no time in reaching 10 with the second part of the campaign still to come. The impressive O’Riley [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WATCH AGAIN: TEN OUT OF TEN, CELTIC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116173</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/watch-again-ten-out-of-ten-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T12:21:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC were under awesome pressure from all angles after two consecutive stumbles in the 2-1 loss to Kilmarnock and the 2-0 defeat from Hearts at Parkhead a week later. Back-to-back failures hadn’t been anticipated as Brendan Rodgers’ side seemingly headed uninterrupted towards their twelfth title in 13 years while leaving their rivals in their slipstream. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recruit, develop, reputation: the virtuous cycle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116166</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/recruit-develop-reputation-the-virtuous-cycle/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T12:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The thing about signing footballers who can transform you, those with real talent which has yet to be realised by the wider market, is that they are unbelievably difficult to find.  Getting this right is not the only requirement in propelling a club forward, but it is a necessary one. You also need to transform [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THREE CHEERS FOR ‘UNIQUE’ CELT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116160</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/three-cheers-for-unique-celt/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T11:34:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAIZEN MAEDA surely fired himself into the Celtic history books in the 3-0 triumph over St Mirren in Paisley last night. The Japanese striker thumped the champions into the lead in only 54 SECONDS – and became the first Hoops player to score the club’s first goal in three successive years. Maeda kicked off his special [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRIBUTE TO SHANE & THE MUSIC OF THE POGUES]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58588</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/tribute-to-shane-the-music-of-the-pogues/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T10:53:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Sheridan (pictured with Shane backstage in the Barrowlands, along with Alan from Shebeen) travels from Glasgow to join us on Saturday 06 Jan for our tribute night to the late, great Shane MacGowan and the music of the Pogues. Paul has been performing as a musician for over 20 years. Best known as […]
The post TRIBUTE TO SHANE & THE MUSIC OF THE POGUES appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘He looked back to his best’: Chris Sutton impressed by ‘powerful’ Celtic star v St Mirren]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185106</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/chris-sutton-delivers-verdict-on-daizen-maedas-performance-after-celtic-beat-st-mirren/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T10:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It didn’t take Celtic long to break the deadlock against St Mirren, with Daizen Maeda helping himself to a first-minute goal. The 26-year-old’s clever run...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Van Persie’: Gustaf Lagerbielke wowed by Celtic teammate after win over St Mirren]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185086</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/gustaf-lagerbielke-compares-celtic-teammate-to-robin-van-persie-after-3-0-win-over-st-mirren/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T09:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After beating Rangers over the weekend, the Celtic players did even better to respond with a comprehensive 3-0 win over St Mirren.  A brilliant start...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘QUITE EMOTIONAL,’ BOSS EXPLAINS HATATE HUG]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116157</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/quite-emotional-boss-explains-hatate-hug/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T08:33:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS and comeback Bhoy Reo Hatate were locked in an emotional embrace in the aftermath of Celtic’s 3-0 win over St Mirren in Paisley last night. The influential Japanese midfielder came on the 71st minute for Paulo Bernardo as the champions eased to three points with strikes from Daizen Maeda, Matt O’Riley and Greg [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘DEMANDS ARE SO MUCH,’ COLD COMFORT FOR RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116154</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/demands-are-so-much-cold-comfort-for-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T07:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S spirited bounce back from back-to-back defeats has seen the team win four games on the trot, score 10 goals and concede only one to restore their eight-point advantage at the Premiership pinnacle. It’s nothing to sneeze at as Brendan Rodgers leads his side into a welcome winter shutdown after admitting he has been fighting [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HIGH FIVES: THE DAY BIG YOGI DESTROYED GERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=61599</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/high-fives-the-day-big-yogi-destroyed-gers/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T06:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend John ‘Yogi’ Hughes passed away in August 2022 at the age of 79. The eighth-highest scoring player in the club’s history with 189 strikes left everyone with a treasure trove of wonderful memories. One of his most unforgettable performances came in an Old Firm encounter on January 3 1966 when Yogi was simply [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REVEALED: CELTIC AND JOHN McGINN: THE TRUTH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=100907</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/revealed-celtic-and-john-mcginn-the-truth/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T06:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WAYWARD tales of how Celtic failed to sign John McGinn from Hibs in August 2018 still abound in football circles. It seemed certain the Scotland international powerhouse, a boyhood Hoops fan, was heading for Parkhead until he was whisked across the border to Aston Villa. The dramatic change of direction in the player’s future stunned [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…OLI BURKE?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=108552</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-oli-burke/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T05:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OLI BURKE came to Celtic with a big reputation when he signed a short-term loan deal from West Brom in January 2019. The 26-year-old Scotland international striker, who had been involved in £28million worth of transfer deals involving Nottingham Forest, RB Leipzig and the Hawthorns outfit, flopped in the east end of Glasgow. Burke was [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ST MIRREN 0 CELTIC 3: HOOPY NEW YEAR AS LIGHTNING MAEDA LEADS THE WAY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116105</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/st-mirren-0-celtic-3-hoopy-new-year-as-lightning-maeda-leads-the-way/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T19:16:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ST MIRREN 0 CELTIC 3 CELTIC were as relentless as the rain in Paisley as they swept St Mirren aside in ruthless fashion to restore their eight-point advantage at the Premiership pinnacle before the winter break. It was breathtaking stuff from non-stop Hoops as they came out the traps at a ferocious pace in a [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[St Mirren v Celtic, GG Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116099</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/st-mirren-v-celtic-gg-live-updates/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T16:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 17:00.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: NAWROCKI IN, LAGERBIELKE ON STAND-BY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116084</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-nawrocki-in-lagerbielke-on-stand-by/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T15:49:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MAIK NAWROCKI will start his first game for Celtic since August when he faces St Mirren in Paisley tonight. The Polish centre-back, a £4.3million recruit from Legia Warsaw in the summer, came on for the injured Stephen Welsh in the Hoops’ 2-1 derby win at Parkhead at the weekend. Gustaf Lagerbielke, who cost £3million from [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[’The man of the season’: Peter Grant hails Celtic 25-year-old who dominated Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185072</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/liam-scales-receives-the-most-glowing-of-verdicts-as-celtic-put-rangers-to-the-sword/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What a season Liam Scales is having for Celtic!  Not even the player himself envisaged such a situation where he is now, not only one...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nawrocki breaking the lines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116098</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/nawrocki-breaking-the-lines/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T12:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The St Mirren result at Aberdeen dropped as you and I glowed in reflective glory from the result at the weekend.  0-3 away from home is an excellent return at any venue for any side, Saturday’s result is a signal that this evening’s opponents are to be taken seriously. Even against a side below them [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I'm not': Celtic boss delivers Liel Abada & Reo Hatate message ahead of St Mirren clash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185056</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-delivers-liel-abada-and-reo-hatate-update-ahead-of-celtics-trip-to-st-mirren/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has confirmed that Liel Abada is further ahead of Reo Hatate in earning minutes for Celtic. The duo have been out for long...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NAT OUT, NIC IN?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116088</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/nat-out-nic-in/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T10:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NAT PHILLIPS has returned to Liverpool after failing to convince during his short-term loan at Celtic, a move revealed by CQN over a fortnight ago. The centre-back answered an SOS from the champions in the summer when there were injury concerns over Cameron Carter-Vickers, Stephen Welsh and £7.3million recruits Maik Nawrocki and Gustaf Lagerbielke. Phillips, 26, made [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weeks after it looked like his Celtic career was over, £4.3m star must now start at St Mirren]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185040</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-message-is-clear-with-maik-nawrocki-after-his-performance-for-celtic-against-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T09:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You have to tip your hat to, Maik Nawrocki. It wasn’t so long ago that the summer signing’s future at Celtic was looking like it...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ST MIRREN v CELTIC: 5-MINUTE QUIZ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116082</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/st-mirren-v-celtic-5-minute-quiz-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T08:51:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC kick off 2024 against St Mirren in Paisley tonight with a 5pm kick-off. The previous meeting between the clubs at Parkhead on November 1 proved to be laced with anxiety as the visitors took an early lead. It was still poised on a tirghtrope at 1-1 with seven minutes of the regulation 90 to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I am surprised’: Celtic legend Chris Sutton blasts Rangers' latest actions after derby day fallout]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185017</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-reacts-to-rangers-actions-amid-criticism-at-sfa-after-celtics-glasgow-derby-day-win/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton delivered a dose of reality to Rangers after they were beaten 2-1 by Brendan Rodgers’ Celtic in the Glasgow derby on Saturday. In...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘VERY HUNGRY,’ RODGERS SPELLS IT OUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116063</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/very-hungry-rodgers-spells-it-out/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T07:58:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is well aware of the threat posed by tonight’s opponents St Mirren. The champions have one hurdle to clear before their well-earned break with their next encounter due on Sunday January 21 in the intriguing Scottish Cup meeting with Highland outfit Buckie Thistle at Parkhead. Stephen Robinson’s side lie in wait in Paisley [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GONE IN 12 MONTHS: FIVE STARS – AND A MANAGER]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115793</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/gone-in-12-months-five-stars-and-a-manager/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T06:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FIVE of the Celtic squad who earned a 2-2 draw at Ibrox EXACTLY a year ago today have left Celtic over the 12-month period. Ange Postecoglou utilised 16 players in the first game of 2023 with Canadian World Cup star Alistair Johnston, a £3.5million recruit from MLS outfit CF Montreal in the January window, making his debut [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEW YEAR PICTURE QUIZ: ALL IS REVEALED]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115269</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/new-year-picture-quiz-all-is-revealed/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T06:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HOW did you get on with CQN‘s Bumper New Year Picture Quiz? We asked you if you could identify the former Celtic players in our six images to test your knowledge. Today we provide the identities of the mystery men. PIC A It’s a young Neil Lennon, of course, sporting a blond look shortly after [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…JOHN GUIDETTI?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=108549</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-john-guidetti/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T05:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOHN GUIDETTI became an instant hit with the Celtic fans after arriving on a season-long loan from Manchester City in September 2014. Ronny Deila urgently required firepower and the Swedish striker looked to be the answer when he scored his first goal in his second appearance, a 3-0 League Cup win over Hearts in Glasgow. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO OVERLOOKED: GOOD NEWS FOR RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116053</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kyogo-overlooked-good-news-for-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T12:35:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC were handed some surprise good news with the shock omission of Kyogo Furuhashi from Japan’s squad for the Asian Cup which starts on January 14. Daizen Maeda and Reo Hatate are included, despite the fact the midfielder has been struggling to overcome a muscular problem after limping off early in the 2-2 Champions League draw [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neil McCann reckons Celtic hero just schooled hyped Rangers man]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185012</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/neil-mccann-reckons-celtic-hero-just-schooled-hyped-rangers-man/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T11:51:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are basking in the aftermath of another derby victory over Rangers and while some are outwardly raging at phantom penalties, the reality is that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DERBY FALL-OUT: 3 QUESTIONS FOR VAR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116024</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/derby-fall-out-3-questions-for-var/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T11:11:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have maintained a dignified silence in the fall-out of the second Glasgow derby of the campaign. The champions, of course, have notched up back-to-back triumphs with Kyogo Furuhashi hitting spectacular winners on both occasions, 1-0 at Ibrox on September 3 and 2-1 at Parkhead at the weekend. There are still some bitter ramifications coming [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Striker boost for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185009</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kyogo-boost-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T10:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Furuhashi will not be travelling around the world mid-season to play for Japan, instead staying in Glasgow to focus on Celtic fixtures. The Japanese...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEW YEAR PICTURE QUIZ: CAN YOU RECOGNISE THESE EX-CELTS?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115259</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/new-year-picture-quiz-can-you-recognise-these-ex-celts/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T07:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT’S time to sharpen your wits as 2024 arrives and have a go on CQN‘s fun New Year Picture Quiz. How much can you remember about these former Celtic players from the recent past? Here are six images of ex-Hoops stars and all you have to do is identify each individual. To help you, we [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£49.3m CELTIC INS AND OUTS: THE STORY SO FAR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115290</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/49-3m-celtic-ins-and-outs-the-story-so-far/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T06:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC were involved in £49.3million worth of transfer activity in the summer. Now the annual January Guessing Game will kick off again as Brendan Rodgers seeks to strengthen his first-team squad. The biggest bit of business done in the summer window was the £25million move for fans’ favourite Filipe Jota to Saudi Arabian outfit Al-Ittihad while Swedish [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JANUARY, FEBRUARY FIXTURES, KICK-OFFS, LIVE TV SCREENINGS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115370</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/january-february-fixtures-kick-offs-live-tv-screenings/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T06:15:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S Premiership game with St Mirren in Paisley tomorow which is scheduled for a 5pm kick-off will be beamed live by Sky Sports. And the holders will also be live on TV when they commence the defence of their Scottish Cup against Buckie Thistle at Parkhead on Sunday January 21. The tie has a 4pm start [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FERGIE AND THE CELTIC OFFER]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=76415</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/fergie-and-the-celtic-offer/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T06:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GREAT Scot Sir Alex Ferguson, the Manchester United legend, celebrated his 82nd birthday yesterday. In an astonishing twist to Fergie’s trophy-laden career, CQN reveals the extraordinary tale from Celtic supremo Dermot Desmond that he offered to DOUBLE the iconic Old Trafford manager’s wages in an effort to lure him to Parkhead. The sensational move came before [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…DANIEL MAJSTOROVIC?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=108731</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-daniel-majstorovic/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T05:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DANIEL MAJSTOROVIC was brought to Celtic by Neil Lennon in August 2010 as a free agent after leaving AEK Athens. It was hoped the solidly-built, shaven-headed central defender would have a presence in the Celtic rearguard. Majstorovic, at 33, was seen as the ideal player to add steel to a back-four that had been too [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘He got nowhere near him’: James McFadden says Celtic star bossed Rangers around]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184993</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/james-mcfadden-hails-callum-mcgregor-for-bossing-rangers-todd-cantwell-during-celtic-win/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T19:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor is Celtic captain for a reason and he proved it during the 2-1 Glasgow derby win over Rangers. From the get-go, Callum McGregor...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['What a player’: Luis Palma hails Celtic 21-year-old after win over Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184977</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/luis-palma-uses-three-words-to-describe-paulo-bernardo-after-his-goal-during-celtics-win-over-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T17:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has taken Paulo Bernardo time to settle in at Celtic, but in recent weeks, he has started to step up and prove his worth....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State of the Club Report, December 23]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115955</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/state-of-the-club-report-december-23/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T13:23:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My friends in Celtic, we finish the year top of the league having just schooled our nearest rivals for the second time in two games.  A dip in form ended just in time to see the club collect nine points from three games, with an important trip to St Mirren to complete before the winter [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘He has had a lot of nonsense’: Neil Lennon defends Celtic duo live on Sky after win over Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184957</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/neil-lennon-slams-what-he-is-hearing-about-brendan-rodgers-kyogo-furuhashi-after-celtic-beat-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic delivered yet another statement of intent by seeing off Rangers in an entertaining 2-1 Glasgow derby win on Saturday. Leading into the game, there...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS 12 RANGERS 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115953</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-12-rangers-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T12:50:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS enjoyed his TWELFTH victory in 15 derby duels as wonder strikes from Paulo Bernardo and Kyogo Furuhashi sent Philippe Clement’s Ibrox outfit to a 2-1 defeat at Parkhead. The 50-year-old Irishman has also had two draws and a solitary defeat in his previous derby encounters over his two stints in charge of the Hoops. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO AND HIS SEVEN FROM HEAVEN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115950</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kyogo-and-his-seven-from-heaven/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T12:26:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO FURUHASHI was in seventh heaven at Parkhead as the curtain came down on the action for 2023. The Japanese international striker completed the calendar year the way he started it – with a memorable goal against Ibrox opposition. His SEVENTH in 12 months. Kyogo, who joined the champions from J-League side Vissel Kobe in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PAULO IN PARADISE: ‘IT WAS REALLY GOOD’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115934</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/paulo-in-paradise-it-was-really-good/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T11:20:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PAULO BERNARDO was in Paradise as he fired in his first goal at Parkhead yesterday. The on-loan Benfica midfielder marked his Glasgow derby debut with a memorable 25th-minute strike to open the scoring in the 2-1 triumph in front of a full house in the east end of Glasgow. Bernardo’s timing was faultless as he drilled [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pat Nevin says it was 'worth' watching Celtic beat Rangers live because of 'genius' player]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184937</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/pat-nevin-says-what-everyone-else-is-thinking-about-kyogo-furuhashi-after-celtic-beat-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Furuhashi. Write him off at your peril!  What a player. What a man. And what a goalscorer he is proving to be for Celtic....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘A BIT OF A FRIGHT,’ ADMITS McGREGOR AFTER ‘MASSIVE WIN’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115930</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/a-bit-of-a-fright-admits-mcgregor-after-massive-win/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T10:51:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CALLUM McGREGOR hailed his team-mates after the 2-1 derby success at Parkhead – but the Celtic skipper also admitted they gave themselves “a bit of a fright”. The influential midfielder deservedly picked up the Man of the Match accolade after a dominant performance that offered the champions a launchpad for the triumph that eased them [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS WELCOMES NEW BHOY AS KEWELL QUITS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115926</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-welcomes-new-bhoy-as-kewell-quits/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T10:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HARRY KEWELL has thanked Celtic for giving him the “opportunity to be part of one of the world’s great football clubs” as he leaves with the champions’ blessing to take up the managerial post at Yokohama F Marinos. And as the Australian legend departed, Brendan Rodgers has welcomed replacement Adam Sadler as the new first-team coach. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I’M VERY, VERY LUCKY TO HAVE HIM HERE,’ RODGERS PRAISES CAPTAIN MARVEL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115923</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/im-very-very-lucky-to-have-him-here-rodgers-praises-captain-marvel/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T09:32:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BEAMING Brendan Rodgers singled out Captain Marvel Callum McGregor for special mention after the champions’ crucial 2-1 victory over Ibrox opposition at a pulsating Parkhead yesterday. Two crackerjack strikes in each half from Paulo Bernardo and Kyogo Furuhashi propelled Celtic to an eight-point advantage at the top of the league as the curtain came down on [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Is that you?': James McFadden fires shots at Kris Boyd for his comments after Celtic beat Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184920</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/james-mcfadden-fires-shots-at-kris-boyd-for-his-comments-after-celtic-beat-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T09:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a beautiful sight to see as Kris Boyd watched Kyogo Furuhashi down Rangers once again during Celtic’s 2-1 win in the Glasgow derby...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WATCH AGAIN CELTIC’S TOP GUNS: BERNARDO’S BULLET AND KYOGO’S CRACKER]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115908</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/watch-again-celtics-top-guns-bernardos-bullet-and-kyogos-cracker/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T08:20:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PAULO BERNARDO and Kyogo Furuhashi were Celtic’s rocket men as they continued their pursuit of their twelfth title in 13 years. The on-loan Benfica midfielder and the prolIfic Japanese hitman were the Hoops striking heroes as they shot down Philippe Clement’s Ibrox outfit in front of a rocking 60,000 capacity Parkhead yesterday as the champions stretched [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Absolute machine': Paulo Bernardo & Gustaf Lagerbielke wowed by Celtic star against Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184903</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/paulo-bernardo-gustaf-lagerbielke-blown-away-by-absolute-machine-celtic-star-against-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T08:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A battered and bloodied Matt O’Riley helped Celtic do what Celtic do best and that’s win Glasgow derbies.  You have to question how he managed...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CCV’S IMPASSIONED BIRTHDAY WISH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115863</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ccvs-impassioned-birthday-wish/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T06:10:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CAMERON CARTER-VICKERS celebrates his 26th birthday today with a fervent wish. The USA World Cup centre-back hopes to return to big-match action as soon as possible after the winter break. Carter-Vickers, who cost £6million from Spurs when he joined in the summer of 2022 following his initial impressive season-long loan, limped out of the 3-0 [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I BELIEVE YOU’RE LOOKING FOR ME?’ SIR ALEX AND THE CELTIC AUTHOR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=74361</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-believe-youre-looking-for-me-sir-alex-and-the-celtic-author/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T06:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SIR ALEX FERGUSON celebrates his 82nd birthday today and CQN would like to add our congratulations to the Manchester United legend. The Scot’s achievements at Old Trafford have been simply phenomenal with THIRTY-EIGHT trophies including two Champion League triumphs and 13 Premier League titles. The Glaswegian has more than earned his place in Football’s Hall of Fame. Ferguson may have [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…CHARLY MUSONDA?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=108625</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-charly-musonda/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T05:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CHARLY MUSONDA was a much-hyped loan signing by Brendan Rodgers from Chelsea on an 18-month deal in January 2018. The move was heralded as a signing coup for the Hoops boss with the Belgian, then an exciting 21-year-old prospect, on the wanted list of a host of interested clubs, headed by Spanish giants Real Madrid. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic subjugate Newco]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115904</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-subjugate-newco/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T18:44:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A fascinating top of the table encounter, with both teams under-strength, ended predictably as the champions had enough in the tank to again put Newco to the sword.  Creating coherent teamwork all over the pitch is an important part of football, and Paulo Bernardo (21) rewarded his manager by opening the scoring for the second [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers delivers hilarious post-match dig at the Rangers hype machine after Celtic win]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184893</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-delivers-hilarious-post-match-dig-at-the-rangers-hype-machine-after-celtic-win/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T16:44:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers is a man who has had to listen to a lot of hype about Rangers in his two spells as Celtic manager. If...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Philippe Clement gets bitter after Celtic show up his Rangers side at Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184888</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/philippe-clement-gets-bitter-after-bhoys-show-up-his-rangers-side-at-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T15:52:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Philippe Clement didn’t take his first defeat as a Rangers manager very well after Celtic beat his side 2-1 in the Scottish Premiership on Saturday....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers says one Celtic player is on 'a different level' after beating Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184883</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-singles-out-top-celtic-performer-on-another-level-vs-rangers-and-reacts-to-big-derby-win/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T15:23:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have won their second derby of the Scottish Premiership season with a 2-1 victory over Rangers at Celtic Park. Paulo Bernardo got the Bhoys...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC 2 RANGERS 1: BIG SHOTS BERNARDO, KYOGO BLAST HOOPS TO GLORY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115869</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-2-rangers-1-big-shots-bernardo-kyogo-blast-hoops-to-glory/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T15:08:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC 2 RANGERS 1 A SPECTACULAR double strike from Paulo Bernardo and Kyogo Furuhashi fired Celtic to a crucial triumph at Parkhead this afternoon. It was a rollicking rocking encounter as the champions eased eight points ahead at the Premiership pinnacle in their quest for their twelfth title in 13 years, but they made life [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clement bubble burst, one star haunts them; 3 things we learned as Celtic beat Rangers again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184878</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/clement-bubble-burst-kyogo-haunts-them-3-things-we-learned-as-celtic-beat-rangers-again/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T14:35:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic once again proved they are the top team in Scotland with a 2-1 victory over Rangers at Celtic Park on Saturday. Paulo Bernardo scored...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic v ‘Rangers’, GG Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115833</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-rangers-gg-live-updates/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T11:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 12:30.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: WELSH IN, HATATE AND ABADA ON STAND-BY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115823</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-welsh-in-hatate-and-abada-on-stand-by/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T11:23:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has given a vote of confidence to Stephen Welsh who takes over from hamstring victim Cameron Carter-Vickers against Rangers at Parkhead today. The former Scotland Under-21 skipper replaced USA World Cup centre-back in the 3-0 win over Dundee at Dens Park on Boxing Day and goes straight into the line-up for the crunch [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic XI confirmed: Hatate and Abada calls, one change, global TV details, instant reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184872</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-vs-rangers-confirmed-one-change-abada-and-hatate-calls-global-tv-details-instant-reaction/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T11:22:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manager Brendan Rodgers has named his Celtic team vs Rangers for today’s massive Scottish Premiership derby at Celtic Park. The full match squad is as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers explains the root of Cameron Carter-Vickers' Celtic issues; return timeline]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184869</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-explains-the-root-of-cameron-carter-vickers-celtic-issues-return-timeline/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T10:45:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers says the knee operation Cameron Carter-Vickers went through during the summer has been the cause of the defender’s challenges at the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star speaks candidly about the dressing room mood ahead of Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184863</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/callum-mcgregor-speaks-candidly-about-the-celtic-dressing-room-mood-ahead-of-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T10:17:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic captain Callum McGregor is no stranger to a derby against Rangers and has approached these matches in a variety of situations. Thankfully for him...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lennoxtown switch up on the way for Celtic as Brendan Rodgers confirms coaching search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184858</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/lennoxtown-switch-up-on-the-way-for-celtic-as-brendan-rodgers-confirms-coaching-search/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T09:25:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has confirmed that Harry Kewell is in talks to leave the club and that he’ll be looking to make a fresh...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers' latest Celtic transfer message isn't very encouraging]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184853</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-latest-celtic-transfer-message-isnt-very-encouraging/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T08:51:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There won’t be any of the early January transfer deals Celtic fans have become accustomed to over the last couple of years going by the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: OPPORTUNITY KNOCKS FOR WIDE BHOYS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115849</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-opportunity-knocks-for-wide-bhoys/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T08:23:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC go into today’s derby skirmish in the firm knowledge they will have to earn the victory. They will not anticipate any breaks from the match officials, on and off the pitch, as they pursue three vital points. The situation has not changed in living memory. It has been ever thus. You and I will [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic summer signing's representatives take action amidst 'unhappy' spell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184850</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/marco-tilios-representatives-take-action-amidst-unhappy-celtic-spell/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T08:22:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marco Tilio is actively seeking a loan exit away from Celtic in the January transfer window, according to a new report in his homeland. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic team news and Predicted XI vs Rangers as returning star "looks really good" in training]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184847</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-news-and-predicted-xi-vs-rangers-as-returning-star-looks-really-good-in-training/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T07:52:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic host Rangers in the Scottish Premiership on Saturday looking to pick up their second derby win of the season under Brendan Rodgers. Celtic picked...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIG NOISES: McGREGOR DERBY AIM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115847</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/big-noises-mcgregor-derby-aim/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T07:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE curtain comes down on the action for 2023 at Parkhead this afternoon when Celtic take on Ibrox opposition in front of a partisan 60,000 sell-out audience. And captain Callum McGregor is eager to make certain the champions sign off in style with a triumph that will push them eight points ahead at the Premiership [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers hits back at Scottish media's Celtic narrative]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184842</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-hits-back-at-scottish-medias-celtic-narrative/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T07:22:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers believes critics of the club are trying to portray a state of constant crisis at the reigning Scottish champions. There have...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers delivers verdict on Philippe Clement's Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184836</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-delivers-verdict-on-philippe-clements-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T06:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers is fully aware that Saturday afternoon’s match at home to Rangers will be a tough test. The Bhoys head into the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN’S SWIPE AT CRISIS TALK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115844</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/brendans-swipe-at-crisis-talk/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T06:39:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS took a swipe at the merchants of doom and gloom who insist Celtic are in perpetual state of crisis. The critics opened fire of the champions after back-to-back defeats against Kilmarnock and Hearts in what admittedly were atrocious performances by a strangely under-par Hoops side. The loss of six Premiership points invited today’s [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COME IN No.6, YOUR TIME IS UP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113134</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/come-in-no-6-your-time-is-up/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T06:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PHILIPPE CLEMENT is only 90 minutes away from becoming the sixth Rangers boss to experience defeat while pitting his wits against Brendan Rodgers. The Belgian, 49, was named as Michael Beale’s successor in mid-October to become the Ibrox club’s FOURTH manager in two years. Clement, who was sacked by AS Monaco in June after only 18 [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS 11 RANGERS 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111794</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-11-rangers-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T06:15:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is looking for his twelfth victory in his 15 games against Ibrox opposition when the teams lock horns at Parkhead this afternoon. The 50-year-old Irishman has also had two draws and a solitary defeat in his previous derby encounters. Rodgers resumed hostilities in this fixture after an absence of four years and nine [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic want to sign £4 million-rated player in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45945</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-4-million-player-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T23:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The defeat at the hands of Lazio was further proof of Celtic’s need to strengthen in the January transfer window. The club might have brought in nine new faces in the summer but a lot of people feel that the team has taken a step back since last season, when they breezed past the competition […]
Celtic want to sign £4 million-rated player in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers sends clear message Celtic board must not ignore]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45941</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/brendan-rodgers-message-celtic-board/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T21:35:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s fate in Europe for this season is sealed after their 2-0 defeat at the hands of Lazio. The result means that the Hoops are guaranteed to finish bottom of their group in the UEFA Champions League. That also means that they will not be dropping down to the Europa League, something that should have […]
Brendan Rodgers sends clear message Celtic board must not ignore - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton publicly criticises Celtic after loss to Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45938</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/chris-sutton-celtic-loss-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T20:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic lost 2-0 away in Rome to Lazio. The Hoops were in the match for a long time before Ciro Immobile came off the bench to score a brace and put the game to bed. The result means that not only are Brendan Rodgers’ side out of the Champions League following the group stages but […]
Chris Sutton publicly criticises Celtic after loss to Lazio - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed £7 million Jeremie Frimpong windfall news]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45933</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-jeremie-frimpong-windfall-news/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremie Frimpong’s rise at Bayer Leverkusen has been fascinating, to say the least. The Dutchman had shown a lot of quality going forward at Celtic as well but not many could have foreseen him becoming one of the most prolific wingbacks in Europe just a few years later. That is exactly what has happened under […]
Celtic handed £7 million Jeremie Frimpong windfall news - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic told 29-goal striker is good enough amid links]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45930</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-told-29-goal-striker-good-enough/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T13:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to add to their options up top this January. Kyogo has done well once again but he is not scoring as frequently as he was last season. On the other hand, Oh Hyeon-gyu has been inconsistent as well and is not at the level required to start for the Hoops right now. There […]
Celtic told 29-goal striker is good enough amid links - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anderlecht consider making offer for Celtic standout in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45927</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/anderlecht-offer-celtic-standout-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T11:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have not had the greatest campaign till now. They were eliminated early from the Scottish League Cup and while they do lead the Premiership, their performances and results have been somewhat inconsistent. Almost half a season on, it feels like the Hoops are still finding their feet under the management of Brendan Rodgers and […]
Anderlecht consider making offer for Celtic standout in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serie A club want to sign Celtic player amid contract worry]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45907</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/serie-club-want-celtic-player-contract/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T22:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic fans hope for more quality players arriving there could be a problem with others heading for the exit door. It seems pretty clear that Brendan Rodgers wants to make the size of the squad more manageable over the next couple of transfer windows and departures are expected. But there is a risk of […]
Serie A club want to sign Celtic player amid contract worry - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur step up bid to sign Celtic-linked player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45918</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/tottenham-hotspur-bid-sign-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur made a fantastic start to the season under the management of Ange Postecoglou. With Harry Kane leaving the club in the summer for Bayern Munich, most expected them to struggle. Instead, they appeared to be putting up an unlikely title challenge and were sitting atop the Premier League table not too long ago. […]
Tottenham Hotspur step up bid to sign Celtic-linked player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boost in race to sign £11 million Real Madrid player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45914</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/celtic-boost-real-madrid-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to sign a goalkeeper in the near future. It is quite clear that Joe Hart is not the long-term solution between the posts. The Englishman’s performances have been criticised lately. Also, he is set to turn 37 years of age before this season comes to an end. So, while he has done a […]
Celtic boost in race to sign £11 million Real Madrid player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio boss Maurizio Sarri makes fantastic Celtic claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45910</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/lazio-boss-maurizio-sarri-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T18:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By now, Celtic fans have accepted that Brendan Rodgers’ side are most probably not going through or even finishing third in their group in the UEFA Champions League. It would be a positive step to get a win in the competition though. It has been quite some time since the Hoops won at this level. […]
Lazio boss Maurizio Sarri makes fantastic Celtic claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic tipped to go for 28-year-old Premiership striker]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45904</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/celtic-tipped-go-premiership-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T12:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans breathed a sigh of relief as the Rangers dropped points at the weekend against Aberdeen. In fact, it took a late penalty for them to even come out with a draw from the game. That means that the Hoops will maintain their strong position at the top of the Scottish Premiership table. That […]
Celtic tipped to go for 28-year-old Premiership striker - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£7.5 million Mathias Kvistgaarden to Celtic transfer update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45900</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/mathias-kvistgaarden-celtic-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T10:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to sign a striker in January. On one hand, we have seen the club struggle for goals in some games this season. When the opposition puts up a resolute defence, the Hoops do not appear to have a lot of answers other than Kyogo, Matt O’Riley or Luis Palma. On the other hand, […]
£7.5 million Mathias Kvistgaarden to Celtic transfer update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur have been eyeing Celtic superstar]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45896</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/tottenham-hotspur-eyeing-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T23:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou made the move to Tottenham Hotspur in the summer and it was only a matter of time before the Australian was linked with a reunion with some Celtic players. The manager enjoyed a lot of success at Parkhead, even though he was at the club for just two seasons, and won five trophies […]
Tottenham Hotspur have been eyeing Celtic superstar - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John McGinn claims he spoke to Celtic players about manager]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45890</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/john-mcginn-spoke-celtic-players/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T21:35:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most Celtic fans will remember how the club missed out on the opportunity to sign John McGinn some years back. The Scot grew up supporting the Hoops but a move to Parkhead failed to materialise even though it had looked close and he ended up moving down south to join Aston Villa. McGinn has risen […]
John McGinn claims he spoke to Celtic players about manager - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic must consider signing striker from Premiership rivals]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45886</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-signing-striker-premiership-rivals/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T20:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there is one position where Celtic need to strengthen during the upcoming January transfer window, it is striker. The Hoops have been pretty inconsistent in front of goal this season so far. Of course, there are games when they can go out and score six times. But then, on days they are having a […]
Celtic must consider signing striker from Premiership rivals - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend takes dig at Rangers player for diving]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45884</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-legend-rangers-player-diving/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T18:35:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Celtic drew 1-1 against Motherwell, the Rangers were handed a major chance to get back into the title race. All they needed to do was win their games in hand and they would be just three points behind the Hoops in the league table. We have seen the Ibrox side not perform at their […]
Celtic legend takes dig at Rangers player for diving - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player criticised after draw against Motherwell]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45881</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-player-criticised-draw-motherwell/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T12:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Titles are not decided this early in the season. That has been proven once again. Not too long ago, Celtic were sitting seven points clear at the top of the Premiership table and most fans felt that the league was pretty much in the bag with the Rangers struggling for any kind of form.  It […]
Celtic player criticised after draw against Motherwell - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgio Chiellini makes superb claim about Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45874</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/giorgio-chiellini-claim-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T10:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Giorgio Chiellini is one of the best defenders of all time and he had some pretty positive comments about Celtic Park recently. The 39-year-old spent the majority of his career playing for Juventus and won more silverware there than one should try to count. Overall, he made more […]
Giorgio Chiellini makes superb claim about Celtic Park - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s problem is very clear and needs solving quick]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45870</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/celtic-problem-needs-solving-quick/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T19:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two more dropped points mean that Celtic have well and truly allowed the Rangers to get back into the title race. A lead which once stood at seven points, could be reduced to three if Philippe Clement’s side are able to win their games in hand. And the sad thing is that the Hoops have […]
Celtic’s problem is very clear and needs solving quick - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic problem after draw]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45866</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/brendan-rodgers-celtic-problem-draw/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T18:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was not the result Celtic were looking for, as they dropped two valuable points against Motherwell. David Turnbull’s goal appeared to have won it for the Hoops but the visitors equalised in the 90th minute and it ended 1-1. That means that if the Rangers win their games in hand, the gap will be […]
Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic problem after draw - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hollywood superstar pictured wearing Celtic jersey]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45861</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/hollywood-pictured-wearing-celtic-jersey/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T12:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Celtic have their fair share of famous fans. Rod Stewart is the first name that comes to most people’s minds, one of the best-selling music artists in history. Lewis Capaldi is another popular musician known to support the Hoops. And several A-list celebrities like Gerard Butler, Snoop Dogg, […]
Hollywood superstar pictured wearing Celtic jersey - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic pushing for priority signing in January window]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45859</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/celtic-priority-signing-january-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T09:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s January transfer window is expected to be a busy one. The club might have made nine signings in the summer, seven arriving on a permanent basis and two on loan, but there are still holes in Brendan Rodgers’ squad that need to be filled. On the other hand, there are way too many players […]
Celtic pushing for priority signing in January window - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable source offers Sydney van Hooijdonk to Celtic update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45854</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/reliable-sydney-van-hooijdonk-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T22:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are believed to be on the lookout for a striker in the January transfer window. There might be a few reasons behind that. Firstly, both Kyogo and Oh Hyeon-gyu might be unavailable for a considerable length of time early next year due to the AFC Asian Cup. They are the club’s two options to […]
Reliable source offers Sydney van Hooijdonk to Celtic update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou claims Celtic success gets dismissed]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45852</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/ange-postecoglou-claims-celtic-success/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T21:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has proven to be a major success in the Premier League since swapping Celtic for Tottenham Hotspur. Of course, a lot of fans were not happy to see him depart after just two years at Parkhead. But he has been very respectful about the club even after leaving. And it is hard not […]
Ange Postecoglou claims Celtic success gets dismissed - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>