<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-08-21T12:18:33.577Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers delivers Treble reality check after Celtic's disappointing cup defeat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171607</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-delivers-treble-reality-check-after-celtics-disappointing-cup-defeat/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic supporters, we have gotten used to winning trebles over the past decade or so. So much so that whenever we don’t manage to...
The post Brendan Rodgers delivers Treble reality check after Celtic's disappointing cup defeat appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stinging defeat leaves us pondering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111264</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/stinging-defeat-leaves-us-pondering/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T11:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No excuses, Celtic were poor and deserved nothing more than they got at Kilmarnock yesterday.  Too often a new central defensive partnership looked for a forward pass and were faced with statuesque targets.  Kilmarnock went man-to-man and were mostly able to keep the contest in the middle of the park until very late in the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS AND THE £30m QUESTION]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111261</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/brendan-rodgers-and-the-30m-question/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T10:50:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS pledged to spend to add quality to his Celtic squad with only TEN days left until the August 31 transfer deadline. The Hoops boss was bitterly disappointed following the inept and unacceptable display from his team as the holders crashed out of the Viaplay League Cup against Kilmarnock yesterday. It was a disjointed [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former referee makes bizarre verdict on Celtic's penalty claim vs Kilmarnock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171604</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/former-referees-bizarre-verdict-on-celtics-penalty-claim-vs-kilmarnock/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T10:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the fallout over Celtic’s defeat to Kilmarnock in the cup continues, the fans will be picking over the bones of the result to understand...
The post Former referee makes bizarre verdict on Celtic's penalty claim vs Kilmarnock appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BBC pundit 'expects' significant transfer movement after Celtic's cup exit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171599</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/pat-bonner-expects-significant-transfer-movement-after-celtics-cup-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic hero, Pat Bonner, has said he expects Brendan Rodgers to tap into the transfer market before the window closes after yesterday’s cup exit...
The post BBC pundit 'expects' significant transfer movement after Celtic's cup exit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arsenal make Kieran Tierney decision amid Celtic links]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43546</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/21/arsenal-kieran-tierney-celtic-links/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T09:05:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with quite a few players as we head towards the end of the summer transfer window. As the result against Kilmarnock showed, with Brendan Rodgers’ side being knocked out of the Scottish League Cup in the second round itself, the club need to bring some quality in. They have seen key […]
Arsenal make Kieran Tierney decision amid Celtic links - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic hero considers ambitious future career move]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171590</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ex-celtic-hero-aiden-mcgeady-considers-ambitious-future-career-move/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic winger, Aiden McGeady has told how he would consider a move into football management when he officially hangs up his playing boots. The...
The post Ex-Celtic hero considers ambitious future career move  appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fergus McCann scheduled for visit to boost high-profile Celtic Foundation initiative]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171508</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/fergus-mccann-scheduled-for-visit-to-boost-high-profile-celtic-foundation-initiative/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taking a welcome break from the football for just a minute, it’s great to report that Fergus McCann is scheduled in for a welcomed visit...
The post Fergus McCann scheduled for visit to boost high-profile Celtic Foundation initiative appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BBC pundits deliver interesting assessment of Celtic’s Rugby Park penalty flashpoint]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171581</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/bbc-pundits-deliver-interesting-assessment-of-celtics-rugby-park-penalty-flashpoint/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before I start, let’s get this off the bat straight away. Celtic didn’t deserve anything out of the cup fixture against Kilmarnock yesterday afternoon. We...
The post BBC pundits deliver interesting assessment of Celtic’s Rugby Park penalty flashpoint appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘ONE OR TWO OF THEM WENT DOWN A LITTLE EASILY,’ McINNES’ SHOCKING CELTIC CLAIM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111241</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/one-or-two-of-them-went-down-a-little-easily-mcinnes-shocking-celtic-claim/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T07:01:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC players were accused of going “down a little easily” by Kilmarnock boss Derek McInnes after his side’s 1-0 dismissal of the Viaplay League Cup holders at Rugby Park yesterday. The Ayrshire club’s gaffer admitted to being anxious after Sead Haksabanovic had been sent tumbling following an awkward outstretched-leg challenge from Lewis Mayo deep in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘YOU DON’T GET ANY SECOND CHANCES,’ McGREGOR’S CROSSROADS ADMISSION]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111237</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/you-dont-get-any-second-chances-mcgregors-crossroads-admission/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T06:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CRESTFALLEN Callum McGregor admits Celtic are at a crucial crossroads after the disappointment of failing to clear the first Viaplay League Cup hurdle against Kilmarnock. The holders saw their two-year grip on ths silverware loosened in a distinctly off-colour and uninspired performance at Rugby Park where they collapsed 1-0 to Marley Watkins’ strike just before [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton sends blunt message about Celtic recruitment]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43544</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/20/chris-sutton-sends-blunt-message-celtic-recruitment/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T21:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If any Celtic fans were hoping to see the club repeat a treble, those are already over. Brendan Rodgers’ side were knocked out from the second round of the Scottish League Cup, as they lost 1-0 against Kilmarnock away at Rugby Park. It was a result that not many would have seen coming and yet, […]
Chris Sutton sends blunt message about Celtic recruitment - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Common sense’: Roy Keane drops Celtic comment about Ange Postecoglou on Sky]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171559</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/common-sense-what-roy-keane-said-about-celtic-and-ange-postecoglou-on/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roy Keane used Celtic as an example to heap praise on Ange Postecoglou after his Tottenham Hotspur side beat Manchester United 2-0 on Saturday. The...
The post ‘Common sense’: Roy Keane drops Celtic comment about Ange Postecoglou on Sky appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BBC pundit left 'stunned' at Celtic's cup performance; one player gets pass marks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171553</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/pat-bonner-left-stunned-at-celtics-cup-performance-one-player-gets-pass-marks/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pat Bonner has delivered his verdict on Celtic’s defeat at Kilmarnock as the BBC pundit admits he was left ‘stunned’ at his former club’s performance....
The post BBC pundit left 'stunned' at Celtic's cup performance; one player gets pass marks appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic player needs surgery]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43541</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/20/brendan-rodgers-celtic-player-surgery/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T19:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already suffered their first big blow of the season. They lost 1-0 away to Kilmarnock to crash out of the Scottish League Cup in the second round. The club’s hopes of repeating the treble are already over. And even more worrying was the performance on the day. Brendan Rodgers’ side are looking tired […]
Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic player needs surgery - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Now the lads realise"; Callum McGregor addresses cup defeat with 'reminder' to Celtic squad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171548</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/now-the-lads-realise-callum-mcgregor-addresses-cup-defeat-with-reminder-to-celtic-squad/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s going to be a long week ahead for Celtic and fans as the realisation that the team have already relinquished a trophy so early...
The post "Now the lads realise"; Callum McGregor addresses cup defeat with 'reminder' to Celtic squad appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic boss offers straight-forward assessment of cup performance vs Kilmarnock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171541</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/neil-lennon-offers-straight-forward-assessment-of-celtics-performance-vs-kilmarnock/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic fans will have left Rugby Park today with more questions than answers as they watched their team crash out of the cup this...
The post Ex-Celtic boss offers straight-forward assessment of cup performance vs Kilmarnock appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton reacts to League Cup disappointment with blunt verdict on Celtic squad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171526</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/chris-sutton-reacts-to-league-cup-disappointment-with-blunt-verdict-on-celtic-squad/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s defeat to Kilmarnock at Rugby Park is clearly a disappointing blow to Brendan Rodgers and his attempt at defending last season’s treble. The team’s...
The post Chris Sutton reacts to League Cup disappointment with blunt verdict on Celtic squad appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers makes plea as Celtic knocked out of Cup]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43537</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/20/brendan-rodgers-plea-celtic-cup/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T18:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rugby Park is always a difficult place to travel to but even then, this is a result that not many Celtic fans would have seen coming. The Hoops were knocked out of the Scottish League Cup in the second round itself. There will be no treble for Brendan Rodgers this time around. And the first […]
Brendan Rodgers makes plea as Celtic knocked out of Cup - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic star will be out for 3 to 4 months]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171532</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-confirms-stephen-welsh-will-miss-next-3-to-4-months-of-celtic-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T17:38:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen Welsh has damaged ligaments in his ankle and will require surgery, ruling him out of the next three to four months of Celtic action....
The post Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic star will be out for 3 to 4 months appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘WE NEED THAT QUALITY,’ RODGERS IN TRANSFER VOW]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111227</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/we-need-that-quality-rodgers-in-transfer-vow/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T17:18:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is poised to plunge into the transfer market to strengthen his Celtic squad after a lacklustre and error-strewn display as the holders crashed out of the Viaplay League Cup this afternoon. The second time-around Hoops boss suffered defeat for the first time in 25 domestic Cup-ties as his team flopped 1-0 to Kilmarnock [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers calls for quality to arrive in late stages of Celtic transfer window]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171523</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-calls-for-quality-to-arrive-in-late-stages-of-celtic-transfer-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T16:45:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers recognises Celtic need some quality signings in the door in the closing stages of the transfer window after watching his team get knocked...
The post Brendan Rodgers calls for quality to arrive in late stages of Celtic transfer window appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers reacts as Celtic crash out of cup in Kilmarnock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171515</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-reacts-as-celtic-crash-out-of-cup-in-kilmarnock/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T16:23:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a deeply disappointing Sunday for Celtic after Kilmarnock beat the reigning Scottish League Cup holders 1-0 at Rugby Park to knock them out...
The post Brendan Rodgers reacts as Celtic crash out of cup in Kilmarnock appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KILMARNOCK 1 CELTIC 0: SWITCHED-OFF HOOPS’ CUP CALAMITY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111215</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kilmarnock-1-celtic-0-switched-off-hoops-cup-calamity/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T16:18:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KILMARNOCK 1 CELTIC 0 ALL good things must come to an end – and so it proved for Brendan Rodgers and Celtic at Rugby Park this afternoon. The second time-around Hoops manager went into this Viaplay League Cup encounter with an impeccable record in domestic Cup competitions in his previous spell at the club. Twenty-four [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kilmarnock v Celtic, Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111210</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kilmarnock-v-celtic-live-updates-18/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T13:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 15.00.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: GUSTAF DEBUT, HOLM IN FROM START]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111211</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-gustaf-debut-holm-in-from-start/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T12:56:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEW bhoy Gustaf Lagerbiekle makes his Celtic debut this afternoon – just four days after sealing his £3million move from Elfsborg. The Swedish centre-back will line up alongside Maik Nawrocki in the heart of the Hoops rearguard for the Viaplay League Cup-tie against Kilmarnock at Rugby Park. Norwegian midfielder Odin Thiago Holm also takes the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic XI confirmed: 2 changes bring excitement, global TV details, instant reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171507</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-vs-kilmarnock-confirmed-big-debut-first-start-global-tv-details-instant-reaction/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T12:51:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manager Brendan Rodgers has named his Celtic team vs Kilmarnock for today’s Scottish League Cup clash at Rugby Park. The full match squad is as...
The post Celtic XI confirmed: 2 changes bring excitement, global TV details, instant reaction appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic eye transfer move for 21-year-old Danish player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43533</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/20/celtic-eye-transfer-move-danish-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T12:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been pretty active in the summer transfer window, adding new faces to their squad till now. Those are Odin Thiago Holm, Marco Tilio, Yang Hyun-jun, Kwon Hyeok-kyu, Maik Nawrocki and Gustaf Lagerbielke. All of them are highly-rated players with a lot of potential. And it looks like the Hoops will be sticking to […]
Celtic eye transfer move for 21-year-old Danish player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers defends criticised Celtic star]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171503</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-defends-criticised-celtic-star/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T11:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers sounds happy with the contributions of Joe Hart as speculation continues about his future at Celtic. Some observers and supporters consider the goalkeeping...
The post Brendan Rodgers defends criticised Celtic star appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers comments cast doubt on Sunday Celtic transfer rumour]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171490</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-comments-cast-doubt-on-sunday-celtic-transfer-rumour/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s recent link to Mathias Kvistgaarden seems to suggest that the club are in the market to add a new striker to the ranks. 67...
The post Brendan Rodgers comments cast doubt on Sunday Celtic transfer rumour appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers gets rough media treatment in Sunday morning paper]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171468</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-gets-rough-media-treatment-in-sunday-morning-paper/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Far be it from me to deny someone else an opinion, but when analysis of Celtic and the Celtic manager feels particularly harsh and mean-spirited,...
The post Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers gets rough media treatment in Sunday morning paper appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Celtic's excellent record vs Kilmarnock won't matter to Brendan Rodgers today]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171474</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/why-celtics-excellent-record-vs-kilmarnock-wont-matter-to-brendan-rodgers-today/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T10:12:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks the day where Celtic get the second part of their defence of the treble underway. Brendan Rodgers will be keen to get his...
The post Why Celtic's excellent record vs Kilmarnock won't matter to Brendan Rodgers today appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jurgen Klinsmann is already 'really impressed' with new Celtic summer signing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171465</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/jurgen-klinsmann-is-already-really-impressed-with-new-celtic-summer-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s foray into the Asian transfer market continued this summer with the additions of Hyunjun Yang and Hyeokkyu Kwon. Both players have had cameo appearances...
The post Jurgen Klinsmann is already 'really impressed' with new Celtic summer signing appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Celtic would be a great move for him"; Danish football expert's verdict on linked striker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171452</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-would-be-a-great-move-for-him-danish-football-experts-verdict-on-linked-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s need to bring in a striker was highlighted this summer when Hyeongyu Oh was ruled out for a number of weeks due to injury....
The post "Celtic would be a great move for him"; Danish football expert's verdict on linked striker appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In-form Sunderland player linked with return to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43529</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/20/sunderland-player-linked-return-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T09:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to bring in some reinforcements before the summer transfer window slams shut. The club have already brought in six new faces but their opening two performances of the league campaign seemed to lack a certain spark that was their last season. Maybe some established and experienced players are required in this youthful squad. […]
In-form Sunderland player linked with return to Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VIAPLAY CUP DRAW TONIGHT: FIVE DOWN, THREE TO GO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111207</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/viaplay-cup-draw-tonight-five-down-three-to-go/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T08:50:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC will discover their Viaplay League Cup quarter-final opponents after this afternoon’s tie against Kilmarnock – providing the holders are not involved in a calamity at Rugby Park. The last-eight draw will be broadcast live on Viaplay immediately after the satellite broadcasters’ coverage of Brendan Rodgers’ team’s meeting with Derek McInnes’ side in Ayrshire. Already [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Holm's big chance, another Sunday debut; Celtic team news and Predicted XI vs Kilmarnock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171444</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/holms-big-chance-another-sunday-debut-celtic-team-news-and-predicted-xi-vs-kilmarnock/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T08:40:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic begin the defence of another trophy in Ayrshire this afternoon, taking on Derek McInnes’ Kilmarnock side in the Scottish League Cup. As last season’s...
The post Holm's big chance, another Sunday debut; Celtic team news and Predicted XI vs Kilmarnock appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hyunjun Yang names teammate who motivates him to be a success at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171439</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/hyunjun-yang-tells-which-club-legend-motivates-him-to-be-a-success-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyunjun Yang has opened up on the Celtic legend who is inspiring him to be a success at Celtic. The South Korean winger joined the...
The post Hyunjun Yang names teammate who motivates him to be a success at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers breaks silence on Celtic's Ibrox ticket allocation stance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171422</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-breaks-silence-on-celtics-ibrox-ticket-allocation-stance/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T07:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The news headlines towards the end of this week were all dominated by the Glasgow Derby ticket allocation story. We all know the reasons why...
The post Brendan Rodgers breaks silence on Celtic's Ibrox ticket allocation stance appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS HINTS AT HART FUTURE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111203</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-hints-at-hart-future/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T07:29:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has offered a hint about the future of veteran keeper Joe Hart. The 36-year-old 75 times-capped England international is out of contract at the end of the season after his £1million switch from Spurs in August 2021. Hart has featured in every major success since his arrival, but there have been persistent reports since [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The verdict as transfer journalist inevitably links Celtic with Patrick Roberts return]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171420</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/the-verdict-as-transfer-journalist-inevitably-links-celtic-with-patrick-roberts-return-despite-injury/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T07:17:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer journalist Alan Nixon believes Celtic are one of the teams interested in Sunderland winger Patrick Roberts this summer. Nixon, who first reported Ben McPherson’s...
The post The verdict as transfer journalist inevitably links Celtic with Patrick Roberts return appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘A REAL SHAME,’ RODGERS WOE FOR McCARTHY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111201</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/a-real-shame-rodgers-woe-for-mccarthy/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T07:04:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORGOTTEN MAN James McCarthy is on his way out at Celtic. The former Republic of Ireland midfielder was signed as a free agent from Crystal Palace in August 2021 and still has two years to run on his contract. However, the 32-year-old Glasgow-born anchorman didn’t start a single game for the champions last season. McCarthy [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Sunday August 20: We Haven’t Started The Fire]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18457</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18457"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T06:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the magic of the League Cup today with Celtic in Kilmarnock to begin their defence of a trophy that’s always nice to have in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Malph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dominik Livakovic at centre of wild Saturday night drama that banks Celtic extra UEFA cash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171415</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/dominik-livakovic-at-centre-of-wild-saturday-night-drama-that-banks-celtic-extra-uefa-cash/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T06:48:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AEK Athens and Dinamo Zagreb played out one of the matches of the season so far on Saturday night for a place in the playoff...
The post Dominik Livakovic at centre of wild Saturday night drama that banks Celtic extra UEFA cash appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wolves boss provides Daniel Podence latest; Celtic target deletes tweet, is omitted from squad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171410</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/wolves-boss-provides-daniel-podence-latest-celtic-target-deletes-tweet-and-is-omitted-from-squad/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T06:27:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wolves boss Gary O’Neil sounds as if he is completely moving on from Celtic transfer target Daniel Podence as an option after omitting him from...
The post Wolves boss provides Daniel Podence latest; Celtic target deletes tweet, is omitted from squad appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC TARGET DANISH STRIKER]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111196</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-target-danish-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T06:25:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is poised to add more firepower to his Celtic attack with a swoop for Danish wonderkid Mathias Kvistgaarden. The Under-21 international striker is on the Hoops manager’s wanted list and he hopes to get the deal done before the August 31 midnight deadline, according to a report in The Scottish Sun. Rodgers acknowledges [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["His agent has been talking"; Rodgers confirms 2021 signing's days at Celtic are numbered]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171407</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/his-agent-has-been-talking-brendan-rodgers-confirms-james-mccarthy-status-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T05:44:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has confirmed that James McCarthy’s days at Celtic are numbered and won’t be a part of his senior squad moving forward. McCarthy joined...
The post "His agent has been talking"; Rodgers confirms 2021 signing's days at Celtic are numbered appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New name enters Celtic transfer mix; Bhoys consider move for exciting attacker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171402</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/new-name-enters-celtic-transfer-mix-bhoys-consider-summer-move-for-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T05:13:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are eyeing a move for Brondby striker Mathias Kvistgaarden before the end of the summer transfer window, it has been reported this weekend. The...
The post New name enters Celtic transfer mix; Bhoys consider move for exciting attacker appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KILMARNOCK v CELTIC: 5-MINUTE QUIZ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111183</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kilmarnock-v-celtic-5-minute-quiz-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T04:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC faced Kilmarnock four times last season – once in the Viaplay League cup semi-final and three times in the Premiership – and won the lot, scoring 13 goals and conceding only one. It’s a sequence they hope to continue when they look horns with the Ayrshire outfit this afternoon. How much can you remember about [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GRIFF 33 TODAY: WHEN THE CHEERS FADE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=95735</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/griff-33-today-when-the-cheers-fade/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T04:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LEIGH GRIFFITHS will celebrate his 33rd birthday today. This time two years ago, the one-time prolific hitman was still a Celtic player. Now, after an unsuccessful loan stint at Dundee and a brief spell at third-tier Falkirk during the wretched 2020/21 campaign, he is turning out for Australian minnows Mandurah City. The somersault in the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss confirms that midfielder is looking to leave]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43525</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/19/celtic-boss-confirms-midfielder-leave/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T22:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been pretty active in the summer transfer window. They have seen their fair share of incomings and outgoings over the past several weeks. Six new players have arrived at the club in the form of Marco Tilio, Odin Thiago Holm, Kwon Hyeok-kyu, Yang Hyun-jun, Maik Nawrocki and Gustaf Lagerbielke. On the other hand, […]
Celtic boss confirms that midfielder is looking to leave - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic want to offload trio before summer window closes]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43522</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/19/celtic-want-trio-summer-window-closes/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T21:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of the focus will be on potential incomings as Celtic have less than two weeks to make some more additions this summer. They have brought in six fresh faces in the ongoing window and all of them are very highly-rated and have the potential to achieve big things in Glasgow. But when you consider […]
Celtic want to offload trio before summer window closes - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers emphasises difficulty of upcoming Celtic mission]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171399</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-emphasises-difficulty-of-upcoming-celtic-mission/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T20:23:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has never lost a cup game as manager of Celtic and obviously wants that streak to continue against Kilmarnock on Sunday – but...
The post Brendan Rodgers emphasises difficulty of upcoming Celtic mission appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 transfers Celtic can still complete before the end of the summer window; Sutton would love it]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171395</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/3-transfers-celtic-can-still-complete-before-the-end-of-the-summer-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T19:43:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have made six summer signings during the current transfer window and manager Brendan Rodgers is already involving them in first-team action. Odin Thiago Holm,...
The post 3 transfers Celtic can still complete before the end of the summer window; Sutton would love it appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kris Boyd urges Celtic to let key player go if no deal is agreed]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43519</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/19/kris-boyd-celtic-key-player-go-deal/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T19:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been an interesting start to Brendan Rodgers’ second stint as the manager of Celtic. The club have won their opening two games in the league and had a positive pre-season campaign as well. The performances have left quite a bit to be desired though. They seem to be missing a spark at the […]
Kris Boyd urges Celtic to let key player go if no deal is agreed - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Injured Celtic player ruled out for at least two months]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43516</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/19/injured-celtic-player-two-months/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T18:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are just two games into the season and Celtic are already facing a bit of a defensive crisis. Of course, that is far from ideal when you consider that their performances in the opening two matches left a lot to be desired. And now, Brendan Rodgers’ side are missing quite a few players as […]
Injured Celtic player ruled out for at least two months - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KILMARNOCK V CELTIC MATCHDAY MINIZINE]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58272</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/kilmarnock-v-celtic-matchday-minizine/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T16:44:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://mailchi.mp/celticfanzine.com/kilmarnock-v-celtic-minizine
The post KILMARNOCK V CELTIC MATCHDAY MINIZINE appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rocco Vata on fire for Celtic B but difficult start to season continues for young team]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171389</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/rocco-vata-on-fire-for-celtic-b-but-difficult-start-to-season-continues-for-young-team/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T15:51:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rocco Vata scored his fifth goal in four games for Celtic B this afternoon but it wasn’t enough for the young Hoops to earn a...
The post Rocco Vata on fire for Celtic B but difficult start to season continues for young team appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Big blow to Bhoys star as Celtic scan results show injury is worse than first thought]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171385</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/horrible-celtic-luck-after-new-contract-stephen-welsh-injury-scan-results-revealed/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T15:14:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Stephen Welsh is facing at least two months out of action after suffering an injury in training just hours after signing his new...
The post Report: Big blow to Bhoys star as Celtic scan results show injury is worse than first thought appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic suffer £12 million Daniel Podence transfer blow]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43512</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/19/celtic-daniel-podence-transfer-blow/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T12:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with a few high-profile names in recent weeks. One of them is that of Wolverhampton Wanderers winger, Daniel Podence. The Portuguese international looks to be headed for the Molineux Stadium exit door and Parkhead has been touted as a potential destination for the 27-year-old. This is not the first time that […]
Celtic suffer £12 million Daniel Podence transfer blow - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO AND THE LARSSON FACTOR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111193</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kyogo-and-the-larsson-factor/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T11:19:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO FURUHASHI has been tasked with a slightly modified role in Brendan Rodgers’ revamp of the team’s playing style. The Japanese international striker scored his 56th goal for the champions in the 2-0 victory over Aberdeen at Pittodrie last weekend. It was added to his counter in the opening-day 4-2 win over Ross County at [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic missed chance to sign £115m player for £1 million]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43509</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/19/celtic-missed-chance-sign-115m-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T09:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are all about identifying talents early on in their careers, bringing them to Parkhead, developing them and then transferring them for hopefully a significantly larger fee than what they had shelled out in the first place. This strategy has often frustrated the club’s supporters but at the same time, it is perhaps the only […]
Celtic missed chance to sign £115m player for £1 million - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: GOALKEEPERS, GUNSLINGERS AND GOLDFISH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111181</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-goalkeepers-gunslingers-and-goldfish/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T08:31:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A FAIR percentage of Joe Hart’s critics wouldn’t know a goalkeeper from a goldfish. The netminder who is immune from the odd clanger has yet to be born. It’s the last line of defence in which an error or a moment’s aberration will usually prove fatal. Hart has made a mistake or two, that comes [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Concerned Chris Sutton calls for swift Celtic action]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171382</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/concerned-chris-sutton-calls-for-swift-celtic-action/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T07:41:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker Chris Sutton reckons the Bhoys are at least three players short of having the squad capable to meet upcoming challenges and has...
The post Concerned Chris Sutton calls for swift Celtic action appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers' latest transfer update suggests Celtic waiting game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171379</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-latest-transfer-update-suggests-celtic-waiting-game/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T06:58:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers says there is nothing ‘imminent’ in terms of incoming transfers after the capture of new Celtic defender Gustaf Lagerbielke through the week. The...
The post Brendan Rodgers' latest transfer update suggests Celtic waiting game appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN BACKS SAFETY-FIRST CELTS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111177</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/brendan-backs-safety-first-celts/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T06:55:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is backing Celtic’s resolute stance on safety demands in the Glasgow derby ticket war. The second time-around Hoops manager was involved in 11 of the pressurised encounters during his first stint at Parkhead and has always insisted the fixture has been damaged by the reduced numbers of travelling supporters and the recent total [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘STRETCHED,’ SUTTON PINPOINTS THREE CELTIC CONCERNS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111174</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/stretched-sutton-pinpoints-three-celtic-concerns/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T06:25:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CHRIS SUTTON insists Brendan Rodgers will have to go into overdrive in the transfer market before the deadline in 12 days’ time. The former Celtic goalscoring hero reckons the returning Hoops manager is THREE players short of a squad that will equipped to handle the challenges at home and abroad. Sutton admits concerns over the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Can tell straight away in training"; New Celtic Bhoy already impressing Rodgers at Lennoxtown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171376</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/you-can-tell-straight-away-in-training-new-celtic-bhoy-already-impressing-rodgers-at-lennoxtown/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T06:23:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing Gustaf Lagerbielke looks set to make his debut for the Bhoys this weekend, just days after making his big move from Elfsborg....
The post "Can tell straight away in training"; New Celtic Bhoy already impressing Rodgers at Lennoxtown appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss pushing the club for Kieran Tierney return]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43492</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/18/celtic-boss-pushing-kieran-tierney/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T22:30:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s still time for Celtic to sign more players this summer in order to boost their squad, as they attempt to defend the treble and make an impact in the Champions League group stages this season. And Brendan Rodgers appears to be trying to bring Kieran Tierney back to the club, in what would be […]
Celtic boss pushing the club for Kieran Tierney return - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[La Liga club hand Kieran Tierney return boost to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43504</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/18/la-liga-kieran-tierney-return-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T21:02:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the more surprising rumours of the summer has seen Kieran Tierney being linked with a return to Celtic. The Scottish international had left the cub in 2019 in a £25 million deal in order to join Arsenal. He has had an up-and-down time in London since then. At the moment, he finds himself […]
La Liga club hand Kieran Tierney return boost to Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss gives firm answer to Daniel Podence question]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43501</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/18/celtic-boss-daniel-podence-question/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T19:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with quite a few high-profile names in recent times, as we are in the last two weeks of the summer transfer window. Time has absolutely flown by and the club have brought in six new faces to Parkhead. The speculation about marquee signings has led nowhere though. Let’s see if that […]
Celtic boss gives firm answer to Daniel Podence question - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player pictured on crutches in new injury fears]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43498</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/18/celtic-player-pictured-crutches-injury/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T18:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We might be just two games into the new season but Celtic are already dealing with a number of injuries. Both Cameron Carter-Vickers and Reo Hatate, two of the club’s best players, were forced off the pitch in the last game against Aberdeen. It is also unclear when Alistair Johnston, a nailed-on starter when fit, […]
Celtic player pictured on crutches in new injury fears - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The overlooked positive of today's Celtic update on Cameron Carter-Vickers and Reo Hatate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171369</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-overlooked-positive-of-todays-celtic-update-on-cameron-carter-vickers-and-reo-hatate/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T16:12:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While most of the headlines surrounding Cameron Carter-Vickers and Reo Hatate focused on their lack of availability for this weekend’s Scottish League Cup clash, a...
The post The overlooked positive of today's Celtic update on Cameron Carter-Vickers and Reo Hatate appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GREEN LIGHT FOR GUSTAF DEBUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111169</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/green-light-for-gustaf-debut/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T15:29:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEW Bhoy Gustaf Lagerbiekle is on course for a quickfire Celtic, as CQN forecast at the beginning of the week. Brendan Rodgers is poised to give the green light for the 23-year-old centre-back to face Kilmarnock in the Viaplay League Cup at Rugby Park on Sunday. Lagerbiekle was officially unveiled as the club’s sixth summer [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers provides update on transfer work at Celtic with 'pipeline' talked up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171360</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-provides-update-on-transfer-work-at-celtic-with-pipeline-talked-up/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T14:23:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers was asked about the recruitment process at the Bhoys this summer and how much involvement he has in that, at a...
The post Brendan Rodgers provides update on transfer work at Celtic with 'pipeline' talked up appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rodgers confirms new Bhoy is fit and available for testing Celtic debut after more injury blows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171357</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/rodgers-confirms-new-bhoy-is-fit-and-available-for-testing-celtic-debut-after-more-injury-blows/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T13:45:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers says new signing Gustaf Lagerbielke is fit and available for this weekend’s Celtic match against Kilmarnock, and he may be needed after another...
The post Rodgers confirms new Bhoy is fit and available for testing Celtic debut after more injury blows appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers takes firm stance as another Celtic summer exit looms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171350</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-takes-firm-stance-as-another-celtic-summer-exit-looms/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T13:27:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic prospect Rocco Vata looks destined for a permanent exit from the club before the end of the summer transfer window. Sky Sports journalist Anthony...
The post Brendan Rodgers takes firm stance as another Celtic summer exit looms appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘RELENTLESS,’ O’RILEY FIRES OUT WARNING]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111158</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/relentless-oriley-fires-out-warning/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T13:22:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY joined Celtic a month after Ange Postecoglou had won his first piece of silverware as Hoops manager following the 2-1 triumph over Hibs in the League Cup Final on December 19 2021. Four other trophies were claimed in the Greek-Australian gaffer’s two years in charge of the Hoops – and the stylish midfielder [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘MASSIVE FOR ME,’ WELSH HAILS RODGERS AS HE SIGNS NEW DEAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111146</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/massive-for-me-welsh-hails-rodgers-as-he-signs-new-deal/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T12:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[STEPHEN WELSH insists he will repay Brendan Rodgers for his faith in his ability after signing a new four-year contract at the champions. The versatile defender didn’t hesitate in penning the deal which will keep him at Celtic until 2027, at least, and he is determined to “kick on now” in his Hoops career after [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports man delivers worrying Celtic exit update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43495</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/18/sky-sports-man-celtic-exit-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T12:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already witnessed plenty of exits this summer. Jota departed the club in order to join Al-Ittihad in a £25 million move. Carl Starfelt has signed with Celta Vigo. Both of them were starters and their departures were headline-grabbers as a result. Other than that, Vasilias Barkas, Conor Hazard and Osaze Urhoghide have left […]
Sky Sports man delivers worrying Celtic exit update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big boost for Celtic as key injured star spotted back in Friday training after surgery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171346</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alistair-johnston-injury-update-big-boost-for-celtic-after-friday-pictures/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T11:29:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic right-back Alistair Johnston is closing in on a return to action after missing the entire pre-season period, pictured back in training at Lennoxtown this...
The post Big boost for Celtic as key injured star spotted back in Friday training after surgery appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Faux grievances, summer shocks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111145</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/faux-grievances-summer-shocks/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T11:06:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[European football forever shocks, never more so that when Hibs and Hearts eliminate two teams you have heard of.  Rosenborg’s star rises and fades with the clock, but they are still vastly more experienced in Europe than Hearts.  Coming from two goals down in the tie to win last night was an heroic result. The [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bizarre bitter outburst from Kilmarnock man ahead of Celtic cup clash this weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171341</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/bizarre-bitter-outburst-from-kilmarnock-boss-derek-mcinnes-ahead-of-celtic-cup-clash/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T10:53:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kilmarnock manager Derek McInnes has decided to step back in time seven months to complain about an incident in a match against Celtic, despite saying...
The post Bizarre bitter outburst from Kilmarnock man ahead of Celtic cup clash this weekend appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Podence transfer twist amid heavy Celtic links]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43489</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/18/daniel-podence-transfer-celtic-links/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T09:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with plenty of players in recent days. One name that has managed to capture the imagination of the supporters is Daniel Podence. The Wolves winger did not participate in pre-season games and was left out of their matchday 1 squad against Manchester United as well. Thus, his exit from the Molineux […]
Daniel Podence transfer twist amid heavy Celtic links - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers – Lets Go Round Again]]></title>
        <id>http://celticunderground.net/?p=6626</id>
        <link href="http://celticunderground.net/brendan-rodgers-lets-go-round-again/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T09:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Brendan Rodgers left us in 2019, my abiding memory of that week was a video posted on social media.  Put together by Tam Sellic’s Son, it was video of Rodgers with the music to the “Wedding March” but with the lyrics changed to “You are a c***!!”.  I was genuinely shocked by how many […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Critical Bill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JUST VAR-CICAL: WEE DEREK’S CELTIC BLEATINGS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111138</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/just-var-cical-wee-dereks-celtic-bleatings/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T08:02:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DEREK McINNES is obviously game for a laugh after his bleatings over a penalty call that didn’t go Kilmarnock’s way in their 2-0 loss to Celtic in the Viaplay League Cup semi-final in April. The Ayrshire club’s boss is preparing for Sunday’s tie against the holders at Rugby Park by pathetically harping on about an [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scotland get UEFA coefficient boost; how it can help Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171338</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/scotland-get-uefa-coefficient-boost-how-it-can-help-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T06:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scottish football is earning its place in the UEFA coefficient listing this week with Premiership clubs beating outfits from countries that are direct rivals to...
The post Scotland get UEFA coefficient boost; how it can help Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC KID AGREES DOUBLE DEAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111134</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-kid-agrees-double-deal/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T06:28:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BOSUN LAWAL has agreed a season-long loan at Scott Brown’s Fleetwood Town – on the same day he extended his Celtic contract to June 2026. The Republic of Ireland Under-21 centre-back will be given game-time in the English third tier and the move south was forecast by CQN almost a MONTH ago. Brendan Rodgers was [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IT’S WAR: CELTIC DERBY TICKET ROW RAGES]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111130</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/its-war-celtic-derby-ticket-row-rages/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T06:01:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC are ready to go to war with the SPFL as the club’s hierarchy insist they will REFUSE tickets to their Ibrox counterparts for the December 30 derby at Parkhead. The Hoops bosses have formally rejected the offer of 708 briefs for the match in Govan on September 3. The Celtic board took this decision [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coach’s Odin Thiago Holm claim should excite Celtic fans]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43442</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/17/coach-odin-thiago-holm-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T22:32:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we have already seen this season, Brendan Rodgers is keen to give players on form the chance to start for Celtic. And following Reo Hatate’s injury against Aberdeen and his own positive displays in recent weeks, one of this summer’s signings could now be set to get an opportunity to shine. Rodgers has already […]
Coach’s Odin Thiago Holm claim should excite Celtic fans - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carl Starfelt sends emotional message to Celtic fans]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43482</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/17/carl-starfelt-emotional-message-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T21:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is hard not to feel that Carl Starfelt did not get the proper recognition that he deserved for his contributions to Celtic over the past two seasons. He was a nailed-on starter throughout Ange Postecoglou’s run at Parkhead. The only others who can say that are Kyogo, Jota, Cameron Carter-Vickers, Joe Hart and Callum […]
Carl Starfelt sends emotional message to Celtic fans - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart, Cameron Carter-Vickers and more respond to Celtic Instagram goodbye]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171333</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/joe-hart-cameron-carter-vickers-and-more-respond-to-carl-starfelt-celtic-goodbye/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T20:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carl Starfelt has said his goodbyes to Celtic in an Instagram post this evening, with his former teammates responding with well wishes. Starfelt has made...
The post Joe Hart, Cameron Carter-Vickers and more respond to Celtic Instagram goodbye appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exciting Champions League comments emerge from the Celtic camp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171330</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-promising-champions-league-ambition-within-the-celtic-camp-becomes-clear/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T20:17:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Matt O’Riley’s comments are anything to go by, the Celtic squad is feeling very positive about their ability to make a mark in Europe...
The post Exciting Champions League comments emerge from the Celtic camp appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic rumoured to be closing in on high-profile signing]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43479</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/17/celtic-rumoured-closing-profile-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T19:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been pretty active in the ongoing summer window. They have brought in six new players to the club in the form of Odin Thiago Holm, Marco Tilio, Yang Hyun-jun, Kwon Hyeok-kyu, Maik Nawrocki and the latest to arrive, Gustaf Lagerbielke. At the same time, some fans have been left a bit underwhelmed by […]
Celtic rumoured to be closing in on high-profile signing - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moussa Dembele sends brilliant message to Celtic fans after impressive debut for Al-Ettifaq]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171325</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/moussa-dembele-sends-message-to-celtic-fans-after-impressive-debut-for-al-ettifaq/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T19:28:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moussa Dembele is finding Celtic fans wherever he goes in the world, something made clear again after his goalscoring debut for Al-Ettifaq in the Saudi...
The post Moussa Dembele sends brilliant message to Celtic fans after impressive debut for Al-Ettifaq appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic find themselves in strong negotiating position to land attacker once worth £16.6m]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171320</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-find-themselves-in-strong-negotiating-position-to-land-attacker-once-worth-16-6m/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Celtic pursuit of Wolves attacker Daniel Podence looks viable despite the English Premier League side putting a high valuation on any transfer move away...
The post Celtic find themselves in strong negotiating position to land attacker once worth £16.6m appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic make double announcement about defender]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43476</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/17/celtic-make-double-announcement-defender/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T18:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have made quite a few additions in the ongoing summer transfer window. One area of the pitch that has been in particular focus is central defence due to a combination of reasons. Carl Starfelt’s exit, the unconvincing performances of Yuki Kobayashi and the question marks over the future of players like Stephen Welsh and […]
Celtic make double announcement about defender - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic make it clear they see a big Bhoys future for 20-year-old talent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171315</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/celtic-make-it-clear-they-see-a-big-bhoys-future-for-bosun-lawal-as-scott-brown-talks-up-qualities/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T17:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have announced that 20-year-old defender Bosun Lawal has committed his next three years to the Bhoys and will now spend a season out on...
The post Celtic make it clear they see a big Bhoys future for 20-year-old talent appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic take pleasing strong stance after yet more nonsense from Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171309</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-take-pleasing-strong-stance-after-yet-more-nonsense-from-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T16:53:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic aren’t going to back down in the ongoing ticket furore surrounding derby matches, insisting that no Rangers fans will be allowed into Celtic Park...
The post Celtic take pleasing strong stance after yet more nonsense from Rangers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More reasons to look forward to the season ahead; 8 ex-Celtic players currently in management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171283</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/more-reasons-to-look-forward-to-the-season-ahead-8-ex-celtic-players-currently-in-management/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T16:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The start of a new football season always brings a new excited feeling to not only Celtic fans but football fans in general. For us...
The post More reasons to look forward to the season ahead; 8 ex-Celtic players currently in management appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["There was interest from other clubs"; Gustaf Lagerbielke explains why he chose Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171299</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/there-was-interest-from-other-clubs-gustaf-lagerbielke-explains-why-he-chose-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gustaf Lagerbielke has revealed that there was interest from other clubs for his services as he opens up on why he chose to sign for...
The post "There was interest from other clubs"; Gustaf Lagerbielke explains why he chose Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s final decision on Ibrox ticket allocation; Rangers make next move]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171292</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-final-decision-on-ibrox-ticket-allocation-rangers-make-next-move/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have made their final decision on the ticket allocation offered to them by Rangers for the first Glasgow Derby of the season at Ibrox....
The post Celtic’s final decision on Ibrox ticket allocation; Rangers make next move appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WAIT FOR IT: WHEN CELTIC WILL LEARN RIVALS IN VIAPLAY CUP DRAW]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111122</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/wait-for-it-when-celtic-will-learn-rivals-in-viaplay-cup-draw/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T14:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC will discover their Viaplay League Cup quarter-final opponents on Sunday night – if, of course, they do not falter against Kilmarnock in their opening tie with a 3pm kick-off at Rugby Park earlier in the day. The last-eight draw will be broadcast live on Viaplay immediately after the satellite broadcasters’ coverage of the holders’ [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris McCart responds as Celtic Youth Academy continues important development strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171277</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/chris-mccart-responds-as-celtic-youth-academy-continues-important-development-strategy/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have announced that they are continuing an important partnership to help secure some of the best young talents of the future. For many of...
The post Chris McCart responds as Celtic Youth Academy continues important development strategy appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lagerbielke arrives not a minute too soon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111113</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/lagerbielke-arrives-not-a-minute-too-soon/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T12:47:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s summer spend continued yesterday with the arrival of 23-year-old Swedish central defender Gustaf Lagerbielke from Elfsborg for a reported £3m fee.  At 1.93m, Gustav is tall, 8cm taller than Cameron Carter-Vickers and Maik Nawrocki, only Christopher Jullien (1.96m) was taller in recent times. Across the squad Celtic are a small team.  Purists who still [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leeds United transfer target urged to make Celtic move]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43473</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/17/leeds-united-target-celtic-move/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T12:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Things appear to be picking up pace for Celtic in the transfer market over the past few days. They have been linked with some high-profile names like Eric Dier and Daniel Podence lately, either of whom would be great additions to this team and a statement of intent on the part of the club. Quentin […]
Leeds United transfer target urged to make Celtic move - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elfsborg Sporting Director's classy message to Celtic and Gustaf Lagerbielke]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171247</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/elfsborg-sporting-directors-classy-message-to-celtic-and-gustaf-lagerbielke/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic eventually sealed the deal to bring Gustaf Lagerbielke to Glasgow this week after the club officially announced the move yesterday. The announcement brought an...
The post Elfsborg Sporting Director's classy message to Celtic and Gustaf Lagerbielke appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘That quality’: Peter Grant backs Celtic to sign player with 'great power' amid rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171250</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-transfer-news-peter-grant-delivers-verdict-on-daniel-podence-rumours/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant has backed Celtic to possibly secure a loan deal for Wolves winger, Daniel Podence.  Brendan Rodgers is keen to implement his own fingerprints...
The post ‘That quality’: Peter Grant backs Celtic to sign player with 'great power' amid rumours appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GUSTAF THE SIXTH – NOW FOR No.7]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111114</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/gustaf-the-sixth-now-for-no-7/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T11:14:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GUSTAF LAGERBIEKLE sealed his five-year deal to Celtic from Elsborg yesterday, as CQN reported. The 23-year-old Swedish international centre-back became Brendan Rodgers’ sixth signing ahead of the August 31 transfer deadline. Lagerbiekle, who cost something in the region of £3million, is the latest in the second time-around Hoops manager’s rebuilding of the treble-winning squad which [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star's interesting comments on how the players feel about recent transfer rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171242</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/matt-orileys-interesting-comments-on-how-the-celtic-players-feel-about-recent-transfer-rumours/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the transfer rumours now in full swing, Celtic have found themselves linked to a variety of players over the last few days. Names like...
The post Celtic star's interesting comments on how the players feel about recent transfer rumours appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed £12 million Daniel Podence transfer boost]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43468</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/17/celtic-daniel-podence-transfer-boost/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T10:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Jota left Celtic earlier this summer in order to join Al-Ittihad, he left a massive gap in the squad as well. It is something that the Hoops need to fill as soon as possible. If the performances over the first few weeks of the league season have shown anything, it is that the club […]
Celtic handed £12 million Daniel Podence transfer boost - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Young Celtic talent speaks for the first time after sealing season-long loan move]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171235</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ben-summers-speaks-for-the-first-time-after-loan-move-celtic-youngster-sets-immediate-target/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Summers has spoken for the first time after sealing his season-long loan move to Scottish Championship side, Dunfermline Athletic. The move ends a year-long...
The post Young Celtic talent speaks for the first time after sealing season-long loan move appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O'Riley delivers verdict on Celtic's performance vs Aberdeen; states one obvious fact]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171230</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/matt-oriley-delivers-verdict-on-celtics-performance-vs-aberdeen-states-one-obvious-fact/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s performance against Aberdeen, despite getting off to a slow start, was one that still delivered a huge result. Going to Pittodrie is always a...
The post  Matt O'Riley delivers verdict on Celtic's performance vs Aberdeen; states one obvious fact appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I'm a real fan"; Peter Grant pinpoints one Celtic star the club must hold onto]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171221</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/im-a-real-fan-peter-grant-pinpoints-one-celtic-star-the-club-must-hold-onto/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T08:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant has reacted to the news reports that Celtic are about to open talks with Liel Abada and Reo Hatate in a bid to...
The post "I'm a real fan"; Peter Grant pinpoints one Celtic star the club must hold onto appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I REALLY BELIEVE WE CAN BEAT ANYBODY,’ O’RILEY EURO BOAST]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111109</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-really-believe-we-can-beat-anybody-oriley-euro-boast/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T08:10:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE nearest Matt O’Riley got to Champions League action two years ago was to switch on his television. Now the gifted playmaker, who was signed for a modest £1.5million from English third-tier outfit MK Dons in January 2022, insists Celtic can make an impact among Europe’s elite this season. London-born O’Riley is looking forward to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers backroom reshuffle ongoing at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171207</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-backroom-reshuffle-ongoing-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic coach, Scott Breddy, leaves the club this week after nine years of service. Breddy was the first-team Strength and Conditioning coach. Breddy made the...
The post Brendan Rodgers backroom reshuffle ongoing at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC IN DOUBLE DEAL BID]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111105</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-in-double-deal-bid/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T07:17:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC are preparing to thrash out new deals with Reo Hatate and Liel Abada. The Japanese midfielder and the Israeli winger, both under contract until June 2026, will be offered lucrative extensions, according to a report in the Daily Record. Hatate and Abada have been been involved in transfer speculation this summer and Brendan Rodgers [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing set to make very quick debut after strong preparation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171202</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/new-celtic-signing-declares-himself-ready-for-quick-debut-after-strong-preparation/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T07:15:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing Gustaf Lagerbielke has declared himself ready to compete for the Bhoys immediately after a summer of strong preparation in Sweden. The Swedish...
The post New Celtic signing set to make very quick debut after strong preparation appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic board make exciting moves to secure future of top talents]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171197</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/big-contract-moves-on-the-way-from-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T05:49:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will open contract talks with two of the club’s most important and exciting players in Reo Hatate and Liel Abada before the end of...
The post The Celtic board make exciting moves to secure future of top talents appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I LOOKED DOWN, MY ANKLE WAS TWICE THE SIZE IT WAS AT KICK-OFF,’ BOBBY MURDOCH, MAN OF THE MATCH IN LISBON]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=35538</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-looked-down-my-ankle-was-twice-the-size-it-was-at-kick-off-bobby-murdoch-man-of-the-match-in-lisbon/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T04:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BOBBY MURDOCH went through all sorts of agonies as Celtic gatecrashed the European big-time in Lisbon. The painful experience was highlighted in author Alex Gordon’s tribute book, ‘The Lisbon Lions: The 40th Anniversary Celebration’, which was published in 2007. The club legend, who would have been 79 today, was a thoughtful midfielder with a delightful touch [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>