<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-08-11T14:08:51.680Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic arrival already impressing Carter-Vickers as he discusses "sad" Starfelt news]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170650</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/new-celtic-arrival-already-impressing-carter-vickers-as-he-discusses-sad-starfelt-news/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T13:55:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Cameron Carter-Vickers is already seeing good things from Maik Nawrocki in training. The pair started Celtic‘s Premiership opener together last Saturday and are...
The post New Celtic arrival already impressing Carter-Vickers as he discusses "sad" Starfelt news appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More than 90 Minutes Match Day]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58246</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/more-than-90-minutes-match-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T13:39:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technology has changed the way we get our fix of Celtic News since we started our Celtic Fanzine, More than 90 Minutes back in 2001. Social media means we can have news in an instant, it may not be true, it could be true  or it is true. When Donald Trump came up with his […]
The post More than 90 Minutes Match Day appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's all looking good as Hatate and Bernabei feature in Celtic training images]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170644</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/its-all-looking-good-as-hatate-and-bernabei-feature-in-celtic-training-images/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T12:12:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spirits seem high at Lennoxtown as Celtic prepare for the clash against Aberdeen on Sunday. It may only be week two of the Premiership season,...
The post It's all looking good as Hatate and Bernabei feature in Celtic training images appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jota already set to leave Al-Ittihad on loan after Celtic exit]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43332</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/11/jota-leave-al-ittihad-celtic-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T12:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was just last month that Jota left Celtic for a transfer fee believed to be around £25 million. The Portuguese winger was a key part of the team that won five trophies over the previous two campaigns and he was also someone who rose to the occasion, scoring several goals in the Glasgow Derby. […]
Jota already set to leave Al-Ittihad on loan after Celtic exit - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday clash could offer insight on Celtic centre-back hunt]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170637</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/sunday-clash-could-offer-insight-on-celtic-centre-back-hunt/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans could get an indication over the situation with Gustaf Lagerbielke this Sunday. The Swedish central-defender’s name has been on the lips of Hoops...
The post Sunday clash could offer insight on Celtic centre-back hunt appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reo, Alexandro: Brendan gets managing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110913</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/reo-alexandro-brendan-gets-managing/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T11:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Finishing third last season, Aberdeen go straight to the Europa League playoff round, so their only competitive game since losing 5-0 at Celtic Park at the end of last season was Saturday’s 0-0 draw at Livingston.  They prepared for the season with only four friendlies, meaning they have seen less game time than anyone else [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Exciting Celtic youngster could depart on loan this summer; must do one thing first]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170627</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/rocco-vata-could-depart-celtic-on-loan-this-summer-must-do-one-thing-first/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic attacker Rocco Vata could be allowed to depart the club on loan this summer, but only if he signs a new contract first. The...
The post Report: Exciting Celtic youngster could depart on loan this summer; must do one thing first appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss sends message about Reo Hatate ‘red flag’]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43329</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/11/celtic-boss-message-reo-hatate/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T09:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate was one of Celtic’s best players during the time of Ange Postecoglou as the manager of the club. In fact, many pundits felt that out of everyone at Parkhead, the Japanese midfielder was the one who was most Premier League-ready. Yet, with the arrival of Brendan Rodgers, it looks like the 25-year-old is […]
Celtic boss sends message about Reo Hatate ‘red flag’ - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘NOT IN MY CONTRACT TO PLAY ANY PLAYER,’ RODGERS CHALLENGE TO REO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110897</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/not-in-my-contract-to-play-any-player-rodgers-challenge-to-reo/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T06:11:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has issued a challenge to Reo Hatate – and every Celtic player – that they must earn their place in his Celtic first team. The Japanese midfielder gave the impression he was distinctly miffed at losing his place to two-goal David Turnbull in the starting line-up for the 4-2 win over Ross County [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers says Celtic star is looking "really good" in training despite fan concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170622</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-addresses-reo-hatate-red-flag-celtic-concern-head-on-with-reassuring-observation/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T05:45:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has reiterated that Reo Hatate has to earn any minutes he gets in a Celtic shirt, but is seeing good signs in training...
The post Brendan Rodgers says Celtic star is looking "really good" in training despite fan concerns appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SNOOZE AND YOU LOSE: BERNABEI NO-SHOW MYSTERY SOLVED]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110895</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/snooze-and-you-lose-bernabei-no-show-mystery-solved/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T05:27:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NO-NONSENSE Brendan Rodgers AXED Alexandro Bernabei from his match day squad for oversleeping and turning up late for a team meeting. The dozy Argentinian left-back got the boot from the pool of players for Celtic’s Premiership opener against Ross County at Parkhead on Saturday. Bernabei, who had scored an excellent goal un the 3-2 win over [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star in hot water with Brendan Rodgers; boundaries set by new boss]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170617</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-star-in-hot-water-with-brendan-rodgers-boundaries-set-by-new-boss/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T05:14:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alexandro Bernabei didn’t feature in the Celtic squad against Ross County because he landed himself in hot water with boss Brendan Rodgers. The Daily Record...
The post Celtic star in hot water with Brendan Rodgers; boundaries set by new boss appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIG YOGI AND LISBON: THE TRUTH (Part Eight)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=95424</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/big-yogi-and-lisbon-the-truth-part-eight/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T04:45:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOHN ‘YOGI’ HUGHES played in five of Celtic eight ties during their great adventure that took Jock Stein’s team to the European Cup Final against Inter Milan in Lisbon on the unforgettable date of May 25 1967. The non-appearance of the iconic Hoops forward has been the subject of conjecture ever since. The goalscoring winger [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic delay in summer signings a cause for concern]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43283</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/10/celtic-delay-summer-signings-concern/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T22:40:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There have been some moves by Celtic in this season’s summer transfer window so far. While the new signings show strong potential, it doesn’t yet feel like the squad has improved when compared to last season. That’s left most fans hoping for more to come. But is there a hold-up on that happening? So far […]
Celtic delay in summer signings a cause for concern - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder set to join Championship club on loan]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43322</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/10/celtic-midfielder-join-championship-club/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T21:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have seen quite a few players depart the club this summer, either on a permanent basis or on loan. Of course, the recent headlines have been grabbed by the exit of Carl Starfelt and understandably so. The Swede was a regular starter for the Hoops and played a major part in their successes over […]
Celtic midfielder set to join Championship club on loan - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michail Antonio’s past comments about Celtic fans reemerge]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43319</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/10/michail-antonio-comments-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T19:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with a number of players in recent times. One of them is Michail Antonio of West Ham United. The Jamaican international has been a stalwart for the Hammers for several years now but could be on the move this summer. And Parkhead has been touted as a possible destination for him. […]
Michail Antonio’s past comments about Celtic fans reemerge - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers outlines next step for rejuvenated Celtic star; tackles contract question]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170608</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-outlines-next-step-for-david-turnbull-tackles-celtic-contract-question/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has outlined the next step for David Turnbull at Celtic. The Hoops midfielder has been rejuvenated in recent weeks and netted a double...
The post Brendan Rodgers outlines next step for rejuvenated Celtic star; tackles contract question appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic closing in on their sixth signing of the summer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43316</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/10/celtic-closing-sixth-signing-summer/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T17:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To be very honest, a lot of Celtic fans have been left underwhelmed by how the summer transfer window has turned out for the Hoops. When Brendan Rodgers was reappointed as manager, there was talk of marquee signings, big-name arrivals and a budget north of £30 million. None of that has come true yet and […]
Celtic closing in on their sixth signing of the summer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans set for bumper Sunday on Sky Sports]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170601</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-fans-set-for-bumper-sunday-on-sky-sports/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans are set for a bumper Sunday on Sky Sports featuring old and current flames. The Hoops are in action at Aberdeen in what...
The post Celtic fans set for bumper Sunday on Sky Sports appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Respect the champions"; Carl Starfelt's crowning off-the-pitch Celtic moment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170594</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/respect-the-champions-carl-starfelts-crowning-off-the-pitch-celtic-moment/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carl Starfelt departed Celtic on Thursday for a move to Celta Vigo. The Swedish central-defender’s departure was confirmed by the club in a statement that...
The post "Respect the champions"; Carl Starfelt's crowning off-the-pitch Celtic moment appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Arzani feeling inspired after Celtic's record-breaking summer transfer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170584</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/daniel-arzani-feels-inspired-after-celtics-record-breaking-summer-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Arzani has been speaking about his time at Celtic, and the summer signing of Marco Tilio. Tilio joined Celtic on the final day of...
The post Daniel Arzani feeling inspired after Celtic's record-breaking summer transfer appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premiership side make allocation decision for upcoming Celtic clash; 2022 example ignored]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170570</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/kilmarnock-make-allocation-decision-for-upcoming-celtic-cup-clash-2022-example-ignored/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kilmarnock will offer Celtic fans one stand for our upcoming League Cup clash at Rugby Park. The Hoops visit Ayrshire in the last 16 of...
The post Premiership side make allocation decision for upcoming Celtic clash; 2022 example ignored appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the Road Again – Aberdeen Away]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58232</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/on-the-road-again-aberdeen-away/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T15:08:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s an away day to Aberdeen on Sunday for those of us lucky enough to have secured a ticket. Away tickets are getting harder and harder to get as Scottish clubs continue to cut allocations while failing to sell out their own stadiums on matchdays when Celtic come to town. Celtic had no problem filling […]
The post On the Road Again – Aberdeen Away appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Phenomenal demand" for Celtic Park beam back of locked out Ibrox derby clash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170568</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/phenomenal-demand-for-celtic-park-beam-back-of-locked-out-ibrox-derby-clash/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T14:41:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ticket sales for Celtic Park beam backs of the upcoming derby between Celtic and Rangers have been strong, to the extent that the club are...
The post "Phenomenal demand" for Celtic Park beam back of locked out Ibrox derby clash appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confirmed: Celtic defender who was given big Japan chance departs on loan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170562</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/confirmed-celtic-defender-who-was-given-big-japan-chance-departs-on-loan/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T13:46:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Ben McPherson has joined Queen’s Park on loan for the rest of the season. The Hoops right-back will play for the Spiders as...
The post Confirmed: Celtic defender who was given big Japan chance departs on loan appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glasgow fan encounters, favourite song, nickname and Boruc texts; Maik Nawrocki's Celtic Q+A]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170556</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/glasgow-fan-encounters-favourite-song-nickname-and-boruc-texts-maik-nawrockis-celtic-qa/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T12:52:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing Maik Nawrocki has been taking part in a social media question and answer session this afternoon, after the club asked for fans...
The post Glasgow fan encounters, favourite song, nickname and Boruc texts; Maik Nawrocki's Celtic Q+A appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic finally make official double exit announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43309</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/10/celtic-official-double-exit-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T12:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While most of the focus has been on incomings, Celtic have seen quite a few players head out of the exit door this summer as well. The likes of Jota, Conor Hazard, Vasilis Barkas and Osaze Urhoghide have left the club on a permanent basis while Liam Shaw and Adam Montgomery have gone out on […]
Celtic finally make official double exit announcement - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch: Former Celtic boss Martin O'Neill steals the show during hilarious cup draw]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170549</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/watch-former-celtic-boss-martin-oneill-steals-the-show-during-hilarious-cup-draw/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T11:48:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic manager Martin O’Neill has made headlines after a hilarious but bizarre cup draw down south. O’Neill was one of those tasked with making...
The post Watch: Former Celtic boss Martin O'Neill steals the show during hilarious cup draw appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dublin date for big John]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58228</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/dublin-date-for-big-john/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T11:44:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Big John Hartson will be back on stage at Peadar Browns, Dublin on Friday 17 Nov 2023. Just over a year since his last visit to the venue. Last year John joined More than 90 Minutes Editor, Andrew Milne to chat about his career and Celtic under Ange Postecoglou before opening up questions from the […]
The post Dublin date for big John appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The incredible record that will stand the test of time as Carl Starfelt exits Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170542</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/the-incredible-record-that-will-stand-the-test-of-time-as-carl-starfelt-exits-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carl Starfelt has departed Celtic to join La Liga side Celta Vigo. The transfer was confirmed by Celtic on Thursday morning, with Starfelt departing the...
The post The incredible record that will stand the test of time as Carl Starfelt exits Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starfelt, value, heroic start. Qualifiers.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110893</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/starfelt-value-heroic-start-qualifiers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T10:59:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When rumours of Carl Starfelt going to Russia first surfaced last week few of us believed them.  Russia?  Not right now.  But we all had the debate, would you sell him?  He has been part of an incredibly successful Celtic central defensive partnership: won five from six trophies, never lost a domestic game in 90 [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: STARFELT SEALS LA LIGA SWITCH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110890</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-starfelt-seals-la-liga-switch/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T10:20:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have confirmed that Carl Starfelt has left the club for La Liga side Celta Vigo. The Swedish international central defender has ended his two-year association with the treble winners after arriving as a £4.2million recruit from Russian outfit Rubin Kazan, as CQN reported at the weekend. The Hoops have not gone into details of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Loan approach made for young Celtic star with a bright future; likely Hoops stance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170536</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/loan-approach-made-for-young-celtic-star-with-a-bright-future-likely-hoops-stance/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T09:34:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Young Celtic star Ben Summers could be on his way out of the club on loan this summer. The midfielder, who made his senior debut...
The post Report: Loan approach made for young Celtic star with a bright future; likely Hoops stance appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player rejects Austrian club to join Championship team]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43305</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/10/celtic-player-rejects-austrian-club-join-championship-team/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T09:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a stacked roster at this point in time and Brendan Rodgers might find it difficult to give enough playing time to everyone involved. Thus, loan moves away might be a good solution for many, especially youngsters who need to be playing regular football at this stage of their career in order to continue […]
Celtic player rejects Austrian club to join Championship team - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Thursday August 10: There May Be Trouble Ahead]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18453</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18453"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T09:22:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scotland’s UCL campaign kicked off last night with “rangers ” storming into a 2-1 lead over Swiss cracks Servette Geneva.   Whilst some might argue,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Malph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[POINT OF NO RETURN: WHY BRENDAN IS ‘REALLY HAPPY’ IN PARADISE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110883</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/point-of-no-return-why-brendan-is-really-happy-in-paradise/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T07:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS signed a three-year contract on his return to Celtic in June and vowed to see it through – unless he was “emptied” by the club’s hierarchy. In other words, gets the boot. However, the Irishman has promised not to exit unexpectedly as happened in February 2019 when he left to to take over [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Rodgers lauds Derek McInnes after result vs Rangers; Scottish Prem boss challenge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170526</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-rodgers-lauds-derek-mcinnes-after-result-vs-rangers-scottish-prem-boss-challenge/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T06:15:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers reckons the Kilmarnock victory over Rangers at the weekend is just further proof of the coaching talent in the Scottish Premiership....
The post Celtic boss Rodgers lauds Derek McInnes after result vs Rangers; Scottish Prem boss challenge appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC DUO TARGETED]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110878</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-duo-targeted/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T06:03:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC pair Ben Summers and Ben McPherson are wanted by Championship clubs as the clocks ticks down to the August 31 deadline. The teenagers are seen as emerging talents at the champions, but there is no likelihood of consistent game-time this season. Brendan Rodgers appears willing to allow both of the talented duo to go [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers on sit down Celtic chat with Starfelt; strength of Jacynta factor made clear]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170522</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-on-sit-down-celtic-chat-with-starfelt-strength-of-jacynta-factor-made-clear/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has shared that Carl Starfelt has been clear and honest regarding his personal situation and desire to leave the Bhoys all...
The post Brendan Rodgers on sit down Celtic chat with Starfelt; strength of Jacynta factor made clear appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers' changing stance on Celtic transfers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170519</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-changing-stance-on-celtic-transfers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T05:15:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers is now not as frustrated with big exits from the Bhoys as he once was, highlighting that a lot of big...
The post Brendan Rodgers' changing stance on Celtic transfers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INSIDE STORY: DRAMATIC NIGHT KING KENNY LEFT CELTIC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=38539</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/inside-story-dramatic-night-king-kenny-left-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T05:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KENNY DALGLISH left Celtic for Liverpool in a British transfer record fee of £440,000 on this day FORTY-SIX years ago. Author Alex Gordon has the inside story of a dramatic evening in the aftermath of the fans’ favourite’s final appearance in the green and white hoops. The rumours concerning Dalglish’s future had been flying around with [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIG YOGI AND LISBON: THE TRUTH (Part Seven)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=95389</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/big-yogi-and-lisbon-the-truth-part-seven/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-10T04:45:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC great John ‘Yogi’ Hughes was missing from Jock Stein’s Lisbon line-up for the history-making triumph on May 25 1967. The non-appearance of the iconic Hoops forward has been the subject of conjecture ever since. Hughes played in five of the eight games leading up to the European Cup Final, but the nearest he got [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player told he is free to leave the club this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43301</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/09/celtic-player-told-free-leave-club/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T22:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It will be interesting to see how the rest of the summer transfer window plays out for Celtic. To be honest, a lot of fans have been left underwhelmed by how things have transpired till now. There were a lot of expectations but a lot of them have not been met. Highly-rated young players have […]
Celtic player told he is free to leave the club this summer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[€20 million Celtic transfer target signs for Galatasaray]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43298</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/09/20-million-celtic-target-galatasaray/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T21:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Celtic brought back Brendan Rodgers for another stint in the Parkhead hot seat, despite how things ended the last time around, the Northern Irishman along with rumours of marquee signings. There were suggestions that the club were ready to make some high-profile addition this summer in order to make a real impact in the […]
€20 million Celtic transfer target signs for Galatasaray - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gustaf Lagerbielke makes superb Celtic claim amid links]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43293</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/09/gustaf-lagerbielke-celtic-claim-links/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T19:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will need to replace Carl Starfelt this summer. The centre-back appears to be on the verge of joining Celta Vigo and an official announcement could be made soon. He has been a regular starter for the Hoops for the past two seasons though and the club will need to bring in someone capable of […]
Gustaf Lagerbielke makes superb Celtic claim amid links - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gustaf Lagerbielke comments make it sound like Celtic deal is close]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170509</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/gustaf-lagerbielke-comments-make-it-sound-like-celtic-deal-is-close/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T18:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gustaf Lagerbielke has spoken very openly about a potential move to Celtic this summer. The Sweden international has been linked with a £3m transfer from...
The post Gustaf Lagerbielke comments make it sound like Celtic deal is close appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player ruled out for 4-6 weeks with calf injury]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43289</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/09/celtic-player-ruled-calf-injury/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T18:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We might be just one game into the new season but Celtic are dealing with their fair share of injuries. It remains to be seen when Alistair Johnston will be fit enough to feature again. The likes of Cameron Carter-Vickers and Maik Nawrocki only returned to action during the final pre-season friendly as well and […]
Celtic player ruled out for 4-6 weeks with calf injury - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers' alternative take on Celtic matches getting longer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170502</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-alternative-take-on-celtic-matches-getting-longer/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T17:43:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has offered an alternative take on Celtic matches getting longer. This season, Celtic fans can expect longer matches than ever before as the...
The post Brendan Rodgers' alternative take on Celtic matches getting longer appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic prove a big attraction once again; upcoming opponents heading for sell-out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170496</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-prove-a-big-attraction-once-again-upcoming-opponents-heading-for-sell-out/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T17:09:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pittodrie is heading for a sell-out for Celtic’s visit this weekend. The Hoops take on Aberdeen on Sunday lunchtime in their first away match of...
The post Celtic prove a big attraction once again; upcoming opponents heading for sell-out appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero's "dance" brought up as Brendan Rodgers prepares for Pittodrie return]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170485</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/scott-brown-dance-brought-up-as-brendan-rodgers-looks-back-on-celtic-pittodrie-memories/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T16:19:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers was asked for some of his best memories of visiting Pittodrie on Wednesday. The Hoops take on Aberdeen at their home...
The post Celtic hero's "dance" brought up as Brendan Rodgers prepares for Pittodrie return appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OH KO BLOW FOR CELTIC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110851</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/oh-ko-blow-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T15:35:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has revealed powerhouse striker Oh Hyeon-gyu will be out for SIX weeks with a calf problem. The South Korean international frontman sustained the injury as he played the entire second-half of James Forrest’s testimonial match against Athletic Bilbao at Parkhead last week. Oh helped to set up the winner for David Turnbull in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers shares good news about Celtic pair not seen yet this season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170475</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-shares-good-news-about-celtic-duo-alistair-johnston-and-marco-tilio/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has shared some good news about injured Celtic duo Alistair Johnston and Marco Tilio. The Canadian and Australian haven’t been seen in action...
The post Brendan Rodgers shares good news about Celtic pair not seen yet this season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lagerbielke, Tierney and more feature as Brendan Rodgers gives Celtic transfer update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170468</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/lagerbielke-tierney-and-more-feature-as-brendan-rodgers-gives-celtic-transfer-latest/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T14:06:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has given an update on the Celtic transfer situation with three-and-a-half weeks of the window to go. The Celtic boss was in front...
The post Lagerbielke, Tierney and more feature as Brendan Rodgers gives Celtic transfer update appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decisive action now required after Fabrizio Romano Celtic departure update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170460</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/decisive-celtic-action-now-required-as-fabrizio-romano-delivers-carl-starfelt-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T12:02:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carl Starfelt’s move to Celta Vigo has been sealed with an announcement surely not far away. Transfer guru Fabrizio Romano has offered an update on...
The post Decisive action now required after Fabrizio Romano Celtic departure update appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers tipped to drop in-form Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43286</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/09/brendan-rodgers-drop-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T12:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic made a winning start to the league season with a 4-2 win over Ross County at the weekend. The same cannot be said about the Rangers, who lost 1-0 away to Kilmarnock. That means that Brendan Rodgers’ side already have a three-point lead over Michael Beale’s team in the Premiership title race. One of […]
Brendan Rodgers tipped to drop in-form Celtic player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston set for trip to Japan after all; Celtic recovery boost]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170454</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alistair-johnston-set-for-trip-to-japan-after-all-celtic-recovery-boost/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T11:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston will face off against some of his Celtic team-mates later this year. That’s because his Canada side have announced a friendly against Japan...
The post Alistair Johnston set for trip to Japan after all; Celtic recovery boost appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£4m up for grabs for Celtic in qualifiers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110842</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/4m-up-for-grabs-for-celtic-in-qualifiers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T11:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Champions League qualifiers do not concern us directly this season, but their outcome will determine whether we ‘earn’ several million pounds.  Two potential qualifiers: Copenhagen and Dinamo Zagreb have higher 10-year coefficients than Celtic.  That metric rewards qualification on a sliding scale.  Celtic will earn an extra £2m if both fail to qualify, half of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lagerbielke, Mbuyamba and the Celtic centre-back setup Brendan Rodgers wants]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170446</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/lagerbielke-mbuyamba-and-the-celtic-centre-back-setup-brendan-rodgers-wants/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers gave some insight in to defensive squad planning on Saturday. Rodgers was quizzed about the club’s centre-back options after he confirmed...
The post Lagerbielke, Mbuyamba and the Celtic centre-back setup Brendan Rodgers wants appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Wednesday August 9: Stories Of The Blues]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18450</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18450"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T09:27:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s quite a lot of speculation about players coming in to Celtic.   In fairness, our intrepid sports reporters have done their bit and managed…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Malph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player changes agent amid Parkhead exit rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43280</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/09/celtic-player-changes-agent-exit-rumours/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T08:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic had a fantastic record of identifying and signing the right players during the time of Ange Postecoglou as manager. That does not mean that every move worked out though, especially in the latter stages of the Australian’s run at Parkhead before he ended up leaving for Tottenham Hotspur as manager. In fact, out of […]
Celtic player changes agent amid Parkhead exit rumours - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: GREEN LIGHT FOR SWEDE – IF THE PRICE IS RIGHT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110837</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-green-light-for-swede-if-the-price-is-right/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T08:15:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ELFSBORG director Stefan Andreasson has confirmed Celtic have made contact about the availability of defender Gustaf Lagerbielke, as CQNreported yesterday. The Hoops are poised to move to strengthen their central defence with Swedish international Carl Starfelt on his way to La Liga outfit Celta Vigo. Brendan Rodgers has identified £3million-rated Lagerbiekle as an ideal addition to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS’ CELTIC MIND GAMES]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110829</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-celtic-mind-games/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T06:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS launched his second stint as Celtic manager with the champions’ 4-2 victory over Ross County at the weekend. The team continued where they left off last season with a win over Highland opposition – Inverness Caley Thistle in the Scottish Cup Final – but the Irishman will not be dwelling on past deeds. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The reality of Celtic's goalkeeper situation as Joe Hart issue hits the mainstream]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170432</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-reality-of-celtics-goalkeeper-situation-as-joe-hart-issue-hits-the-mainstream/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T06:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic goalkeeping position has become a growing talking point over the summer. While current incumbent Joe Hart has been a positive signing overall for...
The post The reality of Celtic's goalkeeper situation as Joe Hart issue hits the mainstream appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic consider sending January arrival out on loan after difficult period]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170426</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-consider-sending-january-arrival-out-on-loan-after-difficult-period/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T06:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are considering letting Yuki Kobayashi go out on loan this summer, according to a report. Football Scotland have offered an update on the Japanese...
The post Report: Celtic consider sending January arrival out on loan after difficult period appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘BRILLIANT,’ HARTSON DEFENDS UNDER-FIRE HART]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110827</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/brilliant-hartson-defends-under-fire-hart/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T06:01:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOHN HARTSON has leapt to the defence of Joe Hart as criticism mounts on the Celtic keeper – after just one competitive game of the season! The 36-year-old 75 times-capped former England international No.1 hesitated for moment early in the Premiership opener against Ross County after a sloppy and careless passback from Anthony Ralston. It [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Strong, quick and comfortable"; Potential new signing seems to be exactly what Celtic need]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170439</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/strong-quick-and-comfortable-gustaf-lagerbielke-seems-to-be-exactly-what-celtic-need/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T05:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans have been offered some more insight on potential new signing Gustaf Lagerbielke. The 23-year-old Swedish central-defender looks like he could be the club’s...
The post "Strong, quick and comfortable"; Potential new signing seems to be exactly what Celtic need appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIG YOGI AND LISBON: THE TRUTH (Part Six)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=95333</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/big-yogi-and-lisbon-the-truth-part-six/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T04:45:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOHN ‘YOGI’ HUGHES played in five of Celtic eight ties during their great adventure that took Jock Stein’s team to the European Cup Final against Inter Milan in Lisbon on the unforgettable date of May 25 1967. The non-appearance of the iconic Hoops forward has been the subject of conjecture ever since. The goalscoring winger [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic target Gustaf Lagerbielke outshines Carl Starfelt in two areas]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43256</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/08/celtic-gustaf-lagerbielke-carl-starfelt/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T22:34:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carl Starfelt’s exit is still to be finalised but Celtic appear to be moving rapidly with an eye on replacing him in their squad. If rumours are accurate, then it seems as though Brendan Rodgers has his eye on another Swedish centre-back to take his place. There have even been suggestions that a £3 million […]
Celtic target Gustaf Lagerbielke outshines Carl Starfelt in two areas - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Journalist hands summer transfer blow to Celtic fans]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43272</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/08/journalist-hands-transfer-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T21:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a pretty stacked squad at the moment, but they could do with a few reinforcements. Most feel that the club have not properly replaced Jota, who left for Al-Ittihad earlier this summer. On the other hand, Carl Starfelt seems to be headed out as well and the Hoops will need to bring in […]
Journalist hands summer transfer blow to Celtic fans - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic must sign Real Madrid goalkeeper this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43267</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/08/celtic-must-sign-real-madrid-goalkeeper/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T19:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is no secret that Celtic could do with another goalkeeper at this point in time. Joe Hart is the number one for the Hoops at the moment and the Englishman deserves credit for the job that he has done since arriving in the summer of 2021. But at the same time, there are clear […]
Celtic must sign Real Madrid goalkeeper this summer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Furuhashi speaks about the affection shown to him by Celtic supporters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170398</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kyogo-furuhashi-speaks-about-the-affection-shown-to-him-by-celtic-supporters/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Kyogo Furuhashi signed his new contract at Celtic this summer, the supporters were overjoyed at the news. There was a fear that he could...
The post Kyogo Furuhashi speaks about the affection shown to him by Celtic supporters appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["We did some workshops"; Brendan Rodgers on the important relationships being built at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170417</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/we-did-some-workshops-brendan-rodgers-on-the-important-relationships-being-built-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has offered some insight in to some behind-the-scenes work Celtic carried out this summer. It’s been a busy old period for the first-team...
The post "We did some workshops"; Brendan Rodgers on the important relationships being built at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Club official confirms Celtic interest in £3 million player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43264</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/08/club-official-confirms-celtic-interest/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T18:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic must find a replacement for Carl Starfelt. It has become quite clear over the past week that the Swedish centre-back is on his way out of Parkhead. He has been a regular starter for the Hoops for the previous two seasons though and it does not feel like the club have anyone in their […]
Club official confirms Celtic interest in £3 million player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers' next matchday squad could be telling for one Celtic star]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170373</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/brendan-rodgers-next-matchday-squad-could-be-telling-for-one-celtic-star/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that the season is well and truly underway, the Celtic fans will be looking forward to every weekend with more gusto than they did...
The post Brendan Rodgers' next matchday squad could be telling for one Celtic star appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swedish football expert's glowing appraisal of reported Celtic target Gustaf Lagerbielke]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170394</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/swedish-football-experts-glowing-appraisal-of-reported-celtic-target-gustaf-lagerbielke/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s pursuit of Gustaf Lagerbielke is now well and truly underway. With the club reportedly already made an offer for the Swedish defender, it looks...
The post Swedish football expert's glowing appraisal of reported Celtic target Gustaf Lagerbielke appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The key Brendan Rodgers message that has offered fresh hope to unfancied Celtic stars]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170410</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-key-brendan-rodgers-message-that-has-offered-fresh-hope-to-unfancied-celtic-stars/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T16:18:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has been making a key point to his Celtic stars in his initial weeks at the club. Rodgers is firmly back in the...
The post The key Brendan Rodgers message that has offered fresh hope to unfancied Celtic stars appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[History repeats itself at the start of a new season for former Celtic ace Tom Rogic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170401</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/history-repeats-itself-at-the-start-of-a-new-season-for-former-celtic-ace-tom-rogic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T15:13:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic favourite Tom Rogic is still without a club as a brand new season gets underway. The Aussie magician, a modern-day icon at Celtic,...
The post History repeats itself at the start of a new season for former Celtic ace Tom Rogic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Exciting prospects"; Chris Sutton's verdict on two Celtic summer signings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170340</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/exciting-prospects-chris-suttons-verdict-on-two-celtic-summer-signings/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been extremely busy in this summer’s transfer window. With five new faces already added to the squad, we have had fleeting glimpses in...
The post "Exciting prospects"; Chris Sutton's verdict on two Celtic summer signings appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The latest on Celtic pursuit of Gustaf Lagerbielke as Elfsborg chief has his say]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170383</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/the-latest-on-celtics-pursuit-of-gustaf-lagerbielke-as-elfsborg-chief-has-his-say/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More details have emerged about Celtic’s interest in Swedish centre-back Gustaf Lagerbielke. We first heard of the Elfsborg defender on Monday evening, with an Expressen...
The post The latest on Celtic pursuit of Gustaf Lagerbielke as Elfsborg chief has his say appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic make enquiries for two players to replace Carl Starfelt]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43257</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/08/celtic-enquiries-two-players-starfelt/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T12:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This summer transfer window is proving to be a tough one for Celtic. The Hoops have already lost one starter in Jota, with the Portuguese winger leaving for Al-Ittihad last month. And now, the club seem to be on the verge of losing another key player from the Ange Postecoglou era, as Carl Starfelt is […]
Celtic make enquiries for two players to replace Carl Starfelt - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Furuhashi shares story of rallying support from his Celtic teammates after World Cup pain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170367</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kyogo-furuhashi-shares-story-of-rallying-support-from-his-celtic-teammates-after-world-cup-pain/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The story of Kyogo Furuhashi not making Japan’s World Cup squad for Qatar dominated the headlines in Scotland last winter. The Japanese striker was widely...
The post Kyogo Furuhashi shares story of rallying support from his Celtic teammates after World Cup pain appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Backfill defender first]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110825</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/backfill-defender-first/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T11:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers was a bit too relaxed looking when announcing the probable departure of Carl Starfelt this week.  You could interpret this as a sign the ‘news’ was not news to him and that a plan to accommodate was at a mature state. Reports from Sweden yesterday suggest we are interested in Gustaf Lagerbielke (23), [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic make enquiries for two centre-backs as Carl Starfelt exit nears]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170362</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-make-enquiries-for-two-centre-backs-as-carl-starfelt-exit-nears/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T10:58:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have made enquiries for two centre-backs with Carl Starfelt’s departure from the club nearing. The Swedish central-defender is set to join Spanish side Celta...
The post Report: Celtic make enquiries for two centre-backs as Carl Starfelt exit nears appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic man Olivier Ntcham finds new club after unsavoury weekend scenes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170343</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-man-olivier-ntcham-finds-new-club-after-unsavoury-weekend-scenes/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic midfielder Olivier Ntcham has found his next club. The French midfielder departed the Hoops for Swansea City right at the end of the...
The post Former Celtic man Olivier Ntcham finds new club after unsavoury weekend scenes appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confirmed: Match officials announced for Aberdeen v Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170345</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/confirmed-match-officials-announced-for-aberdeen-v-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T09:42:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s opening day 4-2 win over Ross County at Parkhead got Brendan Rodgers’ SPFL campaign off to a winning start at the weekend. A double...
The post Confirmed: Match officials announced for Aberdeen v Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Tuesday August 8: Getting Wind Of Change]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18447</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18447"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T09:29:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a few weeks without the pressure of having to qualify for the UCL, manager Brendan Rodgers seems to be ready to make the changes…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Malph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic eye transfer move for West Ham United striker]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43251</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/08/celtic-transfer-west-ham-united-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T09:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a couple of great options up top right now. Kyogo Furuhashi is the main man for the Hoops, coming off a 34-goal 2022/23 campaign. He has already opened his account this time around with a strike against Ross County on Flag Day. Oh Hyeon-gyu has been impressive as well, as he looks to […]
Celtic eye transfer move for West Ham United striker - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Gustaf Lagerbielke has said about his playing style as Celtic make their move]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170334</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/what-gustaf-lagerbielke-has-said-about-his-playing-style-as-celtic-make-their-move/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s reported interest in Gustaf Lagerbielke will have left the fans reaching for their phones and laptops in a bid to find out more about...
The post What Gustaf Lagerbielke has said about his playing style as Celtic make their move appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIRTHDAY BHOY AT CROSSROADS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110820</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/birthday-bhoy-at-crossroads/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T08:13:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIAM SCALES celebrates his 25th birthday today with his Celtic career at the crossroads. The versatile Republic of Ireland defender admitted he was in the dark about his immediate future at the treble winners, as CQN reported last month. Scales spent all of last season on loan at Aberdeen, coincidentally the Hoops’ Premiership opponents in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin O'Neill comments on Rodgers' Parkhead reception with words of advice to the Celtic boss]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170327</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/martin-oneill-comments-on-rodgers-parkhead-reception-with-words-of-advice-to-the-celtic-boss/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers’ first SPFL fixture since he returned to Celtic was one that was highly anticipated for two reasons. The first is that the fans...
The post Martin O'Neill comments on Rodgers' Parkhead reception with words of advice to the Celtic boss  appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC TREBLE TITLE-WINNER ON LOOK-OUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110813</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-treble-title-winner-on-look-out/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T07:32:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic treble title winner Gary Mackay-Steven is on the look-out for a new club – at the age of 32. The one-time Scotland international winger – capped twice – has been without a club since leaving Hearts at the end of his contract in May. A foot injury forced the tricky, ball-playing forward onto [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jan Aage Fjortoft explains how a Celtic legend helped mould his career]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170307</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/jan-aage-fjortoft-explains-how-celtic-legend-david-hay-moulded-his-career/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan Aage Fjortoft has opened up on how Celtic legend, David Hay, helped to mould his career when he was just a fresh-faced teenager. The...
The post Jan Aage Fjortoft explains how a Celtic legend helped mould his career appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Man of the match; first goal for new club, ex-Celtic youth delights his new manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170301</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/man-of-the-match-first-goal-for-new-club-ex-celtic-youth-delights-his-new-manager/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T06:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic youngster, Ewan Otoo got his season at his new club off to a flyer at the weekend with a Man of the Match...
The post Man of the match; first goal for new club, ex-Celtic youth delights his new manager appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£3m SWEDE ON THE BRINK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110809</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/3m-swede-on-the-brink/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T05:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have made a £3million offer for Swedish international centre-back Gustaf Lagerbielke, according to reports. The 23-year-old Elfsborg defender has been targeted by Brendan Rodgers as a replacement for Carl Starfelt who is expected to seal his exit this week in a £5million move to Celta Vigo. Lagerbielke is seen as one of Sweden’s top prospects [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Champions League side enquire about former Celtic man Kieran Tierney]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170316</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/champions-league-side-enquire-about-former-celtic-man-kieran-tierney/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T05:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A fresh report has linked former Celtic defender Kieran Tierney with a Champions League move. The Scotland international is set to enter European football’s premier...
The post Report: Champions League side enquire about former Celtic man Kieran Tierney appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Carl Starfelt's agent makes Sunday appearance for Celtic's benefit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170304</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/carl-starfelts-agent-makes-sunday-appearance-for-celtics-benefit/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T05:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic want to sign defender Gustaf Lagerbielke and Carl Starfelt’s agent has had a part to play, according to a report. On Monday evening, Swedish...
The post Report: Carl Starfelt's agent makes Sunday appearance for Celtic's benefit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIG YOGI AND LISBON: THE TRUTH (Part Five)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=95307</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/big-yogi-and-lisbon-the-truth-part-five/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T04:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE name of John Hughes was missing when Jock Stein named his Celtic line-up for the European Cup Final against Inter Milan in Lisbon on May 25 1967. The giant forward, lovingly known as ‘Yogi’ to his legions of fans, had played in five of the club’s eight ties during their great adventure to propel [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic submit £3 million bid for Carl Starfelt replacement]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43248</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/07/celtic-submit-bid-starfelt-replacement/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T22:34:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As news broke out that Carl Starfelt was set to leave the club this summer, Celtic seem to be wasting no time in trying to find a replacement for him. And it looks like the Hoops could be trying to replace the 28-year-old centre-back this summer with one of his Swedish international teammates. Starfelt has […]
Celtic submit £3 million bid for Carl Starfelt replacement - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player granted permission to complete Parkhead exit]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43243</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/07/celtic-player-permission-parkhead-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T21:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are expected to make a few more additions to Brendan Rodgers’ squad before the summer transfer window slams shut. On the other hand, players are continuing to leave the club as well. Some departures have gone under the radar while others have grabbed the headlines, like Jota leaving for Al-Ittihad. Unfortunately, it looks like […]
Celtic player granted permission to complete Parkhead exit - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic linked with move for Leicester City centre-back]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43238</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/07/celtic-leicester-city-centre-back/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T19:35:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are on the verge of losing one of their starting centre-backs in the form of Carl Starfelt. The Swede has been a nailed-on starter for the club over the past two seasons, playing his part in winning five trophies over that time. His run at Parkhead looks set to come to an end soon […]
Celtic linked with move for Leicester City centre-back - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Early days but recent arrival has made a positive Celtic impression; weekend moment - opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170282</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/early-days-but-maik-nawrocki-has-made-a-positive-celtic-impression-telling-weekend-moment/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maik Nawrocki may only have played 110 minutes for Celtic so far, but we’ve still learned a bit about him. The Polish defender made his...
The post Early days but recent arrival has made a positive Celtic impression; weekend moment - opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic interested in another Manchester City player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43235</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/07/celtic-interested-manchester-city-player-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T18:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quite a few players have made the move from Manchester City to Celtic over the years, either on loan or on a permanent basis. Even this summer, there have been several of the Treble winners’ youngsters, who have been linked with a switch to Parkhead. And now, it looks like it is time to add […]
Celtic interested in another Manchester City player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's early season schedule and 2022 inspiration offers a big opportunity - opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170292</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/celtics-early-season-schedule-and-2022-inspiration-offers-a-big-opportunity/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic won’t have to play two matches per week until the middle of September. With Champions League qualification already in the bag, and a return...
The post Celtic's early season schedule and 2022 inspiration offers a big opportunity - opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Get the whole place buzzing"; Celtic's unseen footage captures class Callum McGregor moment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170288</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/get-the-whole-place-buzzing-celtics-unseen-footage-captures-class-callum-mcgregor-moment/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whoever comes up with these ideas for Celtic should get a pay rise. The club have been heavily involved in giving fans some brilliant social...
The post "Get the whole place buzzing"; Celtic's unseen footage captures class Callum McGregor moment appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An interesting few weeks are ahead for Reo Hatate and Celtic - opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170268</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/an-interesting-few-weeks-are-ahead-for-reo-hatate-and-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It will be interesting to see how things go for both Reo Hatate and Celtic over the coming weeks. The Japan international was a surprise...
The post An interesting few weeks are ahead for Reo Hatate and Celtic - opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton praises 'brave' Brendan Rodgers for Celtic return; addresses weekend fan reception]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170265</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-praises-brave-brendan-rodgers-for-celtic-return-addresses-weekend-fan-reception/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers’ Celtic return was one that came out of the blue for many supporters and one that still touched a raw nerve. Even for...
The post Chris Sutton praises 'brave' Brendan Rodgers for Celtic return; addresses weekend fan reception appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic 'interested' in talented England u21 international]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170249</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-hold-interest-in-talented-manchester-city-youth-prospect/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T13:44:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been listed with a number of clubs in England as holding an interest in young England u21 international, Jason McAtee. At just 20...
The post Report: Celtic 'interested' in talented England u21 international appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic the major contributors as the SPFL release good news from opening weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170248</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-the-major-contributors-as-the-spfl-release-more-good-crowd-news/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were the major contributors as the SPFL released some more good crowd news after the opening weekend of the season. The Premiership, Championship, League...
The post Celtic the major contributors as the SPFL release good news from opening weekend appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BULLY FOR YOU, DAVID]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110806</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/bully-for-you-david/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T13:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAVID TURNBULL celebrated his first start for Celtic in nine months with two goals in the 4-2 opening-day win over Ross County at Parkhead at the weekend. Matt O’Riley is not surprised by the impact of his team-mate who claimed the champions’ first goal of the new campaign with a sweetly-taken penalty-kick in the 17th [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SPFL newcomer's intriguing comments on family link with ex-Celtic hero Artur Boruc]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170235</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/spfl-newcomers-intriguing-comments-on-family-link-with-ex-celtic-hero-artur-boruc/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Max Boruc signed for Hibs earlier this summer, a lot was made in the media about his family link to former Celtic star, Artur...
The post SPFL newcomer's intriguing comments on family link with ex-Celtic hero Artur Boruc appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Champions League picture becomes clearer after Monday draw]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170231</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-champions-league-picture-becomes-clearer-as-qualifying-draw-is-completed/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The draw for UEFA Champions League qualification was concluded on Monday morning, as Celtic continue to watch on. As you’ll know, Celtic have already secured...
The post Celtic Champions League picture becomes clearer after Monday draw appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC 13 SECONDS FROM PERFECT GOAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110801</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-13-seconds-from-perfect-goal/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T12:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BLINK and you might have missed Celtic just failing to claim a contender for Goal of the Season just 86 minutes into the new campaign. The champions were leading 4-1 at the time courtesy of a double from David Turnbull – the first from the penalty spot – and others from Kyogo Furuhashi and Matt [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic keeper assessed after winning debut at new club]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170221</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/conor-hazards-debut-assessed-as-ex-celtic-keeper-gets-off-to-a-winning-start-at-new-club/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic goalkeeper, Conor Hazard, made his debut for Plymouth Argyle this weekend. The Northern Ireland international got off to a winning start and impressed...
The post Ex-Celtic keeper assessed after winning debut at new club appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Celtic require from the final four weeks of the transfer window - opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170224</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/what-celtic-require-from-the-final-four-weeks-of-the-transfer-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T11:44:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The transfer window has just shy of four weeks to run, and Celtic have business to do. The club have signed five new players so...
The post What Celtic require from the final four weeks of the transfer window - opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic goalkeeper completes eventful one-game loan]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43229</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/07/celtic-goalkeeper-one-game-loan/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T11:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a stacked squad at this point in time. Naturally, not everyone is expected to get first-team chances. For some, it is best to leave the club on a permanent basis. On the other hand, for youngsters, loan moves away can be beneficial for their future and help them come to grips with the […]
Celtic goalkeeper completes eventful one-game loan - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo, Maik, Carl]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110800</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kyogo-maik-carl/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T11:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was quite a fascinating weekend in the Scottish Premiership.  Celtic started the action by labouring before taking the lead and moving into cruise control against Ross County.  St Mirren bookended the action by scoring a 95th minute winner at Easter Road.  Motherwell rode their luck to earn a point at Dundee, St Johnstone continued [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New summer signing's absence being felt as former manager makes Celtic admission]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170216</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/maik-nawrockis-absence-being-felt-as-former-manager-makes-celtic-admission/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The signing of Maik Nawrocki this summer already seems like a great piece of business by Brendan Rodgers. The Polish defender already seems to have...
The post New summer signing's absence being felt as former manager makes Celtic admission appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HARTACHE? KEEPER FACES MAKE-OR-BREAK 24 DAYS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110797</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hartache-keeper-faces-make-or-break-24-days/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T09:46:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART has provided a fair bit of ammunition for the snipers who believe he should be replaced as the No.1 Celtic keeper. The 36-year-old 75 times-capped England international was not convincing in the champions’ 4-2 opening-day victory over Ross County at the weekend. Hart will not need CQN or anyone else to emphasise that point. A [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Irony alert as Ibrox figure talks up away fans at Celtic derbies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170205</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/irony-alert-as-ibrox-figure-talks-up-away-fans-at-celtic-derbies/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Bisgrove has amusingly been talking up the importance of away supporters at Celtic vs Rangers matches. The Ibrox chief executive has been in the...
The post Irony alert as Ibrox figure talks up away fans at Celtic derbies appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O'Riley star explains the Kyogo 'adaptation' that Celtic's midfield are exploiting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170202</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/matt-oriley-explains-the-kyogo-tweak-that-celtics-midfield-are-exploiting/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Flag Day opening win for Celtic over Ross County was literally a game of two halves, in the first half! In the opening 20...
The post Matt O'Riley star explains the Kyogo 'adaptation' that Celtic's midfield are exploiting appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O'Riley predicts a big season ahead for rejuvenated Celtic midfielder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170198</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/matt-oriley-predicts-a-big-season-ahead-for-rejuvenated-celtic-midfielder/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Turnbull’s return to a Celtic shirt this preseason and for the SPFL curtain raiser has been a sight for sore eyes for this Hoops...
The post Matt O'Riley predicts a big season ahead for rejuvenated Celtic midfielder appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic plan to replace Carl Starfelt]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43225</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/07/brendan-rodgers-celtic-replace-starfelt/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T08:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past few days, it has become pretty clear that Carl Starfelt will be on his way out of Celtic this summer. The Swede has been a key part of this team since he arrived in 2021 and was a major part of their successes under the management of Ange Postecoglou, winning five out […]
Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic plan to replace Carl Starfelt - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Young Celtic prospect praised despite emergency loan debut defeat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170191</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/young-celtic-prospect-josh-clarke-praised-despite-emergency-loan-debut-defeat/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T07:42:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic got back into the swing of things with their 4-2 win over Ross County at Celtic Park on Flag Day to get the defence...
The post  Young Celtic prospect praised despite emergency loan debut defeat appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HAKSABANOVIC MYSTERY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110792</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/haksabanovic-mystery-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T07:38:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SEAD HAKSABANOVIC was the Celtic matchwinner the last time Ross County featured at Parkhead in November last year. This time around, there was no sign of the Montenegro international winger as the champions claimed an opening-day 4-2 triumph. Haksabanovic, who arrived in a cut-price £1.8million switch from Rubin Kazan in August last year, wasn’t even [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I am grateful"; Celtic star thinks Brendan Rodgers is now playing him in his best position and role]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170187</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/matt-oriley-grateful-brendan-rodgers-is-now-playing-him-in-his-favourite-celtic-position-and-role/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last couple of months, no one has sounded happier with Brendan Rodgers coming into the club than Matt O’Riley and that trend has...
The post "I am grateful"; Celtic star thinks Brendan Rodgers is now playing him in his best position and role appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I NEED TO BE A BIT MORE SELFISH,’ O’RILEY IGNORES PASS MARKS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110788</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-need-to-be-a-bit-more-selfish-oriley-ignores-pass-marks/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T06:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY almost uprooted the net and goalposts with his pulverising piledriver that left Ross County keeper Ross Laidlaw motionless as he sealed Celtic’s opening-day 4-2 triumph. It was an emphatic finish from the midfield mastermind’s so-called weaker foot and was one of the highlights as Brendan Rodgers’ men got their bid for a twelfth [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Monday August 7: Monday Morning Sure Looks Fine]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18443</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18443"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T06:21:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And we’re off.     Scottish football roared back onto the scene over the weekend, and as is usually the case, there were a few…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Malph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What referee told Ross County star about Celtic Park penalty flashpoint]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170182</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/what-referee-nick-walsh-told-ross-county-star-about-celtic-park-penalty-flashpoint/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T06:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ross County forward Simon Murray is convinced he should have had a penalty against Celtic, despite replays showing that he was barely touched by goalkeeper...
The post What referee told Ross County star about Celtic Park penalty flashpoint appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I am happy for him"; Celtic star addresses imminent teammate exit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170177</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/me-carl-and-jota-were-quite-close-matt-oriley-addresses-celtic-transfer-exits/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T05:30:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder Matt O’Riley is experiencing his closest friends leaving the club but reckons change is part of football and has to be embraced. Jota...
The post "I am happy for him"; Celtic star addresses imminent teammate exit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIG YOGI AND LISBON: THE TRUTH (Part Four)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=95194</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/big-yogi-and-lisbon-the-truth-part-four/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T04:45:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOHN ‘YOGI’ HUGHES played in five of Celtic’s eight ties during their great adventure that took Jock Stein’s team to the European Cup Final against Inter Milan in Lisbon on the unforgettable date of May 25 1967. The non-appearance of the iconic Hoops forward has been the subject of conjecture ever since. The goalscoring winger [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>