<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-08-28T20:10:31.853Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic linked with move for England youth international]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43731</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/28/celtic-linked-move-england-youth/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T19:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already signed a couple of centre-backs this summer in the form of Maik Nawrocki and Gustaf Lagerbielke, while Carl Starfelt departed the club. But the Hoops might still need to add another central defender to their ranks before the transfer window slams shut, as that position has been hurt the most by injuries. […]
Celtic linked with move for England youth international - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable journalist hints at future Celtic announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43728</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/28/journalist-future-celtic-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T17:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are rumoured to be looking to add as many as five players over the course of the last few days of the ongoing summer transfer window. Thus, plenty of fresh faces could walk in through the Parkhead door soon. Who those players might be remains a mystery as there are not many concrete links […]
Reliable journalist hints at future Celtic announcement - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The David Potter Archives – Potters Players – Joe Cassidy]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58303</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/the-david-potter-archives-potters-player-joe-cassidy/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T15:08:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Cassidy was a Celtic hero at a time when they needed heroes. The years immediately after the Great War were dire with poverty and so many families lacking a bread winner. Joe first appeared before the Great War but did not feature much. In the war, he won the Military Medal with the Black […]
The post The David Potter Archives – Potters Players – Joe Cassidy appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic linked with late move for Manchester City player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43725</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/28/celtic-late-move-manchester-city-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T13:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are expected to be very busy over the last few days of the summer transfer window. Of course, this is not the position they would have wanted to be in. But the circumstances have made it necessary. The Hoops have looked a shell of their treble-winning selves from last season and it is very […]
Celtic linked with late move for Manchester City player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC PAIR AXED]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111443</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-pair-axed/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T11:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC defenders Anthony Ralston and Greg Taylor have been axed from the Scotland squad for next month’s double-header against Cyprus and England. International boss Steve Clarke has overlooked the Hoops full-backs while skipper Callum McGregor is the solitary player from the champions who is included in the 25-man pool for the games in Larnaca and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Current Celtic issue is not managerial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111441</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/current-celtic-issue-is-not-managerial/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T11:04:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hindsight and all that, but looking back, Celtic’s form slipped in mid-April this year.  We were imperious until that point, but even wins, like the Scottish Cup semi-final win over Newco, were not as impressive than the League Cup Final win over the same opponents a few weeks earlier. The season petered out amid home [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic make early morning double exit announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43722</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/28/celtic-make-double-exit-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T10:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are expected to be pretty busy over the next few days. The club clearly need to bring in reinforcements after they have stumbled out of the gates in the 2023/24 season. Brendan Rodgers’ side are already out of the Scottish League Cup and recently dropped points at home in the Premiership against a St […]
Celtic make early morning double exit announcement - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LUIS PALMA: BYE, BUY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111438</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/luis-palma-bye-buy/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T07:46:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC-BOUND Luis Palma has been sent best wishes by his Aris Thessaloniki boss as he prepares to join the champions in a £4million switch. The Honduran international winger, 23, will undergo the formality of a medical before signing a five-year deal with the Hoops. Palma will become the Parkhead side’s seventh signing of the summer with [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KT NO GO: WHY IT’S SOCIEDAD AND NOT CELTIC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111435</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kt-no-go-why-its-sociedad-and-not-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T06:24:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KIERAN TIERNEY will be playing in the blue and white stripes of Real Sociedad in La Liga in the new season. You get the impression the Scotland international might just have preferred to be wearing the green and white hoops of Celtic in the Premiership. Alas, a year-long loan deal from Arsenal for the one-time [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Man City, Bayern, PSG: Which teams could Celtic get in the Champions League Group Stage?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171778</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/champions-league-group-stage-draw-23-24-which-teams-could-celtic-face/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T05:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Which teams could Celtic face in the Champions League Group Stage for the 23/24 season? Celtic are in the Champions League once again. After Ange...
The post Man City, Bayern, PSG: Which teams could Celtic get in the Champions League Group Stage? appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kieran Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano drops Celtic news ahead of deadline day]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43719</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/27/fabrizio-romano-celtic-news-deadline-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-27T22:30:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans will be nervous going into the last few days of the summer transfer window. There is still a lot of work to be done if the Hoops are to be competitive this season because, to be honest, they have looked anything but that. The supporters will be hoping that we see a repeat […]
Fabrizio Romano drops Celtic news ahead of deadline day - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luis Palma to Celtic transfer confirmed by Aris FC manager]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43714</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/27/luis-palma-celtic-transfer-confirmed/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-27T20:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are expected to remain very busy over the final few days of the summer transfer window. Of course, this is a worrying situation to be in. Ideally, you would want to bring in players as early as possible and have them settled in by the time the season starts. Clearly, things have not played […]
Luis Palma to Celtic transfer confirmed by Aris FC manager - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed double transfer blow before deadline day]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43709</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/27/celtic-double-transfer-deadline-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-27T19:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are looking towards arguably their most important week of the season. They are set to take on the Rangers away at Ibrox in the first Glasgow Derby of the campaign next weekend. But before that, they have a few days to make sure that they adequately strengthen their squad. Because as things stand, this […]
Celtic handed double transfer blow before deadline day - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: One of Celtic's promising summer targets now has a preferred destination]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172487</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-and-james-mcatee-relationship-looking-less-likely-with-his-preferred-destination-named/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-27T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It looks less likely that James McAtee will be playing at Celtic on loan, or otherwise, this season after the latest news from down in...
The post Report: One of Celtic's promising summer targets now has a preferred destination appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed transfer boost ahead of deadline day]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43706</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/27/celtic-transfer-ahead-deadline-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-27T17:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are days away from the end of the summer transfer window. The time has simply flown by but Celtic still find themselves with a lot of work to do. Over the first four games of the season, it has become quite clear that this team is nowhere near good enough to be competing against […]
Celtic handed transfer boost ahead of deadline day - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Lyanco link already over as defender makes Qatar switch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172490</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-and-lyanco-link-already-over-as-defender-makes-qatar-switch/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-27T17:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic won’t be signing Southampton defender Lyanco this summer after Qatari club Al Gharafa announced he has landed in Doha to sign for them. The...
The post Celtic and Lyanco link already over as defender makes Qatar switch appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star dishes out some honesty and concedes there's an AngeBall hangover at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172425</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/daizen-maeda-honestly-concedes-hes-suffering-from-an-angeball-hangover-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-27T16:24:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic attacker Daizen Maeda has admitted he is not on top form right now, laying out his reasons with some honest comments about the transition...
The post Celtic star dishes out some honesty and concedes there's an AngeBall hangover at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC LEGENDS IN HIBS BOSS LINK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111432</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-legends-in-hibs-boss-link/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-27T15:23:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legends Scott Brown and Neil Lennon have been linked with the Hibs manager’s job after Lee Johnson’s sacking today. The Easter Road club are on the look-out for a new boss after the 3-2 loss at home to Livingston which followed on the 5-0 home Europa League Conference first-leg drubbing from Aston Villa. Former [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic rack up 9 goals in another smashing Sunday SWPL win; Champions League soon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172479</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/celtic-rack-up-9-goals-in-another-smashing-sunday-swpl-win-champions-league-soon/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-27T15:08:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic FC Women’s incredibly strong start to the SWPL season continued at home today with a 9-0 thrashing of Dundee United. Maria McAneny, Natalie Ross,...
The post Celtic rack up 9 goals in another smashing Sunday SWPL win; Champions League soon appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton sends message to Celtic player about controversial post]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43697</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/27/chris-sutton-celtic-player-post/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-27T12:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are expected to make plenty of additions to the squad over the last few days of the summer transfer window because it has become quite clear that this team does not have enough quality at the moment. On the other hand, it looks like some players might be on the verge of leaving the […]
Chris Sutton sends message to Celtic player about controversial post - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[98 Minutes of Frustration at Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58294</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/98-minutes-of-frustration-at-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-27T12:24:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I described the performance last week against Kilmarnock as poor and the word frustration comes to mind after sitting through 98 minutes yesterday at Celtic Park. The highlight of last weeks game in Kilmarnock was my first visit to the Peter Scarf CSC club house in Linwood before and after the game. The committee members […]
The post 98 Minutes of Frustration at Celtic Park appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Tell him': Chris Sutton sends a blunt message to Haksabanovic after Celtic star's IG post]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172449</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-sends-a-blunt-message-to-sead-haksabanovic-after-celtic-stars-instagram-post/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-27T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton has told Sead Haksabanovic that he is ‘out of order’ for publicly expressing his discontent after an apparent dig at his current situation...
The post 'Tell him': Chris Sutton sends a blunt message to Haksabanovic after Celtic star's IG post appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pat Bonner says fans were getting ‘frustrated’ with Celtic 25-year-old v St Johnstone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172432</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/pat-bonner-says-fans-were-getting-frustrated-with-celtic-25-year-old-v-st-johnstone/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-27T10:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pat Bonner has shared how the Celtic fans were getting ‘frustrated’ with Liam Scales during the goalless draw at home to St Johnstone on Saturday....
The post Pat Bonner says fans were getting ‘frustrated’ with Celtic 25-year-old v St Johnstone appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HAKSABANOVIC’S STARK MESSAGE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111424</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/haksabanovics-stark-message/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-27T09:50:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SEAD HAKSABANOVIC has sparked transfer speculation following a stark message on Instagram. The Celtic winger has yet to start a first-team game this season and has taken to social media to publish an image with the words: “If they don’t see your value maybe you’re not in the right place.” Haksabanovic was snubbed from the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou signing appears to drop clear Celtic exit hint]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43694</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/27/ange-signing-celtic-exit-hint/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-27T09:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic find themselves in a pretty bad spot right now. Last weekend, they were knocked out of the Scottish League Cup at the hands of Kilmarnock, evaporating all hopes of winning a treble once again this season. Naturally, fans would have been looking for a response when they took on St Johnstone at Parkhead in […]
Ange Postecoglou signing appears to drop clear Celtic exit hint - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE STRIFE O’RILEY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111421</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-strife-oriley/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-27T09:27:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY had FOUR excellent chances to score the crucial breakthrough goal against St Johnstone – and blew the lot. The classy midfielder claimed a meagre four strikes last season, but had hit half that total already in the first two league games this time out with efforts in the wins over Ross County (4-2) [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star stirs the pot with pointed social media post; last thing fans need]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172427</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/if-they-dont-see-your-value-sead-haksabanovic-stirs-the-pot-with-pointed-celtic-instagram-post/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-27T08:56:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic attacker Sead Haksabanovic has appeared to take a dig at those in control of his current situation at the club with a post on...
The post Celtic star stirs the pot with pointed social media post; last thing fans need appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘WE NEED TO IMPROVE,’ BRENDAN EYES TRANSFER RAID]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111420</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/we-need-to-improve-brendan-eyes-transfer-raid/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-27T08:46:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LUIS PALMA is likely to be unveiled within the next 48 hours as Celtic’s SEVENTH signing of the summer. And Brendan Rodgers revealed he needs to bring in more new faces before Thursday’s midnight deadline. Palma is on his way to the champions after his Greek club Aris Thessaloniki agreed a fee in the region [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I've a feeling"; Gary Hooper goes against the grain with Brendan Rodgers and Celtic prediction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172422</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ive-a-feeling-gary-hooper-goes-against-the-grain-with-brendan-rodgers-and-celtic-prediction/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-27T08:32:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Hooper certainly isn’t paying heed to any recent Celtic anxiety. He reckons the Bhoys will have a strong end to the transfer window and,...
The post "I've a feeling"; Gary Hooper goes against the grain with Brendan Rodgers and Celtic prediction appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Dalglish calls for Celtic action and insists club have cash to "make something happen"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172417</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kenny-dalglish-calls-for-celtic-action-and-insists-club-have-cash-to-make-something-happen/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-27T08:03:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Dalglish is expecting and hoping that Celtic pull the finger out in the closing week of the transfer window to start delivering the signings...
The post Kenny Dalglish calls for Celtic action and insists club have cash to "make something happen" appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers names two positives from another damaging Celtic weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172411</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-names-two-positives-from-another-damaging-celtic-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-27T07:12:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans are waking up from disappointment the day before for the second successive week and it’s not the place many of us envisioned we’d...
The post Brendan Rodgers names two positives from another damaging Celtic weekend appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I spoke to the club"; Brendan Rodgers puts transfer ball in Celtic board's court]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172408</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/i-spoke-to-the-club-brendan-rodgers-puts-transfer-ball-in-celtic-boards-court/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-27T06:41:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers says he has made it clear to the club that quality is needed in his Celtic team as the Bhoys enter a critical...
The post "I spoke to the club"; Brendan Rodgers puts transfer ball in Celtic board's court appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘CERTAINLY A CONCERN,’ RODGERS’ IBROX ADMISSION]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111386</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/certainly-a-concern-rodgers-ibrox-admission/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-27T06:22:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS admits he is worried ahead of the first derby of the season at Ibrox a week today. The manager saw his team fire blanks for the second successive game as they limped through an uninspired scoreless stalemate against St Johnstone at Parkhead yesterday. The frustrating performance came just six days after the wretched [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player wants to draw Real Madrid again for one reason]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43688</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/26/celtic-player-draw-real-madrid-reason/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T22:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic faced Real Madrid in a couple of memorable games last season. In the first half of the Parkhead match, the Hoops were certainly the better side and should have gone into the break a couple of goals up, if they had taken their chances. At the end of the night, that ended up costing […]
Celtic player wants to draw Real Madrid again for one reason - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou mentions Celtic player in Tottenham presser]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43684</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/26/ange-celtic-player-tottenham-presser/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T20:30:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur have made a flying start to the season and Ange Postecoglou seems to be enjoying life in the Premier League. With a win over Manchester United already in the bag, the Australian has quickly gone from ‘unknown’ to one of the managers to watch out for. Of course, it will come as no […]
Ange Postecoglou mentions Celtic player in Tottenham presser - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers responds to Celtic fans’ boos at full-time]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43681</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/26/brendan-rodgers-celtic-fans-boos/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T19:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Scottish Premiership had been somewhat of a walk in the park for Brendan Rodgers. Every Celtic fan will remember the Invincible season. Well, things are not going as smoothly for the Northern Irish manager this time around. In fact, he already finds himself under quite a bit of pressure. After Celtic were knocked out […]
Brendan Rodgers responds to Celtic fans’ boos at full-time - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Stewart delivers verdict on sluggish Celtic & "deliberate, loaded" comments from Rodgers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172405</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/michael-stewart-delivers-verdict-on-sluggish-celtic-and-deliberate-loaded-comments-from-brendan-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T18:20:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Stewart reckons Brendan Rodgers has been sending out a pretty deliberate message regarding transfers at Celtic this summer and thinks the Bhoys are in...
The post Michael Stewart delivers verdict on sluggish Celtic & "deliberate, loaded" comments from Rodgers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Green Brigade make a strong derby statement on a disappointing afternoon at Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172392</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-green-brigade-make-a-strong-derby-statement-on-a-disappointing-afternoon-at-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Green Brigade had something to say about next week’s derby at Ibrox on an afternoon to forget at Celtic Park. Two Premiership points were...
The post The Green Brigade make a strong derby statement on a disappointing afternoon at Celtic Park appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This week will make or break Celtic’s 23/24 season]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43676</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/26/week-make-break-celtic-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T17:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All of the positivity that was there surrounding Brendan Rodgers’ return to Celtic has evaporated completely just three weeks into the season. After being knocked out of the Scottish League Cup in the second round at the hands of Kilmarnock, fans would have been expecting a statement performance from the Hoops. Instead, they got a […]
This week will make or break Celtic’s 23/24 season - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers responds to chorus of Celtic Park boos after draw against St Johnstone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172402</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-responds-to-chorus-of-celtic-park-boos-after-draw-against-st-johnstone/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T16:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers understands why Celtic fans expressed their dissatisfaction with today’s events at Celtic Park, feeling that the performance was not up to par. There...
The post Brendan Rodgers responds to chorus of Celtic Park boos after draw against St Johnstone appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers reacts to disappointing day of dropped points at Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172390</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-reacts-to-disappointing-day-of-dropped-points-at-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T16:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s malaise continued today, failing to break down a determined St Johnstone side and only managing a 0-0 result at home in the Scottish Premiership....
The post Brendan Rodgers reacts to disappointing day of dropped points at Celtic Park appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC 0 ST JOHNSTONE 0: SLOPPY HOOPS FIRE BLANKS AGAIN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111379</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-0-st-johnstone-0-sloppy-hoops-fire-blanks-again/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T15:59:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC 0 ST JOHNSTONE 0 SLIPSHOD Celtic fired blanks for the second successive week to drop two unexpected points against the Perth Saints at Parkhead this afternoon. It was a disappointing confrontation the champions dominated, but their accuracy in finishing was simply awful and unacceptable as they toiled to get the ball in the opposition [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic v St Johnstone, GG Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111376</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-st-johnstone-gg-live-updates/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T13:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 15:00.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: JOHNSTON BACK IN SHAKE-UP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111377</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-johnston-back-in-shake-up/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T12:57:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ALISTAIR JOHNSTON makes a surprise return to first-team action as Celtic prepare to face St Johnstone at Parkhead this afternoon. The Canadian World Cup right-back has missed the opening three games of the season with an ankle problem, but gets the green light from Brendan Rodgers to make his comeback against the Perth club. South Korean [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic XI confirmed: Big return, first start, TV details, instant reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172384</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-vs-st-johnstone-confirmed-big-return-first-start-tv-details-instant-reaction/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T12:51:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manager Brendan Rodgers has named his Celtic team vs St Johnstone for today’s Scottish Premiership clash at Celtic Park. The full match squad is as...
The post Celtic XI confirmed: Big return, first start, TV details, instant reaction appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five signings Celtic want to make this week named]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43673</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/26/five-signings-celtic-want-make/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T12:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are set to have a very busy end to the summer transfer window. Of course, that is never the ideal situation to be in. The club have already added six new faces to their squad but despite that, Brendan Rodgers’ side have not looked anywhere near up to par in the first few weeks […]
Five signings Celtic want to make this week named - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Makes me smile"; Joe Hart brings up 2021 injury adversity that offers Celtic important lesson]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172377</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/makes-me-smile-joe-hart-brings-up-2021-injury-adversity-that-offers-celtic-important-lesson/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T11:40:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart has a positive outlook on Celtic’s current injury situation. The Celtic goalkeeper is likely to have an unsettled defence ahead of him for...
The post "Makes me smile"; Joe Hart brings up 2021 injury adversity that offers Celtic important lesson appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improved Celtic Park experience highlighted in neat club video; more work to be done]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172370</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/improved-celtic-park-experience-highlighted-in-neat-club-video-more-work-to-be-done/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T10:50:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The improved Celtic Park matchday experience has been highlighted in a neat video posted by the club on social media. The three-minute video is likely...
The post Improved Celtic Park experience highlighted in neat club video; more work to be done appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luis Palma's father shares the latest on big summer move and it's good news for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172364</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/luis-palmas-father-shares-the-latest-on-big-summer-move-and-its-good-news-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T09:42:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enrique Palma — the father of Luis — has shared the latest on the winger’s proposed move to Celtic. Honduran international Palma seems increasingly likely...
The post Luis Palma's father shares the latest on big summer move and it's good news for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic linked with Southampton’s Brazilian defender]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43669</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/26/celtic-southampton-brazilian-defender/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T09:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to strengthen in multiple positions across the pitch right now. One of them is centre-back. That was not expected to be the case. While Carl Starfelt did leave the club, they brought in a couple of new players there in the form of Gustaf Lagerbielke and Maik Nawrocki. They are struggling with a […]
Celtic linked with Southampton’s Brazilian defender - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major return, 4 changes, fringe player's big chance: Celtic team news and Predicted XI vs Saints]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172360</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/johnston-fringe-chance-4-changes-celtic-team-news-and-predicted-xi-vs-st-johnstone/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T08:40:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today’s Celtic match at home to St Johnstone in the Scottish Premiership presents the perfect opportunity for the Bhoys to bounce back from last week’s...
The post Major return, 4 changes, fringe player's big chance: Celtic team news and Predicted XI vs Saints appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star Reo Hatate brought up during Ange Postecoglou press conference]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172354</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-star-reo-hatate-brought-up-during-ange-postecoglou-press-conference/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T07:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star Reo Hatate got a mention from his former boss Ange Postecoglou on Friday. The Japanese midfielder starred for 18 months under the Australian,...
The post Celtic star Reo Hatate brought up during Ange Postecoglou press conference appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic stalwart responds brilliantly as "crisis" talk is put to him in the media]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172340</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/joe-hart-responds-brilliantly-as-celtic-crisis-talk-gets-a-strange-outing-in-the-media/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic goalkeeper Joe Hart gave a brilliant response as the word “crisis” was put to him in the media. The former England international has had...
The post Celtic stalwart responds brilliantly as "crisis" talk is put to him in the media appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I FEAR FOR CELTIC,’ SUTTON’S URGENT CALL TO RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111365</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-fear-for-celtic-suttons-urgent-call-to-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T06:47:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has five days to work overtime in the transfer market to strengthen his Celtic squad. And former Hoops goal hero Chris Sutton reckons the Parkhead gaffer might need to bring in FIVE new players in a frantic search for top talent. The one-time England international forward also insists the recruits should be ready [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Kano Foundation will celebrate a major milestone at Celtic Park today]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172349</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-kano-foundation-will-celebrate-a-major-milestone-at-celtic-park-today/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T06:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Kano Foundation will celebrate a major milestone at Celtic Park on Saturday. The volunteer-run charity have been bringing kids along to Celtic matches since...
The post The Kano Foundation will celebrate a major milestone at Celtic Park today appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart discusses the possibility of Celtic signing a new goalkeeper; his natural Hoops ending]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172332</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/joe-hart-discusses-the-possibility-of-celtic-signing-a-new-goalkeeper-his-natural-hoops-ending/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart has been speaking about the possibility of Celtic signing a new goalkeeper this summer. The goalkeeping position has been much talked about amongst...
The post Joe Hart discusses the possibility of Celtic signing a new goalkeeper; his natural Hoops ending appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Lyanco pops up for Celtic and the club have a clear centre-back plan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172326</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/lyanco-pops-up-for-celtic-and-the-club-have-a-clear-centre-back-plan/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic would prefer to sign a centre-back on loan in the final week of the transfer window, according to a report. Brendan Rodgers and the...
The post Report: Lyanco pops up for Celtic and the club have a clear centre-back plan appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC v ST JOHNSTONE: 5-MINUTE QUIZ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111356</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-st-johnstone-5-minute-quiz-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T04:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC faced St Johnstone three times last season and won the lot with 10 goals scored and three conceded. How much can you remember about recent encounters against the Perth club? Have a go on CQN’s fun five-minute quiz to test your knowledge. QUESTIONS: 1: Who was the stoppage-time goal hero as the Hoops grabbed [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: CELTIC’S EXTRAVAGANT WASTE OF TIME AND MONEY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111355</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-celtics-extravagant-waste-of-time-and-money/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-26T04:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WHAT is the point of Albian Ajeti? As the clocks throughout Europe tick down towards Thursday’s midnight transfer deadline, there is the mandatory frenzy of activity in the pulsating market place, fraught with anxiety, as the wheeling and dealing goes into overdrive. Stressed-out managers sift through an avalanche of possible purchases as they belatedly attempt [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic linked with Ipswich Town left-back with 14 assists]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43663</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/25/celtic-linked-ipswich-town-left-back/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T22:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are expected to make quite a few signings over the last week of the summer transfer window. One of the areas where they clearly need to improve is left-back. Greg Taylor was outstanding there during the time of Ange Postecoglou as manager. He has not thrived under the management of Brendan Rodgers yet. On […]
Celtic linked with Ipswich Town left-back with 14 assists - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers has his say on controversial Rugby Park incident]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172320</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-has-his-say-on-controversial-rugby-park-incident/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T20:43:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There were lots of talking points coming out of last weekend’s defeat to Kilmarnock in the Scottish League Cup, not least Celtic’s poor performance and...
The post Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers has his say on controversial Rugby Park incident appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic reject transfer bid for key player from Serie A club]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43648</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/25/celtic-reject-transfer-bid-key-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T20:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are keen to get a few more quality players in before the summer transfer window ends. But there is also a fear that the Hoops may see existing top-quality and starting players leave before then too. There’s been concern all summer over whether Reo Hatate may be subject to a transfer bid but the […]
Celtic reject transfer bid for key player from Serie A club - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic v St. Johnstone Matchday Minizine]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58287</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-v-st-johnstone-matchday-minizine/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T18:45:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Click into image to download the Celtic v St. Johnstone Matchday Minizine. Hit subscribe to get matchday edition in your inbox everytime
The post Celtic v St. Johnstone Matchday Minizine appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen McGowan reports Celtic transfer ambition in final week of window]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172315</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/stephen-mcgowan-reports-celtic-transfer-ambition-in-final-week-of-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T18:40:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are looking to follow up the signing of Luis Palma from Aris FC in Greece with a number of other transfers before the end...
The post Stephen McGowan reports Celtic transfer ambition in final week of window appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur player on loan would be perfect for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43656</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/25/tottenham-hotspur-player-loan-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T18:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic find themselves in a very difficult position right now. We are just three games into the season and they already have a substantial injury list. So much so that they might need to start players who would have been at the bottom of the pecking order in their respective positions if everybody was fit […]
Tottenham Hotspur player on loan would be perfect for Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emilio Izaguirre helps seal imminent Celtic transfer despite lucrative offers elsewhere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172311</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/emilio-izaguirre-helps-seal-imminent-celtic-transfer-despite-lucrative-offers-elsewhere/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T17:59:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Incoming Celtic signing Luis Palma sought out a recommendation from popular former Bhoys star Emilio Izaguirre before deciding Scotland was the place for him, The...
The post Emilio Izaguirre helps seal imminent Celtic transfer despite lucrative offers elsewhere appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need a big performance tomorrow at Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58283</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-need-a-big-performance-tomorrow-at-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T17:40:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic players should be chomping at the bit to get back on the pitch and put last week’s very poor performance behind them. Thankfully Brendan Rodgers offered no excuses last Sunday in his post interviews although I’m sure he had a few in the back of his mind having not only witnessed his players […]
The post Celtic need a big performance tomorrow at Celtic Park appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Brendan We Trust – Lisbon Lion John Fallon]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58277</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/in-brendan-we-trust-lisbon-lion-john-fallon/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T17:15:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello troops and welcome to another of my takes on all things Celtic. Here we are at the start of what we hope will be another successful season. Little did we think a couple of months ago, that we would have a new manager in place for the start of the season and undergoing a […]
The post In Brendan We Trust – Lisbon Lion John Fallon appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dominik Livakovic officially exits Dinamo Zagreb after summer of Celtic links; achievable fee]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172305</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/dominik-livakovic-officially-exits-dinamo-zagreb-after-summer-of-celtic-links-achievable-fee/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T17:10:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It had become apparent in recent weeks that Celtic’s links to goalkeeper Dominik Livakovic would not amount to anything, but he has now officially made...
The post Dominik Livakovic officially exits Dinamo Zagreb after summer of Celtic links; achievable fee appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incoming Celtic signing says goodbye to current teammates; Bhoys will change his life with wages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172301</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/incoming-celtic-signing-luis-palma-says-goodbye-to-current-teammates-bhoys-will-change-his-life-with-wages/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T16:32:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Incoming Celtic signing Luis Palma has reportedly said his goodbyes to Aris FC teammates in Greece as he prepares to make the big move to...
The post Incoming Celtic signing says goodbye to current teammates; Bhoys will change his life with wages appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic make transfer breakthrough; Bhoys in final stages of next summer signing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172294</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-make-transfer-breakthrough-bhoys-in-final-stages-of-next-summer-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T15:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have agreed a fee with Greek club Aris FC for winger Luis Palma, it has been reported this afternoon. Sky Sports journalist Anthony Joseph...
The post Celtic make transfer breakthrough; Bhoys in final stages of next summer signing appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic agree deal for seventh signing of the summer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43654</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/25/celtic-agree-deal-seventh-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T15:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic appear to be very busy as we enter the final week of the summer transfer window. There have been suggestions that the club could make three to five signings over the coming days, and the first one of them does not seem to be far away. The Hoops needed to bring in another winger […]
Celtic agree deal for seventh signing of the summer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers shares how long Celtic cup regret lasted; why it differs from supporters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172287</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-shares-how-long-celtic-cup-regret-lasted-why-it-differs-from-supporters/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers reckons the disappointment he feels from Celtic losses lasts around 24 hours. Rodgers hasn’t had too many tough defeats as Celtic manager. Sunday’s...
The post Brendan Rodgers shares how long Celtic cup regret lasted; why it differs from supporters appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£4m PALMA ON BRINK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111358</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/4m-palma-on-brink/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T13:47:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC target Luis Palma is on the brink of a £4million move to the champions. The Honduran winger is expected to become the Hoops’ seventh summer signing after his Greek club Aris Thessaloniki reportedly accepted an enhanced offer from last season’s treble-winners. The 23-year-old international was allowed to sit out training today and is likely to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans can watch former player take on mammoth Real Madrid challenge on Friday night]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172264</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-fans-can-watch-former-player-take-on-mammoth-real-madrid-challenge-on-friday-night/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic defender Carl Starfelt is set to face the mammoth task of Real Madrid on Friday evening. The Swedish defender’s Celta Vigo side host...
The post Celtic fans can watch former player take on mammoth Real Madrid challenge on Friday night appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player close to leaving and joining Serie A club]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43652</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/25/celtic-player-close-leaving-serie-club/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T12:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic rumour mill has been dominated by news of potential incomings over the past few days and understandably so. It is believed that the club could still make as many as five new signings, as they need a goalkeeper, a left-back, a winger, a centre-forward and a centre-back. At the same time, there could […]
Celtic player close to leaving and joining Serie A club - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Team looking like strangers needs time on the pitch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111354</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/team-looking-like-strangers-needs-time-on-the-pitch/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T11:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Picking up maximum points this early in the season when you are joint top of the table alongside St Mirren does not always induce angst.  Immediately after a chastening defeat, things are different.  Celtic slid from control to crisis within 90 minutes last weekend and must collect full points tomorrow to steady our communal nerves. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss confirms the Alistair Johnston news we all wanted to hear; Kilmarnock decision]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172274</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-boss-confirms-the-alistair-johnston-news-we-all-wanted-to-hear-kilmarnock-decision/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T10:42:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston is fit and available for Celtic again this weekend. The Hoops return to Celtic Park on Saturday, looking to make amends for last...
The post Celtic boss confirms the Alistair Johnston news we all wanted to hear; Kilmarnock decision appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Ryan Fraser situation reaches a resolution following Celtic links]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172280</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/ryan-fraser-situation-reaches-a-resolution-following-celtic-links/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T09:33:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent Celtic target Ryan Fraser has agreed a loan switch to Southampton, according to a report. Sky Sports reporter Keith Downie says that the Scotland...
The post Report: Ryan Fraser situation reaches a resolution following Celtic links appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss discusses Luis Palma, Reo Hatate and Liel Abada media reports]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172247</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-discusses-luis-palma-reo-hatate-and-liel-abada-media-reports/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has been asked about a number of important recent Celtic media reports. It’s been a busy old period of Celtic news with players...
The post Celtic boss discusses Luis Palma, Reo Hatate and Liel Abada media reports appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Journalist drops Celtic transfer hint as target misses training]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43644</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/25/journalist-celtic-transfer-hint-training/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T09:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic look set to be active over the final week of the summer transfer window. The club have made six new signings this time around but are still in need of reinforcements in multiple areas across the pitch. The situation is not ideal but hopefully, the Hoops will be able to make the most of […]
Journalist drops Celtic transfer hint as target misses training - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IN SQUAD WE TRUST: RODGERS’ POSITIVE SIGNS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111351</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/in-squad-we-trust-rodgers-positive-signs/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T08:23:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS reckons Celtic will be STRONGER than last season’s treble-winning squad – after the transfer deadline is passed at midnight on Thursday. The second time-around Hoops manager agrees the champions are weaker at the moment than the previous campaign, but hopes to turn that around after some frantic wheeling and dealing within the next six days. Rodgers [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC BRACED FOR O’RILEY MEGABID]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111348</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-braced-for-oriley-megabid/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T07:48:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is bracing himself for a megabid for Matt O’Riley before the midnight transfer deadline on Thursday. Celtic have just knocked back an undisclosed offer from Bologna for the smooth playmaker who was snapped up for a bargain £1.5million from English third-tier club MK Dons in January 2022. The champions were quick to kick [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tony Mowbray makes a definitive statement about the chances of Patrick Roberts joining Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172257</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/tony-mowbray-makes-a-definitive-statement-about-the-chances-of-patrick-roberts-signing-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T07:43:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sunderland manager Tony Mowbray has made a definitive statement amid Celtic links to Patrick Roberts. As we covered on Sunday, Roberts has once again leapt...
The post Tony Mowbray makes a definitive statement about the chances of Patrick Roberts joining Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Wolves make their move in Daniel Podence situation and Celtic talk isn't going away]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172227</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/wolves-make-their-move-in-daniel-podence-situation-and-celtic-talk-isnt-going-away/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T06:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wolves have placed winger Daniel Podence on their transfer list, according to a report, as the Celtic talk continues. Podence has been mentioned as a...
The post Report: Wolves make their move in Daniel Podence situation and Celtic talk isn't going away appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘WE’RE GOING TO HAVE TO RE-JIG,’ HART ON THE CHANGING OF THE GUARD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111346</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/were-going-to-have-to-re-jig-hart-on-the-changing-of-the-guard/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T06:24:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART has spent his first two years at Celtic mainly playing behind the central defensive partnership of Cameron Carter-Vickers and Carl Starfelt. After only three games into the new season, the 36-year-old 75 times-capped England international keeper has performed with THREE different pairs of players directly in front of him. In the opening encounter [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic act decisively after European side submit bid for first-team star]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172239</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-act-quickly-after-surprise-matt-oriley-bid-but-story-may-not-be-over/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T06:12:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have acted decisively to reject a bid for first-team star Matt O’Riley, according to a report. The Denmark youth international has been a Celtic...
The post Report: Celtic act decisively after European side submit bid for first-team star appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Wolves make their move in Daniel Podence situation and Celtic talk isn't going away]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172227</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172227"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T06:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wolves have placed winger Daniel Podence on their transfer list, according to a report, as the Celtic talk continues. Podence has been mentioned as a...
The post Report: Wolves make their move in Daniel Podence situation and Celtic talk isn't going away appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I’m not going to beat about the bush"; Brendan Rodgers' frank Celtic message]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172233</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/im-not-going-to-beat-about-the-bush-brendan-rodgers-frank-celtic-squad-message/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T05:41:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers isn’t trying to kid on the Celtic support about the strength of the current Hoops team. It’s been a hectic few months at...
The post "I’m not going to beat about the bush"; Brendan Rodgers' frank Celtic message appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Positive Celtic picture developing as telling decision is made over transfer target]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172220</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/positive-celtic-picture-developing-as-telling-luis-palma-decision-is-made-in-greece/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T05:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A positive picture seems to be developing for Celtic in their pursuit of Aris Thessaloniki winger Luis Palma. The Honduras international is a name that...
The post Report: Positive Celtic picture developing as telling decision is made over transfer target appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[58 YEARS AGO: WIN THAT SPARKED FIRST 9 IN A ROW]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=95893</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/58-years-ago-win-that-sparked-first-9-in-a-row/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T04:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EXACTLY 58 years ago today, Johnny Divers accepted a pass from Joe McBride and drilled a shot behind Dundee United keeper Donald Mackay. It was the 15th minute of the opening league game of the 1965/66 season on August 25 1965 and it paved the way for a 4-0 victory at Tannadice. The strike from Divers [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou signing wants to leave Celtic this week]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43640</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/24/ange-postecoglou-signing-celtic-week/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T22:30:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are now in the final week of the summer transfer window and this one is going to be vital for Celtic. The Hoops have made a lethargic start to the season and appear to be in need of some creativity up front as well as some defensive solidity at the back. Hopefully, reinforcements will […]
Ange Postecoglou signing wants to leave Celtic this week - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I have been impressed’: Peter Grant reacts to suggestion Celtic should sign Aberdeen star]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172197</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/i-have-been-impressed-peter-grant-reacts-to-suggestion-celtic-should-sign-aberdeen-star/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T21:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant has played down the suggestion that Celtic should sign Aberdeen striker, Bojan Miovski. Kyogo Furuhashi is the main man up top for Celtic...
The post ‘I have been impressed’: Peter Grant reacts to suggestion Celtic should sign Aberdeen star appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[David Ornstein reports disappointing transfer news for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172195</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/david-ornstein-reports-disappointing-kieran-tierney-news-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T20:45:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arsenal defender Kieran Tierney is on the brink of a season-long loan move to La Liga side Real Sociedad, ending any Celtic hope of landing...
The post David Ornstein reports disappointing transfer news for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers now seeing "outstanding" signs in Celtic training after difficult week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172192</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-now-seeing-outstanding-signs-in-celtic-training-after-difficult-week/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T20:29:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s no doubt it’s been a difficult week for Celtic. A defeat, cup exit, question marks about the club’s transfer business and more injuries than...
The post Brendan Rodgers now seeing "outstanding" signs in Celtic training after difficult week appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eric Dier’s stance hands late transfer hope to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43637</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/24/eric-dier-stance-late-transfer-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T20:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eric Dier is one of the players that Celtic have been linked with in recent weeks. At first glance, the rumours seem far-fetched and a move to Parkhead seems pretty unlikely for the England international. But when you consider the circumstances, of both the player and the clubs, it might make a lot of sense. […]
Eric Dier’s stance hands late transfer hope to Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Great energy"; New Celtic signing makes a positive first impression behind scenes at Lennoxtown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172160</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/gustaf-lagerbielke-makes-a-positive-first-celtic-impression-behind-the-scenes-at-lennoxtown/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T19:12:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gustaf Lagerbielke is quickly showing positive traits to key Celtic men such as Brendan Rodgers and Joe Hart behind the scenes at Lennoxtown – and...
The post "Great energy"; New Celtic signing makes a positive first impression behind scenes at Lennoxtown appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Hartson reacts to claim Celtic’s 2023 transfer window has been ‘abysmal’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172162</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/john-hartson-reacts-to-claim-celtics-2023-transfer-window-has-been-abysmal/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Hartson has defended Celtic’s 2023 summer transfer business so far and disagreed that it has been ‘abysmal’. The Celtic legend shared his thoughts on...
The post John Hartson reacts to claim Celtic’s 2023 transfer window has been ‘abysmal’ appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports man names four signings Celtic want to make]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43633</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/24/sky-sports-man-four-signings-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T18:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With just another week left in the summer transfer window, Celtic are expected to be busy. It is never ideal to make signings at the last stages but then a combination of injuries and bad planning have led them here. Over the past three matches of the season, it has become pretty evident that the […]
Sky Sports man names four signings Celtic want to make - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic now identifying "magic" in closing stages of summer transfer window]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172155</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-now-identifying-magic-in-closing-stages-of-summer-transfer-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T17:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers is confident the club will do business in the final week of the summer transfer window, suggesting that they are looking...
The post Celtic now identifying "magic" in closing stages of summer transfer window appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms fringe player will get an opportunity at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172139</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-confirms-fringe-player-will-get-an-opportunity-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[News of Celtic’s defensive injury crisis has spread like wildfire today. With Brendan Rodgers confirming that Cameron Carter-Vickers and Maik Nawrocki will be out for...
The post Brendan Rodgers confirms fringe player will get an opportunity at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers' intriguing new answer on Celtic transfer target as his club take firm stance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172146</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-intriguing-thursday-answer-on-kieran-tierney-as-celtic-hero-is-frozen-out-at-arsenal/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T16:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers wouldn’t be drawn on specific Celtic links to Arsenal defender Kieran Tierney today but did say that the left-back will want to be...
The post Brendan Rodgers' intriguing new answer on Celtic transfer target as his club take firm stance appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Owen Moffat rocks up at surprising Scottish club one year on from Celtic departure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172095</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/owen-moffat-rocks-up-at-surprising-scottish-club-one-year-on-from-celtic-departure/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic youngster Owen Moffat is looking for his next club. The 21-year-old departed the Hoops for a move to Blackpool almost exactly a year...
The post Owen Moffat rocks up at surprising Scottish club one year on from Celtic departure appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disappointing Hatate blow as Celtic boss provides return timelines for Oh, Kobayashi, Johnston]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172136</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/disappointing-hatate-news-as-rodgers-provides-celtic-return-timelines-for-oh-kobayashi-johnston/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T15:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alongside previous updates on Cameron Carter-Vickers and Maik Nawrocki, Brendan Rodgers has also confirmed that Reo Hatate will be missing for Celtic’s upcoming derby clash....
The post Disappointing Hatate blow as Celtic boss provides return timelines for Oh, Kobayashi, Johnston appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic duo will miss Glasgow Derby]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43629</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/24/brendan-rodgers-celtic-duo-glasgow-derby/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T15:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been handed one injury blow after another another at the start of the 2023/24 campaign. This is not the start that Brendan Rodgers would have been hoping for. Not only are several key players out on the sidelines but the Hoops are already out of the Scottish League Cup as well. Unfortunately, there […]
Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic duo will miss Glasgow Derby - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BAD TIMING: RODGERS FAVOURITE SET FOR UNITED]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111328</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/bad-timing-rodgers-favourite-set-for-united/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T14:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JONNY EVANS, who played for Brendan Rodgers at Leicester City, is poised to agree with a one-year deal at Manchester United. The 35-year-old Northern Ireland international centre-back could have been a player to answer an SOS from the Celtic manager. Rodgers revealed earlier today that Cameron Carter-Vickers and Maik Nawrocki will both be out for [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eric Dier's Spurs stance could come at a crucial time for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172134</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/eric-diers-spurs-stance-could-come-at-a-crucial-time-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T14:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will still be reeling from the news that Cameron Carter-Vickers and Maik Nawrocki are set to miss two months of the season due to...
The post Eric Dier's Spurs stance could come at a crucial time for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart shares the story from inside the Celtic camp after damaging weekend loss]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172108</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/joe-hart-shares-the-story-from-inside-the-celtic-camp-after-damaging-kilmarnock-loss/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart has been speaking about the Celtic camp’s reaction to Sunday’s cup loss to Kilmarnock. It was an afternoon to forget for Brendan Rodgers‘...
The post Joe Hart shares the story from inside the Celtic camp after damaging weekend loss appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic transfer re-assessment in final days of window]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172110</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-confirms-celtic-transfer-re-assessment-in-final-days-of-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T13:45:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has confirmed the club will be looking at the central defensive position in the final days of the transfer window after...
The post Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic transfer re-assessment in final days of window appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC DOUBLE SETBACK: CCV AND NAWROCKI OUT EIGHT WEEKS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111317</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-double-setback-ccv-and-nawrocki-out-eight-weeks/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T13:45:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have been dealt a severe double injury setback with Cameron Carter-Vickers AND Maik Nawrocki ruled out for TWO months. It’s a massive blow for Brendan Rodgers who will also be without back-up central defender Stephen Welsh for three to four months after a freak training ground accident on Friday. The Hoops will now move [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms bitter Celtic injury blows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172106</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-confirms-bitter-celtic-injury-blows/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T13:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has confirmed that Cameron Carter-Vickers and Maik Nawrocki will be out for a prolonged period of time. The Celtic manager has confirmed that...
The post Brendan Rodgers confirms bitter Celtic injury blows appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Door open as exciting Celtic transfer target now not even training with first team]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172097</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-will-be-watching-as-kieran-tierney-now-not-even-included-in-arsenal-training/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T12:40:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kieran Tierney is increasingly finding himself on the sidelines at Arsenal after it was reported he is now not even taking part in Mikel Arteta’s...
The post Door open as exciting Celtic transfer target now not even training with first team appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good signs for Rodgers and Celtic as we all prepare for a different feeling this weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172082</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/good-signs-for-rodgers-and-celtic-as-we-all-prepare-for-a-different-feeling-this-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T12:10:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will be aiming for a big response this weekend against St. Johnstone. It’s been a fair old period of time since there was a...
The post Good signs for Rodgers and Celtic as we all prepare for a different feeling this weekend appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic talks for seventh signing of the summer confirmed]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43626</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/24/celtic-talks-seventh-signing-summer/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T12:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been pretty busy during the course of the summer transfer window. While fans are not happy with the lack of big-name, experienced and established additions, the Hoops have brought in six new players to the club regardless. They are Odin Thiago Holm, Marco Tilio, Yang Hyun-jun, Kwon Hyeok-kyu, Maik Nawrocki and Gustaf Lagerbielke. […]
Celtic talks for seventh signing of the summer confirmed - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Celtic have done the right thing"; ex-Hoops hero backs high-profile transfer exit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172078</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-have-done-the-right-thing-ex-hoops-hero-backs-high-profile-transfer-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s transfer business has come under scrutiny over the past few days amid the current injury crisis and the team’s current performances. The club have...
The post "Celtic have done the right thing"; ex-Hoops hero backs high-profile transfer exit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: European side eye Jota move; could team up with a few familiar Celtic names]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172073</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/european-side-eye-jota-move-could-team-up-with-a-few-familiar-celtic-names/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T11:13:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic winger Jota is a target for Fenerbahce, according to a report. Turkish outlet Sporx say that the Super Lig side are ready to...
The post Report: European side eye Jota move; could team up with a few familiar Celtic names appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Helicoptering in central defenders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111315</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/helicoptering-in-central-defenders/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T11:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I know we are all concerned about the injury crisis affecting central defence, but it is difficult to move the dial here in the short term.  Central defence is overwhelmingly about partnerships.  You can try to helicopter someone into the team (think Carl Starfelt two years ago) but it seldom provides an immediate return. If [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant pinpoints the one tactic that is causing Celtic creative problems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172069</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/peter-grant-pinpoints-the-one-tactic-that-is-causing-celtic-creative-problems/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were, and still are, under the microscope this week after the club’s exit from the league cup against Kilmarnock. The 1-0 defeat ended Brendan...
The post Peter Grant pinpoints the one tactic that is causing Celtic creative problems appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O'Riley offers some sound reasoning for Celtic's early season form]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172065</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/matt-oriley-offers-some-sound-reasoning-for-celtics-early-season-form/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s early season form has been a little inconsistent, shall we say? Despite two wins the SPFL, the team hasn’t quite the heights of performance...
The post Matt O'Riley offers some sound reasoning for Celtic's early season form appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Thursday August 24: We Have Stopped]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18465</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18465"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T09:21:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a crisis looming in the centre of the Celtic defence, the board have swung into action and made a bid for Honduran winger Luis…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Malph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic face another battle with Saudi Arabian cash in fresh transfer pursuit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172038</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-face-another-battle-with-saudi-arabian-cash-in-fresh-transfer-pursuit/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic could face another battle with Saudi Arabian cash in their pursuit of Luis Palma. Earlier on Thursday we told you about our fresh move...
The post Report: Celtic face another battle with Saudi Arabian cash in fresh transfer pursuit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Women are flying as Fran Alonso's side lay down early season marker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172061</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/celtic-women-are-flying-as-fran-alonsos-side-lay-down-early-season-marker/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Away from the trials and tribulations that face Brendan Rodgers for a minute, Celtic Women are flying this season as Fran Alonso‘s side continues their...
The post Celtic Women are flying as Fran Alonso's side lay down early season marker appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic close to next signing after making €4.1 million bid]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43620</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/24/celtic-close-next-signing-million-bid/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T08:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic could certainly do with more reinforcements before the summer transfer window slams shut. Their performances over the first three games of the season have shown that this side is missing a creative spark at the moment. They were not able to score against Kilmarnock and got knocked out of the Scottish League Cup in […]
Celtic close to next signing after making €4.1 million bid - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>