<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-07-10T18:12:45.082Z</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-07-10T18:12:45.082Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moussa Dembele’s Sell On Clause]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/moussa-dembeles-sell-on-clause/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/moussa-dembeles-sell-on-clause/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T17:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MOUSSA DEMBELE could be on his way to the Premier League this summer, but it’s not great news for Celtic,. The bhoys sold Moussa for a record fee at the time [£21m] to French side Lyon but also added a sell-on clause. The Hoops always look to get a little extra out of their top […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Ledley makes class Celtic prediction that will be tough for rivals to hear]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/joe-ledley-makes-class-celtic-prediction-that-will-be-tough-for-rivals-to-hear/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/joe-ledley-makes-class-celtic-prediction-that-will-be-tough-for-rivals-to-hear/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T17:26:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Ledley thinks Kyogo Furuhashi is going to be even better for Celtic over the coming season than he was last term, greatly praising the Japanese sensation. The Welshman also thinks this special group are going to win the title again. Kyogo made a wonderful impact at the Bhoys in his debut campaign, arriving last ...
The post Joe Ledley makes class Celtic prediction that will be tough for rivals to hear appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Double Injury Boost: Ange Clears Up Weekend Mystery]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/double-injury-boost-ange-clears-up-weekend-mystery/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/double-injury-boost-ange-clears-up-weekend-mystery/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T17:17:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU has delivered a double injury boost for Celtic fans ahead of the next phase of pre-season. The Hoops played out a 3-3 draw against Rapid Vienna on Saturday but did so without Josip Juranovic or Anthony Ralston. Ange allowed Osaze Urhoghide to play at right back in their absence but the defender didn’t […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fringe player praised by Postecoglou after Austria shift]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/osaze-urhoghide-praised-by-celtic-boss-after-austria-shift/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/osaze-urhoghide-praised-by-celtic-boss-after-austria-shift/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T16:48:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Osaze Urhoghide has had a surprisingly prominent role to play in Celtic’s opening pre-season games, being the only player who has completed both 90 minutes against Wiener Viktoria and Rapid Vienna. Urhoghide has been primarily used as a right-back over both games but also slotted in as a centre-back when Christopher Jullien went off against ...
The post Celtic fringe player praised by Postecoglou after Austria shift appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou provides injury update after Saturday Celtic absences]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-provides-injury-update-after-saturday-celtic-absences/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-provides-injury-update-after-saturday-celtic-absences/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T16:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou has provided an update on Anthony Ralston and Josip Juranovic after they were missing from Saturday’s match squad against Rapid Vienna. The Bhoys boss named almost the entire Austrian group on the bench behind the starters in the 3-3 draw, but the two right-backs were not listed, leading to concerns about ...
The post Ange Postecoglou provides injury update after Saturday Celtic absences appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manage expectations as outlets get excited about weekend transfer update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/ange-postecoglou-manages-expectations-on-celtics-latest-transfer-bid/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/ange-postecoglou-manages-expectations-on-celtics-latest-transfer-bid/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T15:46:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has made it clear that Celtic’s reported bid for Dylan Reid is not relevant in terms of strengthening the first team this summer. Football Scotland has reported that Celtic have had a £125,000 offer accepted for the St Mirren talent, who is still just 17. There’s an expectation other teams could make bids ...
The post Celtic manage expectations as outlets get excited about weekend transfer update appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Aribo Transfer Fee Has Sparked Panic At Ibrox And Led To A Major Strategic Error.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/the-aribo-transfer-fee-has-sparked-panic-at-ibrox-and-led-to-a-major-strategic-error/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/the-aribo-transfer-fee-has-sparked-panic-at-ibrox-and-led-to-a-major-strategic-error/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T15:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you believe what you read in the papers, all is well inside Ibrox and nobody is worried at all. Players are being brought in. Negotiations are underway. The media is presenting a picture of calm over there. It is, as usual, covering a multitude of issues. Ibrox’s transfer policy has failed, and failed utterly. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Player Who Should Be Moved On This Summer]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-player-who-should-be-moved-on-this-summer/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-player-who-should-be-moved-on-this-summer/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T14:38:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re not in the business of looking for negatives when it comes to Celtic. We are a fan media site who always want to be supportive of the club and the players. However, we’re not the Celtic View and when there’s something up for discussion we won’t shy way from it. There are fans out […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banik Ostrava captain hypes up Wednesday&#039;s Celtic clash; strong crowd and atmosphere expected]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/banik-ostrava-captain-hypes-up-wednesdays-celtic-clash-strong-crowd-and-atmosphere-expected/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/banik-ostrava-captain-hypes-up-wednesdays-celtic-clash-strong-crowd-and-atmosphere-expected/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Banik Ostrava are expecting a strong crowd for Wednesday night’s clash at home to Celtic, with captain Jan Lastuvka predicting it will be “a real feast” for those in attendance. Celtic have been invited by the Czech club as part of their centenary celebrations and ticket sales have been strong for the encounter. The fixture ...
The post Banik Ostrava captain hypes up Wednesday&#039;s Celtic clash; strong crowd and atmosphere expected appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rapid 3-3 Celtic - Goals &amp; Reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.jerseydoesntshrink.com/2022/7/10/23202647/rapid-3-3-celtic-goals-reaction</id>
        <link href="https://www.jerseydoesntshrink.com/2022/7/10/23202647/rapid-3-3-celtic-goals-reaction"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T12:14:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Craig Williamson/SNS Group via Getty Images
  

 The hoops second pre season game this summer resulted in an entertaining 3-3 draw with Rapid Vienna. 
Here’s the goals in case you missed them:

Not a lot to take away from games like this where it’s all about fitness, but it was good to see Hatate, O’Riley and Kyogo looking sharp, and it’s good of Joseph Hart to get the blunders out the way now before the domestic campaign kicks off.
There was an immediate reaction to the match on 67HH yesterday which you can find below!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Celtic Will Always Have The Edge Over Our Rivals In The Transfer Market Gold Rush.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/why-celtic-will-always-have-the-edge-over-our-rivals-in-the-transfer-market-gold-rush/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/why-celtic-will-always-have-the-edge-over-our-rivals-in-the-transfer-market-gold-rush/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T12:11:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, the Ibrox club made it known that John Park is now working for them. I wrote a piece on that where I pointed out that our fans would not be losing sleep over it. Today Keevins has written about it in his column; he seems to think it’s a masterstroke. But once again, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Offer accepted: Celtic close to signing £225k-rated gem for Ange; he&#039;s &#039;excellent on the ball&#039;]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-dylan-reid-transfer-gossip-news/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-dylan-reid-transfer-gossip-news/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T11:35:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have had a bid accepted for St Mirren youngster Dylan Reid, according to a report from Football Scotland.  The lowdown: Hot prospect Part of the academy system in Paisley, the 17-year-old made a professional debut for the Premiership side in March 2021 against the Hoops’ Old Firm rivals having just turned 16. Soon after, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘PERFECT TEST,’ ADMITS O’RILEY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/perfect-test-admits-oriley/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/perfect-test-admits-oriley/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T11:02:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY marked his first appearance since the middle of May with the opening goal in Celtic’s 3-3 draw with Rapid Vienna in the Allianz Stadium. The cultured playmaker, who was excused pre-season traiing at Lennoxtown the previous week after Under-21 international duty with Denmark, curled in the opener during his 45-minute outing, as CQN [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judas Day of Infamy – A despicable deed done to hurt Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/judas-day-of-infamy-a-despicable-deed-done-to-hurt-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/judas-day-of-infamy-a-despicable-deed-done-to-hurt-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T10:28:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maurice Johnston was born in Glasgow on 13 April 1963. He began his career at Partick Thistle in 1981, scoring 41 goals in 85 appearances, before winning a transfer to Elton John’s Watford in 1983. Johnston scored 23 league goals in English football, made his international debut, and helped the team reach 1984 FA Cup Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor Drops Title Winning Mask]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/callum-mcgregor-drops-title-winning-mask/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/callum-mcgregor-drops-title-winning-mask/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T10:20:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor played his first match since February without his now trademark protective face mask. The Celtic Captain marched on last season after a very significant cheekbone injury suffered during a Scottish Cup tie. Celtic supporters have grown to love the Celtic Captain’s mask and his performances in it. Not long after Callum sustained the […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer news as Malick Thiaw pushed towards Schalke exit and Ismaila Soro breaks silence after move - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiENkyEglnpryrqXqv3aMT2VQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/celtic-transfer-news-malick-thiaw-27442571"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T08:32:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer news as Malick Thiaw pushed towards Schalke exit and Ismaila Soro breaks silence after move  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers and the transfer bravado is back in Celtic 'tenners' game - Hugh Keevins - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEH2vTT4YqiZ5mwO-W4RUJMUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/rangers-transfer-bravado-making-comeback-27439186"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers and the transfer bravado is back in Celtic 'tenners' game - Hugh Keevins  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Graeme Souness Rangers mantra Gio van Bronckhorst MUST heed to win title back from Celtic - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEMObup3DTx5S6xTsQ-RU2LwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/graeme-souness-rangers-mantra-gio-27440008"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Graeme Souness Rangers mantra Gio van Bronckhorst MUST heed to win title back from Celtic  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dylan Reid’s Celtic transfer offer confirmed as Ange Postecoglou urges patience over further moves - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>1488230735</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/dylan-reids-celtic-transfer-offer-24447507"/>
        <updated>2022-07-09T21:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dylan Reid’s Celtic transfer offer confirmed as Ange Postecoglou urges patience over further moves  Football Scotland
Dylan Reid in Celtic vs Rangers transfer battle as Ange Postecoglou confirms bid for St Mirren starlet  Daily Record
Celtic transfer update with Hoops interest in Premiership starlet confirmed and bid 'accepted'  Glasgow Live
Offer Accepted; Celtic Closing in On Midfield Signing  CeltsAreHere
CELTIC TRANSFER UPDATE AS ANGE CONFIRMS MIDFIELDER BID  Scotzine
View Full coverage on Google News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ismaila Soro seals Celtic transfer exit as FC Arouca announce loan with option to buy - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEE5PGvT7_DgU7rEcgUmtjZ0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-transfer-news/ismaila-soro-seals-celtic-transfer-27441297"/>
        <updated>2022-07-09T20:37:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ismaila Soro seals Celtic transfer exit as FC Arouca announce loan with option to buy  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Six Goals, Lots Of Fouls And A Few Celtic Players With Questions To Answer. - TheCelticBlog.com]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEPe9ee9cRJKxcIQPF2mSHUoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowne-jCzDg-bsDMLnLhQc</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/six-goals-lots-of-fouls-and-a-few-celtic-players-with-questions-to-answer/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-09T19:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Six Goals, Lots Of Fouls And A Few Celtic Players With Questions To Answer.  TheCelticBlog.com]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rapid Vienna 3 Celtic 3 RECAP as Hoops held in six goal thriller in Austria - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CBMiX2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvcmFwaWQtdmllbm5hLXZzLWNlbHRpYy1saXZlLTI3NDM3NTg30gFjaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZGFpbHlyZWNvcmQuY28udWsvc3BvcnQvZm9vdGJhbGwvZm9vdGJhbGwtbmV3cy9yYXBpZC12aWVubmEtdnMtY2VsdGljLWxpdmUtMjc0Mzc1ODcuYW1w</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/rapid-vienna-vs-celtic-live-27437587"/>
        <updated>2022-07-09T17:56:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rapid Vienna 3 Celtic 3 RECAP as Hoops held in six goal thriller in Austria  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer news LIVE as Rangers and Celtic plus Aberdeen, Hearts and Hibs eye signings - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CBMibmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLXRyYW5zZmVyLW5ld3MvdHJhbnNmZXItbmV3cy1saXZlLWNlbHRpYy1yYW5nZXJzLTI3NDM2OTM20gEA</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-transfer-news/transfer-news-live-celtic-rangers-27436936"/>
        <updated>2022-07-09T17:07:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer news LIVE as Rangers and Celtic plus Aberdeen, Hearts and Hibs eye signings  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Davie Robb and 1976 - afc.co.uk]]></title>
        <id>CBMiNWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmFmYy5jby51ay8yMDIyLzA3LzA5L2RhdmllLXJvYmItYW5kLTE5NzYv0gEA</id>
        <link href="https://www.afc.co.uk/2022/07/09/davie-robb-and-1976/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-09T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Davie Robb and 1976  afc.co.uk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Celtic’s midfield general and patter merchant mic’d up at training - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiENWXgFIh2Ztzpvsh83E1ZO8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-celtics-midfield-general-and-patter-merchant-micd-up-at-training/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-09T10:48:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Celtic’s midfield general and patter merchant mic’d up at training  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Miller in furious reaction as Rangers striker clashes with Celtic hero Rab Douglas during Masters derby - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CBMiaWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3Mva2VubnktbWlsbGVyLWZ1cmlvdXMtcmVhY3Rpb24tcmFuZ2Vycy0yNzQzNjE0NdIBAA</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/kenny-miller-furious-reaction-rangers-27436145"/>
        <updated>2022-07-08T21:07:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Miller in furious reaction as Rangers striker clashes with Celtic hero Rab Douglas during Masters derby  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jordan Larsson ‘in contact’ with Celtic over potential transfer - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEO6GbMVkrywyV5pRKpRYCX4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPPfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/jordan-larsson-in-contact-celtic-24442192"/>
        <updated>2022-07-08T18:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jordan Larsson ‘in contact’ with Celtic over potential transfer  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vinicius Souza's Celtic transfer decision ripple effect as Espanyol loan pushes Mohammad Abu Fani up wishlist - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEFF1FA6IBDBrfT9wW-Vw7zMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/vinicius-souzas-celtic-transfer-decision-27435191"/>
        <updated>2022-07-08T18:01:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vinicius Souza's Celtic transfer decision ripple effect as Espanyol loan pushes Mohammad Abu Fani up wishlist  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou swerves Rangers transfer 'trap' as Celtic learn lessons from title defence misstep - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEOAirRzW54QvTuKjHN5goEkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/ange-postecoglou-swerves-rangers-transfer-27434636"/>
        <updated>2022-07-08T16:57:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou swerves Rangers transfer 'trap' as Celtic learn lessons from title defence misstep  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reuben McAllister agrees Hibs transfer despite Celtic, Aston Villa and Newcastle United interest - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEOs4BYslZkrn1-keiJNGHYoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPPfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/reuben-mcallister-agrees-hibs-transfer-24436270"/>
        <updated>2022-07-08T12:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reuben McAllister agrees Hibs transfer despite Celtic, Aston Villa and Newcastle United interest  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Jota Made his Permanent Celtic Decision - CeltsAreHere]]></title>
        <id>CBMiRWh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9ob3ctam90YS1tYWRlLWhpcy1wZXJtYW5lbnQtY2VsdGljLWRlY2lzaW9uL9IBSWh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9ob3ctam90YS1tYWRlLWhpcy1wZXJtYW5lbnQtY2VsdGljLWRlY2lzaW9uL2FtcC8</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/how-jota-made-his-permanent-celtic-decision/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-08T10:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Jota Made his Permanent Celtic Decision  CeltsAreHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>