<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-11-25T16:12:07.729Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic v Motherwell GG Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114519</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-motherwell-gg-live-updates/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T14:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 15:00.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: KYOGO LEADS ATTACK, RALSTON RETURNS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114306</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-kyogo-leads-attack-ralston-returns/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T13:56:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS recalls Anthony Ralston to his starting eleven against Motherwell at Parkhead this afternoon. The Scotland international takes over at right-back from Alistair Johnston who only returned to training yesterday after his return from duty with Canada. Norwegian Odin Holm again gets the nod ahead of David Turnbull and Paulo Bernardo to play alongside skipper [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic team confirmed: One change, Tilio in squad, broadcast details, instant reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181313</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-vs-motherwell-confirmed-one-change-tilio-in-squad-broadcast-details-instant-reaction/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T13:52:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manager Brendan Rodgers has named his Celtic team vs Motherwell for today’s Scottish Premiership clash. The full squad for the Celtic Park match is as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hollywood superstar pictured wearing Celtic jersey]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45861</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/hollywood-pictured-wearing-celtic-jersey/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T12:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Celtic have their fair share of famous fans. Rod Stewart is the first name that comes to most people’s minds, one of the best-selling music artists in history. Lewis Capaldi is another popular musician known to support the Hoops. And several A-list celebrities like Gerard Butler, Snoop Dogg, […]
Hollywood superstar pictured wearing Celtic jersey - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers wants Green Brigade situation resolved at Celtic soon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181309</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-wants-green-brigade-situation-resolved-at-celtic-soon/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T09:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers is hoping for a resolution to the ongoing Green Brigade situation at Celtic “sooner rather than later” but has backed the club’s current...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic team news ahead of Motherwell as Brendan Rodgers discusses Kyogo and Palma status]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181306</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-news-ahead-of-motherwell-as-brendan-rodgers-discusses-kyogo-and-palma-status/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T09:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have no fresh injury concerns ahead of today’s fixture at home to Motherwell, with all of the club’s international contingent returning to Lennoxtown unscathed....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic pushing for priority signing in January window]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45859</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/celtic-priority-signing-january-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T09:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s January transfer window is expected to be a busy one. The club might have made nine signings in the summer, seven arriving on a permanent basis and two on loan, but there are still holes in Brendan Rodgers’ squad that need to be filled. On the other hand, there are way too many players […]
Celtic pushing for priority signing in January window - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton sends message to Mark Lawwell critics with Celtic transfer verdict]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181303</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/chris-sutton-sends-message-to-mark-lawwell-critics-with-celtic-transfer-verdict/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T08:47:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker Chris Sutton says it is “fashionable” to criticise the club’s Head of Scouting and Recruitment, Mark Lawwell, but has pointed out the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REST AND BE CHEERFUL: BRENDAN BREAKS WITH TRADITION]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114514</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rest-and-be-cheerful-brendan-breaks-with-tradition/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T08:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has broken with tradition to ditch Celtic’s annual January warm-weather training in the Middle East. It was the Irishman who instigated the trip in his first time-around as Hoops gaffer, but he has decided on a change of course to allow his players some time to spend with their families over the festive [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers changes up Celtic January plans for "more beneficial" alternative]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181300</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-changes-up-celtic-january-plans-for-more-beneficial-alternative/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T08:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has confirmed the club won’t be taking part in a warm-weather training camp this January, instead staying at Lennoxtown. Over the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS CLEARS UP HONDURAN HOWLER]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114511</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-clears-up-honduran-howler/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T07:54:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has cleared up the mystery of the mistaken identity of one of his international stars. Luis Palma was erroneously reported by some media outlets as being doubtful for this afternoon’s Premiership encounter against Motherwell at Parkhead after apparently sustaining an injury playing for Honduras against Mexico. The claim was wide of the mark [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S SCOTTISH CUP DATE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114506</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtics-scottish-cup-date/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T07:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HOLDERS Celtic will go into the Scottish Cup fourth round draw which will be held tomorrow night. The ballot will be broadcast live on Sportscene on the BBC Scotland channel with coverage starting at 7.15pm. It will also be shown on tablet, mobile or laptop can do so for free via the BBC iPlayer. The Hoops [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: THE PROBLEM WITH BEING A CELTIC PLAYER]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114500</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-the-problem-with-being-a-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T06:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HERE’S a wee tale which I swear is true. I cannot divulge the identity of the individual concerned for fear of embarrassing the unfortunate chap. Back in the mid-seventies, Jock Stein bought a proven goalscorer for Celtic. As ever, the legendary manager was looking to add more firepower to the side and he saw this [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC v MOTHERWELL: 5-MINUTE QUIZ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114303</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-motherwell-5-minute-quiz-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T06:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC struggled to overcome Motherwell in their first Premiership meeting of the season at Fir Park in September. And that performance echoed the two encounters at Parkhead last term when Stuart Kettlewell’s side were one of only two sides to take league points from the east end of Glasgow. How much can you remember about past [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE BERTIE AULD: PART ELEVEN: ‘ENJOYABLE, EXASPERATING AND EXPLOSIVE’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=100049</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-unforgettable-bertie-auld-part-eleven-enjoyable-exasperating-and-explosive/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T05:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bertie Auld was the most irrepressible performer in Jock Stein’s team of all stars who conquered all before them in the sixties. CQN are celebrating the life and incredible times of the club legend in an EXCLUSIVE series with extracts from his best-selling autobiography, ‘A Bhoy Called Bertie‘, co-authored by his friend and writer [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable source offers Sydney van Hooijdonk to Celtic update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45854</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/reliable-sydney-van-hooijdonk-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T22:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are believed to be on the lookout for a striker in the January transfer window. There might be a few reasons behind that. Firstly, both Kyogo and Oh Hyeon-gyu might be unavailable for a considerable length of time early next year due to the AFC Asian Cup. They are the club’s two options to […]
Reliable source offers Sydney van Hooijdonk to Celtic update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anderlecht star leads glowing dressing room tribute to standout Celtic hero]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181296</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/anderlecht-star-leads-glowing-dressing-room-tribute-to-standout-celtic-hero/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T21:43:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder Matt O’Riley has shared he received special praise from experienced Anderlecht goalkeeper Kasper Schmeichel in the wake of his debut for Denmark. O’Riley...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou claims Celtic success gets dismissed]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45852</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/ange-postecoglou-claims-celtic-success/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T21:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has proven to be a major success in the Premier League since swapping Celtic for Tottenham Hotspur. Of course, a lot of fans were not happy to see him depart after just two years at Parkhead. But he has been very respectful about the club even after leaving. And it is hard not […]
Ange Postecoglou claims Celtic success gets dismissed - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic almost pull off stunning Friday comeback vs Brighton in Premier League International Cup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181290</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/celtic-almost-pull-off-stunning-friday-night-comeback-vs-brighton-in-premier-league-international-cup/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T21:02:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic B played their latest fixture in the Premier League International Cup tonight, losing 4-3 away to Brighton & Hove Albion’s U21 side. The match...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers definitively explains the transfer process at Celtic, why Mark Lawwell is needed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181189</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-definitively-explains-the-transfer-process-at-celtic-why-mark-lawwell-is-needed/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T20:27:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has provided supporters with an insight into the process of scouting and recruiting players at the Scottish champions. A lot has...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The latest on Celtic transfer links with Sydney van Hooijdonk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181285</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/the-latest-on-celtic-transfer-links-with-sydney-van-hooijdonk/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T19:57:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have yet to make an official approach to Bologna about the possibility of signing up striker Sydney van Hooijdonk in January. The Scottish champions...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic readying improved offer for £7.5 million striker]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45848</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/celtic-readying-improved-offer-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T19:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are expected to bring in a striker in January. Kyogo has been performing steadily even if not scoring at the rate that he was last season. On the other hand, following a slow start to the season under the management of Brendan Rodgers, Oh Hyeon-gyu is building up some momentum as well and has […]
Celtic readying improved offer for £7.5 million striker - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic ready to pursue £7.5m-rated star in January]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181280</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-set-to-launch-improved-offer-for-in-form-striker-this-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T19:13:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are interested in revisiting their transfer pursuit of Brondby striker Mathis Kvistgaarden in January, a new report has indicated tonight. Football Scotland journalist Mark...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One change, midfielder returns; Celtic Predicted XI vs Motherwell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181269</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/one-change-midfielder-returns-celtic-predicted-xi-vs-motherwell/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T18:57:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic face Motherwell in their first game after the international break, looking to continue the incredible goal-scoring they showcased against Aberdeen last time out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sheffield United legend says he is ready to join Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45844</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/sheffield-united-legend-join-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T18:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have tried to sign a lot of players from England over the years which have not really worked out. The club have continued to enjoy success over the years though and even though the Scottish Premiership might not be the most popular league in the world, there is always the attraction of playing for […]
Sheffield United legend says he is ready to join Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Premier League star says he almost signed for Celtic twice]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181256</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-premier-league-star-opens-up-on-two-celtic-attempts-to-sign-him/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T17:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billy Sharp has revealed he twice turned down a move to Celtic when Neil Lennon was in charge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers' Celtic midfield puzzle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181234</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/brendan-rodgers-celtic-midfield-puzzle/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T15:52:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Reo Hatate still recovering from injury, Brendan Rodgers has rotated between David Turnbull, Paulo Bernardo, and Odin Thiago Holm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pundit says "a lot of money" is heading Celtic's way if deal is done]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181191</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-in-strong-position-with-a-lot-of-money-needed-to-land-matt-oriley/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T15:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic defender Mark Wilson reckons Matt O’Riley will earn Celtic a lot of money next year. O’Riley signed a contract extension in September, extending...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Motherwell boss lauds Celtic ahead of Saturday meeting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181216</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/motherwell-boss-lauds-celtic-ahead-of-saturday-meeting/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T14:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Motherwell manager Stuart Kettlewell has named Celtic as the best team in Scotland at a press conference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mile Jedinak on the Celtic factor that led to Tottenham coaching role]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181207</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/mile-jedinak-on-the-celtic-factor-that-led-to-tottenham-coaching-role/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T14:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mile Jedinak has revealed that his current coaching role at Tottenham wouldn't have been possible without a visit to meet Ange Postecoglou at Celtic during training.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Bhoy says Rodgers and Celtic transfer disconnect has now been fixed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181198</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-bhoy-says-brendan-rodgers-and-celtic-transfer-disconnect-has-now-been-fixed/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T13:48:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker Andy Walker has weighed in on Brendan Rodgers' comments on Celtic's transfer policy at Wednesday's AGM.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kasper Schmeichel offers superb boost to Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45839</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/kasper-schmeichel-offers-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T13:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The international break is always an interesting time for Celtic fans. The club have already been dealing with a number of fitness issues and do not want any more of their players to pick up knocks. In that regard, there has not been a lot to worry about in recent days except for a scare […]
Kasper Schmeichel offers superb boost to Celtic player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing in another quality striker will be on Brendan’s mind.]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58475</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/bringing-in-another-quality-striker-will-be-on-brendans-mind/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T12:21:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic return to action after the international break with Motherwell the visitors to Celtic Park. Every Celtic fan will be hoping they can turn in a performance like the one they signed off with against Aberdeen before the players went off to play for their respective countries. That 6-0 performance was almost perfect on […]
The post Bringing in another quality striker will be on Brendan’s mind. appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic superstar tipped to leave the club by next season]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45835</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/celtic-leave-club-next-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T12:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The reality of life as a Celtic supporter is that more often than not the club’s best performers end up leaving. We saw it in the recent summer transfer window with Jota heading for Al-Ittihad. Over the years, we have seen it many times with the likes of Moussa Dembele, Kieran Tierney, Odsonne Edouard and […]
Celtic superstar tipped to leave the club by next season - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High expectations, the day the season pivoted]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114499</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/high-expectations-the-day-the-season-pivoted/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T12:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Luis Palma’s 87th minute goal should have been enough to secure the win at our visit to Fir Park in September.  Incredibly, Motherwell’s equaliser 8 minutes later was not enough for them to take a point.  A game which couldn’t produce a goal for so long, ended with a flurry. Almost two months later, the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘A BIT UPSET,’ LEGEND’S REACTION TO KID KEEPER QUITTING CELTIC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114489</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/a-bit-upset-legends-reaction-to-kid-keeper-quitting-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T08:16:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic kid gloves Vincent Angelini is determined to emulate a famous relative and play for Scotland at the highest level. The 20-year-old Brentford keeper looks to his grandad, Celtic legend Davie Hay, as his inspiration as he continues to make progress in his fledgling career. The Scotland Under-21 netminder has just returned to the English [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘HEADING IN THE RIGHT DIRECTION,’ INSISTS O’RILEY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114485</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/heading-in-the-right-direction-insists-oriley/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T07:14:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY is brimming with positivity this season – and the rewards are evident as he surges to a new level in his game. The stylish midfield mastermind has become a first-pick for Brendan Rodgers with his classy and polished performances in the champions’ engine room. At the age of 23, after arriving as a [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIRTHDAY BHOY ROY – AND THE NIGHT 10 MEN WON THE TITLE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=75609</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/birthday-bhoy-roy-and-the-night-10-men-won-the-title/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T06:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE great Jock Stein had told the Celtic fans there was a “special talent” emerging through the youths at Parkhead – a powerfully-built teenager by the name of Roy Aitken. The versatile Irvine-born performer made his debut against Stenhousemuir in the League Cup on September 10 1975 at the age of 16 – and there [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE BERTIE AULD: PART TEN: ‘THE MOST IMPORTANT VICTORY’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=78019</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-cup-can-kick-start-a-new-era-insists-wee-bertie/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T05:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bertie Auld was the astute midfield mastermind who combined with Bobby Murdoch to propel Celtic towards glory in the sixties. CQN are celebrating the life and incredible times of the club legend in an EXCLUSIVE series with extracts from his best-selling autobiography, ‘A Bhoy Called Bertie’, co-authored by his friend and writer Alex Gordon. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insiders claim £3 million Celtic signing is not good enough]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45813</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/23/insiders-claim-3-million-celtic-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T22:35:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s still a fair amount of concern from Celtic fans over the club’s summer signings. Although Luis Palma and Yang Hyun-jun are now beginning to show real potential in their performances, many others have yet to do so. And it looks like one signing in particular might not be matching the required standards. Injuries to […]
Insiders claim £3 million Celtic signing is not good enough - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Hartson urges Celtic to bring back former player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45826</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/23/john-hartson-celtic-former-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T21:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Hartson played for Celtic for six very successful seasons. Thus, he knows exactly what it takes to succeed at Parkhead and it looks like the Welshman would like to see one former player make a return to Glasgow. Considering the circumstances, it is unlikely but not impossible by any means. Celtic are heading towards […]
John Hartson urges Celtic to bring back former player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Celtic heroes favourites to become Ireland manager]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45822</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/23/two-celtic-heroes-favourites-ireland/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T19:30:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Republic of Ireland national team are set to begin the search for their next manager. Stephen Kenny is headed for the exit door. His side were not able to qualify for EURO 2024. And now, it remains to be seen who ends up taking his place in the hot seat. Interestingly, a couple of […]
Two Celtic heroes favourites to become Ireland manager - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The talking points from Celtic training with Marco Tilio involved and Kyogo status confirmed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181183</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/the-talking-points-from-celtic-training-with-marco-tilio-involved-and-kyogo-status-confirmed/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are busy preparing for their next match at home to Motherwell on Saturday and the majority of the club’s international contingent have returned to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player pictured at Lennoxtown in injury boost]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45819</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/23/celtic-player-pictured-lennoxtown-injury/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T18:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will return to club action after the international break by taking on Motherwell at the weekend. The Hoops’ last result was a 6-0 win over Aberdeen. But that was almost two weeks ago and Brendan Rodgers’ side will need to rediscover their positive momentum. There is some good news for them in that regard. […]
Celtic player pictured at Lennoxtown in injury boost - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Desmond and Lawwell send firm message about Celtic ownership]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181180</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/desmond-and-lawwell-send-firm-message-about-celtic-ownership/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T17:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic aren’t going to be under new ownership any time soon, something that was made abundantly clear by the Desmond family and chairman Peter Lawwell...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O'Riley namechecks Lennoxtown coach helping him improve at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181176</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/matt-oriley-credits-lennoxtown-coach-helping-him-improve-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T16:27:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder Matt O’Riley is having a fantastic season for the Bhoys and is eager to bring his confident form into a busy schedule for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic make announcement about new partnership]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45815</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/23/celtic-make-announcement-new-partnership/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T15:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic as a club are always looking to find ways to get better, take steps forward in the right direction and change with the times. Over the last few years, we have seen how the Hoops have spread their scouting network further and wider when it comes to signing players. The likes of Kyogo, Reo […]
Celtic make announcement about new partnership - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic urged to sign £4 million-rated player in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45810</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/23/celtic-urged-sign-player-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T12:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are heading into a very important January transfer window. So far, they are leading the Premiership title race. But the upcoming AFC Asian Cup, scheduled to start early next year, could prove to be a turning point if the Hoops are not careful. It is very possible that the likes of Kyogo, Oh Hyeon-gyu, […]
Celtic urged to sign £4 million-rated player in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AGM, buys, refs and new reveal on ownership]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114468</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/agm-buys-refs-and-new-reveal-on-ownership/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T12:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers reclaimed some of his territory disputed by conspiracy theorists at yesterday’s AGM.  The manager explained how transfers worked at Celtic, insisting, “it’s really no different here to most clubs.” The coaches identify the profile of players required, the scouts create a shortlist, and the manager makes the final decision.  Notions than Brendan would [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘RESPECT,’ RODGERS’ DEMAND AGAINST STRUGGLERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114474</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/respect-rodgers-demand-against-strugglers/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T11:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MOTHERWELL have played six Premiership games since Matt O’Riley claimed Celtic’s dramatic stoppage-time clincher in the champions’ 2-1 triumph at Fir Park in late September. Amazingly, Stuart Kettlewell’s side have failed to win any of those encounters with four defeats and two draws in a disappointing sequence for the Lanarkshire club. However, Brendan Rodgers insisted [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC LEGENDS IN BOSS BATTLE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114466</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-legends-in-boss-battle/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T09:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEIL LENNON is poised to go head to head with former Celtic team-mate Roy Keane for the Republic of Ireland manager’s job. The Hoops legend and the Manchester United icon, who made 10 league appearances in season 2005/06 for the Parkhead club, are both in the frame for the post after the Irish FA decided not [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE BERTIE AULD: PART NINE: ‘BIG JOCK AND THE TRIP OF A LIFETIME’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=86853</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-unforgettable-bertie-auld-part-nine-big-jock-and-the-trip-of-a-lifetime/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T05:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bertie Auld teamed up with Bobby Murdoch as Celtic conquered all in the sixties. CQN are celebrating the life and incredible times of the club legend in an EXCLUSIVE series with extracts from his best-selling autobiography, ‘A Bhoy Called Bertie’, co-authored by his friend and writer Alex Gordon. The remarkable life story continues with [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic chief takes cheeky dig at Rangers during AGM]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45789</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/22/celtic-chief-cheeky-rangers-agm/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T22:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic AGM can often be a predictable event. The club’s board are asked questions on the day. As you would expect from people who are usually fans as well as investors, the subject matter of many of them was to be expected. The Green Brigade, player recruitment and VAR are all regular topics raised. […]
Celtic chief takes cheeky dig at Rangers during AGM - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic eyeing Manchester United and Liverpool target]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45802</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/22/celtic-manchester-united-liverpool-target/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T21:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with a number of highly-rated players in recent times, as we head towards the January transfer window. The Hoops are expected to be busy in the winter with both incomings and outgoings. While the fans want some experience to be added to the squad, it looks like the Scottish champions are […]
Celtic eyeing Manchester United and Liverpool target - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers dismisses Celtic transfer rumour]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45797</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/22/rodgers-dismisses-celtic-transfer-rumour/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T19:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Celtic brought back Brendan Rodgers for a second stint at Parkhead, the hope was that the Hoops were looking to take their game to the next level. For that to happen, they would have to make some significant moves in the summer transfer window. There were rumours that the club were ready to break […]
Brendan Rodgers dismisses Celtic transfer rumour - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers makes Virgil van Dijk claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45794</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/22/celtic-brendan-rodgers-virgil-van-dijk/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T18:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will know the importance of the upcoming January transfer window. There is already a need to strengthen in some positions across the pitch. On the other hand, the AFC Asian Cup, which is scheduled to start in January of next year, makes things interesting as well. There are quite a few of the club’s […]
Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers makes Virgil van Dijk claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic scout highly-rated defender wanted by EPL clubs; likely to leave in January]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181147</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-scout-defender-sam-curtis-as-premier-league-clubs-show-interest-january-exit-likely/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T17:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with a move for St Patrick’s Athletic defender Sam Curtis. As reported by 90min, Celtic have recently scouted the right-back with...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key Celtic duo won't return to training until Friday with Motherwell test looming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181163</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/key-celtic-duo-wont-return-to-training-until-friday-with-motherwell-test-looming/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T17:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic stars Alistair Johnston and Luis Palma won’t be back at club training until Friday, giving them little time to prepare for the visit of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Shining light"; Celtic star barely used by Rodgers lauded by homeland media for int'l display]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181150</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-the-irish-media-are-saying-about-celtics-mikey-johnston-after-big-chance-to-impress/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T16:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mikey Johnston has found it difficult at Celtic this season after his return from a productive loan in Portugal last term. Finding himself injured during...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charlie Mulgrew names surprising Celtic player of the year contender]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181114</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/charlie-mulgrews-glowing-liam-scales-verdict-after-celtic-impact/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T16:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Charlie Mulgrew has praised Liam Scales for his performances at Celtic this season with the Republic of Ireland international cementing himself as a first-team regular....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The latest on Paulo Bernardo ahead of big Celtic push]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181084</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-latest-on-paulo-bernardo-ahead-of-big-celtic-push/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T15:57:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paulo Bernardo has continued his Portugal under-21 national team starting streak after featuring against Greece on Monday. Bernardo has now started in five consecutive games...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS IN ‘FINAL DECISION’ STANCE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114458</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-in-final-decision-stance/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T15:46:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS reinforced the need to add quality to his Celtic squad in the January transfer window when he spoke at the club’s AGM at Parkhead today. The Hoops boss has already admitted players will be coming and going after the turn of the year as he reshapes his pool for the second half of the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss drops potential Jota transfer return hint]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45786</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/22/celtic-boss-jota-transfer-return/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T15:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s most high-profile exit in the summer transfer window was that of Jota. The Portuguese winger had established himself as one of the club’s most important players over his two seasons at Parkhead. He would leave in a £25 million move to join Al-Ittihad. But things have not gone as he would have hoped. Jota […]
Celtic boss drops potential Jota transfer return hint - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Chief Financial Officer provides important new context on the club's £72m bank balance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181129</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-chief-financial-officer-provides-important-new-context-on-the-clubs-72m-bank-balance/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T15:26:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Chief Financial Officer Chris McKay has provided new details on why the club’s bank balance in year-end accounts was so high. In Celtic’s annual...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic publish rare new interviews with Peter Lawwell, Michael Nicholson and Chris McKay]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181123</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-publish-rare-new-interviews-with-peter-lawwell-michael-nicholson-and-chris-mckay/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T14:55:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have uploaded new video interviews with chairman Peter Lawwell and chief executive Michael Nicholson on the day the club held their 2023 AGM. Celtic...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers refutes Celtic transfer myth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181117</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-refutes-celtic-transfer-myth/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T14:24:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has stated no players have been pushed onto him during his second spell at the club after concerns were raised at...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Nicholson and Peter Lawwell take Rangers digs at Celtic AGM but a serious point is made]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181111</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/michael-nicholson-and-peter-lawwell-take-rangers-digs-at-celtic-agm-but-a-serious-point-is-made/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T13:53:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Chief Executive Michael Nicholson got a big laugh from the audience at today’s AGM with a quip about how many penalties Rangers win. Nicholson...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Lawwell defends significant increase in Celtic director salaries at AGM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181100</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/peter-lawwell-defends-significant-increase-in-celtic-director-salaries-at-agm/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T13:24:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic chairman Peter Lawwell has defended the increasing salaries paid to club directors in the last financial year. Celtic’s annual report for the financial year...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player ready to leave the club in January window]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45783</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/22/celtic-player-ready-leave-club-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T13:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic squad could undergo some changes in the upcoming January transfer window. Brendan Rodgers appears to have way too many players available to him right now and has not been able to give game time to a number of them. So, expect more to head out of Parkhead rather than arrive in the winter. […]
Celtic player ready to leave the club in January window - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers and Michael Nicholson pledge action on squad issues, investment at Celtic AGM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181093</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-and-michael-nicholson-pledge-action-on-squad-issues-january-investment-at-celtic-agm/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T12:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic 2023 AGM is underway and after a review of the last calendar year with video packages and the passage of routine resolutions, questions...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inevitable cull will see Mikey flourish elsewhere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114435</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/inevitable-cull-will-see-mikey-flourish-elsewhere/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T12:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You and I have talked about Mikey Johnston for over five years.  As a teenager, he was pivotal in a win at Ibrox early in our most recent nine-in-a-row season and seemed set for the top.  Just two days before that game we signed Mohamed Elyounoussi on loan, and the Norwegian international edged ahead of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S UEFA FINES TOTAL OVER £65,000]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114456</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtics-uefa-fines-total-over-65000/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T11:57:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have been hit with £25,240.45 worth of fines by UEFA following fan misbehaviour in the Champions League 2-2 draw with Atletico Madrid at Parkhead. The latest penalty brings the club’s total financial punishment to a staggering £65,710.94 for their involvement in this season’s Champions League. The Hoops have been hit hard again after last [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star makes first start in over 5 months after fitness comeback]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181073</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/marco-tilio-takes-a-big-step-forward-after-celtic-concerns/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T11:53:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marco Tilio has provided Brendan Rodgers with a promising boost on the injury front by starting for the Australia under-23 national team.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Came up in recruitment meeting"; Pundits have their say on Celtic links with exciting striker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181060</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/peter-grant-delivers-verdict-on-what-hes-hearing-about-celtic-and-sydney-van-hooijdonk/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T10:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant and Stephen McGinn have weighed in on Sydney van Hooijdonk’s potential move to Celtic in January. Grant played with Sydney’s father, Pierre, at...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything you need to know about today's Celtic AGM; Euro ambition, Green Brigade ban]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181063</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/everything-you-need-to-know-about-todays-celtic-agm-euro-ambition-green-brigade-ban/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T10:23:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2023 edition of the Celtic Annual General Meeting (AGM) takes place on Wednesday and several important topics surrounding the club are sure to come...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GREEN LIGHT FOR YUKI EXIT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114433</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/green-light-for-yuki-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T09:48:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is poised to give the green light to a loan move for Yuki Kobayashi, as CQN forecast last month. The Japanese centre-back has yet to make a competitive appearance since the Irishman took over from Spurs-bound Ange Postecoglou in June. The Greek-Australian gaffer signed Kobayashi in January after the 23-year-old defender came out [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘ON ANOTHER DAY, I GET MY LEG BROKEN,’ REFLECTIONS FROM O’RILEY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114431</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/on-another-day-i-get-my-leg-broken-reflections-from-oriley/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T08:37:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY celebrated his 23rd birthday yesterday in the aftermath of glowing tributes following his debut for Denmark senior team. The Celtic playmaker turned in his usual polished performance, but couldn’t prevent his adopted nation sliding to a 2-0 loss to Northern Ireland in Belfast, as CQN reported. The result was a mere hiccup for the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I HAD A BIT OF FUN,’ FORGOTTEN CELT SENDS RODGERS REMINDER]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114427</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-had-a-bit-of-fun-forgotten-celt-sends-rodgers-reminder/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T07:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MIKEY JOHNSTON won the Man of the Match award in the Republic of Ireland’s 1-1 draw with New Zealand at the Aviva Stadium in Dublin last night. However, the Celtic winger, who has figured in only 25 minutes for the champions in this campaign, admitted he is still off the pace as far as the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC STRIKER AT CROSSROADS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114422</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-striker-at-crossroads/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T06:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOHNNY KENNY is due to return to Celtic a week tomorrow when his loan deal at Shamrock Rovers expires. The Republic of Ireland Under-21 striker cost the champions £125,000 when they signed him from Sligo Rovers in January 2022, but is still awaiting his first-team debut. Kenny joined the Dublin outfit at the start of the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE BERTIE AULD: PART EIGHT: ‘CAESAR, DINO, OCEANS AND ME’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=86852</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-unforgettable-bertie-auld-part-eight-caesar-dino-oceans-and-me/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T05:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bertie Auld was the most irrepressible Celtic player of Jock Stein’s all-conquering team of the sixties. CQN are celebrating the life and incredible times of the club legend in an EXCLUSIVE series with extracts from his best-selling autobiography, ‘A Bhoy Called Bertie’, co-authored by his friend and writer Alex Gordon. The remarkable life story continues [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Struggling Celtic player sends message to Brendan Rodgers]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45778</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/21/struggling-celtic-player-message-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T23:05:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has a difficult job at Celtic right now. The squad size is not ideal and there are way too many players in certain positions. It would make sense for the club to part ways with some in the upcoming January transfer window. But at the same time, it is also important to make […]
Struggling Celtic player sends message to Brendan Rodgers - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic must try to sign Real Madrid superstar’s brother]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45774</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/21/celtic-must-sign-real-madrid-brother/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T21:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are always on the lookout for bright young talents. We saw the club sign nine players in the summer transfer window, all of them highly-rated youngsters, except for Nat Phillips, who was brought in on loan from Liverpool for just the first half of the season as a result of the number of injuries […]
Celtic must try to sign Real Madrid superstar’s brother - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic tipped to sign £4 million player in January window]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45771</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/21/celtic-tipped-sign-january-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T20:05:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic might have signed nine players in the summer transfer window, but the Hoops are expected to be pretty active in January as well. On one hand, there are a few positions in this current squad where they still need to improve. On the other hand, it feels like there are quite a few who […]
Celtic tipped to sign £4 million player in January window - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kristoffer Ajer makes fantastic admission about Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45769</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/21/kristoffer-ajer-makes-admission-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T18:35:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kristoffer Ajer had a very successful time at Celtic, enjoying a rise from being a young talent to a regular starter for the Hoops. He would leave the club in the summer of 2021 in order to make a move to the Premier League, as the Norwegian joined Brentford. He remains there to this day […]
Kristoffer Ajer makes fantastic admission about Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[English legend admits he has always wanted Celtic job]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45767</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/21/english-legend-wanted-celtic-job/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T17:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Ange Postecoglou decided to leave Celtic in the summer in order to take the Tottenham Hotspur job, the fans were certainly worried about the future. It would be a tough job to replace the Australian. The club did go out and bring in the best option available in the form of Brendan Rodgers. Rodgers […]
English legend admits he has always wanted Celtic job - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic want to sign striker also eyed by Leeds United]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45762</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/21/celtic-striker-eyed-leeds-united/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T13:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have spread their scouting network further and wider in recent years, especially following Ange Postecoglou’s appointment as manager in 2021. The Australian has left since then to join Tottenham Hotspur, but the Hoops have remained true to their transfer policy. And they are now being linked with a South African centre-forward. Celtic certainly need […]
Celtic want to sign striker also eyed by Leeds United - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PL Profit and Sustainability Rules, some window dressing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114420</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/pl-profit-and-sustainability-rules-some-window-dressing/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T12:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not buying the sense of aggrievement from Everton over their 10-point deduction for failing FA Premier League Profit and Sustainability Rules (PSR).  It is the harshest penalty yet given out by the League and puts Everton in the relegation zone, but they are just two points from safety and in sufficiently good form to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JINXED CELT’S REASONS TO BE CHEERFUL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114416</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/jinxed-celts-reasons-to-be-cheerful/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T07:40:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE at last has something to celebrate in the midst of an injury-hampered campaign. Celtic’s Japanese midfielder turns 26 today and is hoping for a change of fortune in the new year. Hatate was taken off early in the 2-2 Champions League draw with Atletico Madrid last month and extensive medical examinations highlighted hamstring [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC EYE WONDERBOY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114413</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-eye-wonderboy/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T07:17:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC are keeping tabs on South African teen sensation Luke Baartman. The eye-catching striker only made his first-team debut for Cape Town Spurs last month and already a host of admirers have been alerted to his talents. The South African Under-17 forward, who is still at school, netted his first goal against Kaiser Chiefs a [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STRIFE O’RILEY: EX-CELT RUINS DEBUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114408</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/strife-oriley-ex-celt-ruins-debut/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T06:40:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY suffered a shock defeat as Northern Ireland wrecked his Denmark debut in Belfast last night. The Celtic midfielder was praised for his performance, but couldn’t prevent a 2-0 loss in the final Euro 2024 qualifier with the Danes already among the countries who have already sealed their place in next summer’s soccer showpiece in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE BERTIE AULD: PART SEVEN: ‘BACK TO CELTIC – AND TAKING A WAGE CUT’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=86841</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-unforgettable-bertie-auld-part-seven-back-to-celtic-and-taking-a-wage-cut/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T05:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bertie Auld was the heartbeat of the Celtic side that conquered all in the sixties. CQN are celebrating the life and incredible times of the club legend in an EXCLUSIVE series with extracts from his best-selling autobiography, ‘A Bhoy Called Bertie’, co-authored by his friend and writer Alex Gordon. The remarkable story continues with [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>