<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-07-29T12:17:34.576Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic v Wolves, GG Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110366</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-wolves-gg-live-updates/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T12:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear before after 14.00.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic XI vs Wolves confirmed: 3 changes, surprise defence, TV details, instant reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169156</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-vs-wolves-confirmed-3-changes-surprise-defence-tv-details-instant-reaction/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T11:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manager Brendan Rodgers has named his Celtic team vs Wolves in today’s Dublin pre-season friendly at the Aviva Stadium. The full match squad is as...
The post Celtic XI vs Wolves confirmed: 3 changes, surprise defence, TV details, instant reaction appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic set for brilliant Dublin backing as thousands arrive for Wolves clash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169153</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-set-for-brilliant-dublin-backing-as-irish-police-struggle-for-numbers/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T11:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will get more brilliant backing in Dublin this afternoon against Wolves. It’s the Hoops penultimate pre-season clash and a tasty one against the Premier...
The post Celtic set for brilliant Dublin backing as thousands arrive for Wolves clash appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star sets ambitious Olympics vision that would have positive consequences for the Hoops]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169146</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-star-sets-ambitious-olympics-vision-that-would-have-positive-consequences-for-the-hoops/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T09:42:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic star Hyunjun Yang has set an ambitious vision for next year’s Olympics. The former Gangwon winger may just have arrived in Scotland but...
The post Celtic star sets ambitious Olympics vision that would have positive consequences for the Hoops appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The cheapest way to watch Celtic vs Wolves today; multiple options for supporters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169140</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/the-cheapest-way-to-watch-celtic-vs-wolves-today-multiple-options-for-supporters/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T09:11:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic face Wolves in Dublin this afternoon and there are plenty of ways for supporters to watch the match. It’s the penultimate friendly of pre-season...
The post The cheapest way to watch Celtic vs Wolves today; multiple options for supporters appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic summer signing tipped to become £15 million player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42995</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/29/celtic-summer-signing-tipped-become-15-million-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T09:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Signing highly-rated young players, developing them and moving them on for significantly bigger transfer fees, has been part of Celtic’s strategy for years. Thus, it should be no surprise that the club have already brought in five youngsters this summer. They are Odin Thiago Holm, Marco Tilio, Yang Hyun-jun, Kwon Hyeok-kyu and Maik Nawrocki. Nawrocki […]
Celtic summer signing tipped to become £15 million player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CCV ON STAND-BY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110364</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ccv-on-stand-by/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T08:36:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CAMERON CARTER-VICKERS is standing by to make an appearance against Wolves at the Aviva Stadium in Dublin this afternoon. The Celtic fans’ favourite missed the last six games of the previous season following his inspirational centre-back outing in the 1-0 Scottish Cup semi-final victory over Michael Beale’s Ibrox side at Hampden on April 30. The [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Bhoy declares himself ready to go at Celtic; sets out how he can immediately improve]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169133</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/new-bhoy-declares-himself-ready-to-go-at-celtic-sets-out-how-he-can-immediately-improve/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyunjun Yang reckons he is ready and prepared to be called into Celtic action quickly after making the switch from South Korea earlier this week....
The post New Bhoy declares himself ready to go at Celtic; sets out how he can immediately improve appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rodgers to go strong, debut potential; Team news and Celtic Predicted XI vs Wolves]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169128</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/rodgers-to-go-strong-debut-potential-celtic-predicted-xi-vs-wolves/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With just a week to go until the start of the Scottish Premiership season, today’s Celtic match against Wolves in Dublin is an important step...
The post Rodgers to go strong, debut potential; Team news and Celtic Predicted XI vs Wolves appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘HE COULD BE A BIG PLAYER,’ SUTTON REVEALS VITAL CELT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110361</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/he-could-be-a-big-player-sutton-reveals-vital-celt/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T06:59:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS took his pre-season signing spree to five when he brought in centre-back Maik Nawrocki from Legia Warsaw during the week. The Polish defender joined Norwegian midfielder Odin Thiago, Australian winger Marco Tilio and South Korean duo anchorman Kwon Hyeon-kyu and flanker Yang Hyun-jun as the second time-around boss strengthens his squad for a [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic signing already "good friends" with new teammate as settling in process begins]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169125</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-signing-already-good-friends-with-new-teammate-as-settling-in-process-begins/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T06:17:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic winger Hyunjun Yang has shared that he has no fears about settling into life across the world from his homeland, because he already...
The post Celtic signing already "good friends" with new teammate as settling in process begins appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE DAY RODGERS – AND GERRARD – WERE LOSERS TO CELTIC IN DUBLIN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110353</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-day-rodgers-and-gerrard-were-losers-to-celtic-in-dublin/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T06:05:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS wasn’t overly-enthusiastic when Celtic won at the Aviva Stadium back on August 11 2013. There was a good reason for that – the Irishman was in the opposition dug-out in front of a sell-out 51,000 crowd in Dublin. The second time-around Hoops boss was in charge of Liverpool at the time and Neil [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sutton pleased with Rodgers reveal after 'slightly strange' Celtic situation; transfers incoming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169121</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-pleased-with-liel-abada-reveal-after-slightly-strange-celtic-situation/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T05:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton believes Liel Abada can be a big player for Celtic this season after Brendan Rodgers revealed he wants to stay at the Bhoys...
The post Sutton pleased with Rodgers reveal after 'slightly strange' Celtic situation; transfers incoming appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DUD WHO COST CELTIC £187,500 PER GAME]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110350</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/dud-who-cost-celtic-187500-per-game/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T05:32:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S £4.5million misfit keeper Vasilis Barkas has finally found a new club after his Hoops contract was scrapped with 12 months still to run. The former Greek international No.1 leaves the champions after featuring in only 24 games after Neil Lennon made him the most expensive netminder in the club’s history when he bought him [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big profit: Celtic tipped to double or triple their money on new signing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169117</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/big-profit-celtic-tipped-to-double-or-triple-their-money-on-new-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T05:15:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic star Dariusz Dziekanowski has given a thumbs up to the transfer move for central defender Maik Nawrocki, believing the Bhoys could eventually double...
The post Big profit: Celtic tipped to double or triple their money on new signing appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: LET’S SAY YES TO THE BHOY WHO SAID NO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110337</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-lets-say-yes-to-the-bhoy-who-said-no/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T04:45:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE airwaves are usually infested by a superabundance of hoo-ha, hullabaloo, duplicity and deception when unscrupulous agents get to work to promote the availability of their clients. Foxes could take lessons in cunning from these shameless, exploitative characters when they hit overdrive and the neon dollar signs are flashing before their eyes. The players they [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘THERE’S A LONG WAY TO GO’: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Eighteen)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=94588</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/theres-a-long-way-to-go-the-tommy-burns-story-part-eighteen/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T04:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS refused to throw in the towel as the pressure mounted in his third year as Celtic manager during the turbulent 1996/97 crusade. The fans’ favourite had returned to the club on July 12 1994 and had won the Scottish Cup in his debut campaign. That was followed by a barren term and all [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newcastle United player reportedly in talks with Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42991</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/28/newcastle-united-player-talks-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T22:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have continued to sign some very highly-rated youngsters from around the world this summer and it is good to see them sticking with the transfer strategy that brought them so much success under the management of Ange Postecoglou. At the same time though, they will have to bring in some experienced and established players […]
Newcastle United player reportedly in talks with Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[€5 million Celtic flop joins Dutch club on free transfer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42986</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/28/5-million-celtic-dutch-club-free/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T21:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a fantastic record in recent years when it comes to identifying the right players and then signing them. That has been one of the biggest reasons why they were able to recover from the bad position they found themselves in after the 2020/21 campaign and went on to win five of the six […]
€5 million Celtic flop joins Dutch club on free transfer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Messi, Joe Hart banter, Gerrard downed; It's rarely dull when Celtic visit the Aviva Stadium]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169106</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/messi-joe-hart-banter-gerrard-defeat-its-rarely-dull-when-celtic-visit-the-aviva-stadium/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T20:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will play at the Aviva Stadium for the fifth time on Saturday, and it’s rarely dull at the home of Irish football. The Hoops...
The post Messi, Joe Hart banter, Gerrard downed; It's rarely dull when Celtic visit the Aviva Stadium appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Former Celtic star Jota about to be joined by another big name at Al Ittihad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169092</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/former-celtic-star-jota-about-to-be-joined-by-another-big-football-name-at-al-ittihad/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic star Jota is about to be joined by another big name in world football, according to a report. The Hoops attacker departed for...
The post Report: Former Celtic star Jota about to be joined by another big name at Al Ittihad appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed major boost in race to sign Tete for free]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42982</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/28/celtic-handed-major-tete-free/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T19:34:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One high profile player that Celtic have been linked with in recent times is Brazilian winger, Tete. It is believed that he has become a free agent and that will only increase interest in his signature this summer. Brendan Rodgers will know him well already, having managed him for a few months during their time […]
Celtic handed major boost in race to sign Tete for free - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confirmed travellers as Celtic squad pictured leaving for Dublin; new Bhoys involved]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169090</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/confirmed-travellers-as-celtic-squad-pictured-leaving-for-dublin-new-bhoys-involved/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T19:12:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We now know the bulk of the Celtic squad that are travelling to Dublin to take on Wolves at the Aviva Stadium tomorrow, with some...
The post Confirmed travellers as Celtic squad pictured leaving for Dublin; new Bhoys involved appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Documentary thumping, 3:45am kick-off; Celtic's last ten friendlies against English teams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169078</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/documentary-thumping-345am-kick-off-celtics-last-ten-friendlies-against-english-teams/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s always something on the line when Celtic take on English opposition, even in a friendly. Tomorrow will be no different as Brendan Rodgers‘ Hoops...
The post Documentary thumping, 3:45am kick-off; Celtic's last ten friendlies against English teams appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic offered £15 million Fabian Rieder transfer boost]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42979</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/28/celtic-fabian-rieder-transfer-boost/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T18:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are rumoured to be ready to break their transfer record this summer. It currently remains the £9 million fee that they shelled out in order to sign Odsonne Edouard from PSG in 2018. It was a bold move at that point of time as the French striker was only 20 years of age but […]
Celtic offered £15 million Fabian Rieder transfer boost - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I'm buzzing for it"; Two Wolves stars can't wait to play "huge" Celtic in Dublin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169073</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/im-buzzing-for-it-two-wolves-stars-cant-wait-to-play-huge-celtic-in-dublin/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T17:41:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic take on Wolverhampton Wanderers in Dublin on Saturday and for two of the Premier League side’s Irish contingent it’s set to be a special...
The post "I'm buzzing for it"; Two Wolves stars can't wait to play "huge" Celtic in Dublin appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The latest on James Forrest Testimonial ticket sales after initially slow Celtic Park uptake]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169061</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/the-latest-on-james-forrest-testimonial-ticket-sales-after-initially-slow-celtic-park-uptake/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this month it appeared that the Celtic vs Athletic Bilbao friendly, a testimonial for long-serving winger James Forrest, hadn’t exactly captured the imagination of...
The post The latest on James Forrest Testimonial ticket sales after initially slow Celtic Park uptake appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic to take part in Premier League International Cup; full list of teams, tough draw]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169056</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/celtic-to-take-part-in-premier-league-international-cup-full-list-of-teams-tough-draw/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An under-23 Celtic side will again take part in the prestigious Premier League International Cup throughout the 2023/24 season, with some of the best youth...
The post Celtic to take part in Premier League International Cup; full list of teams, tough draw appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: English club enquire about former Celtic youngster Karamoko Dembele]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169027</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/report-english-club-enquire-about-former-celtic-youngster-karamoko-dembele/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic youngster Karamoko Dembele may be being lined up for his next move. A report from L’Équipe says that the attacker is being courted...
The post Report: English club enquire about former Celtic youngster Karamoko Dembele appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[€20 million Celtic target now available on free transfer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42976</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/28/20-million-celtic-target-free-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T16:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Brendan Rodgers was appointed by Celtic for a second stint in the Parkhead hot seat, there were rumours that the club were ready to make some marquee additions and break their transfer record this summer, in order to provide the Northern Irishman with a squad that could make an impact in the Champions League […]
€20 million Celtic target now available on free transfer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Euro 2028 heading to Scotland after Friday UEFA update; why Celtic Park won't be involved]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169036</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/euro-2028-heading-to-scotland-after-friday-uefa-update-why-celtic-park-wont-be-involved/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There was some exciting news for Scottish football fans earlier today when UEFA announced that the UK & Ireland were now the sole bidders for...
The post Euro 2028 heading to Scotland after Friday UEFA update; why Celtic Park won't be involved appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reasons to be hopeful as Celtic fans await next exciting transfer report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169038</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/reasons-to-be-hopeful-as-celtic-fans-await-next-exciting-transfer-report/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was always set to be an important transfer window for Celtic, and it has unsurprisingly had tongues wagging so far. It seems like the...
The post Reasons to be hopeful as Celtic fans await next exciting transfer report appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Everyone wants a slice of Celtic” – Lee Naylor talks up “big crowd” Dublin visit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169029</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/everyone-wants-a-slice-of-celtic-lee-naylor-talks-up-big-crowd-dublin-visit/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T13:43:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lee Naylor reckons that Celtic will face pressure this weekend in Dublin. The ex-defender made his name with our upcoming opponents Wolves before transferring to...
The post “Everyone wants a slice of Celtic” – Lee Naylor talks up “big crowd” Dublin visit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The SPFL acted after recent ticket dispute; could factor in Celtic and Rangers story]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169017</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-spfl-acted-after-recent-ticket-dispute-could-factor-in-celtic-and-rangers-story/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SPFL recently stepped in on a ticket dispute, as the Celtic and Rangers allocation furore continues. We’re in to about the ninth or tenth...
The post The SPFL acted after recent ticket dispute; could factor in Celtic and Rangers story appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Police Scotland asleep at the wheel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110335</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/police-scotland-asleep-at-the-wheel/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T11:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The Away Club shall have the right to claim admission for its supporters of up to 20% of the spectator capacity of the Registered Ground at which the Match is to be played.”  That, with a small caveat for the Safety at Sports Ground Act, 1975, is the simple rule which governs away ticket allocation [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£44m star with Celtic history, Irish favourite, Rodgers record; The big test Wolves will provide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169010</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/44m-star-with-celtic-history-irish-favourite-rodgers-record-the-big-test-we-can-expect-from-wolves/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic face Wolves in Dublin on Saturday in our penultimate friendly fixture. It’s been a pretty speedy run through pre-season this year. Fans have only...
The post £44m star with Celtic history, Irish favourite, Rodgers record; The big test Wolves will provide appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans set for disruption as large sporting event comes to Glasgow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169000</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-fans-set-for-disruption-as-large-sporting-event-comes-to-glasgow-spfl-statement/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T09:42:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SPFL have issued some advice to Celtic supporters and fans of other Glasgow sides as a large sporting event comes to the city. Glasgow...
The post Celtic fans set for disruption as large sporting event comes to Glasgow appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic told to stop player from leaving as offer expected]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42971</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/28/celtic-told-stop-player-leaving-offer/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T09:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already seen one regular starter leave this summer in the form of Jota. The Portuguese winger was a major part of their successes over the past couple of seasons and the club will need to find a suitable replacement for him. The Hoops have brought in a couple of wingers in the form […]
Celtic told to stop player from leaving as offer expected - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Rangers take illogical Celtic Park ticket stance and it could be heading to the SPFL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168992</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/rangers-take-illogical-celtic-park-ticket-stance-and-it-could-be-heading-to-the-spfl/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T06:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers are set to demand they get tickets for upcoming derbies at Celtic Park, despite there being no Celtic fans at the first fixture between...
The post Report: Rangers take illogical Celtic Park ticket stance and it could be heading to the SPFL appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC LOAN STAR TEAMS UP WITH LARSSON JNR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110329</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-loan-star-teams-up-with-larsson-jnr/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T06:36:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic loan star Mohamed Elyounoussi will team up with Henrik Larsson’s son Jordan in Denmark in the new season. The Norwegian left-sided forward, who spent two seasons at Parkhead, was linked with a return after quitting relegated Southampton at the end of his contract in the summer. However, Elyounoussi, 28, has brought an end [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic included on global list of most valuable football brands; only Scottish entry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168984</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-included-on-global-list-of-most-valuable-football-brands-only-scottish-entry/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T05:49:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been included on a list of the 50 most valuable global brands in club football alongside Real Madrid, Barcelona and other massive clubs...
The post Celtic included on global list of most valuable football brands; only Scottish entry appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New signing shares ambitious Celtic dream]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168980</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/new-signing-hyeokkyu-kwons-ambitious-celtic-dream/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T05:15:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic midfielder Hyeokkyu Kwon is ready to live out his dreams at the Bhoys after signing a five-year deal at the club. Kwon is...
The post New signing shares ambitious Celtic dream appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[McSTAY RETURNS, CADETE NO GOAL IBROX STORM: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Seventeen)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=94522</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/mcstay-returns-cadete-no-goal-ibrox-storm-the-tommy-burns-story-part-seventeen/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T04:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE fates appeared to be snarling at Tommy Burns as he experienced extreme turbulence during his third year as Celtic manager during the tempestuous 1996/97 crusade. The fans’ favourite had returned to the club on July 12 1994 and had won the Scottish Cup in his debut campaign. That was followed by a barren term [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers ready to add key member to Celtic backroom team]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42927</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/27/brendan-rodgers-ready-member-team/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T22:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been a great week for Celtic went it comes to recruitments. Hyun-jun Yang, Hyeok-kyu Kwon and Maik Nawrocki have all signed for the Hoops. Three new players in within a week is pretty good going and there could be more to come in the future, as the club continue to reshape their shape. […]
Brendan Rodgers ready to add key member to Celtic backroom team - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic target agrees deal to join Andrea Pirlo’s team]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42964</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/27/celtic-target-agrees-andrea-pirlo-team/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T21:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with quite a few players this summer and it is only natural that they are not going to end up signing all or even most of them. The Hoops have made five additions already though, with the latest one being Maik Nawrocki. The Polish youth international has been signed from Legia […]
Celtic target agrees deal to join Andrea Pirlo’s team - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Curve new members call as Celtic fans get set for more stunning tifos]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168955</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/north-curve-new-members-call-as-celtic-fans-get-set-for-another-season-of-stunning-tifos/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T20:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[North Curve Celtic have been pretty quiet in recent weeks, but they’re now looking forward to the start of the competitive action. Celtic will get...
The post North Curve new members call as Celtic fans get set for more stunning tifos appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans can enjoy long-standing radio show in a new way this season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168973</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-fans-can-enjoy-clyde-superscoreboard-in-a-new-way-this-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans will be able to enjoy Clyde Superscoreboard in a new way this season. The long-standing, popular radio phone-in has a new studio and...
The post Celtic fans can enjoy long-standing radio show in a new way this season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable journalist offers Dominik Livakovic to Celtic news]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42961</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/27/journalist-dominik-livakovic-celtic-news/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T19:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of Celtic fans believe that Celtic need to sign a new goalkeeper this summer. Joe Hart has played his part in winning five trophies over the past two seasons, but some of his recent displays have left the supporters less than impressed. Also, he is 36 years of age and not a long-term […]
Reliable journalist offers Dominik Livakovic to Celtic news - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Short but sweet; Hyeokkyu Kwon sends first online message to the Celtic support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168967</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/short-but-sweet-hyeokkyu-kwon-sends-first-online-message-to-the-celtic-support/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T18:43:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyeokkyu Kwon has sent out his first online message to the Celtic support. The South Korean was announced as a Celtic player earlier in the...
The post Short but sweet; Hyeokkyu Kwon sends first online message to the Celtic support appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing throws up potential for Brendan Rodgers tactical switch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168951</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/new-celtic-signing-throws-up-potential-for-brendan-rodgers-tactical-switch/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new Brendan Rodgers era is well under as the Celtic boss added three new summer signings this week. The additions of Hyeokkyu Kwon, Hyunjun...
The post New Celtic signing throws up potential for Brendan Rodgers tactical switch appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£16 million Celtic-linked player set to join European rivals]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42957</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/27/16-million-celtic-european-rivals/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T18:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with a long list of players in recent times and they have already completed five signings as well. Odin Thiago Holm, Marco Tilio, Yang Hyun-jun, Kwon Hyeok-kyu and Maik Nawrocki are the fresh faces to have arrived at the club this summer. They are all highly-rated youngsters and are believed to […]
£16 million Celtic-linked player set to join European rivals - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch: Former Celtic man has an evening to forget in latest embarrassment for Scottish football]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168941</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/watch-former-celtic-man-has-an-evening-to-forget-in-latest-embarrassment-for-scottish-football/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic goalkeeper David Marshall had an evening to forget as Hibernian suffered European embarrassment on Thursday. As we covered earlier in the day, the...
The post Watch: Former Celtic man has an evening to forget in latest embarrassment for Scottish football appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James Forrest's brilliant contribution as two charities will benefit from Celtic testimonial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168927</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/james-forrests-brilliant-contribution-as-two-charities-will-benefit-from-celtic-testimonial/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic continues their preparations to face Wolves in Dublin in the next stage of their preseason preparations, there is another significant date in the...
The post James Forrest's brilliant contribution as two charities will benefit from Celtic testimonial appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Former Celtic star finds next club; will join up with Hoops legend's son]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168926</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/mohamed-elyounoussi-finds-his-next-club-will-join-up-with-celtic-legends-son/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T16:11:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic attacker Mohamed Elyounoussi has found his new club, according to a report. Danish outlet BT are reporting that Elyounoussi is about to sign...
The post Report: Former Celtic star finds next club; will join up with Hoops legend's son appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Offers expected for Celtic player following rule change]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42954</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/27/offers-expected-celtic-player-rule/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T16:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have quite a few players in the squad right now who are not expected to play much football moving forward. As a result, it would make sense for all parties involved for them to head for the Parkhead exit door this summer, either on loan or on a permanent basis. One player who appears […]
Offers expected for Celtic player following rule change - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic prospects reach youth tournament final]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168900</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/celtic-prospects-reach-youth-tournament-final/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Away from the rigours of the Celtic first team for a moment, we have some news from the Celtic Academy where our young stars of...
The post Celtic prospects reach youth tournament final appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The solution to derby ticket furore is obvious as Celtic take correct Ibrox stance - opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168906</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-solution-to-derby-ticket-furore-is-obvious-as-celtic-take-correct-ibrox-stance/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T15:10:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are set to refuse tickets once again for our upcoming derby against Rangers at Ibrox. The Scottish Sun report that we won’t be taking...
The post The solution to derby ticket furore is obvious as Celtic take correct Ibrox stance - opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The likely explanation as Maik Nawrocki is missing from Celtic training]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168890</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-likely-explanation-as-maik-nawrocki-is-absent-from-celtic-training/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New signing Maik Nawrocki was nowhere to be seen in Celtic training on Thursday. Brendan Rodgers‘ side are back at Lennoxtown, preparing for Saturday’s friendly...
The post The likely explanation as Maik Nawrocki is missing from Celtic training appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's Lennoxtown footage will delight the fans; two key players return to training]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168887</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-lennoxtown-footage-will-delight-the-fans-two-key-players-return-to-training/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the new season just over a week away, the Celtic fans will be excited to see the return of football after what seems like...
The post Celtic's Lennoxtown footage will delight the fans; two key players return to training appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crucial season begins for Scottish clubs in Europe today; the Celtic situation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168872</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/crucial-season-begins-for-scottish-clubs-in-europe-today-the-celtic-situation/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T13:12:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new season of European competition begins for Scottish sides on Thursday, even if Celtic won’t be involved for a few months. These days, Celtic...
The post Crucial season begins for Scottish clubs in Europe today; the Celtic situation appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Miller's bizarre claim of 3 Rangers players that would make Celtic's Treble-winning team]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168869</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kenny-millers-bizarre-claim-of-3-rangers-players-that-would-make-celtics-treble-winning-team/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T12:41:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a person that reads and listens to a lot of opinions surrounding Celtic and Scottish football and how events around the game can affect...
The post Kenny Miller's bizarre claim of 3 Rangers players that would make Celtic's Treble-winning team appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's latest transfer benefits German side as they cite "big potential"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168863</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-latest-transfer-benefits-german-side-as-sporting-director-cites-big-potential/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T11:42:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The signing of Maik Nawrocki was welcomed by everyone at Celtic. From the manager to the fans, we were all delighted to have added the...
The post Celtic's latest transfer benefits German side as they cite "big potential" appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The latest update on every current Celtic first-team injury we know about]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168858</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-latest-update-on-every-current-celtic-first-team-injury-we-know-about/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T11:10:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are well an truly back for the new season, even if the competitive action is still to start. The Hoops have played a few...
The post The latest update on every current Celtic first-team injury we know about appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Olympic sized egos]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110319</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/olympic-sized-egos/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T10:58:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve done my best to avoid the ridiculous summer hype from across the city, which appears as regularly as rain during the Fair.  Ex-Celt Kenny Miller and poor old Barry Ferguson are wheeled out for their hot takes on how Celtic are in trouble this time, with all the accuracy of a stopped clock. Their [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans will watch with interest as two SPFL clubs buck the ticket allocation trend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168852</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-fans-will-watch-with-interest-as-two-spfl-clubs-buck-the-ticket-allocation-trend/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans have had to endure the recent hardship of having their away ticket allocation cut by a number of clubs over the last two...
The post Celtic fans will watch with interest as two SPFL clubs buck the ticket allocation trend appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recent departure shares first post Celtic video; new life looks good]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168845</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/aaron-mooy-shares-first-post-celtic-video-new-life-looks-good/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic midfielder Aaron Mooy has shared a first look at his new life. The Australian retired from football at the age of 32 last...
The post Recent departure shares first post Celtic video; new life looks good appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["That's my concern": ex-Celtic hero highlights problem position ahead of new season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168837</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/thats-my-concern-peter-grant-highlights-problem-position-for-celtic-ahead-of-new-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s pre-season tour of Japan has, I think we can all agree, been a rousing success. As well as boosting our profile off the park,...
The post "That's my concern": ex-Celtic hero highlights problem position ahead of new season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maik Nawrocki hopes his Celtic move can make his next 'dream' come true]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168830</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/maik-nawrocki-hopes-his-celtic-move-can-make-his-next-dream-come-true/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The signing of Polish u21 defender, Maik Nawrocki hogged the headlines as the former Legia Warsaw defender became Brendan Rodgers’ fifth summer signing. Nawrocki spent...
The post Maik Nawrocki hopes his Celtic move can make his next 'dream' come true appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Celtic players set to join Austrian club on loan]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42951</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/27/four-celtic-players-austrian-club/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T09:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have enjoyed a lot of success in recent times. They have won eleven of the last twelve league titles, and have won a domestic treble in five of the last seven seasons. Despite that, there is one complaint that the supporters have had. And that is regarding the club’s inability to bring through their […]
Four Celtic players set to join Austrian club on loan - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Women to face Rangers as Fran Alonso's side book place in Glasgow Cup Final]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168825</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/celtic-women-to-face-rangers-as-fran-alonsos-side-book-place-in-glasgow-cup-final/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fran Alonso looks to continue the success he’s had at Celtic after a 4-0 win over Partick Thistle sent his side into the Glasgow Cup...
The post Celtic Women to face Rangers as Fran Alonso's side book place in Glasgow Cup Final appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOR TODD’S SAKE, CUT IT OUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110315</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/for-todds-sake-cut-it-out/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T07:19:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CHRIS SUTTON, Celtic’s former goal hero, appears to have taken another sideswipe in his ongoing war of words with Toss Cantwell. The ex-Norwich City players have been involved in a verbal spat on social media since Michael Beale signed the one-time much-vaunted midfielder for the Ibrox club in January. Sutton seems to have opened fire [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic in the Fair City]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58184</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-in-the-fair-city/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T07:18:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic arrive this weekend to the capital. It’s been 5 years since Celtic took their side to Dublin with them taking on Shamrock Rovers at Tallaght Stadium and they return this time again with the same manager something I don’t think many would of expected. Brendan Rodgers side will take on Wolves in front of […]
The post Celtic in the Fair City appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New signing left blown away by first Celtic Park visit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168818</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/new-signing-left-blown-away-by-first-celtic-park-visit/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T06:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New signing Maik Nawrocki has told reporters he was ‘shocked’ by the size of Celtic Park on his first visit to the stadium but is...
The post New signing left blown away by first Celtic Park visit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Offers expected for Celtic squad player in wake of Wednesday decision]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168813</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/offers-expected-for-celtic-squad-player-in-wake-of-wednesday-decision/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Italian clubs are expected to follow up on long-standing interest in Celtic defender Stephen Welsh, The Daily Record has reported. [27/07 print edition, page 55]...
The post Report: Offers expected for Celtic squad player in wake of Wednesday decision appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROARING SUCCESS: NEW BHOY IN KROOS CONTROL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110297</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/roaring-success-new-bhoy-in-kroos-control/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T05:40:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MAIK NAWROCKI wants to be a big noise at Celtic after becoming Brendan Rodgers’ fifth pre-season signing. The towering Polish centre-back sealed his anticipated five-year deal from Legia Warsaw yesterday – and he can’t wait to get started in his new home. Nawrocki is particularly looking forward to Champions League nights at Parkhead after admitting [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New signing Maik Nawrocki shares his playing style and personality; what to expect at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168807</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/new-signing-maik-nawrocki-shares-his-playing-style-and-personality-what-to-expect-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T05:15:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maik Nawrocki was officially unveiled as a Celtic player at a media conference at Celtic Park on Wednesday and clued in fans on what to...
The post New signing Maik Nawrocki shares his playing style and personality; what to expect at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MESSI 4 GIAKOUMAKIS 0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110291</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/messi-4-giakoumakis-0/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T05:11:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic striker Giorgos Giakoumakis was a loser when he came face to face with world superstar Lionel Messi last night. The ex-Barcelona star hammered in two first-half goals as his new club Inter Miami romped to a 4-0 victory over Atlanta United in Fort Lauderdale to advance to the knock-out stage of the League [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘SHEER STUPIDITY’: DI CANIO IN THE WARS: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Sixteen)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=94499</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/sheer-stupidity-di-canio-in-the-wars-the-tommy-burns-story-part-sixteen/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-27T04:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS was experiencing extreme turbulence during his third year as Celtic manager in an explosive 1996/97 crusade. The fans’ favourite had returned to the club on July 12 1994 and had won the Scottish Cup in his debut campaign. That was followed by a barren term and all eyes were on the boss as [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All Hail James Forrest – Etims Podcast]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18431</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18431"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T22:33:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Etims get together to discuss: The surreall Pre-Season which has seen Brendan return as if he was never away. Is he Sir Keir Starmer or…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Desi Mond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic reportedly make new offer for Dominik Livakovic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42946</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/26/celtic-new-offer-dominik-livakovic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T22:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans were delighted when the club were linked with a move for Dominik Livakovic early on in the summer transfer window. Many believe that the Hoops need to bring in a new goalkeeper and have not been impressed by Joe Hart’s recent performances, even though the Englishman has done a good job over the […]
Celtic reportedly make new offer for Dominik Livakovic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Head-scratching Al-Ettifaq Celtic post gets a response from Steven Gerrard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168796</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/head-scratching-al-ettifaq-celtic-post-gets-a-response-from-steven-gerrard/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T20:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Al Ettifaq — the Saudi Pro League club managed by Steven Gerrard — sent out a Celtic based post on Wednesday. The Dammam-based club have...
The post Head-scratching Al-Ettifaq Celtic post gets a response from Steven Gerrard appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic urged to sign £35 million player on loan deal]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42942</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/26/celtic-urged-35-million-player-loan/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T20:30:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been very active in the summer transfer window when it comes to signing players. They recently completed their fifth incoming, bringing in Maik Nawrocki from Legia Warsaw. The Polish youth international is very highly-rated and could challenge the likes of Carl Starfelt and Cameron Carter-Vickers for a spot in the backline. All the […]
Celtic urged to sign £35 million player on loan deal - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The full Celtic squad depth picture after Yang, Kwon and Nawrocki arrivals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168780</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-full-celtic-squad-depth-picture-after-yang-kwon-and-nawrocki-arrivals/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T20:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic squad has undergone a fair bit of change since the end of last season. On June 3, the Hoops clinched another domestic treble...
The post The full Celtic squad depth picture after Yang, Kwon and Nawrocki arrivals appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic Invincible makes next move; club announcement made]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168782</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ex-celtic-striker-moussa-dembele-makes-next-move-club-announcement-made/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker, Moussa Dembele has finally sealed his next move after his new club made the announcement on Twitter tonight. Dembele had been out...
The post Ex-Celtic Invincible makes next move; club announcement made appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steven Gerrard’s team pay Celtic tribute on Twitter]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42937</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/26/steven-gerrard-team-celtic-tribute/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T19:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steven Gerrard is not someone that Celtic fans are too fond of. After all, the Englishman managed the Rangers for more than three years. During that time, he was only able to guide them to one trophy. But it was a big one nonetheless, as it prevented the Hoops from completing a historic 10IAR. Gerrard’s […]
Steven Gerrard’s team pay Celtic tribute on Twitter - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic arrival backs up club's status as the biggest and best in Scotland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168774</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/maik-nawrocki-backs-up-celtics-status-as-the-biggest-and-best-in-scotland/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T18:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing Maik Nawrocki says he has left the biggest club in Poland to move to the biggest one in Scotland. The centre-back has...
The post New Celtic arrival backs up club's status as the biggest and best in Scotland appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Honoured": Hyeokkyu Kwon on signing for Celtic; tells the fans exactly what to expect from him]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168769</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/honoured-hyeokkyu-kwon-on-signing-for-celtic-tells-the-fans-exactly-what-to-expect-from-him/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic get the process of unveiling their three latest signings, the fans will be excited to hear from the new players and get a...
The post "Honoured": Hyeokkyu Kwon on signing for Celtic; tells the fans exactly what to expect from him appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing mentions Toni Kroos in media conference]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42933</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/26/new-celtic-signing-toni-kroos-media/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T17:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic might not have made any marquee signings this summer yet, but they have brought in some very highly-rated young talents from around the globe, who can go on to be key players for the club if their development goes according to expectations. The Hoops’ latest addition is Polish youth international, Maik Nawrocki. Nawrocki has […]
New Celtic signing mentions Toni Kroos in media conference - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pleasing comments suggest the Celtic support are about to take over the Aviva Stadium]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168739</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/pleasing-comments-suggest-the-celtic-support-are-about-to-take-over-the-aviva-stadium/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic support may be about to take over the Aviva Stadium this weekend, based on some recent comments. The Hoops are in Dublin for...
The post Pleasing comments suggest the Celtic support are about to take over the Aviva Stadium appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's first real transfer statement arrived on Wednesday; what should happen next - opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168751</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/maik-nawrocki-is-celtics-first-statement-signing-of-the-summer-how-to-build-on-it/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maik Nawrocki’s move to Celtic was announced on Wednesday. The Polish central-defender has joined the club on a five-year deal from Legia Warsaw. It is...
The post Celtic's first real transfer statement arrived on Wednesday; what should happen next - opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's nickname for Maik Nawrocki; player's Instagram message to fans, Legia's classy goodbye]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168747</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-nickname-for-maik-nawrocki-players-instagram-message-to-fans-legias-classy-goodbye/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been a busy week for Celtic and the fans as the club unveiled three new signings to continue strengthening the team under Brendan Rodgers....
The post Celtic's nickname for Maik Nawrocki; player's Instagram message to fans, Legia's classy goodbye appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real Madrid star's Celtic Park comments heard loud and clear by Maik Nawrocki]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168758</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/real-madrid-stars-celtic-park-comments-were-heard-loud-and-clear-by-maik-nawrocki/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maik Nawrocki has been speaking about the atmosphere at Celtic Park on Champions League nights. The Polish defender joined the club on a five-year deal...
The post Real Madrid star's Celtic Park comments heard loud and clear by Maik Nawrocki appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans face ticket headache as SPFL club CEO explains why away ticket allocations are being cut]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168736</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-fans-face-ticket-headache-as-hearts-ceo-explains-why-away-ticket-allocations-are-being-cut/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hearts CEO, Andrew McKinlay has confirmed that the Edinburgh club plan to reduce away ticket allocations next season for all clubs except Hibernian. The Edinburgh...
The post Celtic fans face ticket headache as SPFL club CEO explains why away ticket allocations are being cut appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[K League expert's glowing verdict on new Korean signings will delight the Celtic support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168712</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/k-league-experts-glowing-verdict-on-new-korean-signings-will-delight-the-celtic-support/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic fans will, undoubtedly, have the lowdown on new signings Hyunjun Yang and Hyeokkyu Kwon. The supporters will have all done their research and...
The post K League expert's glowing verdict on new Korean signings will delight the Celtic support appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Italian FA make changes to registration rules; could impact Celtic and other Scottish clubs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168725</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/italian-fa-make-changes-to-registration-rules-could-impact-celtic-and-other-scottish-clubs/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T13:16:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Italian FA have made changes to squad registration rules that could impact Celtic and other Scottish clubs. Italy has become a popular destination for...
The post Italian FA make changes to registration rules; could impact Celtic and other Scottish clubs appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: The unseen Cameron Carter-Vickers work during Celtic Japan trip]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168717</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-unseen-cameron-carter-vickers-work-during-celtic-trip-to-japan/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cameron Carter-Vickers was putting in the hard graft while his Celtic team-mates were in Japan. The first-team squad visited Asia for a week-long tour last...
The post Report: The unseen Cameron Carter-Vickers work during Celtic Japan trip appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kwon Hyeok-kyu, Yang Hyun-Jun and Maik Nawrocki Press Conference]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58179</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/maik-nawrocki-press-conference/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T12:32:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New signings Kwon Hyeok-kyu, Yang Hyun-Jun and Maik Nawrocki will be annouced to the press and members of Celtic Fan media today at a press conference at Celtic Park at 2:30pm.  Maik Nawrocki has become the latest addition to Brendan Rodgers’ Celtic squad after the defender today joined the club on a five-year deal from […]
The post Kwon Hyeok-kyu, Yang Hyun-Jun and Maik Nawrocki Press Conference appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic offered Fabian Rieder boost by Bundesliga club]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42925</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/26/celtic-offered-fabian-rieder-bundesliga/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T12:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the rumours of record-breaking signings this summer, Celtic have not made any such moves till now. Instead, they have brought in Odin Thiago Holm from Valerenga, Marco Tilio from Melbourne City FC, Yang Hyun-jun from Gangwon FC, Kwon Hyeok-kyu from Busan IPark and Maik Nawrocki from Legia Warsaw. All of them are highly-rated youngsters, […]
Celtic offered Fabian Rieder boost by Bundesliga club - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maik Nawrocki and Brendan Rodgers' previous meeting; memorable night for Celtic star]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168701</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/maik-nawrocki-and-brendan-rodgers-previous-meeting-memorable-night-for-celtic-star/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing Maik Nawrocki has already met Brendan Rodgers in his short career. The Polish centre-back may only be 22-years-old and have a handful...
The post Maik Nawrocki and Brendan Rodgers' previous meeting; memorable night for Celtic star appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Brendan Rodgers set to make key backroom addition at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168658</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-set-to-make-key-backroom-addition-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s evolvement and development under Brendan Rodgers looks set to continue this week as the Celtic manager is set to add another member to his...
The post Report: Brendan Rodgers set to make key backroom addition at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maik Nawrocki joins Celtic from Legia Warsaw]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58176</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/maik-nawrocki-joins-celtic-from-legia-warsaw/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T11:31:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maik Nawrocki has become the latest addition to Brendan Rodgers’ Celtic squad after the defender today joined the club on a five-year deal from Legia Warsaw, subject to international clearance. The 22-year-old Polish Under-21 internationalist helped Legia Warsaw win the Polish Cup last season, scoring the final spot-kick in a 6-5 penalty shoot-out victory over […]
The post Maik Nawrocki joins Celtic from Legia Warsaw appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fran Alonso adds sixth summer signing to the Celtic Women's squad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168693</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/murphy-agnew-becomes-fran-alonsos-sixth-addition-to-the-celtic-womens-squad/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have announced that forward, Murphy Agnew has joined the club on a two-year deal. Agnew becomes Fran Alonso’s sixth summer signing as the Spaniard...
The post Fran Alonso adds sixth summer signing to the Celtic Women's squad appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nawrocki, good in air, passes through the lines, focussed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110287</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/nawrocki-good-in-air-passes-through-the-lines-focussed/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T11:01:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic confirmed the signing of German-born Poland youth international central defender Maik Nawrocki (22) this morning.  The player emerged through the Werder Bremen youth system and featured only seven times before going on loan two weeks after his 20th birthday to Warta Poznan in the Polish topflight. He spent half a season at Warta where [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic reference Lennoxtown leak in amusing fashion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168685</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-reference-lennoxtown-leak-in-amusing-fashion/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T10:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have referenced a photo leak from Lennoxtown earlier this week in amusing fashion. On Wednesday morning the club announced the signing of Maik Nawrocki...
The post Celtic reference Lennoxtown leak in amusing fashion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed Dominik Livakovic transfer boost out of nowhere]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42920</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/26/celtic-dominik-livakovic-transfer-boost/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T09:31:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There had been rumours early on in the summer transfer window that Celtic were looking to make a few marquee signings. One of the players that they were being linked with at that point of time was Dominik Livakovic. If the Hoops were able to sign the Croatian national team number one, then it would […]
Celtic handed Dominik Livakovic transfer boost out of nowhere - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: NAWROCKI BECOMES SIGNING No.5]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110278</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-nawrocki-becomes-signing-no-5/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T09:25:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MAIK NAWROCKI became Brendan Rodgers’ fifth pre-season capture when the centre-back signed a five-year contract today. The 22-year-old Polish defender had been targeted by the returning Celtic manager, as CQN reported last week. A transfer deal rising to £5.2million with Legia Warsaw was thrashed out and Nawrocki was quick to agree personal terms. Beaming Hoops gaffer [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maik Nawrocki's first Celtic interview; new signing looking forward to the Champions League]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168675</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/maik-nawrockis-first-celtic-interview-new-signing-looking-forward-to-the-champions-league/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T09:15:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maik Nawrocki has said that he is looking forward to the Champions League next season as the defender delivered his first interview in the green...
The post Maik Nawrocki's first Celtic interview; new signing looking forward to the Champions League appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers speaks as Celtic announce Maik Nawrocki; player reaction, contract details]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168661</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-speaks-as-celtic-announce-maik-nawrocki-player-reaction-contract-details/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T08:32:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have announced Maik Nawrocki as their fifth summer singing in the new era under Brendan Rodgers. The former Legia Warsaw defender joins the club...
The post Brendan Rodgers speaks as Celtic announce Maik Nawrocki; player reaction, contract details appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN SWOOPS FOR BACKROOM RECRUIT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110275</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/brendan-swoops-for-backroom-recruit/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T07:58:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has added analyst Jack Lyons to his Celtic backroom staff. The Scot left the Parkhead side to follow the Irishman when he departed for Leicester City in February 2019. Now the pair are poised to be reunited at the champions following Rodgers’ appointment last month after the exit of Ange Postecoglou for Spurs. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["It’s very different": Matt O'Riley on life at Celtic under Brendan Rodgers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168651</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/its-very-different-matt-oriley-on-life-at-celtic-under-brendan-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Brendan Rodgers returned for a second spell at Celtic, a lot of the chat surrounding the appointment was about whether or not he would...
The post "It’s very different": Matt O'Riley on life at Celtic under Brendan Rodgers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Return of Brendan Rodgers to the Celtic Park Dugout]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58170</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/brendan-rodgers-to-the-celtic-park-dugout/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T07:21:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the curtain came down on last season. Celtic were planning a pre-season Asian tour of Japan and South Korea and Ange Postecoglou was set to lead Celtic for a homecoming of sorts for him after his successful spell in Japan. Maybe the plan was then to move on to South Korea and announce the […]
The post The Return of Brendan Rodgers to the Celtic Park Dugout appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘HARD NOT TO BE VERY HAPPY AT CELTIC,’ ADMITS O’RILEY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110268</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hard-not-to-be-very-happy-at-celtic-admits-oriley/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T06:44:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY insists he doesn’t pay much attention to transfer speculation linking him with a move from Celtic. The smooth 23-year-old midfielder arrived at the club in a bargain £1.5million switch from English third-tier outfit MK Dons in January 2022 – and has seen his value soar with a series of eye-catching displays for the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O'Riley admires Celtic stars even more after trip to Japan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168643</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/matt-oriley-admires-celtic-stars-even-more-after-trip-to-japan/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T06:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O’Riley seems to have even more admiration for Celtic’s Japan stars after a recent trip to the country. The Hoops arrived back in Scotland...
The post Matt O'Riley admires Celtic stars even more after trip to Japan appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pat Bonner's verdict on Brendan Rodgers' Celtic return; what he must do to impress fans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168549</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/pat-bonners-verdict-on-brendan-rodgers-celtic-return-what-he-must-do-to-win-over-the-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T06:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers’ return to Celtic certainly raised a few eyebrows this summer. We all know why, but many fans still can’t believe that he has...
The post Pat Bonner's verdict on Brendan Rodgers' Celtic return; what he must do to impress fans appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NO OLD PALS’ ACT AS CELTIC CULT HERO MAKES LOSING START]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110262</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/no-old-pals-act-as-celtic-cult-hero-makes-losing-start/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T05:45:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC cult hero Efe Ambrose has signed for his SEVENTH Scottish club after agreeing a short-term deal with Queen of the South. The experienced campaigner made a quickfire debut in last night’s League Cup match against East Fife at Palmerston which ended in a goalless draw before the Fifers won 5-3 on penalty-kicks. It was [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["There's so much more to him": Callum McGregor's intriguing insight on Celtic boss]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168581</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/theres-so-much-more-to-him-callum-mcgregors-intriguing-insight-on-celtic-boss/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T05:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The return of Brendan Rodgers to Paradise was not welcomed by all Celtic fans when the news was announced that the Irishman was coming back...
The post "There's so much more to him": Callum McGregor's intriguing insight on Celtic boss appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has already made development intentions clear to Celtic stars]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168636</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-has-already-made-development-intentions-clear-to-celtic-stars/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T05:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has already made his intentions to develop young Celtic talent clear. The Celtic first-team squad Rodgers has inherited is a pretty young one....
The post Brendan Rodgers has already made development intentions clear to Celtic stars appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC DOUBLE BOOST]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110259</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-double-boost/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T04:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has received a welcome double boost as he prepares for the new season. CAMERON CARTER-VICKERS, who missed the final six games of the previous campaign after undergoing knee surgery, is poised to resume full training. MAIK NAWROCKI, the towering Polish centre-back targeted by the returning boss, is on the brink of finalising his switch [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PIERRE’S PAY ROW, BOSS SEES RED IN OLD FIRM FLARE-UP: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Fifteen)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=94452</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/pierres-pay-row-boss-sees-red-in-old-firm-flare-up-the-tommy-burns-story-part-fifteen/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T04:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS’ third year as Celtic manager was developing into a rollicking rollercoaster. The fans’ favourite had returned to the club on July 12 1994 and had won the Scottish Cup in his debut campaign. That was followed by a barren term and all eyes were on the boss as a new challenging and testing [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arsenal make Kieran Tierney decision amid Celtic return rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42917</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/25/arsenal-kieran-tierney-celtic-return/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T22:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the arrival of Brendan Rodgers for a second stint in the Parkhead hot seat, there were rumours that Celtic were looking to make some marquee signings in the summer transfer window, with an aim to make an impact in the UEFA Champions League group stage. More than a month has passed since then but […]
Arsenal make Kieran Tierney decision amid Celtic return rumours - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player told to not join West Ham United this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42909</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/25/celtic-player-west-ham-united-summer/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T21:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already seen one key player leave the club this summer in Jota. The Portuguese winger has completed a £25 million move to Al-Ittihad. It was unexpected and the Hoops now need to replace him. The 24-year-old had been a nailed on starter over the past couple of seasons. And it is quite clear […]
Celtic player told to not join West Ham United this summer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic complete Real Madrid deal and make a big SWPL statement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168615</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/celtic-complete-real-madrid-deal-and-make-a-big-swpl-statement/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have announced the loan signing of Paula Partido from Real Madrid. The Spanish teenager joins up with Fran Alonso’s side for the duration of...
The post Celtic complete Real Madrid deal and make a big SWPL statement appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player makes permanent exit to join French club]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42901</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/25/celtic-player-exit-french-club/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T19:31:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With two more new signings announced by Celtic so far this week in the form of Yang Hyun-jun and Kwon Hyeok-kyu, and another expected very soon, the focus has been more on incoming players. But Brendan Rodgers and his team will have a close eye on the need for some players to move out too. […]
Celtic player makes permanent exit to join French club - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Underrated Celtic quality finally gets some credit as Hoops star tops worldwide list]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168626</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/underrated-liel-abada-quality-finally-gets-some-credit-as-celtic-star-tops-worldwide-list/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star Liel Abada has finally received some credit for an underrated quality he possesses. The Israel international has been a terrific contributor for Celtic...
The post Underrated Celtic quality finally gets some credit as Hoops star tops worldwide list appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Soul Podcast The Fields of Athenry Christy Dignam Tribute with Aslan’s Billy McGuinness]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58167</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-soul-podcast-the-fields-of-athenry-christy-dignam-tribute-with-aslans-billy-mcguinness/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T18:44:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are in Dublin this weekend to take on Wolves in a pre-season friendly at the Aviva Stadium. One of Dublin’s finest bands Aslan have just released their version of the “The Fields of Athenry” The last recording made by the band with their lead singer, Christy Dignam who sadly passed away recently. Christy will […]
The post Celtic Soul Podcast The Fields of Athenry Christy Dignam Tribute with Aslan’s Billy McGuinness appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I couldn't say no": New signing Luana Muñoz on why she signed for Celtic Women]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168606</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/i-couldnt-say-no-new-signing-luana-munoz-on-why-she-signed-for-celtic-women/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic Women signing, Luana Muñoz has opened up on why she took the leap to leave Argentina and make the move to Glasgow to...
The post "I couldn't say no": New signing Luana Muñoz on why she signed for Celtic Women appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans urged to make active choice in Dublin this weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168593</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-fans-urged-to-make-active-choice-in-dublin-this-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans have been given some advice ahead of this weekend’s fixture in Dublin. The Celts are preparing for their latest pre-season clash, with Wolves...
The post Celtic fans urged to make active choice in Dublin this weekend appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic-linked player appears to drop major transfer hint]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42904</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/25/celtic-linked-player-transfer-hint/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T18:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been superb when it comes to identifying the right talents from around the world and then bringing them to Parkhead. Just this summer, they have added four fresh faces to their ranks in the form of Odin Thiago Holm, Marco Tilio, Kwon Hyeok-kyu and Yang Hyun-jun. And more are expected to follow over […]
Celtic-linked player appears to drop major transfer hint - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic hero explains his role within the Football Association of Ireland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168598</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-hero-pat-bonner-explains-his-role-within-the-football-association-of-ireland/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic goalkeeper, Pat Bonner, is a legend of the club in the eyes of the Celtic support. Certainly in my time growing up, Bonner...
The post Former Celtic hero explains his role within the Football Association of Ireland appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Explained: Celtic's pot three chances and who you should support in Champions League qualifying]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168580</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/explained-celtics-pot-three-chances-and-who-you-should-be-supporting-in-champions-league-qualifying/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T16:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second round of Champions League qualifying got underway on Tuesday evening and there is some interest for Celtic. Yes, we’ve had our spot booked...
The post Explained: Celtic's pot three chances and who you should support in Champions League qualifying appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five players who could still depart Celtic this summer as positive streamlining continues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168571</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/five-players-who-could-still-depart-celtic-this-summer-as-positive-streamlining-continues/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have carried out some positive work in the transfer window in recent weeks. The likes of Marco Tilio, Hyeokkyu Kwon and Hyunjun Yang have...
The post Five players who could still depart Celtic this summer as positive streamlining continues appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic make Flag Day announcement; Paradise set for opening day celebrations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168535</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-make-flag-day-announcement-paradise-set-for-opening-day-celebrations/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have announced that the opening league fixture of the new season against Ross County has now officially sold out. In an announcement on Twitter,...
The post Celtic make Flag Day announcement; Paradise set for opening day celebrations appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic exit confirmed as fringe player joins French lower league club]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168528</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-defender-osaze-urhoghide-attracting-interest-from-french-lower-league-side/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender, Osaze Urhoghide has joined French Ligue 2 side Amiens after the club made the announcement on their official website. [Amiens FC] After losing...
The post Celtic exit confirmed as fringe player joins French lower league club appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ONE GAME – AND IT’S FAREWELL TO OSAZE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110252</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/one-game-and-its-farewell-to-osaze/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T13:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OSAZE URHOGHIDE has left Celtic after just one start in two years after arriving from Sheffield Wednesday. The 23-year-old defender took his bow in the 3-2 Europa League win over Real Betis at Parkhead in December 2021 – and was never seen again. Urhoghide spent last season on a second loan stint at Belgian outfit [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic defender 'jumped at the chance' to sign for 6th SPFL club since leaving Paradise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168520</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/former-celtic-defender-signs-for-6th-spfl-club-since-leaving-paradise/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T12:43:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic defender, Efe Ambrose has signed for Queen of the South in a short-term deal that will last until the end of this year....
The post Former Celtic defender 'jumped at the chance' to sign for 6th SPFL club since leaving Paradise appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘UNBELIEVABLE,’ CELTIC CENTURIAN EYES LEGEND’S HAUL OF FAME]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110248</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/unbelievable-celtic-centurian-eyes-legends-haul-of-fame/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T12:35:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JAMES FORREST is on course to eclipse Celtic great Billy McNeill’s trophy haul. The unassuming winger has lifted 22 domestic honours, the same total amassed by the Lisbon Lion in his playing days. However, McNeill is one ahead after guiding Jock Stein’s all-conquering team to their historic European Cup triumph in Lisbon on May 25 [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aberdeen keen on signing Celtic player this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42898</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/25/aberdeen-keen-signing-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T12:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of the Celtic headlines in recent days have been dominated by arrivals. The club recently announced the signings of Kwon Hyeok-kyu from Busan IPark and Yang Hyun-jun from Gangwon FC. They are believed to be close to signing Maik Nawrocki from Legia Warsaw in a £4 million transfer as well. On the other hand, […]
Aberdeen keen on signing Celtic player this summer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor's valuable advice to the youngsters on Celtic's tour of Japan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168492</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/callum-mcgregors-valuable-advice-to-the-youngsters-on-celtics-tour-of-japan/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic captain, Callum McGregor, has offered some valuable advice to the young Celtic players who are on the verge of the Celtic first team. Brendan...
The post Callum McGregor's valuable advice to the youngsters on Celtic's tour of Japan appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lots to do before September]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110247</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/lots-to-do-before-september/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T11:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After two significant departures in the form of Aaron Mooy and Jota, Celtic’s incoming transfers rose to four yesterday with confirmation of five-year deals for Koreans Kwon Hyeok-kyu (22) and Yang Hyun-jun (21).  Marco Tilio (21) and Odin Thiago Holm (20) arrived earlier this month.  German-born Polish defender Maik Nawrocki (22) is in town and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The promising Australian youth defender on trial at Celtic B]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168482</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/the-promising-australian-defender-on-trial-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Celtic announcing the signings of Hyunjun Yang and Hyeokkyu Kwon yesterday, the club are expected to follow that up at some point this week,...
The post The promising Australian youth defender on trial at Celtic B appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic star shone recently against elite opposition; massively exciting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168478</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/hyunjun-yang-shone-recently-against-elite-opposition-massively-exciting-from-a-celtic-perspective/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing Hyunjun Yang already has experience of playing against some top players. The 21-year-old was confirmed as Celtic‘s third signing of the summer...
The post New Celtic star shone recently against elite opposition; massively exciting appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upcoming Celtic clash to get proper television treatment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168467</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/upcoming-celtic-pre-season-clash-to-get-proper-television-treatment/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s fixture against Wolves on Saturday will be shown live on television. As we told you last week, Celtic have already announced some positive arrangements...
The post Upcoming Celtic clash to get proper television treatment appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic linked with Manchester United transfer target]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42894</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/25/celtic-linked-manchester-united-target/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T09:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have quite the reputation for signing young talents from around the world, developing them at Parkhead and ultimately helping them get moves to one of the top five European leagues. Thus, the Hoops are obviously an attractive option for players looking to showcase their talents at a high level in Europe. Just this summer, […]
Celtic linked with Manchester United transfer target - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor explains his 'new found appreciation' for Celtic's Asian stars after Japan Tour]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168464</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/callum-mcgregor-explains-his-new-found-appreciation-for-celtics-asian-stars-after-japan-tour/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that the Japan Tour is officially concluded for the summer, Callum McGregor has been speaking about how the trip has made him appreciate the...
The post Callum McGregor explains his 'new found appreciation' for Celtic's Asian stars after Japan Tour appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A strange English media take as Japan record is broken days after Celtic visit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168453</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/a-strange-english-media-take-as-japan-record-is-broken-days-after-celtic-visit/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T08:14:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic should be jealous of the star-power of Manchester City in Japan, according to some English media. Brendan Rodgers’ first-team have now returned back to...
The post A strange English media take as Japan record is broken days after Celtic visit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GO ON, CELTIC, MAIK OUR DAY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110238</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/go-on-celtic-maik-our-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T08:05:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is edging closer to completing a triple signing swoop with Polish centre-back Maik Nawrocki poised to pledge his future to Celtic. The returning Hoops boss yesterday completed the deals for South Korean double-act Yang Hyun-jun, a winger from Gangwon FC, and midfielder anchorman Hyun Hyeok-kyu, from Busan iPark. They join Norwegian midfielder Odin Thiago [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's interest in talented defender looks over; but not because of Fabrizio Romano's update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168448</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtics-interest-in-talented-defender-looks-over-but-not-because-of-fabrizio-romanos-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have long been linked with young defender Xavier Mbuyamba over the course of the summer. 67 Hail Hail first discussed Celtic’s apparent interest in...
The post Celtic's interest in talented defender looks over; but not because of Fabrizio Romano's update appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I WILL WORK HARD,’ NEW BHOY KWON’S PROMISE TO THE FANS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110226</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-will-work-hard-new-bhoy-kwons-promise-to-the-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T07:23:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MIDFIELDER Kwon Hyeok-kyu completed a South Korean double when he followed compatriot Yang Hyun-jun in making a dream come true by signing for Celtic. The 22-year-old anchorman also agreed a five-year deal following Brendan Rodgers’ fourth pre-season signing as he strengthens his squad for the new campaign. Kwon admitted he once envisaged following in the bootsteps [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic already enjoying big benefit of new Brendan Rodgers approach]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168436</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-already-enjoying-big-benefit-of-new-brendan-rodgers-approach/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T06:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If it’s one thing Celtic players have made clear since Brendan Rodgers returned as manager, it’s that they’re enjoying a new, more open feel to...
The post Celtic already enjoying big benefit of new Brendan Rodgers approach appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic flex European connection in promising fashion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168444</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-flex-european-connection-in-promising-fashion/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T05:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are set to send two of the B team’s brightest prospects out on a loan to Europe, having struck up an ongoing partnership with...
The post Celtic flex European connection in promising fashion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star opens up on 'frustrating' 5-start season, lauds what Brendan Rodgers now brings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168439</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/james-forrest-opens-up-on-frustrating-5-start-season-lauds-what-brendan-rodgers-now-brings-to-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T05:11:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic winger James Forrest has admitted it was “frustrating” not to start as many games as he would have liked last season but is now...
The post Celtic star opens up on 'frustrating' 5-start season, lauds what Brendan Rodgers now brings appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TWENTY-SIX YEARS AGO: THE SNAG THAT ALMOST KO’d HENRIK DEAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=71110</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/twenty-six-years-ago-the-snag-that-almost-kod-henrik-deal/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T05:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HENRIK LARSSON became a genuine Celtic legend during his glorious, mesmerising and breathtaking seven years at the club. But his move from Feyenoord to Paradise exactly 26 years ago almost didn’t take place when an eleventh-hour hitch materialised. Today, in a CQN EXCLUSIVE extract from Davie Hay’s autobiography, ‘The Quiet Assassin’, co-authored by Alex Gordon, we reveal [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PROBLEM PILE-UP IN PARADISE: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Fourteen)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=94397</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/problem-pile-up-in-paradise-the-tommy-burns-story-part-fourteen/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T04:30:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE third year of Tommy Burns’ managerial career at Celtic was not going according to plan. The fans’ favourite had returned to the club on July 12 1994 and had won the Scottish Cup in his debut campaign. That was followed by a barren term and all eyes were on the boss as a new [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>