<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-09-10T14:08:18.379Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Dalglish says Celtic got "one of the transfer bargains of the millennium" from £4m deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173907</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kenny-dalglish-says-celtic-got-one-of-the-transfer-bargains-of-the-millennium-from-4m-deal/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T13:54:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend Kenny Dalglish has lauded striker Kyogo Furuhashi after scoring yet another derby goal last weekend. The Japanese forward now has six goals in...
The post Kenny Dalglish says Celtic got "one of the transfer bargains of the millennium" from £4m deal appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic urged to bring back former striker on free transfer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44085</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/10/celtic-urged-bring-back-former-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T12:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic could do with another striker at this point in time. There were suggestions that the club were looking for one towards the end of the summer transfer window but an addition up top was not made. Luis Palma is capable of playing in a more central role as well though, so perhaps he could […]
Celtic urged to bring back former striker on free transfer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CROCKED CELT ‘SEEMS TO BE ANGRY’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111825</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/crocked-celt-seems-to-be-angry/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T09:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIEL ABADA has joined the growing Celtic injury list – and he could face a MONTH on the sidelines to add to Brendan Rodgers’ woes. The Israeli wing ace has been sent home from his country’s international squad after sustaining a knock in training. The Hoops medical staff will check the extent of the problem, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JOCK STEIN: ‘THE BIG MAN, ME AND GOING ON STRIKE’: DAVIE HAY LOOKS BACK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=54271</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/jock-stein-the-big-man-me-and-going-on-strike-davie-hay-looks-back/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T04:32:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAVIE HAY mourned the loss of a good friend and mentor when Jock Stein passed away 38 years ago today. However, the Celtic legend recalls a time when he and the Hoops gaffer were at loggerheads. Here is an extract from Davie’s autobiography, ‘The Quiet Assassin,‘ co-authored by Alex Gordon and published by Black and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JOCK STEIN: TOP TEN QUOTES]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=54260</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/jock-stein-top-ten-quotes/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T04:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WHEN Jock Stein talked, others listened. Here are 10 of some his most notable quotes: “Football is nothing without fans.” *** “Cups are not won by individuals, but by men in a team who put their club before personal prestige.” *** “Unlike many other Celts, I cannot claim that Celtic was my first love … [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JOCK STEIN: ‘WHEN WILL WE SEE YOUR LIKE AGAIN?’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=54252</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/jock-stein-when-will-we-see-your-like-again/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T04:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LEGENDARY Celtic manager Jock Stein, at the age of 62, passed away on this day 38 years ago. This is an extract from author Alex Gordon’s ‘Lisbon Lions: 40th Anniversary Celebration‘ publication which paid tribute to the Big Man. JOCK STEIN had his back turned to the pitch when West German referee Kurt Tschenscher put the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY CALLAGHAN: GREAT UNCAPPED CELTS (Part Six)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.cqnmagazine.com/?p=4894</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/tommy-callaghan-great-uncapped-celts-part-six/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T04:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CQN is turning the spotlight once again on the Celtic players who never had the honour of playing for their country. Tommy Callaghan was Jock Stein’s third signing for the club – following Joe McBride and Willie Wallace – when he arrived from Dunfermline in 1968. He became a key player for Big Jock and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player earns praise from Jurgen Klinsmann after debut]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44031</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/09/celtic-player-jurgen-klinsmann-debut/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T22:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Playing for Celtic can help your international career. That’s pretty clear from this break with one Hoops ace even making his debut for his national team. There have been some question marks at times about whether playing in the Scottish Premiership could hurt such prospects. Especially when both Kyogo Furuhashi and Reo Hatate missed out […]
Celtic player earns praise from Jurgen Klinsmann after debut - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heartbreak for Celtic after dramatic Saturday night UWCL 11-10 penalties defeat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173900</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/heartbreak-for-celtic-after-dramatic-saturday-night-uwcl-11-10-penalties-defeat/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T21:03:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic FC Women are out of the UEFA Women’s Champions League after a dramatic penalty shoot-out defeat against Valerenga in Norway. Celtic lost a very...
The post Heartbreak for Celtic after dramatic Saturday night UWCL 11-10 penalties defeat appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Beale on brink of sack after losing to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44077</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/09/michael-beale-brink-sack-losing-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T21:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Michael Beale arrived as the manager of the Rangers, he came in with a lot of expectations and many of their fans believed that he was the man to topple Celtic. After all, he was a part of Steven Gerrard’s coaching staff at Ibrox and was believed to be the mastermind behind the team […]
Michael Beale on brink of sack after losing to Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sead Haksabanovic makes questionable Celtic claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44074</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/09/sead-haksabanovic-makes-celtic-claim/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T19:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Haksabanovic left Celtic on Deadline Day to join Stoke City on a season-long loan. It was a move that made sense for all parties involved. The player certainly was not getting a lot of chances at Parkhead and did not seem to be particularly happy with his situation, judging from his social media activity before […]
Sead Haksabanovic makes questionable Celtic claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating goals they didn't score; hilarious Celtic Rangers video emerges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173894</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celebrating-goals-they-didnt-score-hilarious-celtic-rangers-video-emerges/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T18:32:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every time Celtic win a derby match against Rangers it’s satisfying for a number of different reasons. It gives the club an obvious sporting advantage...
The post Celebrating goals they didn't score; hilarious Celtic Rangers video emerges appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed injury boost ahead of Champions League]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44070</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/09/celtic-handed-injury-champions-league/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T18:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will take on Dundee FC right after the international break. But fans cannot be blamed for already having half an eye on the upcoming Champions League campaign. The Hoops are set to face Feyenoord away at De Kuip in their opening game of the group stage of Europe’s elite competition. Of course, Celtic were […]
Celtic handed injury boost ahead of Champions League - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend Scott Brown releases lengthy statement on Instagram after Fleetwood Town sacking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173889</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-legend-scott-brown-releases-lengthy-statement-on-instagram-after-fleetwood-town-sacking/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T16:59:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic captain Scott Brown has had his say after leaving his position as Fleetwood Town manager last weekend. The English League One side parted...
The post Celtic legend Scott Brown releases lengthy statement on Instagram after Fleetwood Town sacking appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World-famous musician shares picture with Celtic man]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44066</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/09/world-famous-musician-celtic-man/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T16:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic certainly do have their fair share of world-famous supporters. The likes of Rod Stewart and Lewis Capaldi have never hidden their love for the club. Snoop Dogg has also been seen wearing the Hoops on more than one occasion. And it looks like we might have to add another name to that list very […]
World-famous musician shares picture with Celtic man - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic injury worries deepen as scan results provide bad news; major doubt for Champions League]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173884</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-injury-worries-deepen-after-liel-abada-scan-results-major-doubt-for-champions-league-opener/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T15:53:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The news from Bucharest on Liel Abada isn’t positive after the Celtic winger limped out of Israel training ahead of their match against Romania. Israeli...
The post Celtic injury worries deepen as scan results provide bad news; major doubt for Champions League appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[91% pass rate, defensive importance; Celtic star shines alongside expensive midfield at int'l level]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173879</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/91-pass-rate-defensive-importance-celtic-hero-shines-alongside-expensive-midfield-at-intl-level/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T15:10:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It may have been Scott McTominay and John McGinn who stole the headlines in Scotland’s midfield on Friday night, but Celtic captain Callum McGregor was...
The post 91% pass rate, defensive importance; Celtic star shines alongside expensive midfield at int'l level appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exciting new Celtic Bhoy cited as part of "generational change" for his country by national boss]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173874</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/new-celtic-bhoy-cited-as-part-of-generational-change-for-his-country-by-national-boss/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T14:37:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyunjun Yang made his debut for South Korea on Thursday night and although he only got a few minutes of action, he already has an...
The post Exciting new Celtic Bhoy cited as part of "generational change" for his country by national boss appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["It's obvious"; Joe Ledley left very impressed by Celtic star's progress since Rodgers came in]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173869</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/its-obvious-joe-ledley-impressed-as-celtic-star-ups-his-game-from-last-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T13:42:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic midfielder Joe Ledley has given a big thumbs up to Matt O’Riley and his progress working under Brendan Rodgers this season. O’Riley has...
The post "It's obvious"; Joe Ledley left very impressed by Celtic star's progress since Rodgers came in appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player ruled out for a month in fresh injury blow]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44062</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/09/celtic-player-fresh-injury-blow/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T13:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been struggling with injury problems at the start of the 2023/24 campaign. Brendan Rodgers’ side were able to get a win away at Ibrox last weekend but that does not mean that they are in good form at the moment. It was their first victory in three games. This team needs to build […]
Celtic player ruled out for a month in fresh injury blow - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can it really be 45 years ?]]></title>
        <id>http://celticunderground.net/?p=6639</id>
        <link href="http://celticunderground.net/can-it-really-be-45-years/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T09:36:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks the 45th anniversary of one of my favourite Celtic games of all time. In an excerpt taken from the book, Ten Men Won The League, we take a look back at a memorable game from 1978. These were still the days of drinking alcohol in the ground and open terracings. A more violent, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>St Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton is concerned about one Celtic star's big game ability but new Bhoy gets good review]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173864</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-has-concerns-about-david-turnbull-at-celtic-but-new-signing-gets-positive-review/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T09:21:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton has been running the rule over Brendan Rodgers’ midfield options at Celtic during the international break, as the Bhoys prepare for a very...
The post Chris Sutton is concerned about one Celtic star's big game ability but new Bhoy gets good review appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: ‘NO BAD FOR AN EFFIN’ LINSEMAN, EH, WALTER?’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111790</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-no-bad-for-an-effin-linseman-eh-walter/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T04:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AS a veteran of way too many Hampden and Wembley skirmishes – and I’ve got the scars to prove it – I am looking forward to Tuesday’s 150th anniversary match between Scotland and England at “Celtic’s second home,” as Bertie Auld used to call our national stadium. Contrary to popular belief, I was not among [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JOHN FALLON: GREAT UNCAPPED CELTS (Part Five)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.cqnmagazine.com/?p=4885</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/john-fallon-great-uncapped-celts-part-five/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T04:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CQN is turning the spotlight once again on the Celtic players who never had the honour of playing for their country. Goalkeeper John Fallon played an important part in Celtic winning the Scottish Cup when they overcame Dunfermline 3-2 in April 1965 – the club’s first silverware in eight years. He was in Jock Stein’s [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing Luis Palma was close to joining Portuguese club]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44039</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/08/celtic-signing-luis-palma-portuguese/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T22:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many Celtic fans were unhappy with the club’s summer business, with no star names arriving at Parkhead despite the Scottish champions making a number of signings. One of those was Luis Palma, who signed a 5-year contract with the Hoops after joining from Greek side Aris FC for a transfer fee believed to be around […]
New Celtic signing Luis Palma was close to joining Portuguese club - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Wyatt-Hupton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic make brilliant announcement about Parkhead]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44049</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/08/celtic-make-announcement-parkhead/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T21:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are one of the most popular football teams on the planet. Those looking from the outside might not fully realise just how big the fanbase of the club is. After all, the Scottish Premiership is not one of the best-known leagues all over the world. But it is no joke to put 60,000 fans […]
Celtic make brilliant announcement about Parkhead - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing tells homeland media how big Bhoys move is for him, first impressions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173859</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/luis-palma-tells-honduran-media-how-much-celtic-move-means-to-him-first-impressions/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T20:38:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Luis Palma was only at Celtic for a matter of days before jetting off to Miami training and then on to Jamaica for upcoming duties...
The post New Celtic signing tells homeland media how big Bhoys move is for him, first impressions appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TV details confirmed for must-watch Saturday Celtic event]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173856</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/tv-details-confirmed-for-celtics-must-watch-saturday-uwcl-event/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T20:13:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic FC Women’s fixture away to Valerenga on Saturday will be broadcast live to worldwide subscribers of the club’s Celtic TV service, including those in...
The post TV details confirmed for must-watch Saturday Celtic event appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key Celtic player suffers injury on international duty]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44045</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/08/key-celtic-player-injury-international/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T19:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a lot of positivity around Celtic Park at the moment after the team were able to get a 1-0 win over the Rangers away at Ibrox last weekend. Heading into that game, Brendan Rodgers’ side had not been in great form, winning only two of their four games. But a Glasgow Derby victory […]
Key Celtic player suffers injury on international duty - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin O'Neill notes "really huge blow" to Rangers beyond derby defeat to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173851</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/martin-oneill-notes-really-huge-blow-to-rangers-beyond-derby-defeat-to-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T19:25:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic manager Martin O’Neill has pointed out the widening gap between the Bhoys and arch-rivals Rangers – not just on the pitch but off...
The post Martin O'Neill notes "really huge blow" to Rangers beyond derby defeat to Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic statement helps add enough pressure to prompt pleasing U-turn]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173848</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-statement-helps-add-enough-pressure-to-prompt-pleasing-u-turn/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T18:43:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The joint chorus of messaging from Scottish football regarding proposed plans that would drastically impact the movement of football fans across the country has prompted...
The post Celtic statement helps add enough pressure to prompt pleasing U-turn appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recently sacked manager set to replace Celtic legend]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44042</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/08/recently-manager-replace-celtic-legend/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T18:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Brown enjoyed a very promising debut campaign in management with Fleetwood Town, improving their position in the English League One while going on an unexpected run in the FA Cup as well. Of course, Celtic fans would have been watching closely, as the club icon is considered by many as a future prospect to […]
Recently sacked manager set to replace Celtic legend - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Struggling Celtic player told what his biggest problem is]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44036</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/08/struggling-celtic-player-told-problem/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T15:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The departure of Ange Postecoglou and the arrival of Brendan Rodgers has naturally had an impact on a number of players. Both managers are known for their building winning teams, but the approach that they take to that is pretty different. And one Celtic player in particular seems to be having a tough time adjusting […]
Struggling Celtic player told what his biggest problem is - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confirmed: Celtic Park finally gets the EA Sports treatment and it looks stunning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173844</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/confirmed-celtic-park-finally-gets-the-ea-sports-treatment-and-it-looks-stunning/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T15:13:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Park is finally confirmed to be featuring in the latest edition of EA Sports’ football video game series and the club have uploaded some...
The post Confirmed: Celtic Park finally gets the EA Sports treatment and it looks stunning appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio want to sign Celtic player who could leave soon]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44033</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/08/lazio-want-sign-celtic-player-leave/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T12:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are set to come up against Lazio in the UEFA Champions League this season, having been placed in the same group alongside Atletico Madrid and Feyenoord. The Hoops had met the Italian club some years back in the Europa League, and had impressively won both those games, home and away, under the management of […]
Lazio want to sign Celtic player who could leave soon - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Celtic's current UEFA ranking compares to Champions League rivals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173831</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/how-celtics-current-uefa-ranking-compares-to-champions-league-rivals/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans are counting down the days until the team returns to the UEFA Champions League. We’re no different here at 67 Hail Hail. It’s...
The post How Celtic's current UEFA ranking compares to Champions League rivals appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans can get their Hoops fix this weekend; Masters Cup chosen for live coverage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173825</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-fans-can-get-their-hoops-fix-this-weekend-masters-cup-chosen-for-live-coverage/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans will be able to get their Hoops fix this weekend when the Masters Cup takes place at the Braehead Arena. Masters Football is...
The post Celtic fans can get their Hoops fix this weekend; Masters Cup chosen for live coverage appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uefa funding, haves and have nots]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111821</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/uefa-funding-haves-and-have-nots/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T11:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uefa’s new funding distribution model, announced yesterday, is a bit of a mixed bag for Celtic.  Payments for performance in the Champions League increase, which is a nod to clubs from the big leagues, who always perform better.  This will be partly paid for by a reduction in distribution from the TV Pot, currently a [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Still basking in the sun after beating the rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58378</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/still-basking-in-the-sun-after-beating-the-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T10:56:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This international break Celtic will have 11 players on duty with their countries. Hopefully they all come back fit and pick up no injuries as we bask in the September sun after beating the rangers on Sunday. It was a sweet victory. Celtic went into the game with a long list of injuries and on […]
The post Still basking in the sun after beating the rangers appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ballsy Brendan Rodgers call that went under the radar in Celtic derby win]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173796</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-ballsy-brendan-rodgers-call-that-went-under-the-radar-in-celtic-derby-win/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers led Celtic to victory at Ibrox on Sunday, and he did it with the majority of the squad he inherited. There was a...
The post The ballsy Brendan Rodgers call that went under the radar in Celtic derby win appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic anthem makes an appearance alongside Larsson, Keane and Petrov in Bulgaria]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173818</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-anthem-makes-an-appearance-alongside-larsson-keane-and-petrov-in-bulgaria/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There was a pretty big Celtic connection at a charity match organised by Stiliyan Petrov in Sofia this week. Almost 20,000 people are said to...
The post Celtic anthem makes an appearance alongside Larsson, Keane and Petrov in Bulgaria appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hail "incredible response" to limited edition kit; disappointing news for online shoppers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173838</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-hail-incredible-response-to-special-kit-but-theres-disappointing-news-for-online-shoppers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have offered an update on the ‘limited edition 120 years of Hoops jersey’ that was launched a week ago. Last Friday, the much-hyped kit...
The post Celtic hail "incredible response" to limited edition kit; disappointing news for online shoppers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Luis Palma international schedule that could hold up first Celtic start]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173790</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-luis-palma-international-schedule-that-could-hold-up-first-celtic-start/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans are patiently waiting to see new recruit Luis Palma in action for the club. The winger, who joined on a five-year deal from...
The post The Luis Palma international schedule that could hold up first Celtic start appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UEFA announce more details about the vast Champions League pot on offer to Celtic next season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173809</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/uefa-announce-more-details-about-the-vast-champions-league-pot-on-offer-to-celtic-next-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As you will know by now, the UEFA Champions League is entering a new era from new season and Celtic will be involved. The Champions...
The post UEFA announce more details about the vast Champions League pot on offer to Celtic next season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recent Celtic signing is now a full international; Hoops may have a star on their hands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173783</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-hyunjun-yang-rapid-rise-continues-and-celtic-may-have-a-star-on-their-hands/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic attacker Hyunjun Yang’s rapid rise continued on Thursday as he made his debut for South Korea. The speedy winger joined the Hoops from Gangwon...
The post Recent Celtic signing is now a full international; Hoops may have a star on their hands appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HAIL THE HART STOPPER]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111809</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hail-the-hart-stopper/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T05:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART will be the man in possession of the gloves when Celtic embark on another Champions League quest. The 36-year-old 75 times-capped England international keeper has surely answered his critics with his recent displays, particularly his sound and near-flawless performance in the 1-0 win at Ibrox on Sunday. The shotstopper utilised all his experience to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers shares his plans for international break; change from first Celtic spell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173802</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-shares-his-plans-for-international-break-change-from-his-first-celtic-spell/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers says he wants to enjoy more of Scotland in his second stint as Celtic manager. Rodgers returned to the Hoops hot seat in...
The post Brendan Rodgers shares his plans for international break; change from first Celtic spell appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BOBBY LENNOX 10 ALBIAN AJETI 9]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111805</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/bobby-lennox-10-albian-ajeti-9/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T05:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bobby Lennox scored TEN goals in two games within two weeks in 1968. That’s one more strike than Albian Ajeti managed in TWO years at the Parkhead club. The expensive Swiss misfit, reportedly on £25,000-per-week, eventually left the Hoops this week with the tag of being one of the worst purchases in the club’s history. Ajeti [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODDIE MacDONALD: GREAT UNCAPPED CELTS (Part Four)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.cqnmagazine.com/?p=4792</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/roddie-macdonald-great-uncapped-celts-part-four/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T04:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CQN is turning the spotlight once again on the Celtic players who never had the honour of playing for their country. Roddie MacDonald became a trusted centre-half for Jock Stein as he searched for a long-term replacement for club icon Billy McNeill. However, the towering Highlander was never deemed good enough to get into a Scotland [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player admits he enjoyed keeping Ibrox quiet]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44001</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/07/celtic-player-enjoyed-ibrox-quiet/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T22:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic might not have brought big-name players this summer, but there are certainly a whole host of new faces at the club right now after nine additions were made in the recently concluded transfer window. And it could have been a tough early test at Ibrox for new signing Gustaf Lagerbielke. Instead, it looks like […]
Celtic player admits he enjoyed keeping Ibrox quiet - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Journalist claims Celtic failed to make two priority signings]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44023</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/07/journalist-claims-celtic-two-signings/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T21:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are coming off an interesting summer transfer window. On one hand, the club made plenty of signings. Nine new players were brought in, seven on a permanent basis and two, Nat Phillips and Paulo Bernardo, on loan. But on the other hand, they did not bring in experienced and established names to Parkhead, something […]
Journalist claims Celtic failed to make two priority signings - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's place in global Opta Power Rankings compared to Champions League opponents]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173780</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-place-in-global-opta-power-rankings-compared-to-champions-league-opponents/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T19:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are undoubtedly the underdogs heading into the UEFA Champions League group stage, but Brendan Rodgers and his team will relish that status and look...
The post Celtic's place in global Opta Power Rankings compared to Champions League opponents appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur player holds talks amid Celtic rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44020</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/07/tottenham-hotspur-talks-celtic-rumours/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T19:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic did not make any high-profile additions to their squad this summer, to the disappointment of many fans. The biggest name that they brought in is arguably Nat Phillips. And even he is only on a season-long loan and was barely playing at Liverpool. That does not mean that the Hoops were not linked with […]
Tottenham Hotspur player holds talks amid Celtic rumours - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boyd left bemused by Rangers failure to stop excellent Celtic exploit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173775</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/boyd-left-bemused-by-rangers-failure-to-stop-excellent-celtic-exploit/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T19:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic captain Tom Boyd wasn’t surprised by the quality of Callum McGregor’s performance for the Bhoys on Sunday, but was taken aback by Rangers’...
The post Boyd left bemused by Rangers failure to stop excellent Celtic exploit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fee Celtic paid to Benfica for Jota’s Al-Ittihad move confirmed]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44015</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/07/fee-celtic-paid-benfica-jota-al-ittihad/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T18:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic lost one of their most important players this summer in the form of Jota. The Portuguese winger was a key part of the successes that the Hoops enjoyed during the two seasons under the management of Ange Postecoglou. He was instrumental in all five trophies that the Scottish club won during that period of […]
Fee Celtic paid to Benfica for Jota’s Al-Ittihad move confirmed - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['It'd be fantastic’: Peter Grant excited by rumour coming out about 'intelligent' Celtic ace]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173753</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/itd-be-fantastic-peter-grant-excited-by-rumour-coming-out-about-intelligent-celtic-ace/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T16:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant is excited to hear that Matt O’Riley could be penning down a new long-term contract at Celtic. Not only was Grant pleased with...
The post 'It'd be fantastic’: Peter Grant excited by rumour coming out about 'intelligent' Celtic ace appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The exciting Celtic XI Rodgers can unleash after new signings and injury returns]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173635</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/sudden-excitement-how-celtic-could-line-up-once-injured-stars-and-new-signings-are-available/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T16:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic players that took to the field at Ibrox on Sunday are unlikely ever to start together again. Looking back with the benefit of...
The post The exciting Celtic XI Rodgers can unleash after new signings and injury returns appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Somehow cooler"; New signing delivers verdict on Celtic experience so far]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173735</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/somehow-cooler-gustaf-lagerbielke-has-an-interesting-verdict-on-celtic-derby-experience/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T15:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gustaf Lagerbielke has been speaking in Sweden about a frantic last week at Celtic. The central defender only joined the Brendan Rodgers revolution in mid-August....
The post "Somehow cooler"; New signing delivers verdict on Celtic experience so far appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero urges Rocco Vata to make Parkhead exit]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44010</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/07/celtic-hero-rocco-vata-parkhead-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T15:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rocco Vata is a player who has made quite the splash at the youth levels for Celtic. He has been in tremendous form for the B team and under ideal circumstances, one would hope to see him playing for the senior side very soon. But unfortunately, it looks like there are major doubts over his […]
Celtic hero urges Rocco Vata to make Parkhead exit - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Benfica confirm in accounts exactly how much they got from Celtic in total for Jota]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173750</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/benfica-confirm-in-accounts-how-much-they-got-from-celtic-in-total-for-jota/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T15:01:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More details on Celtic’s transfer business involving Jota has emerged from Portugal this week. The winger signed on a loan-to-buy basis from Benfica in 2021,...
The post Benfica confirm in accounts exactly how much they got from Celtic in total for Jota appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Healthy former Celtic contingent building at Championship club]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173725</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/my-friends-healthy-former-celtic-contingent-building-at-lower-league-scottish-club/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T14:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic youngster Owen Moffat has been speaking about the reasons for his switch back north of the border. The 21-year-old departed Celtic last summer...
The post Healthy former Celtic contingent building at Championship club appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Antoine Griezmann makes superb claim about Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43997</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/07/antoine-griezmann-makes-claim-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T12:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were drawn into a tough but exciting group in the Champions League. They will come up against Atletico Madrid, Lazio and Feyenoord in Europe’s elite competition. Now, it is by no means a simple task for Brendan Rodgers’ side. On the contrary, most would consider them as the underdogs against all of those teams. […]
Antoine Griezmann makes superb claim about Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As rivals make headlines for social media activity, the Celtic story couldn't be more different]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173661</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/as-rivals-make-headlines-for-social-media-activity-the-celtic-story-couldnt-be-more-different/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been amusing to watch the fall-out from Celtic’s derby win over Rangers on Sunday. It was a wonderful afternoon for the Hoops as...
The post As rivals make headlines for social media activity, the Celtic story couldn't be more different appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New contracts for some but not all]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111820</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/new-contracts-for-some-but-not-all/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T11:03:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O’Riley had recently turned 21 when he joined Celtic from MK Dons in January 2022.  He was an immediate success, before form shaded a tad, in particular when Ange Postecoglou varied midfield combinations. This season he has started all five competitive games, with performances eclipsing anything seen before.  He is still young with plenty [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Every Celtic absentee at Ibrox and when we can expect to see them play again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173642</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/every-celtic-absentee-at-ibrox-and-when-we-can-expect-to-see-them-play-again/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic managed to secure a momentous win at Ibrox on Sunday while missing several first-team players. Without key personnel, and any supporters inside the ground,...
The post Every Celtic absentee at Ibrox and when we can expect to see them play again appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch: Nine different angles of stunning Celtic derby winner]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173715</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/class-celtic-content-kyogos-stunning-ibrox-strike-from-nine-different-angles/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic media team are rightfully basking in the glory of Kyogo Furuhashi’s stunning winner at Ibrox on Sunday. Those in charge of social media...
The post Watch: Nine different angles of stunning Celtic derby winner appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All hope not lost for Celtic one year on from the night that could have been]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173680</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/all-hope-not-lost-for-celtic-one-year-on-from-the-night-that-could-have-been/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s one year since the night that could have been for Celtic. While the final scoreline on our big Champions League return read Celtic 0-3...
The post All hope not lost for Celtic one year on from the night that could have been appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Disrespectful’: Peter Grant slams Ally McCoist for his comments related to Celtic & Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173682</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/disrespectful-peter-grant-slams-ally-mccoist-for-his-comments-related-to-celtic-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant wasn’t happy with Ally McCoist for his comments about Celtic’s win against Rangers at Ibrox. Speaking to Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers on Wednesday,...
The post ‘Disrespectful’: Peter Grant slams Ally McCoist for his comments related to Celtic & Rangers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Impressive new Celtic contract strategy showing no signs of stopping]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173673</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/impressive-new-celtic-contract-strategy-showing-no-signs-of-stopping-obvious-next-target/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems very much like Matt O’Riley is the next star in line for a new contract at Celtic. The Danish youth international has been...
The post Report: Impressive new Celtic contract strategy showing no signs of stopping appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Antoine Griezmann shares what he knows about Celtic ahead of Champions League fight]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173621</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/antoine-griezmann-shares-what-he-knows-about-celtic-ahead-of-champions-league-fight/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Atletico Madrid superstar Antoine Griezmann has been speaking about Celtic ahead of the upcoming UEFA Champions League group stage. The Hoops are in Group E...
The post Antoine Griezmann shares what he knows about Celtic ahead of Champions League fight appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disappointing news for former Celtic hero as manager search nears a conclusion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173628</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/hibernian-learn-from-recent-celtic-past-as-neil-lennon-decision-is-made/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic manager Neil Lennon won’t be the new boss of Hibernian, according to a report. The Scotsman have offered an update on the Premiership...
The post Disappointing news for former Celtic hero as manager search nears a conclusion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SALES TALK (Part Two): BRENDAN’S £18.25m SPEND]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111804</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/sales-talk-part-two-brendans-18-25m-spend/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T05:01:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS spent £18.25million in putting his Celtic jigsaw together for his second stint in charge of the champions. Coincidentally, the Irishman, just like his predecessor Ange Postecoglou the previous summer, brought in nine recruits. And, in an identical situation, the final player to arrive was a loan signing. Last season it was Oliver Abildgaard [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SALES TALK (Part One): ANGE’S £20m SPLASH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111801</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/sales-talk-part-one-anges-20m-splash/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T05:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU spent £20million in the 2022 summer market as he prepared for his second – and final – season as Celtic manager. The Greek-Australian gaffer brought in nine recruits with the last arrival being Danish international midfielder Oliver Abildgaard who signed a one-year loan deal from Rubin Kazan. The 6ft-plus enforcer joined his former [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[’To be fair’: Brendan Rodgers agrees with Ally McCoist’s 'quite frank' Celtic-Rangers claim]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173649</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/to-be-fair-brendan-rodgers-agrees-with-ally-mccoists-quite-frank-celtic-rangers-claim/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T04:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers agreed with Ally McCoist’s assessment that Celtic’s clash against Rangers at Ibrox was ‘bang average’. Perhaps Celtic winning 1-0 is a reason why...
The post ’To be fair’: Brendan Rodgers agrees with Ally McCoist’s 'quite frank' Celtic-Rangers claim appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ANDY LYNCH: GREAT UNCAPPED CELTS (Part Three)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.cqnmagazine.com/?p=4780</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/andy-lynch-great-uncapped-celts-part-three/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T04:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CQN is turning the spotlight once again on the Celtic players who never had the honour of playing for their country. Andy Lynch may have been a trusted defender for Jock Stein, but never got the nod to get into a Scotland squad. The legendary Hoops manager thought he was buying a flying machine at [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic set to offer new contract to £10 million-plus player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43961</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/06/celtic-offer-10-million-plus-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T22:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic added nine new players to their squad over the summer transfer window. It will be interesting to see how they do at Parkhead. Most of them might not be established names in the game but they certainly do appear to have a lot of potential. At the same time, it is important that the […]
Celtic set to offer new contract to £10 million-plus player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Booooooooh! – The ETims Podcast]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18482</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18482"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T20:58:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hector, Monty and Desi get together to salute The Alamo Celtic Team who stood tall against all the odds and fears and came away from…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Desi Mond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers makes Celtic declaration for Champions League]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43955</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/06/rodgers-makes-celtic-champions-league/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T20:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The season is well underway now for Celtic as they sit joint top of the Premiership with Motherwell and have a Glasgow Derby win at Ibrox over the Rangers already in the bag. Soon the Hoops will kick off their Champions League campaign too and Brendan Rodgers has had his say regarding their approach for […]
Brendan Rodgers makes Celtic declaration for Champions League - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Barry Ferguson says ‘top-class’ Celtic player now worth ‘Kieran Tierney money’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173603</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/barry-ferguson-says-top-class-celtic-player-now-worth-kieran-tierney-money/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T19:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Barry Ferguson thinks Kyogo Furuhashi is now worth ‘Kieran Tierney-type money’ for Celtic. The Japan star downed Rangers over the weekend at Ibrox when he...
The post Barry Ferguson says ‘top-class’ Celtic player now worth ‘Kieran Tierney money’ appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano confirms Celtic have agreed new deal]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43960</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/06/fabrizio-romano-celtic-agreed-new-deal/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T18:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been handing out new deals left, right and centre in recent times as it looks like the Hoops are keen to keep their most important players. Callum McGregor, Kyogo, Daizen Maeda and Liel Abada have all agreed contract extensions. It is believed that the club are aiming to do the same with Matt […]
Fabrizio Romano confirms Celtic have agreed new deal - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Japan picture is looking better for Celtic during this international break]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173507</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-positive-japan-picture-for-celtic-during-this-international-break/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The picture is positive for Celtic and our Japan stars during this international break. Things haven’t always been straightforward for our Japanese contingent over the...
The post The Japan picture is looking better for Celtic during this international break appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero already tips summer signing for future exit]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43957</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/06/celtic-hero-summer-signing-future-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T16:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic made nine additions over the course of the recently concluded summer transfer window. A lot of fans were not happy with the new arrivals though as the club mostly stuck to making ‘project’ signings rather than bringing in proven and experienced players who could make a positive impact on the team from the get-go. […]
Celtic hero already tips summer signing for future exit - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen McGinn wants Celtic to make a move in derby allocation mess; reality is different]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173554</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/stephen-mcginn-wants-celtic-to-make-a-move-in-derby-allocation-mess-reality-is-different/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen McGinn has shared some interesting thoughts on the ongoing derby allocation mess between Celtic and Rangers. The Hoops came out on top at Ibrox...
The post Stephen McGinn wants Celtic to make a move in derby allocation mess; reality is different appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wednesday UWCL joy as Celtic secure historic European result]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173598</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/wednesday-uwcl-joy-as-celtic-secure-historic-european-result/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T13:54:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic FC Women have picked up their first-ever win in the UEFA Women’s Champions League with a superb 1-0 result against Brondby this afternoon. Club...
The post Wednesday UWCL joy as Celtic secure historic European result appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Class Joe Hart interview clip emerges on Celtic social media]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173582</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/class-joe-hart-interview-clip-emerges-on-celtic-social-media/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A class clip from a recent interview with Joe Hart has emerged on Celtic social media. The Hoops goalkeeper has been a terrific presence ever...
The post Class Joe Hart interview clip emerges on Celtic social media appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Up against it; the number of tickets Celtic will receive for Feyenoord away clash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173584</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/up-against-it-the-number-of-tickets-celtic-will-receive-for-feyenoord-away-clash/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T11:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a little bit scary to think that Celtic will open their UEFA Champions League campaign against Feyenoord in less than two weeks. By the...
The post Up against it; the number of tickets Celtic will receive for Feyenoord away clash appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summer 23 Transfer Window assessment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111819</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/summer-23-transfer-window-assessment/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T11:02:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a busy transfer window, Celtic signed nine new players and sold four from the first team squad.  Central defence saw two planned arrivals: Maik Nawrocki (22) and Gustaf Lagerbielke (23), and the departure of Carl Starfelt (28).  Starfelt’s two-year partnership with Cameron Carter-Vickers was remarkably successful.  They only once experience defeat in a domestic [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some interesting takeaways as Sky Sports announce latest batch of Celtic fixtures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173539</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/some-interesting-takeaways-as-sky-sports-announce-latest-batch-of-celtic-fixtures/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There were a few interesting takeaways as Sky Sports announced their latest batch of Celtic fixtures on Tuesday. Brendan Rodgers‘ Hoops have been on the...
The post Some interesting takeaways as Sky Sports announce latest batch of Celtic fixtures appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["The status of Celtic is huge"; international boss confirms Hoops growth in far-flung country]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173524</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-status-of-celtic-is-huge-international-boss-confirms-pleasing-hoops-growth-in-far-flung-country/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jurgen Klinsmann says that Celtic have become a big deal in South Korea. The former Bayern Munich and Tottenham Hotspur forward is now in charge...
The post "The status of Celtic is huge"; international boss confirms Hoops growth in far-flung country appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Nothing': Rodgers compares Celtic-Rangers atmosphere to English football's biggest rivalry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173562</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/nothing-like-brendan-rodgers-compares-celtic-rangers-atmosphere-to-liverpool-manchester-united/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T08:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers says there is ‘nothing like’ the atmosphere in Celtic and Rangers games, as he compared it to Liverpool and Manchester United. Prior to...
The post 'Nothing': Rodgers compares Celtic-Rangers atmosphere to English football's biggest rivalry appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big day arrives for Celtic in UEFA Women's Champions League; format explained, how to watch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173545</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/big-day-arrives-for-celtic-in-uefa-womens-champions-league-format-explained-how-to-watch/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The big day has arrived for Celtic as they get their UEFA Women’s Champions League campaign underway on Wednesday. Fran Alonso‘s side are in Oslo...
The post Big day arrives for Celtic in UEFA Women's Champions League; format explained, how to watch appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I will always be very grateful"; star finally opens up on summer Celtic departure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173500</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/carl-starfelt-has-some-great-things-to-say-about-celtic-reaction-to-rodgers-jacynta-comments/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carl Starfelt has had some great things to say about Celtic as he finally opened up on his summer departure from the club. The Swedish...
The post "I will always be very grateful"; star finally opens up on summer Celtic departure appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic stance on controversial government proposals; strong Scottish football message sent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173531</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-celtic-stance-on-controversial-government-proposals-strong-scottish-football-message-sent/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic stance on some recent government proposals on supporters’ buses has become clear. On Tuesday, Scottish football fans were left incensed after a consultation...
The post The Celtic stance on controversial government proposals; strong Scottish football message sent appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jurgen Klinsmann shares what Brendan Rodgers told him about Celtic trio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173515</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/jurgen-klinsmann-shares-what-brendan-rodgers-told-him-about-celtic-trio/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jurgen Klinsmann has been speaking about his relationship with Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers. As current boss of South Korea, the former VfB Stuttgart and Tottenham...
The post Jurgen Klinsmann shares what Brendan Rodgers told him about Celtic trio appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC: DEAL OR NO DEAL? THE HILARIOUS AND THE HYSTERICAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111798</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-deal-or-no-deal-the-hilarious-and-the-hysterical/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T05:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THERE was speculation at the weekend that Kasper Schmeichel may emerge as a target for Brendan Rodgers. The link was that the Danish international, a free agent after being released by Nice, had played for the Irishman during their time together at Leicester City. CQN ignored the reports. Frankly, we didn’t believe them and saw [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS 32 RANGERS 7]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111794</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-32-rangers-7/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T04:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS reminded his Celtic players he knew how to win at Ibrox before Sunday’s confrontation. And the second time-around Hoops boss emphasised those words by sending out a determined bunch of Hoops stars who battled in front of a hostile 50,000 crowd to claim a 1-0 victory courtesy of a sensational volley from Kyogo [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IAN YOUNG: GREAT UNCAPPED CELTS (Part Two)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.cqnmagazine.com/?p=4760</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ian-young-great-uncapped-celts-part-two/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T04:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CQN is turning the spotlight again on the Celtic players who never had the honour of playing for their country. Ian Young, the solid, unspectacular right-back who sadly passed away in December 2019 at the age of 76, never got the nod to get into a Scotland squad. Young rarely hit the headlines with his [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>