<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2022-12-04T09:17:40.032Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who is new Celtic transfer signing Alistair Johnston?]]></title>
        <id>fadbc19c103f33dfa779aa15a8b1e929</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23168343.new-celtic-transfer-signing-alistair-johnston/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-04T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The versatile defender has had an interesting career path to take him to Parkhead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic On This Day – 4th December – David Potter’s Celtic Diary]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-on-this-day-4th-december-david-potters-celtic-diary/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-on-this-day-4th-december-david-potters-celtic-diary/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-04T00:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Historian David Potter each morning on The Celtic Star looks back at key Celtic events and matches on this day starting on 4th December 1909. David’s latest book The Celtic Rising ~ 1965 The Year Jock Stein Changed Everything is very close to selling out on Celtic Star Books with just a few books remaining. Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer Latest – Celtic contact Mohamed Magdy’s agent about January move to Paradise]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/transfer-latest-celtic-contact-mohamed-magdys-agent-about-january-move-to-paradise/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/transfer-latest-celtic-contact-mohamed-magdys-agent-about-january-move-to-paradise/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T23:33:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have contacted Mohamed Magdy’s representatives ahead of making a move for the player in the January transfer window. Magdy is one who has been linked previously to the club, although nothing transpired last summer and the player remained at his team Al-Ahly.The 26-year-old playmaker is a typical number 10 and Football Scotland have reported Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“I’m going to need a new phone,”  Celtic’s New Bhoy Ally Johnston]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/im-going-to-need-a-new-phone-celtics-new-bhoy-ally-johnston/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/im-going-to-need-a-new-phone-celtics-new-bhoy-ally-johnston/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T23:19:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the preceding period in the build-up to Canadian World Cup star, Ally Johnston signing for Celtic, the defender joked that he would need a new phone as his old iPhone was blowing up with messages about his prospective move to Celtic Park. There was a melee of activity surrounding the 24-year-old after his performance Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celts in Qatar: Aaron Mooy bows out as unlucky Australia succumb to Messi’s magic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celts-in-qatar-aaron-mooy-bows-out-as-unlucky-australia-succumb-to-messis-magic/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celts-in-qatar-aaron-mooy-bows-out-as-unlucky-australia-succumb-to-messis-magic/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T22:42:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That’s another of Celtic’s World Cup Stars that will be en-route home to Paradise shortly after Aaron Mooy and his Australia teammates faltered to some Messi magic in the Round of 16. Following Cameron Carter-Vickers in returning home soon, Aaron has been fantastic for his country and did himself and Oz extremely proud.The Aussies just Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Yep…’ – Alistair Johnston Reveals Crazy Reaction to Celtic Move]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/alistair-johnstone-celtic-move-phone/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/alistair-johnstone-celtic-move-phone/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T22:36:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic defender Alistair Johnston has declared he will need a new phone after moving to Celtic. The player joked during the World Cup that his phone nearly melted when the interest from Celtic became public, and now he 100% needs a new phone after the deal was confirmed on Saturday afternoon. Yep… it’s official. […]
The post ‘Yep…’ – Alistair Johnston Reveals Crazy Reaction to Celtic Move first appeared on Celts Are Here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic B 5 Edinburgh University 0]]></title>
        <id>http://celticunderground.net/celtic-b-5-edinburgh-university-0/</id>
        <link href="http://celticunderground.net/celtic-b-5-edinburgh-university-0/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T22:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The match today between Celtic and Edinburgh Uni, was over as a competition more or less straight away. Celtic dominated possession for the full 90 minutes and managed to put five past them. The definition of men against boys. Celtic struggled finding the final product after missing a number of chances in the first 20 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Very Interested in Versatile Dutch Striker; Report]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-very-interested-in-versatile-dutch-striker-report/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-very-interested-in-versatile-dutch-striker-report/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T22:27:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC are said to be “very interested” in striker Said Hamulic. The 22-year-old is currently playing in the Polish top flight and has had an impressive start to the season with his side Stal Mielic. [TuttoMercatoWeb] The 6″1′ attacker has netted nine goals and assisted four in his debut season and is being linked with […]
The post Celtic Very Interested in Versatile Dutch Striker; Report first appeared on Celts Are Here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Messi finds way to break down resilient Aussies as Hearts, Celtic, Dundee United and St Mirren stars return to clubs with heads held high]]></title>
        <id>3941125</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/international/messi-finds-way-to-break-down-resilient-aussies-as-hearts-celtic-dundee-united-and-st-mirren-stars-return-to-clubs-with-heads-held-high-3941125"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T22:25:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In defying the odds, Australia spent their time in Qatar proving that team work, togetherness, solid preparation, pride, heart and endeavour can pepper holes in perceived limitations and help exceed expectations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moira Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou factor helps Celtic push through £3m deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/alistair-johnston-makes-it-clear-how-big-a-factor-ange-postecoglou-is-in-celtic-negotiations/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/alistair-johnston-makes-it-clear-how-big-a-factor-ange-postecoglou-is-in-celtic-negotiations/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T22:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston has made it clear the presence of Ange Postecoglou was instrumental in convincing him that Celtic was the place he wanted to play football in his prime years. Johnston has signed a five-year contract at the Bhoys after Celtic agreed to a £3m deal with MLS side CF Montreal. The 24-year-old is obviously ...
The post Ange Postecoglou factor helps Celtic push through £3m deal appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cho Gue sung fuels Celtic succession theory after favourite position poser - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CBMiXWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvY2hvLWd1ZS1zdW5nLWZ1ZWxzLWNlbHRpYy0yODY0ODczMdIBYWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvY2hvLWd1ZS1zdW5nLWZ1ZWxzLWNlbHRpYy0yODY0ODczMS5hbXA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiXWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvY2hvLWd1ZS1zdW5nLWZ1ZWxzLWNlbHRpYy0yODY0ODczMdIBYWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvY2hvLWd1ZS1zdW5nLWZ1ZWxzLWNlbHRpYy0yODY0ODczMS5hbXA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T22:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cho Gue sung fuels Celtic succession theory after favourite position poser  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real Madrid leading race for Jeremie Frimpong as Celtic set to benefit]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/real-madrid-leading-race-for-jeremie-frimpong-as-celtic-to-benefit/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/real-madrid-leading-race-for-jeremie-frimpong-as-celtic-to-benefit/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T22:03:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Real Madrid are favourites to sign Jeremie Frimpong, which means that Celtic will likely net a hefty sell-on fee. The Bayer Leverkusen full-back is set to return to the Bundesliga club following the World Cup in Qatar. Frimpong and his Dutch teammates will face up against Lionel Messi’s Argentina in the Quarter Finals.According to a Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic youngsters coming through Lennoxtown set for another big Postecoglou chance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/ange-postecoglou-confirms-rocco-vata-and-bosun-lawal-celtic-status-as-another-big-chance-beckons/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/ange-postecoglou-confirms-rocco-vata-and-bosun-lawal-celtic-status-as-another-big-chance-beckons/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T21:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has confirmed Rocco Vata and Bosun Lawal will travel with the Celtic squad for this week’s training camp in Portugal as the duo edge closer to competitive involvement at the Bhoys. Both players, as well as Scott Robertson, travelled with the senior side for the Sydney Super Cup and have been involved in ...
The post Celtic youngsters coming through Lennoxtown set for another big Postecoglou chance appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Please Nip This “Lawwell And His Trophies At Celtic” Nonsense In The Bud.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/12/articles-and-features/lets-please-nip-this-lawwell-and-his-trophies-at-celtic-nonsense-in-the-bud/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/12/articles-and-features/lets-please-nip-this-lawwell-and-his-trophies-at-celtic-nonsense-in-the-bud/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T21:13:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there is one part of the narrative of Peter Lawwell that continues to annoy me and offend me above and beyond everything else it is this talk about the success “he” has brought to the club. And that’s how it’s always framed. As his success. But Lawwell was a bean counter. A CEO. Albiet […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston underlines his Celtic transfer joy as defender celebrates move with a toast to Parkhead - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>1671251218</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMicGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvYWxpc3RhaXItam9obnN0b24tdW5kZXJsaW5lcy1jZWx0aWMtdHJhbnNmZXItMjg2NDgyMDPSAXRodHRwczovL3d3dy5kYWlseXJlY29yZC5jby51ay9zcG9ydC9mb290YmFsbC9mb290YmFsbC1uZXdzL2FsaXN0YWlyLWpvaG5zdG9uLXVuZGVybGluZXMtY2VsdGljLXRyYW5zZmVyLTI4NjQ4MjAzLmFtcA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T20:40:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston underlines his Celtic transfer joy as defender celebrates move with a toast to Parkhead  Daily Record
Alistair Johnston signs Celtic F.C.  TSN
CF Montreal transfer D Alistair Johnston to Celtic FC  Yardbarker
Alistair Johnston sends “beyond buzzing” social media message to Celtic supporters  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News
“I’m going to need a new phone,” Celtic’s New Bhoy Ally Johnston  The Celtic Star
View Full coverage on Google News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agent of 20-cap international claims new Celtic interest in his client]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/agent-claims-celtic-contact-for-playmaking-egyptian-international/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/agent-claims-celtic-contact-for-playmaking-egyptian-international/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T20:32:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The agent of Mohamed Magdy, known as Afsha, has claimed renewed Celtic interest in his client ahead of the January transfer window. Football Scotland reports tonight that the Bhoys have made initial contact with his representatives. Maher Nawfal, who works with the player, provides a quote to the outlet. He said: “There has been interest ...
The post Agent of 20-cap international claims new Celtic interest in his client appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Afsha’s Agent Makes Interesting Celtic Claim]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/afsha-celtic-transfer-latest/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/afsha-celtic-transfer-latest/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T20:23:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reports on Saturday evening claim that Celtic have now made contact with Egyptian playmaker Afsha over a deal to bring him to the club. Ashfa, 26, currently plays for El Ahly Cairo and is contracted to the club until 2024. Maher Nawfal, Afsha’s representative, told Football Scotland on Saturday evening the Hoops have made their […]
The post Afsha’s Agent Makes Interesting Celtic Claim first appeared on Celts Are Here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[&#039;Celtic have...&#039; - Sky Sports journalist drops big Parkhead off-field claim ahead of January]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-spl-peter-lawwell-anthony-joseph-news-updates/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-spl-peter-lawwell-anthony-joseph-news-updates/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T20:05:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic CEO Peter Lawwell will return to Parkhead as non-executive chairman at the beginning of January, according to Sky Sports journalist Anthony Joseph. The Lowdown: Lawwell left Celtic in 2021 The 63-year-old took up his role of CEO at Parkhead back in 2003 and remained the position until 2021, overseeing numerous different managers and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Bhoy Alistair Johnston Spots Something Brilliant in Milan Bar]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/new-bhoy-alistair-johnston-spots-something-brilliant-in-milan-bar/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/new-bhoy-alistair-johnston-spots-something-brilliant-in-milan-bar/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T20:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic new bhoy Alistair Johnston is enjoying some down time after participating in the World Cup with Canada. On the day his move to Celtic was confirmed, the right-back was in Milan, taking a break before he gets ready to meet up with his new teammates. Alistair posted a video on his Instagram story, watching […]
The post New Bhoy Alistair Johnston Spots Something Brilliant in Milan Bar first appeared on Celts Are Here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion: Peter Lawwell, Ghost at the Feast and no amount of spin will change that - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CBMiamh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vb3Bpbmlvbi1wZXRlci1sYXd3ZWxsLWdob3N0LWF0LXRoZS1mZWFzdC1hbmQtbm8tYW1vdW50LW9mLXNwaW4td2lsbC1jaGFuZ2UtdGhhdC_SAW5odHRwczovL3RoZWNlbHRpY3N0YXIuY29tL29waW5pb24tcGV0ZXItbGF3d2VsbC1naG9zdC1hdC10aGUtZmVhc3QtYW5kLW5vLWFtb3VudC1vZi1zcGluLXdpbGwtY2hhbmdlLXRoYXQvYW1wLw</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiamh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vb3Bpbmlvbi1wZXRlci1sYXd3ZWxsLWdob3N0LWF0LXRoZS1mZWFzdC1hbmQtbm8tYW1vdW50LW9mLXNwaW4td2lsbC1jaGFuZ2UtdGhhdC_SAW5odHRwczovL3RoZWNlbHRpY3N0YXIuY29tL29waW5pb24tcGV0ZXItbGF3d2VsbC1naG9zdC1hdC10aGUtZmVhc3QtYW5kLW5vLWFtb3VudC1vZi1zcGluLXdpbGwtY2hhbmdlLXRoYXQvYW1wLw?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T18:38:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion: Peter Lawwell, Ghost at the Feast and no amount of spin will change that  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremie Frimpong Celtic windfall latest as Real Madrid join signing race - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CBMidmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLXRyYW5zZmVyLW5ld3MvamVyZW1pZS1mcmltcG9uZy1jZWx0aWMtdHJhbnNmZXItd2luZGZhbGwtMjg2NDc0NjTSAXpodHRwczovL3d3dy5kYWlseXJlY29yZC5jby51ay9zcG9ydC9mb290YmFsbC9mb290YmFsbC10cmFuc2Zlci1uZXdzL2plcmVtaWUtZnJpbXBvbmctY2VsdGljLXRyYW5zZmVyLXdpbmRmYWxsLTI4NjQ3NDY0LmFtcA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMidmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLXRyYW5zZmVyLW5ld3MvamVyZW1pZS1mcmltcG9uZy1jZWx0aWMtdHJhbnNmZXItd2luZGZhbGwtMjg2NDc0NjTSAXpodHRwczovL3d3dy5kYWlseXJlY29yZC5jby51ay9zcG9ydC9mb290YmFsbC9mb290YmFsbC10cmFuc2Zlci1uZXdzL2plcmVtaWUtZnJpbXBvbmctY2VsdGljLXRyYW5zZmVyLXdpbmRmYWxsLTI4NjQ3NDY0LmFtcA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T18:15:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremie Frimpong Celtic windfall latest as Real Madrid join signing race  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston sends “beyond buzzing” social media message to Celtic supporters - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CBMicWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL25ld3MvYWxpc3RhaXItam9obnN0b24tc2VuZHMtYmV5b25kLWJ1enppbmctc29jaWFsLW1lZGlhLW1lc3NhZ2UtdG8tY2VsdGljLXN1cHBvcnRlcnMv0gF1aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuNjdoYWlsaGFpbC5jb20vbmV3cy9hbGlzdGFpci1qb2huc3Rvbi1zZW5kcy1iZXlvbmQtYnV6emluZy1zb2NpYWwtbWVkaWEtbWVzc2FnZS10by1jZWx0aWMtc3VwcG9ydGVycy8_YW1w</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMicWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL25ld3MvYWxpc3RhaXItam9obnN0b24tc2VuZHMtYmV5b25kLWJ1enppbmctc29jaWFsLW1lZGlhLW1lc3NhZ2UtdG8tY2VsdGljLXN1cHBvcnRlcnMv0gF1aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuNjdoYWlsaGFpbC5jb20vbmV3cy9hbGlzdGFpci1qb2huc3Rvbi1zZW5kcy1iZXlvbmQtYnV6emluZy1zb2NpYWwtbWVkaWEtbWVzc2FnZS10by1jZWx0aWMtc3VwcG9ydGVycy8_YW1w?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T18:14:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston sends “beyond buzzing” social media message to Celtic supporters  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic sign Alistair Johnston - length of deal, when he will arrive, 'biggest clubs in the world']]></title>
        <id>3941052</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-sign-alistair-johnston-length-of-deal-when-he-will-arrive-biggest-clubs-in-the-world-3941052"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T17:15:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have confirmed the signing of Canada’s World Cup star Alistair Johnston from MLS side CF Montreal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Agent Victor' - Alistair Johnston details Wanyama role in Celtic move]]></title>
        <id>da67a772cea1b51740450d1ccbd39a5f</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23168144.agent-victor---alistair-johnston-details-wanyama-role-celtic-move/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T16:12:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former Celtic midfielder urged his team-mate to make the move to Glasgow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin O'Neill in hilarious Rangers quip as Celtic legend delivers mic drop after Michael Beale 'advice' poser - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CBMiaGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvbWFydGluLW9uZWlsbC1oaWxhcmlvdXMtcmFuZ2Vycy1xdWlwLTI4NjQ2NDU50gFsaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZGFpbHlyZWNvcmQuY28udWsvc3BvcnQvZm9vdGJhbGwvZm9vdGJhbGwtbmV3cy9tYXJ0aW4tb25laWxsLWhpbGFyaW91cy1yYW5nZXJzLXF1aXAtMjg2NDY0NTkuYW1w</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiaGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvbWFydGluLW9uZWlsbC1oaWxhcmlvdXMtcmFuZ2Vycy1xdWlwLTI4NjQ2NDU50gFsaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZGFpbHlyZWNvcmQuY28udWsvc3BvcnQvZm9vdGJhbGwvZm9vdGJhbGwtbmV3cy9tYXJ0aW4tb25laWxsLWhpbGFyaW91cy1yYW5nZXJzLXF1aXAtMjg2NDY0NTkuYW1w?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T16:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Martin O'Neill in hilarious Rangers quip as Celtic legend delivers mic drop after Michael Beale 'advice' poser  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin O'Neill drops hilarious Rangers quip after Michael Beale advice poser - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CBMiaGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvbWFydGluLW9uZWlsbC1oaWxhcmlvdXMtcmFuZ2Vycy1xdWlwLTI4NjQ2NDU50gEA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiaGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvbWFydGluLW9uZWlsbC1oaWxhcmlvdXMtcmFuZ2Vycy1xdWlwLTI4NjQ2NDU50gEA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T16:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Martin O'Neill drops hilarious Rangers quip after Michael Beale advice poser  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston Makes Five-Year Celtic Move - Northern Tribune]]></title>
        <id>CBMiN2h0dHBzOi8vbm9ydGhlcm50cmlidW5lLmNhL2NlbHRpYy1mYy1hbGlzdGFpci1qb2huc3Rvbi_SAQA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiN2h0dHBzOi8vbm9ydGhlcm50cmlidW5lLmNhL2NlbHRpYy1mYy1hbGlzdGFpci1qb2huc3Rvbi_SAQA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T15:15:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston Makes Five-Year Celtic Move  Northern Tribune]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston signs Celtic F.C. - TSN]]></title>
        <id>1671251218</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiP2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRzbi5jYS9hbGlzdGFpci1qb2huc3Rvbi1zaWducy1jZWx0aWMtZi1jLTEuMTg4Nzk3MNIBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T14:15:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston signs Celtic F.C.  TSN
Alistair Johnston Transferred to Celtic FC  OurSports Central
Alistair Johnston details Celtic signing motivation  Scottish Daily Express
Celtic transfer news: Alistair Johnston joins Scottish champions amid doubt over futures of Josip Juranovic and Giorgos Giakoumakis  Sky Sports
View Full coverage on Google News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic announce signing of Canada star Alistair Johnston]]></title>
        <id>52d7095b1e3247e1315098da1d1254b6</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23167992.celtic-announce-signing-canada-star-alistair-johnston/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T14:04:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The defender has completed a transfer move from MLS side CF Montreal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cho Gue Sung shows Celtic fans mind games quality after Cristiano Ronaldo 'insults' sparked row - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CBMiT2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Noby1ndWUtc3VuZy1zaG93cy1jZWx0aWMtMjg2NDUyMzLSAVNodHRwczovL3d3dy5kYWlseXJlY29yZC5jby51ay9zcG9ydC9mb290YmFsbC9jaG8tZ3VlLXN1bmctc2hvd3MtY2VsdGljLTI4NjQ1MjMyLmFtcA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiT2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Noby1ndWUtc3VuZy1zaG93cy1jZWx0aWMtMjg2NDUyMzLSAVNodHRwczovL3d3dy5kYWlseXJlY29yZC5jby51ay9zcG9ydC9mb290YmFsbC9jaG8tZ3VlLXN1bmctc2hvd3MtY2VsdGljLTI4NjQ1MjMyLmFtcA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T11:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cho Gue Sung shows Celtic fans mind games quality after Cristiano Ronaldo 'insults' sparked row  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yuki Kobayashi's Ange Postecoglou surprise ahead of Celtic reunion]]></title>
        <id>cd65e638cfda9c3fc17e2d54c146bcb5</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23167819.yuki-kobayashis-ange-postecoglou-surprise-ahead-celtic-reunion/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T11:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The defender was impressed after facing Ange Postecoglou's Yokohama Marinos in Japan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou in Alistair Johnston Celtic transfer update as Hoops boss told he's signing a 'warrior' - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CBMiX2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2FuZ2UtcG9zdGVjb2dsb3UtYWxpc3RhaXItam9obnN0b24tY2VsdGljLTI4NjQ0OTYw0gFjaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZGFpbHlyZWNvcmQuY28udWsvc3BvcnQvZm9vdGJhbGwvYW5nZS1wb3N0ZWNvZ2xvdS1hbGlzdGFpci1qb2huc3Rvbi1jZWx0aWMtMjg2NDQ5NjAuYW1w</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiX2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2FuZ2UtcG9zdGVjb2dsb3UtYWxpc3RhaXItam9obnN0b24tY2VsdGljLTI4NjQ0OTYw0gFjaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZGFpbHlyZWNvcmQuY28udWsvc3BvcnQvZm9vdGJhbGwvYW5nZS1wb3N0ZWNvZ2xvdS1hbGlzdGFpci1qb2huc3Rvbi1jZWx0aWMtMjg2NDQ5NjAuYW1w?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T10:53:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou in Alistair Johnston Celtic transfer update as Hoops boss told he's signing a 'warrior'  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou 'delighted' Celtic have Peter Lawwell back as new chairman - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CBMibWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsc2NvdGxhbmQuY28udWsvc3BmbC9zY290dGlzaC1wcmVtaWVyc2hpcC9hbmdlLXBvc3RlY29nbG91LWRlbGlnaHRlZC1jZWx0aWMtcGV0ZXItMjU2NjUyMDHSAXFodHRwczovL3d3dy5mb290YmFsbHNjb3RsYW5kLmNvLnVrL3NwZmwvc2NvdHRpc2gtcHJlbWllcnNoaXAvYW5nZS1wb3N0ZWNvZ2xvdS1kZWxpZ2h0ZWQtY2VsdGljLXBldGVyLTI1NjY1MjAxLmFtcA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMibWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsc2NvdGxhbmQuY28udWsvc3BmbC9zY290dGlzaC1wcmVtaWVyc2hpcC9hbmdlLXBvc3RlY29nbG91LWRlbGlnaHRlZC1jZWx0aWMtcGV0ZXItMjU2NjUyMDHSAXFodHRwczovL3d3dy5mb290YmFsbHNjb3RsYW5kLmNvLnVrL3NwZmwvc2NvdHRpc2gtcHJlbWllcnNoaXAvYW5nZS1wb3N0ZWNvZ2xvdS1kZWxpZ2h0ZWQtY2VsdGljLXBldGVyLTI1NjY1MjAxLmFtcA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T08:59:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou 'delighted' Celtic have Peter Lawwell back as new chairman  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou more worried about what's for dinner than new Rangers manager Michael Beale - Irish Mirror]]></title>
        <id>CBMibmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmlyaXNobWlycm9yLmllL3Nwb3J0L3NvY2Nlci9zY290dGlzaC1mb290YmFsbC9jZWx0aWMtZmMvY2VsdGljLWJvc3MtYW5nZS1wb3N0ZWNvZ2xvdS1tb3JlLTI4NjQ0NDQ20gFyaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuaXJpc2htaXJyb3IuaWUvc3BvcnQvc29jY2VyL3Njb3R0aXNoLWZvb3RiYWxsL2NlbHRpYy1mYy9jZWx0aWMtYm9zcy1hbmdlLXBvc3RlY29nbG91LW1vcmUtMjg2NDQ0NDYuYW1w</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMibmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmlyaXNobWlycm9yLmllL3Nwb3J0L3NvY2Nlci9zY290dGlzaC1mb290YmFsbC9jZWx0aWMtZmMvY2VsdGljLWJvc3MtYW5nZS1wb3N0ZWNvZ2xvdS1tb3JlLTI4NjQ0NDQ20gFyaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuaXJpc2htaXJyb3IuaWUvc3BvcnQvc29jY2VyL3Njb3R0aXNoLWZvb3RiYWxsL2NlbHRpYy1mYy9jZWx0aWMtYm9zcy1hbmdlLXBvc3RlY29nbG91LW1vcmUtMjg2NDQ0NDYuYW1w?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T08:20:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou more worried about what's for dinner than new Rangers manager Michael Beale  Irish Mirror]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australia v Argentina - Hearts star's value, Celtic and Dundee United duo impress, stopping Lionel Messi]]></title>
        <id>3940244</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/australia-v-argentina-hearts-stars-value-celtic-and-dundee-united-duo-impress-stopping-lionel-messi-3940244"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lionel Messi. For some, the greatest of his generation. For others, the greatest to ever play the game. Millions, in Argentina and world wide, are willing him to win the greatest tournament of them all. The next stop on that quest in Qatar 2022 is the SPFL Select, sorry Australia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Plan already in place' - Celtic linked with in-form ace as Postecoglou backed to replace Giorgos Giakoumakis]]></title>
        <id>3940833</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/plan-already-in-place-celtic-linked-with-in-form-ace-as-postecoglou-backed-to-replace-giorgos-giakoumakis-3940833"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T07:13:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been backed to have a “plan already in place” if Giorgos Giakoumakis was to leave the club – and the Scottish champions have been linked with an in-form Dutch striker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angus Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shunsuke Nakamura provides Celtic stories for Yuki Kobayashi as Kyogo turns Japanese scout in winter transfer - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CBMiY2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL3NodW5zdWtlbmFrYW11cmEtcHJvdmlkZXMtY2VsdGljLXN0b3JpZXMteXVraS0yODY0MzE0OdIBZ2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL3NodW5zdWtlbmFrYW11cmEtcHJvdmlkZXMtY2VsdGljLXN0b3JpZXMteXVraS0yODY0MzE0OS5hbXA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiY2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL3NodW5zdWtlbmFrYW11cmEtcHJvdmlkZXMtY2VsdGljLXN0b3JpZXMteXVraS0yODY0MzE0OdIBZ2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL3NodW5zdWtlbmFrYW11cmEtcHJvdmlkZXMtY2VsdGljLXN0b3JpZXMteXVraS0yODY0MzE0OS5hbXA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shunsuke Nakamura provides Celtic stories for Yuki Kobayashi as Kyogo turns Japanese scout in winter transfer  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Postecoglou hails Celtic return of 'instrumental' Lawwell]]></title>
        <id>d8eb02344799e7ebaf79a2099938ff4f</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23167465.postecoglou-hails-celtic-return-instrumental-lawwell/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU has welcomed the return of Peter Lawwell to Celtic, saying that the former chief executive was ‘instrumental’ in bringing him...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic On This Day – 3rd December – David Potter’s Celtic Diary]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-on-this-day-3rd-december-david-potters-celtic-diary/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-on-this-day-3rd-december-david-potters-celtic-diary/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T00:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Historian David Potter each morning on The Celtic Star looks back at key Celtic events and matches on this day starting on  3rd December 1898. David’s latest book The Celtic Rising ~ 1965 The Year Jock Stein Changed Everything is very close to selling out on Celtic Star Books with just a few books remaining. Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yuki Kobayashi explains Celtic move, lifts lid on Kyogo talks and what manager expects of him]]></title>
        <id>3940357</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/yuki-kobayashi-explains-celtic-move-lifts-lid-on-kyogo-talks-and-what-manager-expects-of-him-3940357"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T22:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s stock is understandably at an all-time high in Japan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I'll deal with it': Ange Postecoglou has say on potential issues within squad amid Giorgos Giakoumakis speculation]]></title>
        <id>3940590</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/ill-deal-with-it-ange-postecoglou-has-say-on-potential-issues-within-squad-amid-giorgos-giakoumakis-speculation-3940590"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou says he will deal with any issues as they arise with the happiness of his squad after reports this week that striker Giorgios Giakoumakis will look to leave the club in January after contract talks broke down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has say on potential Alistair Johnston and Cho Gue-sung Celtic transfers]]></title>
        <id>3940432</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/ange-postecoglou-has-say-on-potential-alistair-johnston-and-cho-gue-sung-celtic-transfers-3940432"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou hopes there will be developments soon on the potential signing of defender Alistair Johnston.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yuki Kobayashi sold on Celtic move by Shunsuke Nakamura]]></title>
        <id>3f12775acf2a313aae8270374ce0ae0f</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23167460.yuki-kobayashi-sold-celtic-move-shunsuke-nakamura/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PREPARATION for player unveilings can often involve a deep-dive into their past to uncover any links with the club they have moved to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou addresses Alastair Johsnton and possible exits]]></title>
        <id>c3e0b703a009d2d451458b01b4ccf666</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23167458.ange-postecoglou-addresses-alastair-johsnton-possible-exits/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU has admitted that Canada defender Alistair Johnston is ‘definitely on his radar’ after Celtic were reported to have agreed a £3m fee...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou talks up Celtic bargain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-sets-yuki-kobayashi-expectations-but-talks-up-celtic-bargain/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-sets-yuki-kobayashi-expectations-but-talks-up-celtic-bargain/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T21:54:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou is delighted to get Yuki Kobayashi in the door at Celtic, believing the chance to sign him at the end of his contract was too good to turn down. Kobayashi is arriving as a free agent from Vissel Kobe, where he made 78 appearances in total at the heart of their defensive line. ...
The post Ange Postecoglou talks up Celtic bargain appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou swerves Alistair Johnston question but states exciting Celtic January intent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/ange-postecoglou-swerves-alistair-johnston-question-but-states-class-celtic-january-intent/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/ange-postecoglou-swerves-alistair-johnston-question-but-states-class-celtic-january-intent/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T21:22:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou refused to be drawn on reported Celtic interest in Alistair Johnston today but did reaffirm his intent to have the Bhoys in a stronger position at the end of January. Celtic have been widely reported to be on the brink of a move for Johnston in recent days, potentially becoming the club’s second ...
The post Ange Postecoglou swerves Alistair Johnston question but states exciting Celtic January intent appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic 'very interested' in Said Hamulic as Dutch striker gathers transfer interest - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CBMiaWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsc2NvdGxhbmQuY28udWsvc3BmbC9zY290dGlzaC1wcmVtaWVyc2hpcC9jZWx0aWMtdmVyeS1pbnRlcmVzdGVkLXNhaWQtaGFtdWxpYy0yNTY2NDM3NdIBbWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsc2NvdGxhbmQuY28udWsvc3BmbC9zY290dGlzaC1wcmVtaWVyc2hpcC9jZWx0aWMtdmVyeS1pbnRlcmVzdGVkLXNhaWQtaGFtdWxpYy0yNTY2NDM3NS5hbXA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiaWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsc2NvdGxhbmQuY28udWsvc3BmbC9zY290dGlzaC1wcmVtaWVyc2hpcC9jZWx0aWMtdmVyeS1pbnRlcmVzdGVkLXNhaWQtaGFtdWxpYy0yNTY2NDM3NdIBbWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsc2NvdGxhbmQuY28udWsvc3BmbC9zY290dGlzaC1wcmVtaWVyc2hpcC9jZWx0aWMtdmVyeS1pbnRlcmVzdGVkLXNhaWQtaGFtdWxpYy0yNTY2NDM3NS5hbXA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T21:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic 'very interested' in Said Hamulic as Dutch striker gathers transfer interest  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best International Players to Play for Celtic this Century]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/best-international-players-to-play-for-celtic-this-century/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/best-international-players-to-play-for-celtic-this-century/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T21:05:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Founded in 1887 in the East End of Glasgow by founding father Brother Walfrid, Celtic is the biggest football clubs in the World and the only club from Scotland to win the European Cup, now the Champions League, to become Champions of Europe.The club is one of five across the globe to have won over Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If The Lawwell Appointment Is Such A Good One, Why Are Celtic Low-Keying It?]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/12/articles-and-features/if-the-lawwell-appointment-is-such-a-good-one-why-are-celtic-low-keying-it/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/12/articles-and-features/if-the-lawwell-appointment-is-such-a-good-one-why-are-celtic-low-keying-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T21:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As my good friend Paddy Sinat over on Vital Celtic said earlier on today, and as others echoed in the past few hours, the club announced Peter Lawwell’s appointment as chairman in the most low key way possible. I noticed it when I saw the official club statement. When we announce a signing or an […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate&#039;s helpful advice for new Celtic signing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/reo-hatates-helpful-advice-for-new-celtic-signing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/reo-hatates-helpful-advice-for-new-celtic-signing/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T20:48:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate advised new Celtic signing Yuki Kobayashi to rest as much as possible prior to his big move to Scotland, having experienced fatigue after his switch last season. Kobayashi, like Daizen Maeda, Reo Hatate and Yosuke Ideguchi before him, are arriving in Glasgow after a long J-League season that is played over the summer ...
The post Reo Hatate&#039;s helpful advice for new Celtic signing appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic showing serious interest in 9-goal Dutch attacker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/report-celtic-showing-interest-in-9-goal-dutch-attacker/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/report-celtic-showing-interest-in-9-goal-dutch-attacker/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T20:15:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are “very interested” in Dutch attacker Said Hamulic, TuttoMercatoWeb in Italy have reported this week. The outlet believes that clubs from France, Belgium, Italy and the Netherlands are tracking the progress of the versatile forward, who currently plays for Stal Mielic in the Polish top flight. But it’s said Celtic are showing the most ...
The post Report: Celtic showing serious interest in 9-goal Dutch attacker appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The gaslighting of the Celtic support has returned alongside Peter Lawwell]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/the-gaslighting-of-the-celtic-support-has-returned-alongside-peter-lawwell/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/the-gaslighting-of-the-celtic-support-has-returned-alongside-peter-lawwell/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T19:44:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the song goes ‘for a minute there, I lost myself’. I was under the impression Celtic had begun to modernise, had started to play catch-up with those football clubs who had taken advantage of our hitherto decade of inertia to embrace modern analytical processes and think outside the box in the recruitment of players, Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero returns to full first-team training after 2 month absence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/hes-ready-to-go-celtic-hero-makes-return-after-2-month-absence/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/hes-ready-to-go-celtic-hero-makes-return-after-2-month-absence/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T19:40:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor is “ready to go” and make an impact for Celtic once again, Ange Postecoglou confirmed today as the midfielder returned to full first-team squad training. McGregor travelled with the group to Sydney but looked to be taking part in non-contact training as he rehabilitated from the knee injury sustained against RB Leipzig on ...
The post Celtic hero returns to full first-team training after 2 month absence appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic Boss’s Michael Beale Slap-Down Was Deliciously, Devilishly Dismissive.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/12/articles-and-features/the-celtic-bosss-michael-beale-slap-down-was-deliciously-devilishly-dismissive/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/12/articles-and-features/the-celtic-bosss-michael-beale-slap-down-was-deliciously-devilishly-dismissive/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T19:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What a superb answer Ange gave today to the obvious question about the new boss at Ibrox. Beale is the new darling of the media, and this city can only really have one of those at a time. Ange will not give up that crown without a fight. Beale may have smarmed them, but Ange […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin O’Neill: “Brian Clough Changed My Life Forever” – A Celtic Exchange Exclusive]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/martin-oneill-brian-clough-changed-my-life-forever-a-celtic-exchange-exclusive/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/martin-oneill-brian-clough-changed-my-life-forever-a-celtic-exchange-exclusive/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T18:43:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An indication of just how far the Celtic Fan Media has developed over the last couple of years is the fact that the quite excellent Celtic Exchange podcast, yesterday managed to get an exclusive interview with former Celtic manager Martin O’Neill. We’ll cover this on The Celtic Star over the next few days starting this Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yuki Kobayashi Press Conference]]></title>
        <id>http://celticunderground.net/yuki-kobayashi-press-conference/</id>
        <link href="http://celticunderground.net/yuki-kobayashi-press-conference/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T18:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing Yuki Kobayashi touched down in Glasgow today. I was in attendance at the fan media press conference. I was impressed with what I heard. He sounded up to the test and has a great idea of what he has to do to make a name for himself at the club. When asked […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leigh Griffiths: A Man Ever In Search Of A Negative Headline.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/12/articles-and-features/articles/leigh-griffiths-a-man-ever-in-search-of-a-negative-headline/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/12/articles-and-features/articles/leigh-griffiths-a-man-ever-in-search-of-a-negative-headline/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T18:07:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is impossible not to marvel at the life of Leigh Griffiths away from the football pitch. Every time he seems as if he might get his act together on the field and give himself a chance of rebuilding something of his career he is spectacularly derailed by something that rises out of the headlines […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable reporters drop more surprise Celtic exit news; Postecoglou may lose &#039;effective player&#039;]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/giorgos-giakoumakis-poised-shock-celtic-exit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/giorgos-giakoumakis-poised-shock-celtic-exit/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T18:05:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic forward Giorgos Giakoumakis is poised for a surprise January exit from the Premiership champions, according to reliable reporters Scott Burns and Duncan Castles. The Lowdown: 25 goals for Celtic… The Greece marksman took time to settle in at Parkhead after arriving in Scotland last year due to a number of issues. However, the 27-year-old […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yuki Kobayashi – Celtic’s new signing speaks to Celtic Fan Media]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/yuki-kobayashi-celtics-new-signing-speaks-to-celtic-fan-media/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/yuki-kobayashi-celtics-new-signing-speaks-to-celtic-fan-media/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T17:52:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s latest signing Yuki Kobayashi spoke to the Celtic fan media after arriving in Glasgow to play for the Scottish Champions. Yuki Kobayashi was immediately thrown into an intense round of media duties including a photoshoot and various interviews plus the customary Welcome to Celtic interview with Celtic TV.22-year old Kobayashi is a left sided Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing Yuki Kobayashi explains Japanese player's success]]></title>
        <id>0d037d6146039be7e7cc9593dd11d4d9</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23167105.new-signing-yuki-kobayashi-explains-japanese-players-celtic-success/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T17:10:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The centre-back reveals why he thinks players from Japan have been such a success at Parkhead]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gio sacked, Beale In: “That registering below what I’m having for dinner tonight,” Ange Postecoglou - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CBMieGh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vZ2lvLXNhY2tlZC1iZWFsZS1pbi10aGF0LXJlZ2lzdGVyaW5nLWJlbG93LXdoYXQtaW0taGF2aW5nLWZvci1kaW5uZXItdG9uaWdodC1hbmdlLXBvc3RlY29nbG91L9IBfGh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vZ2lvLXNhY2tlZC1iZWFsZS1pbi10aGF0LXJlZ2lzdGVyaW5nLWJlbG93LXdoYXQtaW0taGF2aW5nLWZvci1kaW5uZXItdG9uaWdodC1hbmdlLXBvc3RlY29nbG91L2FtcC8</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMieGh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vZ2lvLXNhY2tlZC1iZWFsZS1pbi10aGF0LXJlZ2lzdGVyaW5nLWJlbG93LXdoYXQtaW0taGF2aW5nLWZvci1kaW5uZXItdG9uaWdodC1hbmdlLXBvc3RlY29nbG91L9IBfGh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vZ2lvLXNhY2tlZC1iZWFsZS1pbi10aGF0LXJlZ2lzdGVyaW5nLWJlbG93LXdoYXQtaW0taGF2aW5nLWZvci1kaW5uZXItdG9uaWdodC1hbmdlLXBvc3RlY29nbG91L2FtcC8?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T17:10:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gio sacked, Beale In: “That registering below what I’m having for dinner tonight,” Ange Postecoglou  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Hearts fixtures moved as Sky Sports gear up for a Super Sunday - Scottish Daily Express]]></title>
        <id>CBMiX2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnNjb3R0aXNoZGFpbHlleHByZXNzLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2NlbHRpYy1oZWFydHMtZml4dHVyZXMtbW92ZWQtc2t5LTI4NjQxNDcx0gFjaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuc2NvdHRpc2hkYWlseWV4cHJlc3MuY28udWsvc3BvcnQvZm9vdGJhbGwvY2VsdGljLWhlYXJ0cy1maXh0dXJlcy1tb3ZlZC1za3ktMjg2NDE0NzEuYW1w</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiX2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnNjb3R0aXNoZGFpbHlleHByZXNzLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2NlbHRpYy1oZWFydHMtZml4dHVyZXMtbW92ZWQtc2t5LTI4NjQxNDcx0gFjaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuc2NvdHRpc2hkYWlseWV4cHJlc3MuY28udWsvc3BvcnQvZm9vdGJhbGwvY2VsdGljLWhlYXJ0cy1maXh0dXJlcy1tb3ZlZC1za3ktMjg2NDE0NzEuYW1w?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T17:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Hearts fixtures moved as Sky Sports gear up for a Super Sunday  Scottish Daily Express]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer news: Alistair Johnston deal being finalised amid doubt over futures of Josip Juranovic and Giorgos Giakoumakis - Sky Sports]]></title>
        <id>CBMitQFodHRwczovL3d3dy5za3lzcG9ydHMuY29tL2Zvb3RiYWxsL25ld3MvMTE3ODEvMTI3NjAxNzMvY2VsdGljLXRyYW5zZmVyLW5ld3MtYWxpc3RhaXItam9obnN0b24tZGVhbC1iZWluZy1maW5hbGlzZWQtYW1pZC1kb3VidC1vdmVyLWZ1dHVyZXMtb2Ytam9zaXAtanVyYW5vdmljLWFuZC1naW9yZ29zLWdpYWtvdW1ha2lz0gG5AWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnNreXNwb3J0cy5jb20vYW1wL2Zvb3RiYWxsL25ld3MvMTE3ODEvMTI3NjAxNzMvY2VsdGljLXRyYW5zZmVyLW5ld3MtYWxpc3RhaXItam9obnN0b24tZGVhbC1iZWluZy1maW5hbGlzZWQtYW1pZC1kb3VidC1vdmVyLWZ1dHVyZXMtb2Ytam9zaXAtanVyYW5vdmljLWFuZC1naW9yZ29zLWdpYWtvdW1ha2lz</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMitQFodHRwczovL3d3dy5za3lzcG9ydHMuY29tL2Zvb3RiYWxsL25ld3MvMTE3ODEvMTI3NjAxNzMvY2VsdGljLXRyYW5zZmVyLW5ld3MtYWxpc3RhaXItam9obnN0b24tZGVhbC1iZWluZy1maW5hbGlzZWQtYW1pZC1kb3VidC1vdmVyLWZ1dHVyZXMtb2Ytam9zaXAtanVyYW5vdmljLWFuZC1naW9yZ29zLWdpYWtvdW1ha2lz0gG5AWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnNreXNwb3J0cy5jb20vYW1wL2Zvb3RiYWxsL25ld3MvMTE3ODEvMTI3NjAxNzMvY2VsdGljLXRyYW5zZmVyLW5ld3MtYWxpc3RhaXItam9obnN0b24tZGVhbC1iZWluZy1maW5hbGlzZWQtYW1pZC1kb3VidC1vdmVyLWZ1dHVyZXMtb2Ytam9zaXAtanVyYW5vdmljLWFuZC1naW9yZ29zLWdpYWtvdW1ha2lz?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T16:47:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer news: Alistair Johnston deal being finalised amid doubt over futures of Josip Juranovic and Giorgos Giakoumakis  Sky Sports]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yuki Kobayashi reveals his reason for Celtic signing]]></title>
        <id>ce9013a80407ccf5baba066f6afddb6a</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23166977.yuki-kobayashi-reveals-reason-celtic-signing/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T16:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He has signed a five-year-deal at Parkhead]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hibs left embarrassed after announcing FC Edinburgh friendly will now take place behind closed doors after lack of tickets sold - Scottish Daily Express]]></title>
        <id>CBMiZWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnNjb3R0aXNoZGFpbHlleHByZXNzLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2hpYnMtbGVmdC1lbWJhcnJhc3NlZC1hZnRlci1hbm5vdW5jaW5nLTI4NjQwOTkz0gEA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiZWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnNjb3R0aXNoZGFpbHlleHByZXNzLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2hpYnMtbGVmdC1lbWJhcnJhc3NlZC1hZnRlci1hbm5vdW5jaW5nLTI4NjQwOTkz0gEA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T15:56:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hibs left embarrassed after announcing FC Edinburgh friendly will now take place behind closed doors after lack of tickets sold  Scottish Daily Express]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hearts and Celtic games moved for TV coverage as Sky announce latest  of 11 live fixtures]]></title>
        <id>3940415</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/hearts/hearts-and-celtic-games-moved-for-tv-coverage-as-sky-announce-latest-of-11-live-fixtures-3940415"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T15:27:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hearts and Celtic’s January fixtures at Livingston and Dundee United respectively have been rescheduled for television.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which players might transfer to Celtic in the future? - Celtic Quick News]]></title>
        <id>CBMiV2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmNlbHRpY3F1aWNrbmV3cy5jby51ay93aGljaC1wbGF5ZXJzLW1pZ2h0LXRyYW5zZmVyLXRvLWNlbHRpYy1pbi10aGUtZnV0dXJlL9IBW2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmNlbHRpY3F1aWNrbmV3cy5jby51ay93aGljaC1wbGF5ZXJzLW1pZ2h0LXRyYW5zZmVyLXRvLWNlbHRpYy1pbi10aGUtZnV0dXJlL2FtcC8</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiV2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmNlbHRpY3F1aWNrbmV3cy5jby51ay93aGljaC1wbGF5ZXJzLW1pZ2h0LXRyYW5zZmVyLXRvLWNlbHRpYy1pbi10aGUtZnV0dXJlL9IBW2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmNlbHRpY3F1aWNrbmV3cy5jby51ay93aGljaC1wbGF5ZXJzLW1pZ2h0LXRyYW5zZmVyLXRvLWNlbHRpYy1pbi10aGUtZnV0dXJlL2FtcC8?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T15:10:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Which players might transfer to Celtic in the future?  Celtic Quick News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WATCH: New Celtic signing Yuki Kobayashi arrives in Glasgow]]></title>
        <id>55a7b7c5aa792f3266a7815536d97e0a</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23166333.new-celtic-signing-yuki-kobayashi-arrives-glasgow/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T14:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Japanese defender has joined from Vissel Kobe]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yuki Kobayashi arrives ahead of Celtic deal as Japanese star gets the welcome to Glasgow treatment - Glasgow Live]]></title>
        <id>CBMiUGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmdsYXNnb3dsaXZlLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L3l1a2kta29iYXlhc2hpLWFycml2ZXMtYWhlYWQtY2VsdGljLTI1NjU5OTA40gFUaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZ2xhc2dvd2xpdmUuY28udWsvc3BvcnQveXVraS1rb2JheWFzaGktYXJyaXZlcy1haGVhZC1jZWx0aWMtMjU2NTk5MDguYW1w</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiUGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmdsYXNnb3dsaXZlLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L3l1a2kta29iYXlhc2hpLWFycml2ZXMtYWhlYWQtY2VsdGljLTI1NjU5OTA40gFUaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZ2xhc2dvd2xpdmUuY28udWsvc3BvcnQveXVraS1rb2JheWFzaGktYXJyaXZlcy1haGVhZC1jZWx0aWMtMjU2NTk5MDguYW1w?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T14:03:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yuki Kobayashi arrives ahead of Celtic deal as Japanese star gets the welcome to Glasgow treatment  Glasgow Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Virals: Celtic pulling out all the stops to get big weekend attendance - Read Celtic]]></title>
        <id>CBMiaGh0dHBzOi8vcmVhZGNlbHRpYy5jb20vMjAyMi8xMi8wMi92aXJhbHMtY2VsdGljLXB1bGxpbmctb3V0LWFsbC10aGUtc3RvcHMtdG8tZ2V0LWJpZy13ZWVrZW5kLWF0dGVuZGFuY2Uv0gEA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiaGh0dHBzOi8vcmVhZGNlbHRpYy5jb20vMjAyMi8xMi8wMi92aXJhbHMtY2VsdGljLXB1bGxpbmctb3V0LWFsbC10aGUtc3RvcHMtdG8tZ2V0LWJpZy13ZWVrZW5kLWF0dGVuZGFuY2Uv0gEA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Virals: Celtic pulling out all the stops to get big weekend attendance  Read Celtic]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin O'Neill in hilarious Celtic dressing room jest as former boss reveals Neil Lennon and Bobo Balde rivalry - Scottish Daily Express]]></title>
        <id>CBMiZmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnNjb3R0aXNoZGFpbHlleHByZXNzLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL21hcnRpbi1vbmVpbGwtaGlsYXJpb3VzLWNlbHRpYy1kcmVzc2luZy0yODYzOTM5MtIBAA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiZmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnNjb3R0aXNoZGFpbHlleHByZXNzLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL21hcnRpbi1vbmVpbGwtaGlsYXJpb3VzLWNlbHRpYy1kcmVzc2luZy0yODYzOTM5MtIBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T13:53:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Martin O'Neill in hilarious Celtic dressing room jest as former boss reveals Neil Lennon and Bobo Balde rivalry  Scottish Daily Express]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic powerbroker Desmond hails Lawwell as 'outstanding']]></title>
        <id>a114ac0c1cb9ffecc348f9034fdd1ab1</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23166007.celtic-powerbroker-desmond-incoming-chairman-lawwell-outstanding/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T13:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Parkhead side's principal shareholder had nothing but good things to say about the 63-year-olds return to the board]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Lawwell's new Celtic role: What Desmond, Postecoglou, Bankier and man himself had to say about appointment]]></title>
        <id>3940072</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/peter-lawwells-new-celtic-role-what-desmond-postecoglou-bankier-and-man-himself-had-to-say-about-appointment-3940072"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T13:01:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have announced that Peter Lawwell will take up the role of non-executive chairman of the club next month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lawwell Gets The Chairmanship As Celtic Insults The Fans With A Massive Step Backwards. - TheCelticBlog.com]]></title>
        <id>CBMiiwFodHRwczovL3RoZWNlbHRpY2Jsb2cuY29tLzIwMjIvMTIvYXJ0aWNsZXMtYW5kLWZlYXR1cmVzL2xhd3dlbGwtZ2V0cy10aGUtY2hhaXJtYW4tYXMtY2VsdGljLWluc3VsdHMtdGhlLWZhbnMtd2l0aC1hLW1hc3NpdmUtc3RlcC1iYWNrd2FyZHMv0gGPAWh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljYmxvZy5jb20vMjAyMi8xMi9hcnRpY2xlcy1hbmQtZmVhdHVyZXMvbGF3d2VsbC1nZXRzLXRoZS1jaGFpcm1hbi1hcy1jZWx0aWMtaW5zdWx0cy10aGUtZmFucy13aXRoLWEtbWFzc2l2ZS1zdGVwLWJhY2t3YXJkcy9hbXAv</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiiwFodHRwczovL3RoZWNlbHRpY2Jsb2cuY29tLzIwMjIvMTIvYXJ0aWNsZXMtYW5kLWZlYXR1cmVzL2xhd3dlbGwtZ2V0cy10aGUtY2hhaXJtYW4tYXMtY2VsdGljLWluc3VsdHMtdGhlLWZhbnMtd2l0aC1hLW1hc3NpdmUtc3RlcC1iYWNrd2FyZHMv0gGPAWh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljYmxvZy5jb20vMjAyMi8xMi9hcnRpY2xlcy1hbmQtZmVhdHVyZXMvbGF3d2VsbC1nZXRzLXRoZS1jaGFpcm1hbi1hcy1jZWx0aWMtaW5zdWx0cy10aGUtZmFucy13aXRoLWEtbWFzc2l2ZS1zdGVwLWJhY2t3YXJkcy9hbXAv?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T12:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawwell Gets The Chairmanship As Celtic Insults The Fans With A Massive Step Backwards.  TheCelticBlog.com]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Lawwell returns as Celtic chairman and Dermot Desmond hails 'outstanding candidate' - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CBMiaWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvcGV0ZXItbGF3d2VsbC1yZXR1cm5zLWNlbHRpYy1jaGFpcm1hbi0yODYzODk1MtIBbWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvcGV0ZXItbGF3d2VsbC1yZXR1cm5zLWNlbHRpYy1jaGFpcm1hbi0yODYzODk1Mi5hbXA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiaWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvcGV0ZXItbGF3d2VsbC1yZXR1cm5zLWNlbHRpYy1jaGFpcm1hbi0yODYzODk1MtIBbWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvcGV0ZXItbGF3d2VsbC1yZXR1cm5zLWNlbHRpYy1jaGFpcm1hbi0yODYzODk1Mi5hbXA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T12:45:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Lawwell returns as Celtic chairman and Dermot Desmond hails 'outstanding candidate'  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Lawwell returns to Celtic as non-executive chairman]]></title>
        <id>c4b39d6637bc4ff904de23809d089a17</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23165900.peter-lawwell-returns-celtic-non-executive-chairman/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T12:44:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Lawwell has returned to Celtic as a director of the club and the new non-executive chairman.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“It was fantastic. I am talking now and almost getting goosebumps,” Fran Alonso - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CBMiZmh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vaXQtd2FzLWZhbnRhc3RpYy1pLWFtLXRhbGtpbmctbm93LWFuZC1hbG1vc3QtZ2V0dGluZy1nb29zZWJ1bXBzLWZyYW4tYWxvbnNvL9IBamh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vaXQtd2FzLWZhbnRhc3RpYy1pLWFtLXRhbGtpbmctbm93LWFuZC1hbG1vc3QtZ2V0dGluZy1nb29zZWJ1bXBzLWZyYW4tYWxvbnNvL2FtcC8</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiZmh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vaXQtd2FzLWZhbnRhc3RpYy1pLWFtLXRhbGtpbmctbm93LWFuZC1hbG1vc3QtZ2V0dGluZy1nb29zZWJ1bXBzLWZyYW4tYWxvbnNvL9IBamh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vaXQtd2FzLWZhbnRhc3RpYy1pLWFtLXRhbGtpbmctbm93LWFuZC1hbG1vc3QtZ2V0dGluZy1nb29zZWJ1bXBzLWZyYW4tYWxvbnNvL2FtcC8?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T11:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“It was fantastic. I am talking now and almost getting goosebumps,” Fran Alonso  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Josip Juranovic Tottenham transfer floated as Celtic prepare for exit]]></title>
        <id>a63cdf06daf12f8dd9ac44b6dba1e151</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23165577.josip-juranovic-tottenham-transfer-floated-celtic-prepare-exit/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T11:35:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Tottenham goalkeeper Paul Robinson reckons Josip Juranovic could be the perfect fit for his former club.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur tipped to have interest in Celtic World Cup star as 'low millions' signing praised for impact]]></title>
        <id>3939728</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/tottenham-hotspur-tipped-to-have-interest-in-celtic-world-cup-star-as-low-millions-signing-praised-for-impact-3939728"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T11:17:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur manager Antonio Conte could look to Celtic star Josip Juranovic to improve his options on the right of defence, according to a former Spurs and England star.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angus Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Isaac Price hits back to  Celtic's Matt O'Riley over 'red card' tackle]]></title>
        <id>c6ead7da7485dbd7e007070c56ed63b2</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23165464.isaac-price-hits-back-celtics-matt-oriley-red-card-tackle/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T11:16:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EVERTON superkid Isaac Price has broken his silence on his horror tackle on Celtic's Matt O'Riley that the Hoops midfielder claimed could have broken his leg and admitted it was 'naughty.']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sead Haksabanovic Celtic transfer details revealed as top agent brokered bargain deal to bring winger to Parkhead - Scottish Daily Express]]></title>
        <id>CBMiaGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnNjb3R0aXNoZGFpbHlleHByZXNzLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL3NlYWQtaGFrc2FiYW5vdmljLWNlbHRpYy10cmFuc2Zlci1kZXRhaWxzLTI4NjM3MTg10gEA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiaGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnNjb3R0aXNoZGFpbHlleHByZXNzLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL3NlYWQtaGFrc2FiYW5vdmljLWNlbHRpYy10cmFuc2Zlci1kZXRhaWxzLTI4NjM3MTg10gEA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T10:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sead Haksabanovic Celtic transfer details revealed as top agent brokered bargain deal to bring winger to Parkhead  Scottish Daily Express]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Stars Set To Face Each Other In World Cup Last 16 | Celts Are Here - CeltsAreHere]]></title>
        <id>CBMiUmh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtc3RhcnMtc2V0LXRvLWZhY2UtZWFjaC1vdGhlci1pbi13b3JsZC1jdXAtbGFzdC0xNi_SAVZodHRwczovL2NlbHRzYXJlaGVyZS5jb20vY2VsdGljLXN0YXJzLXNldC10by1mYWNlLWVhY2gtb3RoZXItaW4td29ybGQtY3VwLWxhc3QtMTYvYW1wLw</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiUmh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtc3RhcnMtc2V0LXRvLWZhY2UtZWFjaC1vdGhlci1pbi13b3JsZC1jdXAtbGFzdC0xNi_SAVZodHRwczovL2NlbHRzYXJlaGVyZS5jb20vY2VsdGljLXN0YXJzLXNldC10by1mYWNlLWVhY2gtb3RoZXItaW4td29ybGQtY3VwLWxhc3QtMTYvYW1wLw?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T10:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Stars Set To Face Each Other In World Cup Last 16 | Celts Are Here  CeltsAreHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers v Aberdeen | Semi-Final Ticket Info - afc.co.uk]]></title>
        <id>CBMiUmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmFmYy5jby51ay8yMDIyLzEyLzAyL3JhbmdlcnMtdi1hYmVyZGVlbi1zZW1pLWZpbmFsLXRpY2tldC1pbmZvcm1hdGlvbi_SAQA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiUmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmFmYy5jby51ay8yMDIyLzEyLzAyL3JhbmdlcnMtdi1hYmVyZGVlbi1zZW1pLWZpbmFsLXRpY2tldC1pbmZvcm1hdGlvbi_SAQA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T10:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers v Aberdeen | Semi-Final Ticket Info  afc.co.uk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sead Haksabanovic dealmaker reveals Celtic delight over transfer success and plan that led him to Parkhead - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CBMibmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3Mvc2VhZC1oYWtzYWJhbm92aWMtZGVhbG1ha2VyLXJldmVhbHMtY2VsdGljLTI4NjM2ODM40gFyaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZGFpbHlyZWNvcmQuY28udWsvc3BvcnQvZm9vdGJhbGwvZm9vdGJhbGwtbmV3cy9zZWFkLWhha3NhYmFub3ZpYy1kZWFsbWFrZXItcmV2ZWFscy1jZWx0aWMtMjg2MzY4MzguYW1w</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMibmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3Mvc2VhZC1oYWtzYWJhbm92aWMtZGVhbG1ha2VyLXJldmVhbHMtY2VsdGljLTI4NjM2ODM40gFyaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZGFpbHlyZWNvcmQuY28udWsvc3BvcnQvZm9vdGJhbGwvZm9vdGJhbGwtbmV3cy9zZWFkLWhha3NhYmFub3ZpYy1kZWFsbWFrZXItcmV2ZWFscy1jZWx0aWMtMjg2MzY4MzguYW1w?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T09:49:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sead Haksabanovic dealmaker reveals Celtic delight over transfer success and plan that led him to Parkhead  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic face fight to land striker target as Scottish champions get tidy World Cup cash boost]]></title>
        <id>3939399</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-face-fight-to-land-striker-target-as-scottish-champions-get-tidy-world-cup-cash-boost-3939399"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T09:20:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will face a fight to land South Korean World Cup star Gue-sung Cho with reported competition from Europe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angus Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic star Leigh Griffiths' home raided by 10 cops in two-and-a-half hour search - Daily Star]]></title>
        <id>CBMiV2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5c3Rhci5jby51ay9zcG9ydC9mb290YmFsbC9sZWlnaC1ncmlmZml0aHMtc2VhcmNoLXBvbGljZS1wcm9iZS0yODYzNjE3MdIBW2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5c3Rhci5jby51ay9zcG9ydC9mb290YmFsbC9sZWlnaC1ncmlmZml0aHMtc2VhcmNoLXBvbGljZS1wcm9iZS0yODYzNjE3MS5hbXA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiV2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5c3Rhci5jby51ay9zcG9ydC9mb290YmFsbC9sZWlnaC1ncmlmZml0aHMtc2VhcmNoLXBvbGljZS1wcm9iZS0yODYzNjE3MdIBW2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5c3Rhci5jby51ay9zcG9ydC9mb290YmFsbC9sZWlnaC1ncmlmZml0aHMtc2VhcmNoLXBvbGljZS1wcm9iZS0yODYzNjE3MS5hbXA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T08:41:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic star Leigh Griffiths' home raided by 10 cops in two-and-a-half hour search  Daily Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic dealt Cho Gue-sung transfer blow as Ferencvaros enter race]]></title>
        <id>72a68ad2e1ea96f2dd1aedf7a8b2ce42</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23164898.celtic-dealt-cho-gue-sung-transfer-blow-ferencvaros-enter-race/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T08:33:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ferencvaros have entered the race to sign South Korea striker Cho Gue-sung after an impressive showing at the World Cup in Qatar.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mindsets, rules & risks: Scottish FA's heading restrictions in focus - Celtic Way]]></title>
        <id>CBMia2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmNlbHRpY3dheS5jby51ay9mZWF0dXJlcy8yMzE2MjcxOS5taW5kc2V0cy1ydWxlcy1yaXNrcy1zY290dGlzaC1mYXMtaGVhZGluZy1yZXN0cmljdGlvbnMtZm9jdXMv0gEA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMia2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmNlbHRpY3dheS5jby51ay9mZWF0dXJlcy8yMzE2MjcxOS5taW5kc2V0cy1ydWxlcy1yaXNrcy1zY290dGlzaC1mYXMtaGVhZGluZy1yZXN0cmljdGlvbnMtZm9jdXMv0gEA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T07:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mindsets, rules & risks: Scottish FA's heading restrictions in focus  Celtic Way]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgos Giakoumakis and the Celtic transfer exit risk won't impact Ange's 'out and out' striker hunt - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>1679694461</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMibGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvZ2lvcmdvcy1naWFrb3VtYWtpcy1jZWx0aWMtdHJhbnNmZXItZXhpdC0yODYzMjEzMNIBcGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvZ2lvcmdvcy1naWFrb3VtYWtpcy1jZWx0aWMtdHJhbnNmZXItZXhpdC0yODYzMjEzMC5hbXA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgos Giakoumakis and the Celtic transfer exit risk won't impact Ange's 'out and out' striker hunt  Daily Record
Celtic looking to sign another World Cup sensation  The Celtic Bhoys
Celtic join Cho Gue-sung Transfer Chase Celts Are Here  CeltsAreHere
Celtic's Giorgos Giakoumakis transfer stance - TCW Panel | Celtic Way  Celtic Way
Cho Gue-sung Celtic switch threat as Borussia Dortmund target Korean World Cup star  Scottish Daily Express
View Full coverage on Google News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Fitzwater handed bumper Livingston transfer price tag as David Martindale makes contract confession - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CBMia2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvamFjay1maXR6d2F0ZXItaGFuZGVkLWJ1bXBlci1saXZpbmdzdG9uLTI4NjMzMzUx0gFvaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZGFpbHlyZWNvcmQuY28udWsvc3BvcnQvZm9vdGJhbGwvZm9vdGJhbGwtbmV3cy9qYWNrLWZpdHp3YXRlci1oYW5kZWQtYnVtcGVyLWxpdmluZ3N0b24tMjg2MzMzNTEuYW1w</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMia2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvamFjay1maXR6d2F0ZXItaGFuZGVkLWJ1bXBlci1saXZpbmdzdG9uLTI4NjMzMzUx0gFvaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZGFpbHlyZWNvcmQuY28udWsvc3BvcnQvZm9vdGJhbGwvZm9vdGJhbGwtbmV3cy9qYWNrLWZpdHp3YXRlci1oYW5kZWQtYnVtcGVyLWxpdmluZ3N0b24tMjg2MzMzNTEuYW1w?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Fitzwater handed bumper Livingston transfer price tag as David Martindale makes contract confession  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic On This Day – 2nd December – David Potter’s Celtic Diary]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-on-this-day-2nd-december-david-potters-celtic-diary/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-on-this-day-2nd-december-david-potters-celtic-diary/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T00:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Historian David Potter each morning on The Celtic Star looks back at key Celtic events and matches on this day starting on  2 December 1905. David’s latest book The Celtic Rising ~ 1965 The Year Jock Stein Changed Everything is very close to selling out on Celtic Star Books with just a few books remaining. Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Path Now Clear for Expected Celtic Announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/path-now-clear-for-expected-celtic-announcement/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/path-now-clear-for-expected-celtic-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T22:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s gone quiet on the Alistair Johnston Transfer front over the last 48 hours. The player has been in Qatar for the World Cup, so can’t exactly be anywhere else to seal a deal. The Canadian right-back has now played his final game of his countries World Cup campaign and will shortly heading back to […]
The post Path Now Clear for Expected Celtic Announcement first appeared on Celts Are Here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SFA admit one of their controversial Celtic decisions looked "strange"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/sfa-admit-one-of-their-controversial-celtic-decisions-looked-strange/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/sfa-admit-one-of-their-controversial-celtic-decisions-looked-strange/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T21:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scottish FA Chief Executive Ian Maxwell doesn’t believe the perception of the decision to rule Celtic star Jota offside against Motherwell matters, because VAR technology got the offside call right regardless. There was controversy in the wake of the Bhoys win over the Steelmen last month after one of the cameras in operation failed to ...
The post SFA admit one of their controversial Celtic decisions looked "strange" appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celts in Qatar: Daizen’s Delight – Japan shock Spain to win the Group]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celts-in-qatar-daizens-delight-japan-shock-spain-to-win-the-group/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celts-in-qatar-daizens-delight-japan-shock-spain-to-win-the-group/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T21:49:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s becoming more and more the World Cup of shockers as yet another big scalp has taken place tonight. Japan have beaten Spain 2-1 to qualify for the knockout stages of the World Cup in Qatar. Daizen Maeda is now the fourth Celtic player in the Round of 16 as he joins, Josip Juranovic, Aaron Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All Eyes on Celtic Stock Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/all-eyes-on-celtic-stock-exchange/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/all-eyes-on-celtic-stock-exchange/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T21:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CeltsAreHere attended this year’s AGM where the question of who would succeed Ian Bankier as Celtic chairman came up during the shareholder Q&A. Ian Bankier will be stepping down as chairman when the clock strikes midnight on Hogmanay. We’re now into December with no news of his successor to date. Mr Bankier responded to the […]
The post All Eyes on Celtic Stock Exchange first appeared on Celts Are Here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic women look to get back to winning ways : Celtic FC vs Dundee United match preview]]></title>
        <id>http://celticunderground.net/celtic-women-look-to-get-back-to-winning-ways-celtic-fc-vs-dundee-united-match-preview/</id>
        <link href="http://celticunderground.net/celtic-women-look-to-get-back-to-winning-ways-celtic-fc-vs-dundee-united-match-preview/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T21:42:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If interested you can watch the woman's team this weekend at the Excelsior Stadium for the perfect family day out! Kids go free and there is a shuttle bus from Airdrie train station.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston Celtic transfer hint dropped by Canada boss - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CBMiamh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvYWxpc3RhaXItam9obnN0b24tY2VsdGljLXRyYW5zZmVyLWhpbnQtMjg2MzQ0MjLSAW5odHRwczovL3d3dy5kYWlseXJlY29yZC5jby51ay9zcG9ydC9mb290YmFsbC9mb290YmFsbC1uZXdzL2FsaXN0YWlyLWpvaG5zdG9uLWNlbHRpYy10cmFuc2Zlci1oaW50LTI4NjM0NDIyLmFtcA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiamh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvYWxpc3RhaXItam9obnN0b24tY2VsdGljLXRyYW5zZmVyLWhpbnQtMjg2MzQ0MjLSAW5odHRwczovL3d3dy5kYWlseXJlY29yZC5jby51ay9zcG9ydC9mb290YmFsbC9mb290YmFsbC1uZXdzL2FsaXN0YWlyLWpvaG5zdG9uLWNlbHRpYy10cmFuc2Zlci1oaW50LTI4NjM0NDIyLmFtcA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T21:27:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston Celtic transfer hint dropped by Canada boss  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Controversial, crazy two hours: Japan, Spain, Germany and Costa Rica involved in World Cup's greatest group denouement]]></title>
        <id>3939272</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/controversial-crazy-two-hours-japan-spain-germany-and-costa-rica-involved-in-world-cups-greatest-group-denouement-3939272"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T21:26:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just when you thought you’d seen it all. If Wednesday’s Group C drama with Argentina, Poland, Mexico and Saudi Arabia wasn’t enough for you, then surely what we witnessed in Group E on Thursday has left you sated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2 Celtic stars will now face each other in knockout World Cup game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/world-cup/2-celtic-bhoys-will-now-face-each-other-in-knockout-world-cup-game/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/world-cup/2-celtic-bhoys-will-now-face-each-other-in-knockout-world-cup-game/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T21:21:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda’s Japan will play Josip Juranovic’s Croatia in the last 16 of the World Cup after a dramatic day of action at the Qatar tournament. Japan, remarkably, finished as winners of Group E after beating both Germany and Spain over the last week. Meanwhile, Croatia are also through, drawing with Belgium today to secure ...
The post 2 Celtic stars will now face each other in knockout World Cup game appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda completes Celtic World Cup clean sweep as all FOUR Parkhead stars go into last 16 - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CBMiWWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2RhaXplbi1tYWVkYS1jb21wbGV0ZXMtY2VsdGljLXdvcmxkLTI4NjM0NDMx0gFdaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZGFpbHlyZWNvcmQuY28udWsvc3BvcnQvZm9vdGJhbGwvZGFpemVuLW1hZWRhLWNvbXBsZXRlcy1jZWx0aWMtd29ybGQtMjg2MzQ0MzEuYW1w</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiWWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2RhaXplbi1tYWVkYS1jb21wbGV0ZXMtY2VsdGljLXdvcmxkLTI4NjM0NDMx0gFdaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZGFpbHlyZWNvcmQuY28udWsvc3BvcnQvZm9vdGJhbGwvZGFpemVuLW1hZWRhLWNvbXBsZXRlcy1jZWx0aWMtd29ybGQtMjg2MzQ0MzEuYW1w?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T21:12:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda completes Celtic World Cup clean sweep as all FOUR Parkhead stars go into last 16  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Ibrox Players Line Up To Urge Sevco To Adopt The Strategy That Killed Rangers.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/12/blogs/ex-ibrox-players-line-up-to-urge-sevco-to-adopt-the-strategy-that-killed-rangers/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/12/blogs/ex-ibrox-players-line-up-to-urge-sevco-to-adopt-the-strategy-that-killed-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T21:03:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last couple of days, the Ibrox fans have been treated to the views of people who should never, ever open a corner shop. Financially illiterate, bloated with the usual supremacist guff and completely impervious to the lessons of history they have demanded insanity from the club that they profess to have the deepest […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good News and Bad News for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/good-news-and-bad-news-for-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/good-news-and-bad-news-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T21:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The World Cup has provided some shocks so far and Celtic players at the competition have been at the forefront of them. The good news for Celtic and their World Cup stars is they’ve all made it through to the knockout stages of the World Cup with their countries in what can only be seen […]
The post Good News and Bad News for Celtic first appeared on Celts Are Here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Daizen Maeda verdict as Celtic star&#039;s Japan shock the world yet again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/world-cup/the-daizen-maeda-verdict-as-celtic-heros-japan-shock-the-world-yet-again/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/world-cup/the-daizen-maeda-verdict-as-celtic-heros-japan-shock-the-world-yet-again/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T20:54:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All four of Celtic’s representatives at the World Cup are now through to the knockout last 16 of the tournament after Daizen Maeda’s Japan pulled off a stunning upset against Spain. Maeda was handed his second start of the group stage up against the Spanish on a dramatic night that, at various stages, had all ...
The post The Daizen Maeda verdict as Celtic star&#039;s Japan shock the world yet again appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star Daizen Maeda's World Cup continues as Japan beat Spain]]></title>
        <id>31107fcb24d08b0fabd8811ef26132c2</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23164671.celtic-star-daizen-maedas-world-cup-continues-japan-beat-spain/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T20:54:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Hoops striker joins three other teammates in the knockout stages of the competition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Things Can Change’ – Celtic Star Tipped to be Dropped by Ange in Next 12 Months]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/things-can-change-celtic-star-tipped-to-be-dropped-by-ange-in-next-12-months/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/things-can-change-celtic-star-tipped-to-be-dropped-by-ange-in-next-12-months/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T20:49:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker Frank McAvennie believes Joe Hart won’t be Celtic’s number one by this time next year, tipping his current understudy Benjamin Siegrist to become the new hoops number one. Joe has been a stalwart in Ange Postecoglou’s side since making the £1m move from Spurs 18 months ago. Joe has been a fantastic […]
The post ‘Things Can Change’ – Celtic Star Tipped to be Dropped by Ange in Next 12 Months first appeared on Celts Are Here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Celtic Will Be Looking to Cash In‘ on Inconsistent Parkhead Star – Pundit]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-will-be-looking-to-cash-in-on-inconsistent-parkhead-star-pundit/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-will-be-looking-to-cash-in-on-inconsistent-parkhead-star-pundit/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T19:56:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tan McManus believes Celtic could and should cash in on Josip Juranovic in January after the emergence of Alistair Johnston as a top January target. Johnston played his final game of the World Cup on Thursday evening and now looked destined to head to the Hoops sooner rather than later. It leaves Juranovic’s future up […]
The post ‘Celtic Will Be Looking to Cash In‘ on Inconsistent Parkhead Star – Pundit first appeared on Celts Are Here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic to face even more VAR as Scottish FA ramp up rollout]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/report-celtic-to-face-even-more-var-as-scottish-fa-ramp-up-rollout/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/report-celtic-to-face-even-more-var-as-scottish-fa-ramp-up-rollout/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Video Assistant Referees (VAR) will be used in the Scottish Cup from the Fourth Round stage, but only for matches where the Scottish Premiership side is at home, The Scotsman has reported this evening. VAR is already being used in the top flight, with its implementation so far attracting the ire of many fans, pundits ...
The post Report: Celtic to face even more VAR as Scottish FA ramp up rollout appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celts in Qatar – Daizen Maeda starts for Japan against Spain]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celts-in-qatar-daizen-maeda-starts-for-japan-against-spain/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celts-in-qatar-daizen-maeda-starts-for-japan-against-spain/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T19:13:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda has been recalled to the starting XI for Japan in their crucial World Cup match against Spain tonight. The forward has yet to score at the tournament and this evening would be a perfect time for his to open his account at Qatar 2022.The Celtic striker was the only player from the club Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Yuki Kobayashi of Vissel Kobe leaves for Celtic” with Fan Media Conference confirmed]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/yuki-kobayashi-of-vissel-kobe-leaves-for-celtic-with-fan-media-conference-confirmed/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/yuki-kobayashi-of-vissel-kobe-leaves-for-celtic-with-fan-media-conference-confirmed/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T18:58:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we patiently await the restart of domestic action and look forward to Ange Postecoglou and his Celtic team firing onwards in the pursuit of another treble for the club, there is also one eye on transfer business in and out of Celtic. One signing is already confirmed, whilst another seems to be a mere Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VAR to be used in the Scottish Cup from the fourth round - but only up to 6 of the 16 fixtures]]></title>
        <id>3939220</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/var-to-be-used-in-the-scottish-cup-from-the-fourth-round-but-only-up-to-6-of-the-16-fixtures-3939220"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T18:40:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VAR is set to be used in the Scottish Cup, starting from the fourth round next month with the arrival of the Premiership sides.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Beale sets bold Rangers title target to topple Celtic and 'win 56 as soon as possible' - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CBMiZWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsc2NvdGxhbmQuY28udWsvc3BmbC9zY290dGlzaC1wcmVtaWVyc2hpcC9taWNoYWVsLWJlYWxlLXNldHMtYm9sZC1yYW5nZXJzLTI1NjUzMTEx0gFpaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZm9vdGJhbGxzY290bGFuZC5jby51ay9zcGZsL3Njb3R0aXNoLXByZW1pZXJzaGlwL21pY2hhZWwtYmVhbGUtc2V0cy1ib2xkLXJhbmdlcnMtMjU2NTMxMTEuYW1w</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiZWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsc2NvdGxhbmQuY28udWsvc3BmbC9zY290dGlzaC1wcmVtaWVyc2hpcC9taWNoYWVsLWJlYWxlLXNldHMtYm9sZC1yYW5nZXJzLTI1NjUzMTEx0gFpaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZm9vdGJhbGxzY290bGFuZC5jby51ay9zcGZsL3Njb3R0aXNoLXByZW1pZXJzaGlwL21pY2hhZWwtYmVhbGUtc2V0cy1ib2xkLXJhbmdlcnMtMjU2NTMxMTEuYW1w?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T17:49:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Beale sets bold Rangers title target to topple Celtic and 'win 56 as soon as possible'  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Beale makes Rangers title vow as he wants '56' and claims catching Celtic can be achieved - Scottish Daily Express]]></title>
        <id>CBMiYGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnNjb3R0aXNoZGFpbHlleHByZXNzLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL21pY2hhZWwtYmVhbGUtbWFrZXMtcmFuZ2Vycy10aXRsZS0yODYzMjgxM9IBZGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnNjb3R0aXNoZGFpbHlleHByZXNzLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL21pY2hhZWwtYmVhbGUtbWFrZXMtcmFuZ2Vycy10aXRsZS0yODYzMjgxMy5hbXA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiYGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnNjb3R0aXNoZGFpbHlleHByZXNzLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL21pY2hhZWwtYmVhbGUtbWFrZXMtcmFuZ2Vycy10aXRsZS0yODYzMjgxM9IBZGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnNjb3R0aXNoZGFpbHlleHByZXNzLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL21pY2hhZWwtYmVhbGUtbWFrZXMtcmFuZ2Vycy10aXRsZS0yODYzMjgxMy5hbXA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T17:41:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Beale makes Rangers title vow as he wants '56' and claims catching Celtic can be achieved  Scottish Daily Express]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Josip Juranovic qualifies for World Cup last 16]]></title>
        <id>104a184e7f3dfd214f7ce8a34cebac20</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23164351.celtic-defender-josip-juranovic-qualifies-world-cup-last-16/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T17:13:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Hoops right-back will represent Croatia in the knockout stages of the tournament]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Josip Juranovic enhances Celtic value with fine Croatia display as Alistair Johnston has bad miss for Canada]]></title>
        <id>3939107</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/josip-juranovic-enhances-celtic-value-with-fine-croatia-display-as-alistair-johnston-has-bad-miss-for-canada-3939107"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T17:03:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic right-back Josip Juranovic put in another assured display for Croatia as they secured their place in the last 16 of the World Cup with a 0-0 draw against Belgium.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Haksabanovic can play 'even better' for Celtic claims former coach]]></title>
        <id>832db2474ac2297b4bf116abae79d755</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23164233.haksabanovic-can-play-even-better-celtic-claims-former-coach/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T16:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Montenegrin has become a fans favourite since joining from Rubin Kazan]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic new boy Yuki Kobayashi prepares to jet in to Scotland]]></title>
        <id>c627a811d1da59fcfde0b8e286f2fd3c</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23164193.celtic-new-boy-yuki-kobayashi-prepares-jet-scotland/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T16:40:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 22-year-old recently signed a five-year deal with the Scottish champions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic 'transfer target' Oscar Gloukh's release clause revealed]]></title>
        <id>f1eaf637d6fbf038870a7905ad5dd018</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23163900.celtic-transfer-target-oscar-gloukhs-release-clause-revealed/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T15:41:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 18-year-old is said to have been scouted by a whopping 25 clubs throughout Europe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic looking to sign another World Cup sensation - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>CBMiTGh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljYmhveXMuY29tLzIwMjIvMTIvMDEvY2VsdGljLWxvb2tpbmctc2lnbi1hbm90aGVyLXdvcmxkLWN1cC_SAVBodHRwczovL3RoZWNlbHRpY2Job3lzLmNvbS8yMDIyLzEyLzAxL2NlbHRpYy1sb29raW5nLXNpZ24tYW5vdGhlci13b3JsZC1jdXAvYW1wLw</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiTGh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljYmhveXMuY29tLzIwMjIvMTIvMDEvY2VsdGljLWxvb2tpbmctc2lnbi1hbm90aGVyLXdvcmxkLWN1cC_SAVBodHRwczovL3RoZWNlbHRpY2Job3lzLmNvbS8yMDIyLzEyLzAxL2NlbHRpYy1sb29raW5nLXNpZ24tYW5vdGhlci13b3JsZC1jdXAvYW1wLw?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T15:36:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic looking to sign another World Cup sensation  The Celtic Bhoys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Giakoumakis bombshell was foreshadowed by Celtic boss Postecoglou]]></title>
        <id>2390f4288b37199e1498abb1ae96faf5</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23163625.giakoumakis-bombshell-foreshadowed-celtic-boss-postecoglou/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T15:35:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's been reported the Greek forward is set to leave Celtic Park in January after failing to agree a new contract.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oscar Gloukh transfer clause as Celtic release price set by Maccabi Tel Aviv while January suitors line up - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CBMicGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLXRyYW5zZmVyLW5ld3Mvb3NjYXItZ2xvdWtoLXRyYW5zZmVyLWNsYXVzZS1jZWx0aWMtMjg2MzAyNzTSAXRodHRwczovL3d3dy5kYWlseXJlY29yZC5jby51ay9zcG9ydC9mb290YmFsbC9mb290YmFsbC10cmFuc2Zlci1uZXdzL29zY2FyLWdsb3VraC10cmFuc2Zlci1jbGF1c2UtY2VsdGljLTI4NjMwMjc0LmFtcA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMicGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLXRyYW5zZmVyLW5ld3Mvb3NjYXItZ2xvdWtoLXRyYW5zZmVyLWNsYXVzZS1jZWx0aWMtMjg2MzAyNzTSAXRodHRwczovL3d3dy5kYWlseXJlY29yZC5jby51ay9zcG9ydC9mb290YmFsbC9mb290YmFsbC10cmFuc2Zlci1uZXdzL29zY2FyLWdsb3VraC10cmFuc2Zlci1jbGF1c2UtY2VsdGljLTI4NjMwMjc0LmFtcA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T14:07:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oscar Gloukh transfer clause as Celtic release price set by Maccabi Tel Aviv while January suitors line up  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lucy Ashworth-Clifford suffered ACL injury against Rangers – Fran Alonso - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CBMiYWh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vbHVjeS1hc2h3b3J0aC1jbGlmZm9yZC1zdWZmZXJlZC1hY2wtaW5qdXJ5LWFnYWluc3QtcmFuZ2Vycy1mcmFuLWFsb25zby_SAWVodHRwczovL3RoZWNlbHRpY3N0YXIuY29tL2x1Y3ktYXNod29ydGgtY2xpZmZvcmQtc3VmZmVyZWQtYWNsLWluanVyeS1hZ2FpbnN0LXJhbmdlcnMtZnJhbi1hbG9uc28vYW1wLw</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiYWh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vbHVjeS1hc2h3b3J0aC1jbGlmZm9yZC1zdWZmZXJlZC1hY2wtaW5qdXJ5LWFnYWluc3QtcmFuZ2Vycy1mcmFuLWFsb25zby_SAWVodHRwczovL3RoZWNlbHRpY3N0YXIuY29tL2x1Y3ktYXNod29ydGgtY2xpZmZvcmQtc3VmZmVyZWQtYWNsLWluanVyeS1hZ2FpbnN0LXJhbmdlcnMtZnJhbi1hbG9uc28vYW1wLw?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T13:50:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lucy Ashworth-Clifford suffered ACL injury against Rangers – Fran Alonso  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Furuhashi Japan situation explained as legend hails Celtic form]]></title>
        <id>9b26e8dbe09a2038254bae42ae7de247</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23162926.kyogo-furuhashi-japan-situation-explained-legend-hails-celtic-form/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T13:41:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE Japanese forward was left out of the World Cup squad.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart won’t be Celtic number one next season – expert - Football Insider]]></title>
        <id>CBMiWWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsaW5zaWRlcjI0Ny5jb20vam9lLWhhcnQtd29udC1iZS1jZWx0aWMtbnVtYmVyLW9uZS1uZXh0LXNlYXNvbi1leHBlcnQv0gFdaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZm9vdGJhbGxpbnNpZGVyMjQ3LmNvbS9qb2UtaGFydC13b250LWJlLWNlbHRpYy1udW1iZXItb25lLW5leHQtc2Vhc29uLWV4cGVydC8_YW1w</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiWWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsaW5zaWRlcjI0Ny5jb20vam9lLWhhcnQtd29udC1iZS1jZWx0aWMtbnVtYmVyLW9uZS1uZXh0LXNlYXNvbi1leHBlcnQv0gFdaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZm9vdGJhbGxpbnNpZGVyMjQ3LmNvbS9qb2UtaGFydC13b250LWJlLWNlbHRpYy1udW1iZXItb25lLW5leHQtc2Vhc29uLWV4cGVydC8_YW1w?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T12:51:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart won’t be Celtic number one next season – expert  Football Insider]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic B stage dramatic late comeback as they return to winning ways - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CBMibWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL2NlbHRpYy15b3V0aC9jZWx0aWMtYi1zdGFnZS1kcmFtYXRpYy1sYXRlLWNvbWViYWNrLWFzLXRoZXktcmV0dXJuLXRvLXdpbm5pbmctd2F5cy_SAXFodHRwczovL3d3dy42N2hhaWxoYWlsLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMteW91dGgvY2VsdGljLWItc3RhZ2UtZHJhbWF0aWMtbGF0ZS1jb21lYmFjay1hcy10aGV5LXJldHVybi10by13aW5uaW5nLXdheXMvP2FtcA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMibWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL2NlbHRpYy15b3V0aC9jZWx0aWMtYi1zdGFnZS1kcmFtYXRpYy1sYXRlLWNvbWViYWNrLWFzLXRoZXktcmV0dXJuLXRvLXdpbm5pbmctd2F5cy_SAXFodHRwczovL3d3dy42N2hhaWxoYWlsLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMteW91dGgvY2VsdGljLWItc3RhZ2UtZHJhbWF0aWMtbGF0ZS1jb21lYmFjay1hcy10aGV5LXJldHVybi10by13aW5uaW5nLXdheXMvP2FtcA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic B stage dramatic late comeback as they return to winning ways  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hard work set to get underway from today for Celtic squad - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CBMiWmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL25ld3MvaGFyZC13b3JrLXNldC10by1nZXQtdW5kZXJ3YXktZnJvbS10b2RheS1mb3ItY2VsdGljLXNxdWFkL9IBXmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL25ld3MvaGFyZC13b3JrLXNldC10by1nZXQtdW5kZXJ3YXktZnJvbS10b2RheS1mb3ItY2VsdGljLXNxdWFkLz9hbXA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiWmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL25ld3MvaGFyZC13b3JrLXNldC10by1nZXQtdW5kZXJ3YXktZnJvbS10b2RheS1mb3ItY2VsdGljLXNxdWFkL9IBXmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL25ld3MvaGFyZC13b3JrLXNldC10by1nZXQtdW5kZXJ3YXktZnJvbS10b2RheS1mb3ItY2VsdGljLXNxdWFkLz9hbXA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hard work set to get underway from today for Celtic squad  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor injury timeline revealed as Celtic star prepares for return - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CBMibGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL25ld3MvY2FsbHVtLW1jZ3JlZ29yLWluanVyeS10aW1lbGluZS1yZXZlYWxlZC1hcy1jZWx0aWMtc3Rhci1wcmVwYXJlcy1mb3ItcmV0dXJuL9IBcGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL25ld3MvY2FsbHVtLW1jZ3JlZ29yLWluanVyeS10aW1lbGluZS1yZXZlYWxlZC1hcy1jZWx0aWMtc3Rhci1wcmVwYXJlcy1mb3ItcmV0dXJuLz9hbXA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMibGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL25ld3MvY2FsbHVtLW1jZ3JlZ29yLWluanVyeS10aW1lbGluZS1yZXZlYWxlZC1hcy1jZWx0aWMtc3Rhci1wcmVwYXJlcy1mb3ItcmV0dXJuL9IBcGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL25ld3MvY2FsbHVtLW1jZ3JlZ29yLWluanVyeS10aW1lbGluZS1yZXZlYWxlZC1hcy1jZWx0aWMtc3Rhci1wcmVwYXJlcy1mb3ItcmV0dXJuLz9hbXA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor injury timeline revealed as Celtic star prepares for return  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic set for huge injury boost as Callum McGregor eyes first-team return ahead of Premiership restart]]></title>
        <id>3937926</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-set-for-huge-injury-boost-as-callum-mcgregor-eyes-first-team-return-ahead-of-premiership-restart-3937926"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T09:18:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are to receive a huge injury boost with Callum McGregor scheduled to make his return to first-team action ahead of the Premiership restart later this month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angus Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor Celtic injury comeback timeline revealed]]></title>
        <id>5dd127077280e071f8334aa964cbb389</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23161711.callum-mcgregor-celtic-injury-comeback-timeline-revealed/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T08:13:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE Parkhead skipper is set to return in a friendly match against Rennes this month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic 'join transfer race' for South Korea striker Cho Gue-sung]]></title>
        <id>3c69a79f11102f68fc23a23c155d3fa9</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23161676.celtic-join-transfer-race-south-korea-striker-cho-gue-sung/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T07:33:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC are reportedly among a host of European clubs keen to sign the striker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VAR in Scottish football - 30 games, the investment, the benefits, the improvements but one question persists]]></title>
        <id>3937738</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/var-in-scottish-football-30-games-the-investment-the-benefits-the-improvements-but-one-question-persists-3937738"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tucked in behind housing estates and cul-de-sacs, across the road from a car garage, surrounded by industrial estates and a sign for a food truck is the nondescript office buildings in Baillieston which acts as the epicentre to one of the biggest and arguably the most controversial of changes to Scottish football. VAR.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic line up second World Cup star, 21-goal South Korean but ace could exit as contract talks stall]]></title>
        <id>3937807</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-line-up-second-world-cup-star-21-goal-south-korean-but-ace-could-exit-as-contract-talks-stall-3937807"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T06:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are keen on South Korean World Cup star Gue-sung Cho but will likely face stiff competition from around Europe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angus Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Josip Juranovic Celtic Transfer Rumour - Celts Are Here - CeltsAreHere]]></title>
        <id>CBMiQGh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9qb3NpcC1qdXJhbm92aWMtY2VsdGljLXRyYW5zZmVyLXJ1bW91ci_SAYkBaHR0cHM6Ly9jZWx0c2FyZWhlcmUuY29tL2pvc2lwLWp1cmFub3ZpYy1jZWx0aWMtdHJhbnNmZXItcnVtb3VyL2FtcC8_ZmJjbGlkPUl3QVIzQU4tdzUzZzd2bUg3WHJEV296c1ZEZFUzbEpDTmh2bWlhX0RxanJmMmxmVkxydG5heWNnQTB2LWs</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiQGh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9qb3NpcC1qdXJhbm92aWMtY2VsdGljLXRyYW5zZmVyLXJ1bW91ci_SAYkBaHR0cHM6Ly9jZWx0c2FyZWhlcmUuY29tL2pvc2lwLWp1cmFub3ZpYy1jZWx0aWMtdHJhbnNmZXItcnVtb3VyL2FtcC8_ZmJjbGlkPUl3QVIzQU4tdzUzZzd2bUg3WHJEV296c1ZEZFUzbEpDTmh2bWlhX0RxanJmMmxmVkxydG5heWNnQTB2LWs?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T06:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Josip Juranovic Celtic Transfer Rumour - Celts Are Here  CeltsAreHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Josip Juranovic Celtic Transfer Rumour - Celts Are Here - CeltsAreHere]]></title>
        <id>CBMiQGh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9qb3NpcC1qdXJhbm92aWMtY2VsdGljLXRyYW5zZmVyLXJ1bW91ci_SAURodHRwczovL2NlbHRzYXJlaGVyZS5jb20vam9zaXAtanVyYW5vdmljLWNlbHRpYy10cmFuc2Zlci1ydW1vdXIvYW1wLw</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiQGh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9qb3NpcC1qdXJhbm92aWMtY2VsdGljLXRyYW5zZmVyLXJ1bW91ci_SAURodHRwczovL2NlbHRzYXJlaGVyZS5jb20vam9zaXAtanVyYW5vdmljLWNlbHRpYy10cmFuc2Zlci1ydW1vdXIvYW1wLw?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T06:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Josip Juranovic Celtic Transfer Rumour - Celts Are Here  CeltsAreHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic FC youth coach who sexually abused teenage players in Scotland dies in prison - The Irish News]]></title>
        <id>CBMipwFodHRwczovL3d3dy5pcmlzaG5ld3MuY29tL25ld3Mvbm9ydGhlcm5pcmVsYW5kbmV3cy8yMDIyLzEyLzAxL25ld3MvZm9ybWVyX2NlbHRpY19mY195b3V0aF9jb2FjaF93aG9fc2V4dWFsbHlfYWJ1c2VkX3RlZW5hZ2VfcGxheWVyc19pbl9zY290bGFuZF9kaWVzX2luX3ByaXNvbi0yOTIyOTg4L9IBAA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMipwFodHRwczovL3d3dy5pcmlzaG5ld3MuY29tL25ld3Mvbm9ydGhlcm5pcmVsYW5kbmV3cy8yMDIyLzEyLzAxL25ld3MvZm9ybWVyX2NlbHRpY19mY195b3V0aF9jb2FjaF93aG9fc2V4dWFsbHlfYWJ1c2VkX3RlZW5hZ2VfcGxheWVyc19pbl9zY290bGFuZF9kaWVzX2luX3ByaXNvbi0yOTIyOTg4L9IBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T01:08:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic FC youth coach who sexually abused teenage players in Scotland dies in prison  The Irish News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic On This Day – 1st December – David Potter’s Celtic Diary]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-on-this-day-1st-december-david-potters-celtic-diary/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-on-this-day-1st-december-david-potters-celtic-diary/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T00:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Historian David Potter each morning on The Celtic Star looks back at key Celtic events and matches on this day starting on 1st December 1906. David’s latest book The Celtic Rising ~ 1965 The Year Jock Stein Changed Everything is very close to selling out on Celtic Star Books with just 24 books remaining. Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Improved Giakoumakis Contract Talks Break Down]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/report-improved-giakoumakis-contract-talks-break-down/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/report-improved-giakoumakis-contract-talks-break-down/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T23:23:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s being reported on Wednesday evening that Celtic will look to sell Gorgios Giakoumakis in the January transfer window if they can’t come to an agreement over a new deal. Two very well placed sources in Scott Burns and Duncan Castles have reported Giakoumakis is unhappy with his current Celtic deal and is looking for […]
The post Report: Improved Giakoumakis Contract Talks Break Down first appeared on Celts Are Here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Improved Giakoumakis Contract Talks Break Down Celts Are Here - CeltsAreHere]]></title>
        <id>CBMiT2h0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9yZXBvcnQtaW1wcm92ZWQtZ2lha291bWFraXMtY29udHJhY3QtdGFsa3MtYnJlYWstZG93bi_SAQA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiT2h0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9yZXBvcnQtaW1wcm92ZWQtZ2lha291bWFraXMtY29udHJhY3QtdGFsa3MtYnJlYWstZG93bi_SAQA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T23:23:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Improved Giakoumakis Contract Talks Break Down Celts Are Here  CeltsAreHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Improved Giakoumakis Contract Talks Break Down Celts Are Here - CeltsAreHere]]></title>
        <id>CBMiT2h0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9yZXBvcnQtaW1wcm92ZWQtZ2lha291bWFraXMtY29udHJhY3QtdGFsa3MtYnJlYWstZG93bi_SAVNodHRwczovL2NlbHRzYXJlaGVyZS5jb20vcmVwb3J0LWltcHJvdmVkLWdpYWtvdW1ha2lzLWNvbnRyYWN0LXRhbGtzLWJyZWFrLWRvd24vYW1wLw</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiT2h0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9yZXBvcnQtaW1wcm92ZWQtZ2lha291bWFraXMtY29udHJhY3QtdGFsa3MtYnJlYWstZG93bi_SAVNodHRwczovL2NlbHRzYXJlaGVyZS5jb20vcmVwb3J0LWltcHJvdmVkLWdpYWtvdW1ha2lzLWNvbnRyYWN0LXRhbGtzLWJyZWFrLWRvd24vYW1wLw?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T23:23:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Improved Giakoumakis Contract Talks Break Down Celts Are Here  CeltsAreHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic join Cho Gue-sung Transfer Chase]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-join-cho-gue-sung-transfer-chase/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-join-cho-gue-sung-transfer-chase/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T23:12:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC are chasing the signing of another World Cup star — this time Ange wants South Korea striker Cho Gue-sung to join the Hoops in Glasgow. SunSport has revealed the Scottish Champions are keen to bring in her 6ft 2” frontman who Ange has been watching since before he became the manager of Celtic. The […]
The post Celtic join Cho Gue-sung Transfer Chase first appeared on Celts Are Here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic join Cho Gue-sung Transfer Chase Celts Are Here - CeltsAreHere]]></title>
        <id>CBMiQWh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtam9pbi1jaG8tZ3VlLXN1bmctdHJhbnNmZXItY2hhc2Uv0gFFaHR0cHM6Ly9jZWx0c2FyZWhlcmUuY29tL2NlbHRpYy1qb2luLWNoby1ndWUtc3VuZy10cmFuc2Zlci1jaGFzZS9hbXAv</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiQWh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtam9pbi1jaG8tZ3VlLXN1bmctdHJhbnNmZXItY2hhc2Uv0gFFaHR0cHM6Ly9jZWx0c2FyZWhlcmUuY29tL2NlbHRpYy1qb2luLWNoby1ndWUtc3VuZy10cmFuc2Zlci1jaGFzZS9hbXAv?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T23:12:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic join Cho Gue-sung Transfer Chase Celts Are Here  CeltsAreHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cho Gue sung 'wanted' by Celtic as South Korea World Cup goal hero sees Euro suitors pile up - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CBMiXmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvY2hvLWd1ZS1zdW5nLXdhbnRlZC1jZWx0aWMtMjg2MjQ5MDTSAWJodHRwczovL3d3dy5kYWlseXJlY29yZC5jby51ay9zcG9ydC9mb290YmFsbC9mb290YmFsbC1uZXdzL2Noby1ndWUtc3VuZy13YW50ZWQtY2VsdGljLTI4NjI0OTA0LmFtcA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiXmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvY2hvLWd1ZS1zdW5nLXdhbnRlZC1jZWx0aWMtMjg2MjQ5MDTSAWJodHRwczovL3d3dy5kYWlseXJlY29yZC5jby51ay9zcG9ydC9mb290YmFsbC9mb290YmFsbC1uZXdzL2Noby1ndWUtc3VuZy13YW50ZWQtY2VsdGljLTI4NjI0OTA0LmFtcA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T22:51:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cho Gue sung 'wanted' by Celtic as South Korea World Cup goal hero sees Euro suitors pile up  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgos Giakoumakis 'set for' Celtic January transfer exit]]></title>
        <id>2c0960aee57ef3ab5e53190f6f48083a</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23161534.giorgos-giakoumakis-set-for-celtic-january-transfer-exit/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T22:44:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Talks between the club and the Greek striker over a new and improved contract have broken down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[50 YEARS A CELT]]></title>
        <id>http://celticunderground.net/50-years-a-celt-2/</id>
        <link href="http://celticunderground.net/50-years-a-celt-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T22:31:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 18th of November marked the 50th anniversary of my first time attending a Celtic game. Or the first one certainly that I can remember. On that day in 1972 my old Dad took me to see Celtic at the tender age of 6, and although it wasn’t actually the first time he had taken […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scottish Premiership benefits from VAR with 8% increase in correct decisions as SFA claims 'it has worked']]></title>
        <id>3937548</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/scottish-premiership-benefits-from-var-with-8-increase-in-correct-decisions-as-sfa-claims-it-has-worked-3937548"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scottish FA chief Ian Maxwell has said VAR "has worked” with the Scottish Premiership benefiting from an eight per cent increase in the success rate for big decisions in games since its introduction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ian Maxwell addresses Celtic controversy as he explains Hawkeye factor]]></title>
        <id>8e279b1ff2ce214ba0cd3f58e562f046</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23161200.ian-maxwell-says-var-working-addresses-celtic-controversy/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SFA chief-executive is satisfied VAR is 'working' as he revealed positive feedback from clubs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beale Has Proved Good At Running His Mouth. We’ll See What Else He’s Got.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/11/articles-and-features/beale-has-proved-good-at-running-his-mouth-well-see-what-else-hes-got/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/11/articles-and-features/beale-has-proved-good-at-running-his-mouth-well-see-what-else-hes-got/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T22:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Beale. What a start he’s made as Ibrox gaffer. He’s closed the gap just by opening his gob. He has Ryan Kent playing brilliantly, albeit in training against his own mates. He has taken “the cards” out of the hands of the contract rebels, although they can still talk to any club they want […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who is Ange’s Standout Celtic Summer Signing?]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/who-is-anges-standout-celtic-summer-signing/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/who-is-anges-standout-celtic-summer-signing/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T21:34:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There were a total of nine arrivals at Celtic during the summer, with a few of the previous season’s players signing permanent deals. The trio of Jota, Daizen Maeda and Cameron Carter-Vickers trio had all been on loan at the Hoops during the previous term and played a huge part in the club winning two […]
The post Who is Ange’s Standout Celtic Summer Signing? first appeared on Celts Are Here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MOOY v MESSI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/mooy-v-messi/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/mooy-v-messi/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T21:28:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AARAN MOOY will face Lionel Messi when Australia take on Argentina in the World Cup last 16 shoot-out in Qatar on Saturday evening. The Celtic midfielder was impressive again as the Socceroos booked their second spot in Group D behind reigning champions France on a day of high drama. Mathew Leckie scored a superb goal [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy’s star role as Australia qualify for Last 16]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/aaron-mooys-star-role-as-australia-qualify-for-last-16/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/aaron-mooys-star-role-as-australia-qualify-for-last-16/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T21:24:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder Aaron Mooy played a star role for Australia this afternoon as they qualified for the Last 16. The 32-year-old was given the seemingly daunting task of curbing Manchester United’s Christian Eriksen.Mooy was excellent in breaking up the Danes as they tried to push forward, marking Eriksen out of the game and limited them Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[&#039;Guilty of a few... &#039; - Frank McAvennie hails £18k-p/w Celtic ace for honest remarks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/daizen-maeda-praised-champions-league-verdict-mcavennie/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/daizen-maeda-praised-champions-league-verdict-mcavennie/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T21:15:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star Daizen Maeda has been praised by former Hoops striker Frank McAvennie for his honesty in acknowledging the mistakes made by himself and his team-mates in the wake of their Champions League failure this season.  The Lowdown: Champions League catastrophe  The Group F offering to Celtic was never a kind draw, but the Premiership […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ligue 1 side make announcement about Celtic game - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>CBMiR2h0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljYmhveXMuY29tLzIwMjIvMTEvMzAvbGlndWUtMS1zaWRlLWFubm91bmNlbWVudC1jZWx0aWMv0gFLaHR0cHM6Ly90aGVjZWx0aWNiaG95cy5jb20vMjAyMi8xMS8zMC9saWd1ZS0xLXNpZGUtYW5ub3VuY2VtZW50LWNlbHRpYy9hbXAv</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiR2h0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljYmhveXMuY29tLzIwMjIvMTEvMzAvbGlndWUtMS1zaWRlLWFubm91bmNlbWVudC1jZWx0aWMv0gFLaHR0cHM6Ly90aGVjZWx0aWNiaG95cy5jb20vMjAyMi8xMS8zMC9saWd1ZS0xLXNpZGUtYW5ub3VuY2VtZW50LWNlbHRpYy9hbXAv?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T21:13:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ligue 1 side make announcement about Celtic game  The Celtic Bhoys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou Tipped for Big Time EPL Move]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/ange-postecoglou-tipped-for-premier-league/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/ange-postecoglou-tipped-for-premier-league/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T21:10:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU’s former assistant Peter Cklamovski has claimed that the Celtic manager is one of the best in the business but has admitted he’ll soon be in the Premier League to prove it. The Aussie gaffer has been linked to numerous jobs Down South since he guided Celtic to the league title in his first […]
The post Ange Postecoglou Tipped for Big Time EPL Move first appeared on Celts Are Here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For His Own Good, Leigh Griffiths Should Not Return To Celtic Park As A Player.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/11/articles-and-features/for-his-own-good-leigh-griffiths-should-not-return-to-celtic-park-as-a-player/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/11/articles-and-features/for-his-own-good-leigh-griffiths-should-not-return-to-celtic-park-as-a-player/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T20:55:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leigh Griffiths being linked with a move to Morton, at just the moment we draw them in the Scottish Cup, has an odd kind of cosmic logic to it. It would give the game extra juice, that’s for damned sure, and the press would have a field day with their “you just know what’s in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For His Own Good, Leigh Griffiths Should Not Return To Celtic Park As A Player. - TheCelticBlog.com]]></title>
        <id>CBMihgFodHRwczovL3RoZWNlbHRpY2Jsb2cuY29tLzIwMjIvMTEvYXJ0aWNsZXMtYW5kLWZlYXR1cmVzL2Zvci1oaXMtb3duLWdvb2QtbGVpZ2gtZ3JpZmZpdGhzLXNob3VsZC1ub3QtcmV0dXJuLXRvLWNlbHRpYy1wYXJrLWFzLWEtcGxheWVyL9IB0AFodHRwczovL3RoZWNlbHRpY2Jsb2cuY29tLzIwMjIvMTEvYXJ0aWNsZXMtYW5kLWZlYXR1cmVzL2Zvci1oaXMtb3duLWdvb2QtbGVpZ2gtZ3JpZmZpdGhzLXNob3VsZC1ub3QtcmV0dXJuLXRvLWNlbHRpYy1wYXJrLWFzLWEtcGxheWVyLz91dG1fc291cmNlPXRodW1ibmFpbCZ1dG1fbWVkaXVtPWludGVybmFsJnV0bV9jYW1wYWlnbj1yZWxhdGVkLXN0b3JpZXMmYW1w</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMihgFodHRwczovL3RoZWNlbHRpY2Jsb2cuY29tLzIwMjIvMTEvYXJ0aWNsZXMtYW5kLWZlYXR1cmVzL2Zvci1oaXMtb3duLWdvb2QtbGVpZ2gtZ3JpZmZpdGhzLXNob3VsZC1ub3QtcmV0dXJuLXRvLWNlbHRpYy1wYXJrLWFzLWEtcGxheWVyL9IB0AFodHRwczovL3RoZWNlbHRpY2Jsb2cuY29tLzIwMjIvMTEvYXJ0aWNsZXMtYW5kLWZlYXR1cmVzL2Zvci1oaXMtb3duLWdvb2QtbGVpZ2gtZ3JpZmZpdGhzLXNob3VsZC1ub3QtcmV0dXJuLXRvLWNlbHRpYy1wYXJrLWFzLWEtcGxheWVyLz91dG1fc291cmNlPXRodW1ibmFpbCZ1dG1fbWVkaXVtPWludGVybmFsJnV0bV9jYW1wYWlnbj1yZWxhdGVkLXN0b3JpZXMmYW1w?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T20:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For His Own Good, Leigh Griffiths Should Not Return To Celtic Park As A Player.  TheCelticBlog.com]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Park Open for Business During World Cup]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-park-open-for-business-during-world-cup/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-park-open-for-business-during-world-cup/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T20:45:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic Park Sports Bar will now be open every weekend, with the newest addition to the stadium initially opening on match days. [Celtic FC] Punters can now enjoy a drink with some bar snacks out with match days, and is a great addition for those touring the stadium across the weekend, for a before/after […]
The post Celtic Park Open for Business During World Cup first appeared on Celts Are Here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Park Open for Business During World Cup Celts Are Here - CeltsAreHere]]></title>
        <id>CBMiSGh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtcGFyay1vcGVuLWZvci1idXNpbmVzcy1kdXJpbmctd29ybGQtY3VwL9IBTGh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtcGFyay1vcGVuLWZvci1idXNpbmVzcy1kdXJpbmctd29ybGQtY3VwL2FtcC8</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiSGh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtcGFyay1vcGVuLWZvci1idXNpbmVzcy1kdXJpbmctd29ybGQtY3VwL9IBTGh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtcGFyay1vcGVuLWZvci1idXNpbmVzcy1kdXJpbmctd29ybGQtY3VwL2FtcC8?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T20:45:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Park Open for Business During World Cup Celts Are Here  CeltsAreHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exciting Celtic Women Update]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/exciting-celtic-women-update/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/exciting-celtic-women-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T20:28:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC WOMEN are trying to attract fans with the mens team currently on a break. Fran Alsonso’s side are playing Dundee United on Sunday, with a 16.10 kick off. It’s a great time to watch the side, looking to get back to winning ways after their derby draw at the weekend. The fixture is set […]
The post Exciting Celtic Women Update first appeared on Celts Are Here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World Cup Celtic Stars; Current State of Play]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/world-cup-celtic-stars-current-state-of-play/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/world-cup-celtic-stars-current-state-of-play/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T20:20:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AARON MOOY and Australia are through to the last 16 of the World Cup after they beat Denmark 1-0 to finish second place to France in Group D. The midfielder joins Celtic defender Cameron Carter-Vickers in the next round of the competition, with half of the Hoops’ stars now secured a knockout place stage. Josip […]
The post World Cup Celtic Stars; Current State of Play first appeared on Celts Are Here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Past V Future? – Juranović and Johnston feature as Croatia beat Canada 4-1]]></title>
        <id>http://celticunderground.net/past-v-future-juranovic-and-johnston-feature-as-croatia-beat-canada-4-1/</id>
        <link href="http://celticunderground.net/past-v-future-juranovic-and-johnston-feature-as-croatia-beat-canada-4-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T20:20:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As day eight of the World Cup commenced, the mouthwatering Group F match between Spain and Germany looked pick of the bunch, but for Celtic fans they would keep a keen eye on proceedings in the earlier match in the group as 2018 finalists, Croatia, played the tournaments rookies, Canada.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kye Rowles, Harry Souttar and Aaron Mooy all shine as Australia make history and book a place in last 16]]></title>
        <id>3937754</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/hearts/kye-rowles-harry-souttar-and-aaron-mooy-all-shine-as-australia-make-history-and-book-a-place-in-last-16-3937754"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T19:15:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Australia edged towards a clutch of World Cup firsts, including their first spot in the last 16 since 2006, two group wins for the first time, and their first clean sheet in 11 attempts against a European side on the greatest stage, there was almost grudging respect from pundits who, even at half-time, were predicting this would be the Socceroos curtain call.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moira Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exclusive: Celtic confident of agreeing £5m+ Josip Juranovic deal after terms agreed - Football Insider]]></title>
        <id>CBMiRGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsaW5zaWRlcjI0Ny5jb20vY2VsdGljLXNvdXJjZXMtanVyYW5vdmljLWphbnVhcnkv0gFIaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZm9vdGJhbGxpbnNpZGVyMjQ3LmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtc291cmNlcy1qdXJhbm92aWMtamFudWFyeS8_YW1w</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiRGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsaW5zaWRlcjI0Ny5jb20vY2VsdGljLXNvdXJjZXMtanVyYW5vdmljLWphbnVhcnkv0gFIaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZm9vdGJhbGxpbnNpZGVyMjQ3LmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtc291cmNlcy1qdXJhbm92aWMtamFudWFyeS8_YW1w?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T18:55:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exclusive: Celtic confident of agreeing £5m+ Josip Juranovic deal after terms agreed  Football Insider]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's Next Five Very Difficult Fixtures Celts Are Here - CeltsAreHere]]></title>
        <id>CBMiNmh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtZmMtbmV4dC1maXZlLWZpeHR1cmVzL9IBf2h0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtZmMtbmV4dC1maXZlLWZpeHR1cmVzL2FtcC8_ZmJjbGlkPUl3QVIwYnZOdDlnZlo2ajRYVEFDbXlzVHFZMldKdHFSUzdybXAwYmVrajZ4X0NId1NtNnpuLTdabWU0Vmc</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiNmh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtZmMtbmV4dC1maXZlLWZpeHR1cmVzL9IBf2h0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtZmMtbmV4dC1maXZlLWZpeHR1cmVzL2FtcC8_ZmJjbGlkPUl3QVIwYnZOdDlnZlo2ajRYVEFDbXlzVHFZMldKdHFSUzdybXAwYmVrajZ4X0NId1NtNnpuLTdabWU0Vmc?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T17:40:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's Next Five Very Difficult Fixtures Celts Are Here  CeltsAreHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's Next Five Very Difficult Fixtures Celts Are Here - CeltsAreHere]]></title>
        <id>CBMiNmh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtZmMtbmV4dC1maXZlLWZpeHR1cmVzL9IBf2h0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtZmMtbmV4dC1maXZlLWZpeHR1cmVzL2FtcC8_ZmJjbGlkPUl3QVIzUGRmZUU4WEc0TWNNcnhOdXVXdWx0SENfR3h4VVhkek5qVTRXRm9KXzI1UUkyV3psNm1zTzdmdFk</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiNmh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtZmMtbmV4dC1maXZlLWZpeHR1cmVzL9IBf2h0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtZmMtbmV4dC1maXZlLWZpeHR1cmVzL2FtcC8_ZmJjbGlkPUl3QVIzUGRmZUU4WEc0TWNNcnhOdXVXdWx0SENfR3h4VVhkek5qVTRXRm9KXzI1UUkyV3psNm1zTzdmdFk?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T17:40:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's Next Five Very Difficult Fixtures Celts Are Here  CeltsAreHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's Next Five Very Difficult Fixtures Celts Are Here - CeltsAreHere]]></title>
        <id>CBMiNmh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtZmMtbmV4dC1maXZlLWZpeHR1cmVzL9IBOmh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtZmMtbmV4dC1maXZlLWZpeHR1cmVzL2FtcC8</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiNmh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtZmMtbmV4dC1maXZlLWZpeHR1cmVzL9IBOmh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtZmMtbmV4dC1maXZlLWZpeHR1cmVzL2FtcC8?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T17:40:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's Next Five Very Difficult Fixtures Celts Are Here  CeltsAreHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou 'one of world's best coaches']]></title>
        <id>bbeda499c147ff6e1013c88bd385a108</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23160963.celtic-boss-ange-postecoglou-one-worlds-best-coaches/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T17:03:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Hoops manager has been backed to support the statement in the Premier League.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lundstram insists it's 'not impossible' for Rangers to catch Celtic]]></title>
        <id>66efe92955c20b6e97eb8f9c830a6f24</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23160662.lundstram-insists-not-impossible-rangers-catch-celtic/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T16:03:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou's men are nine-points clear of their Glasgow rivals as things stand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers 'won't stop' in bid to chase down Celtic, say Michael Beale]]></title>
        <id>58b33bed7a0a27651e66ec4582f0edb3</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23160652.rangers-wont-stop-bid-chase-celtic-say-michael-beale/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T16:01:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Hoops currently lead their arch rivals by nine-points at the summit of the Premiership table.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston: €4m Celtic transfer could be 'announced soon' as defender to become second January signing]]></title>
        <id>3937409</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/alistair-johnston-eu4m-celtic-transfer-could-be-announced-soon-as-defender-to-become-second-january-signing-3937409"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T15:40:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are closing in on completing the signing of Canada’s World Cup star Alistair Johnston.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angus Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic told to pay €5 million fee for international star - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>CBMiQGh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljYmhveXMuY29tLzIwMjIvMTEvMzAvY2VsdGljLXRvbGQtNS1taWxsaW9uLWZlZS_SAURodHRwczovL3RoZWNlbHRpY2Job3lzLmNvbS8yMDIyLzExLzMwL2NlbHRpYy10b2xkLTUtbWlsbGlvbi1mZWUvYW1wLw</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiQGh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljYmhveXMuY29tLzIwMjIvMTEvMzAvY2VsdGljLXRvbGQtNS1taWxsaW9uLWZlZS_SAURodHRwczovL3RoZWNlbHRpY2Job3lzLmNvbS8yMDIyLzExLzMwL2NlbHRpYy10b2xkLTUtbWlsbGlvbi1mZWUvYW1wLw?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T15:03:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic told to pay €5 million fee for international star  The Celtic Bhoys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic to face Rennes in friendly as Ange Postecoglou steps up Premiership preparation - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEGZ4H-PnHacdmGM0Vi727UgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPLfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiUWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsc2NvdGxhbmQuY28udWsvc3BmbC9jZWx0aWMtZmFjZS1yZW5uZXMtZnJpZW5kbHktYW5nZS0yNTYzOTM1MNIBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T12:29:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic to face Rennes in friendly as Ange Postecoglou steps up Premiership preparation  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic to face Rennes in friendly as Ange Postecoglou steps up Premiership preparation - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CBMiUWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsc2NvdGxhbmQuY28udWsvc3BmbC9jZWx0aWMtZmFjZS1yZW5uZXMtZnJpZW5kbHktYW5nZS0yNTYzOTM1MNIBVWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsc2NvdGxhbmQuY28udWsvc3BmbC9jZWx0aWMtZmFjZS1yZW5uZXMtZnJpZW5kbHktYW5nZS0yNTYzOTM1MC5hbXA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiUWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsc2NvdGxhbmQuY28udWsvc3BmbC9jZWx0aWMtZmFjZS1yZW5uZXMtZnJpZW5kbHktYW5nZS0yNTYzOTM1MNIBVWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsc2NvdGxhbmQuY28udWsvc3BmbC9jZWx0aWMtZmFjZS1yZW5uZXMtZnJpZW5kbHktYW5nZS0yNTYzOTM1MC5hbXA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T12:29:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic to face Rennes in friendly as Ange Postecoglou steps up Premiership preparation  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Summer Target Made Available for Transfer Celts Are Here - CeltsAreHere]]></title>
        <id>CBMiQWh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9mb3JtZXItY2VsdGljLXRyYW5zZmVyLXRhcmdldC1hdmFpbGFibGUv0gGKAWh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9mb3JtZXItY2VsdGljLXRyYW5zZmVyLXRhcmdldC1hdmFpbGFibGUvYW1wLz9mYmNsaWQ9UEFBYVllcXdTUG9GZWR4VGwzTG0wb3huRTZxLXlQSFk0ZVdZdWRJbEQ5dUFNdUpWeFJRcDZJQTZrcFBqUQ</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiQWh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9mb3JtZXItY2VsdGljLXRyYW5zZmVyLXRhcmdldC1hdmFpbGFibGUv0gGKAWh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9mb3JtZXItY2VsdGljLXRyYW5zZmVyLXRhcmdldC1hdmFpbGFibGUvYW1wLz9mYmNsaWQ9UEFBYVllcXdTUG9GZWR4VGwzTG0wb3huRTZxLXlQSFk0ZVdZdWRJbEQ5dUFNdUpWeFJRcDZJQTZrcFBqUQ?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T12:01:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Summer Target Made Available for Transfer Celts Are Here  CeltsAreHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QPR players sent Mick Beale warning as they're told to forget Rangers exit fallout - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEI4XsJ_igC1PC_umephQFrYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPLfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiTGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsc2NvdGxhbmQuY28udWsvc3BmbC9xcHItcGxheWVycy1zZW50LW1pY2stYmVhbGUtMjU2Mzg3OTLSAQA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T11:57:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[QPR players sent Mick Beale warning as they're told to forget Rangers exit fallout  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mohamed Magdy to Celtic transfer back ON as Al Ahly reverse hands off warning and name £4m price tag - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CBMiWGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL21vaGFtZWQtbWFnZHktY2VsdGljLXRyYW5zZmVyLWJhY2stMjg2MTc1NDbSAVxodHRwczovL3d3dy5kYWlseXJlY29yZC5jby51ay9zcG9ydC9mb290YmFsbC9tb2hhbWVkLW1hZ2R5LWNlbHRpYy10cmFuc2Zlci1iYWNrLTI4NjE3NTQ2LmFtcA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiWGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL21vaGFtZWQtbWFnZHktY2VsdGljLXRyYW5zZmVyLWJhY2stMjg2MTc1NDbSAVxodHRwczovL3d3dy5kYWlseXJlY29yZC5jby51ay9zcG9ydC9mb290YmFsbC9tb2hhbWVkLW1hZ2R5LWNlbHRpYy10cmFuc2Zlci1iYWNrLTI4NjE3NTQ2LmFtcA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T10:48:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mohamed Magdy to Celtic transfer back ON as Al Ahly reverse hands off warning and name £4m price tag  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mohamed Magdy to Celtic transfer back ON as Al Ahly reverse hands off warning and name £4m price tag - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEE41NWukw3V2neVs0tVkRDYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiWGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL21vaGFtZWQtbWFnZHktY2VsdGljLXRyYW5zZmVyLWJhY2stMjg2MTc1NDbSAQA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T10:48:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mohamed Magdy to Celtic transfer back ON as Al Ahly reverse hands off warning and name £4m price tag  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic-linked Afsha priced at £4m just months after £300k bid accepted]]></title>
        <id>d85abfe6c88b95e5e5e5e2d023e49441</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23159172.celtic-linked-afsha-priced-4m-just-months-300k-bid-accepted/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T10:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE creative playmaker is an international teammate of Liverpool icon Mo Salah and is tipped to become their next big import to European football.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou titled 'Celtic Rangers' manager in Aussie event gaffe]]></title>
        <id>7bcc5e21c68aba7fd880b506a1392c6c</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23159086.ange-postecoglou-titled-celtic-rangers-manager-aussie-event-gaffe/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T10:06:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FANS couldn't believe the club name gaffe by the Australian Institute of Sport.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cameron Carter-Vickers USA start explained with nod to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>73c3b35b77ecc2aa8fde108fb594deed</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23159000.cameron-carter-vickers-usa-start-explained-nod-celtic/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T09:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[USA coach Gregg Berhalter has revealed Cameron Carter-Vickers' start for his country at the World Cup came after careful consideration of his Celtic displays.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sensational late night Celtic transfer news emerges - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>1671251218</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiRmh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljYmhveXMuY29tLzIwMjIvMTEvMzAvbGF0ZS1uaWdodC1jZWx0aWMtdHJhbnNmZXItbmV3cy_SAUpodHRwczovL3RoZWNlbHRpY2Job3lzLmNvbS8yMDIyLzExLzMwL2xhdGUtbmlnaHQtY2VsdGljLXRyYW5zZmVyLW5ld3MvYW1wLw?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T08:32:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sensational late night Celtic transfer news emerges  The Celtic Bhoys
Report: Canada’s Alistair Johnston set for move to Celtic FC  Sportsnet.ca
Exclusive: Celtic confident of agreeing £5m+ Josip Juranovic deal after terms agreed  Football Insider
When Alistair Johnston to Celtic transfer announcement is expected as new reports hint at imminent unveiling  Daily Record
The intriguing aspect of Alistair Johnston’s career that prepares him for Celtic demand  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News
View Full coverage on Google News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[McAvennie issues ‘big’ Celtic claim as Daizen Maeda quotes emerge - Football Insider]]></title>
        <id>CBMiY2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsaW5zaWRlcjI0Ny5jb20vbWNhdmVubmllLWlzc3Vlcy1iaWctY2VsdGljLWNsYWltLWFzLWRhaXplbi1tYWVkYS1xdW90ZXMtZW1lcmdlL9IBZ2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsaW5zaWRlcjI0Ny5jb20vbWNhdmVubmllLWlzc3Vlcy1iaWctY2VsdGljLWNsYWltLWFzLWRhaXplbi1tYWVkYS1xdW90ZXMtZW1lcmdlLz9hbXA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiY2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsaW5zaWRlcjI0Ny5jb20vbWNhdmVubmllLWlzc3Vlcy1iaWctY2VsdGljLWNsYWltLWFzLWRhaXplbi1tYWVkYS1xdW90ZXMtZW1lcmdlL9IBZ2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsaW5zaWRlcjI0Ny5jb20vbWNhdmVubmllLWlzc3Vlcy1iaWctY2VsdGljLWNsYWltLWFzLWRhaXplbi1tYWVkYS1xdW90ZXMtZW1lcmdlLz9hbXA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[McAvennie issues ‘big’ Celtic claim as Daizen Maeda quotes emerge  Football Insider]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[McAvennie issues ‘big’ Celtic claim as Daizen Maeda quotes emerge - Football Insider]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEGD0GBRwEbHQcxwq0gVqHzUqMwgEKioIACIQnJ4k3aT29tENAyPF0QESjSoUCAoiEJyeJN2k9vbRDQMjxdEBEo0w4IzKBg</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiY2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsaW5zaWRlcjI0Ny5jb20vbWNhdmVubmllLWlzc3Vlcy1iaWctY2VsdGljLWNsYWltLWFzLWRhaXplbi1tYWVkYS1xdW90ZXMtZW1lcmdlL9IBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[McAvennie issues ‘big’ Celtic claim as Daizen Maeda quotes emerge  Football Insider]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cameron Carter Vickers stars on World Cup debut as Celtic defender helps USA to last 16 - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CBMiaGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsc2NvdGxhbmQuY28udWsvc3BmbC9zY290dGlzaC1wcmVtaWVyc2hpcC9jYW1lcm9uLWNhcnRlci12aWNrZXJzLXN0YXJzLXdvcmxkLTI1NjM1Njg40gFsaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZm9vdGJhbGxzY290bGFuZC5jby51ay9zcGZsL3Njb3R0aXNoLXByZW1pZXJzaGlwL2NhbWVyb24tY2FydGVyLXZpY2tlcnMtc3RhcnMtd29ybGQtMjU2MzU2ODguYW1w</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiaGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsc2NvdGxhbmQuY28udWsvc3BmbC9zY290dGlzaC1wcmVtaWVyc2hpcC9jYW1lcm9uLWNhcnRlci12aWNrZXJzLXN0YXJzLXdvcmxkLTI1NjM1Njg40gFsaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZm9vdGJhbGxzY290bGFuZC5jby51ay9zcGZsL3Njb3R0aXNoLXByZW1pZXJzaGlwL2NhbWVyb24tY2FydGVyLXZpY2tlcnMtc3RhcnMtd29ybGQtMjU2MzU2ODguYW1w?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-29T21:32:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cameron Carter Vickers stars on World Cup debut as Celtic defender helps USA to last 16  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cameron Carter Vickers stars on World Cup debut as Celtic defender helps USA to last 16 - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEAlXnv-zmrmkWGuvxIAHbqUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPPfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiaGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsc2NvdGxhbmQuY28udWsvc3BmbC9zY290dGlzaC1wcmVtaWVyc2hpcC9jYW1lcm9uLWNhcnRlci12aWNrZXJzLXN0YXJzLXdvcmxkLTI1NjM1Njg40gEA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-29T21:32:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cameron Carter Vickers stars on World Cup debut as Celtic defender helps USA to last 16  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>