<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2022-07-28T15:23:59.098Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic winger Aiden McGeady suffers bitter injury blow ahead of Scottish season start]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-winger-aiden-mcgeady-suffers-bitter-injury-blow-ahead-of-scottish-season-start/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-winger-aiden-mcgeady-suffers-bitter-injury-blow-ahead-of-scottish-season-start/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T14:40:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic star Aiden McGeady could be set to miss up to three months of the new season for Hibs, having only signed for the Edinburgh club this summer. The 36-year-old signed for Hibs after five years at Sunderland, helping the club to promotion from League One into the Championship at the end of last ...
The post Former Celtic winger Aiden McGeady suffers bitter injury blow ahead of Scottish season start appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic defender could get his move to England after unexpected rise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ex-celtic-defender-could-get-his-move-to-england-with-bid-submitted/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ex-celtic-defender-could-get-his-move-to-england-with-bid-submitted/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic defender Jack Hendry could be set for a move to England, after newly-relegated Burnley submitted a bid to Club Brugge for the 27 year old, according to a report. Burnley manager Vincent Kompany has already recruited from his homeland, having himself moved from Anderlecht to England this summer, with a deal agreed for ...
The post Ex-Celtic defender could get his move to England after unexpected rise appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["It doesn&#039;t get much more difficult"; Opposition manager discusses Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/it-doesnt-get-much-more-difficult-opposition-manager-discusses-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/it-doesnt-get-much-more-difficult-opposition-manager-discusses-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aberdeen manager Jim Goodwin has deemed Sunday’s Premiership curtain raiser at Celtic Park as difficult a start as his side could have asked for. The Dons have enjoyed an imperious start to their season with four wins in the Premier Sports Cup group stage but the former St Mirren midfielder and manager sees Sunday’s bout ...
The post "It doesn&#039;t get much more difficult"; Opposition manager discusses Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andy Walker’s Choice For Celtic’s Most Important Player This Year Is … Interesting.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/andy-walkers-choice-for-celtics-most-important-player-this-year-is-interesting/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/andy-walkers-choice-for-celtics-most-important-player-this-year-is-interesting/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andy Walker picked his crucial player at every club in the league list today, and although a lot of sites are bizarrely publicising what Kris Boyd said, as if any of us care who he thinks Celtic’s most potent player will be, there’s be very little talk about Walker’s. And Walker’s, to me, is more […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scotsman writers make Celtic-Rangers title prediction, who will finish third, and all SPFL winners and losers]]></title>
        <id>3785598</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/scotsman-writers-make-celtic-rangers-title-prediction-who-will-finish-third-and-all-spfl-winners-and-losers-3785598"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T13:28:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anticipation is building for the opening weekend of the league season ahead of what promises to be another exciting and unpredictable chapter in Scottish football.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angus Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REVEALED: X-FACTOR JOTA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/revealed-x-factor-jota/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/revealed-x-factor-jota/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T13:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KRIS BOYD has revealed he is an admirer of Filipe Jota, Celtic’s flying Portuguese winger. The mesmerising touchline ace impressed during his season-long loan from Benfica and made the transfer permanent in the summer when he agreed a £6.5million four-year switch from the Lisbon giants. Jota set up a conveyor belt of chances for the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports pundit tips surprise midfielder to be key star for Celtic this season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/sky-sports-pundit-tips-midfielder-to-be-key-star-for-celtic-this-season/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/sky-sports-pundit-tips-midfielder-to-be-key-star-for-celtic-this-season/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker and Sky Sports pundit Andy Walker has tipped Hoops midfielder David Turnbull for a starring role this season. The 23-year-old has been a consistent performer for the club since joining from Motherwell in the 2020 summer window. However, last season the Scotland internationalist’s season was hindered by injury after picking up a ...
The post Sky Sports pundit tips surprise midfielder to be key star for Celtic this season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Talented Celtic youngster completes Scottish league loan move]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/talented-celtic-youngster-secures-scottish-league-loan-move/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/talented-celtic-youngster-secures-scottish-league-loan-move/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic youngster Ben Wylie has completed a loan move to Scottish League One side Airdrieonians. The 20-year-old joined the club’s academy in 2018 and has progressed through the ranks up to the Celtic B side last campaign. Wylie was a regular part of Tommy McIntyre’s young Hoops side in their first season in the Lowland ...
The post Talented Celtic youngster completes Scottish league loan move appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer Latest – Celtic send B Team star Ben Wylie out on loan to Airdrie]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/transfer-latest-celtic-send-b-team-star-ben-wylie-out-on-loan-to-airdrie/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/transfer-latest-celtic-send-b-team-star-ben-wylie-out-on-loan-to-airdrie/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T11:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Airdrie FC today confirmed that they have concluded a loan deal with Celtic for Irish midfielder Ben Wylie, who was one of the star performers in the Celtic B team’s debut season in the Lowland League last year. Wylie recently signed a new contract at Celtic so this move can be seen as being very Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kris Boyd predicts Rangers new signing to solve goal 'problem' as he names Celtic star with x-factor - Scottish Daily Express]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEM69_KNi6Pyi5VBulCL-42MqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowi76vCzCYyccDMKvzuAc</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottishdailyexpress.co.uk/sport/football/kris-boyd-predicts-rangers-new-27600121"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T11:53:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kris Boyd predicts Rangers new signing to solve goal 'problem' as he names Celtic star with x-factor  Scottish Daily Express]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I feel confident - Vasilis Barkas reflects upon new season preparations after Celtic exit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-feel-confident-vasilis-barkas-reflects-upon-new-season-preparations-after-celtic-exit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-feel-confident-vasilis-barkas-reflects-upon-new-season-preparations-after-celtic-exit/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic goalkeeper Vasilis Barkas has opened up on pre-season preparations with current loan side FC Utrecht after his recent Parkhead exit. The 28-year-old is looking to kick start his career once again, off the back of a disappointing two years at Celtic Park. Barkas joined the Hoops in the summer of 2020 for a ...
The post "I feel confident - Vasilis Barkas reflects upon new season preparations after Celtic exit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“I feel confident – Vasilis Barkas reflects upon new season preparations after Celtic exit - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEG_2DnSBWK5FjcjmkOWgxkkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMLbFpgY</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-feel-confident-vasilis-barkas-reflects-upon-new-season-preparations-after-celtic-exit/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I feel confident – Vasilis Barkas reflects upon new season preparations after Celtic exit  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Danny Lennon backing Aaron Mooy to be a Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/danny-lennon-backing-aaron-mooy-to-be-a-celtic-star/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/danny-lennon-backing-aaron-mooy-to-be-a-celtic-star/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T11:35:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Danny Lennon knows a thing or two about new Celtic recruit Aaron Mooy. Lennon coached Mooy during his time in the Scottish Premiership with St Mirren, when he played for the Paisley side a decade or so ago. Lennon initially used Mooy as a No.10 and revealed he didn’t see him as the deep-lying sort Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mikey, Moh and converting talent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/mikey-moh-and-converting-talent/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/mikey-moh-and-converting-talent/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T11:34:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I could not make sense of why we signed Mohamed Elyounoussi on loan from Southampton in the last days of the 2019 summer transfer window.  He played in Mikey Johnston’s position, a prospect I had great hopes for.  Just days later, Mikey was a star at Ibrox, winning possession (albeit without much difficulty) and setting [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s Summer Scouting Mission; Abu Fani Latest]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtics-summer-scouting-mission-abu-fani-latest/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtics-summer-scouting-mission-abu-fani-latest/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T11:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been very proactive this summer when it comes to getting business done. We’re just about to get back into SPFL action and the bulk of our transfer activity has already been concluded. Hoops supporters who have followed the club in the 21st century will know that’s not always been a given. The club […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic pundits spark Rangers fury as Ibrox callers left raging by title predictions - Hotline - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEMeGUsAYBlenMGIyJx0Qj-4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/celtic-pundits-spark-rangers-fury-27599416"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T11:15:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic pundits spark Rangers fury as Ibrox callers left raging by title predictions - Hotline  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: “I think Celtic have the best bench,” Peter Grant tips Celtic for more title glory]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/video-i-think-celtic-have-the-best-bench-peter-grant-tips-celtic-for-more-title-glory/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-i-think-celtic-have-the-best-bench-peter-grant-tips-celtic-for-more-title-glory/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T11:07:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the prediction that will surprise no-one in Scottish football as former Celtic midfielder Peter Grant tips his old club to retain the Scottish Premiership title, outlining his reasoning by arguing that Ange Postecoglou has around 22 first team players in his squad and that’s something that theRangers at this stage simply cannot match. Grant Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Celtic will be 'envious' of Rangers, according to former Parkhead defender]]></title>
        <id>3785264</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/why-celtic-will-be-envious-of-rangers-according-to-former-parkhead-defender-3785264"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T10:58:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic defender Michael Gray believes his former club will be spurred on by Rangers’ Europa League exploits last season after being “envious” of their rivals’ run to the final in Seville.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Oliver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Police Scotland’s Investigation Into The Ibrox Fans Was A Farce That Bilked The Taxpayer.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/police-scotlands-investigation-into-the-ibrox-fans-was-a-farce-that-bilked-the-taxpayer/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/police-scotlands-investigation-into-the-ibrox-fans-was-a-farce-that-bilked-the-taxpayer/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T10:57:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So yesterday, Police Scotland ended their investigation into the racist and sectarian singing by a section of the Ibrox fan-base during a march to a game last season. They claimed that in spite of months investigating this they didn’t produce enough evidence to make a case. It’s like some kind of sick joke when you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic continue transfer scouting mission with final decision set to be made]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/report-celtic-continue-mohammed-abu-fani-scouting-mission-with-final-decision-set-to-be-made/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/report-celtic-continue-mohammed-abu-fani-scouting-mission-with-final-decision-set-to-be-made/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic reportedly continued their scouting mission of Maccabi Haifa midfielder Mohammed Abu Fani on Wednesday evening as the Israeli side took on Olympiacos in UCL qualifying. The 24-year-old has been linked with a move to Parkhead throughout the window, with Ange Postecoglou on the hunt for a new midfield enforcer. It is expected that the ...
The post Report: Celtic continue transfer scouting mission with final decision set to be made appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic vs Aberdeen: TV channel, live stream & kick-off time]]></title>
        <id>0e9f9e974f77415243791f27b329b726</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20584370.celtic-vs-aberdeen-tv-channel-live-stream-kick-off-time/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T10:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SCOTTISH football is back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer update as Hoops tipped to have 'no option but to sell' player after exit collapse - Glasgow Live]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEAq79EX8PNAg5IfcVIQpkqIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow96D9CjDOy_QCMPvp0wU</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowlive.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/celtic-transfer-update-hoops-tipped-24607862"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T09:44:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer update as Hoops tipped to have 'no option but to sell' player after exit collapse  Glasgow Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["A big eye-opener" - Celtic summer signing opens up on previous Scottish Football experience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/a-big-eye-opener-celtic-summer-signing-opens-up-on-previous-scottish-football-experience/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/a-big-eye-opener-celtic-summer-signing-opens-up-on-previous-scottish-football-experience/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder Aaron Mooy has opened up on his early experiences of Scottish Football from his time spent at St Mirren. The 31-year-old became Ange Postecoglou’s sixth new addition of the window, adding to the Hoops midfield options for the campaign ahead. Mooy is a player that the Celtic manager knows well from his spell ...
The post "A big eye-opener" - Celtic summer signing opens up on previous Scottish Football experience appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic star Stuart Armstrong on relationship with Rangers hero Joe Aribo at Southampton]]></title>
        <id>dcc5e523f310c44a40de4dfae3068a61</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20584169.ex-celtic-star-stuart-armstrong-relationship-rangers-hero-joe-aribo-southampton/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T09:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic star Stuart Armstrong has lifted the lif on his relationship with Joe Aribo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic set to land extra Champions League bonus]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-set-to-land-extra-champions-league-bonus/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-set-to-land-extra-champions-league-bonus/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T08:45:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are set to receive an extra Champions League bonus after Greek side Olympiacos were knocked out of the competition last night. The qualifying process for the biggest club competition in the world is well underway, with sides from across Europe battling it out for the final few places this season. The Hoops support have ...
The post Celtic set to land extra Champions League bonus appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“A real buzz about the place”, love it – Maestro-Esq from Calmac”]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/a-real-buzz-about-the-place-love-it-maestro-esq-from-calmac/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/a-real-buzz-about-the-place-love-it-maestro-esq-from-calmac/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T08:40:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Echoes of the Maestro from Callum McGregor in his interview with Celtic TV yesterday as the Celtic captain looks ahead to flag day at Celtic Park on Sunday, where he will be given the honour of unfurling the flag to signify that Celtic are the Champions again. And the club, who yesterday completed work on Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘It’s Amazing’; Callum McGregor Addresses Celtic Fans Ahead of Sunday]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/its-amazing-callum-mcgregor-addresses-celtic-fans-ahead-of-sunday/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/its-amazing-callum-mcgregor-addresses-celtic-fans-ahead-of-sunday/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T08:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor is no stranger to the expectations set at Celtic and once he unfurls the flag to mark last seasons success, he wants to the then focus on what’s to come.  Since making his debut for the club in 2014, the Celtic captain has won an incredible 17 major honours at the club. If […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic kid Jonathan Afolabi 'offered trial' by Forest Green Rovers]]></title>
        <id>a96b3ce33915ed4ce6f9c3ef0d4a7eca</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20584037.ex-celtic-kid-jonathan-afolabi-offered-trial-forest-green-rovers/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T08:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JONATHAN AFOLABI has been offered a trial at a League One club, according to a report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Hendry subject of Burnley transfer bid as ex Celtic defender wanted by Vincent Kompany - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEMYf-zqMhTjQiUijJ7dmu44qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPPfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/jack-hendry-subject-burnley-transfer-24607488"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T08:27:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Hendry subject of Burnley transfer bid as ex Celtic defender wanted by Vincent Kompany  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero Peter Grant questions why ex-club didn't move for former Hibs star Josh Doig]]></title>
        <id>58953505d41d896a8f166d8ac2ea10bd</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20583934.celtic-hero-peter-grant-questions-ex-club-didnt-move-former-hibs-star-josh-doig/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T08:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PETER GRANT has questioned why Celtic didn't make a move for Josh Doig this summer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘BEST SQUAD’: CELTIC HERO PRAISES ANGE, TIPS HOOPS FOR TITLE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/best-squad-celtic-hero-praises-ange-tips-hoops-for-title/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/best-squad-celtic-hero-praises-ange-tips-hoops-for-title/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T08:02:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC hero Peter Grant is convinced Ange Postecoglou will celebrate back-to-back Premiership titles. The Greek-Australian turned the squad upside down following his appointment in June last year. He inherited a dispirited pool of players who had failed miserably in their historic attempt at 10 in a row and hadn’t made a dent on the two [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Booked for Three Season Defining Games in a Week]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-booked-for-three-season-defining-games-in-a-week/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-booked-for-three-season-defining-games-in-a-week/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T07:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are set to face a tough week of football with it being confirmed that the game against Ross County in the Premier Sports cup will take place on Wednesday 31 August.  It was potentially the hardest tie the Hoops could have been given away from home with the Staggies having topped their group even […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mohammad Abu Fani lands Celtic coefficient windfall as Champions League cash rises after Olympiacos thrashing - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEDdHDVEuh4AeORcEcKavkCQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/mohammad-abu-fani-lands-celtic-27596608"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T07:24:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mohammad Abu Fani lands Celtic coefficient windfall as Champions League cash rises after Olympiacos thrashing  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The great Rangers transfer deep dive but is Gio van Bronckhorst’s side stronger or weaker than last season? - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEOkuP1bBO_-_IlbwwYWyqWAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/great-rangers-transfer-deep-dive-27590565"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The great Rangers transfer deep dive but is Gio van Bronckhorst’s side stronger or weaker than last season?  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC CLEAR-OUT: FIVE DOWN AND FIVE TO GO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-clear-out-five-down-and-five-to-go/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-clear-out-five-down-and-five-to-go/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T06:16:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OSAZE URHOGHIDE has agreed a second loan spell with KV Oostende. The 22-year-old versatile former Sheffield Wednesday defender arrived at the Hoops last summer and spent the second half of the season with the Belgian Pro League side. The Dutch right-back or centre-half made six first-team appearances and the club were keen to make the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant in total Rangers title write off as smirking Celtic hero makes 'best squad' case - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEENNbOesHWd1Y_170CDhLEQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/peter-grant-total-rangers-title-27596402"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T06:14:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant in total Rangers title write off as smirking Celtic hero makes 'best squad' case  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Without Rangers and Celtic Scotttish top flight has European standing of League of Ireland - Aberdeen and Hibs damned by the parallel]]></title>
        <id>3784689</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/without-rangers-and-celtic-scotttish-top-flight-has-european-standing-of-league-of-ireland-aberdeen-and-hibs-damned-by-the-parallel-3784689"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than just Motherwell’s progress in the Conference League is at stake against Sligo Rovers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EX-CELTS ON LOOK-OUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ex-celts-on-look-out/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ex-celts-on-look-out/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T05:37:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOM ROGIC has been the main focus of attention of former Celtic players who are on the look-out for a new club this summer. The 29-year-old Ausralian playmaker, who left the Hoops after nine and half years and a landslide of 16 honours, has already knocked back a lucrative offer to join Indonesian champions Persija [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy reveals early Celtic connection to Harry Kewell as he revisits famous Rangers strike - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEJQcQcgFo012e-tCFOhJuO0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/aaron-mooy-reveals-early-celtic-27589176"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy reveals early Celtic connection to Harry Kewell as he revisits famous Rangers strike  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GRIFF: THE GLORY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/griff-the-glory/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/griff-the-glory/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T04:10:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[COLOURFUL and controversial, Leigh Griffiths rode an emotional rollercoaster during his eight years at Celtic. The lively little marksman fired in over a century of goals for the Hoops and may have expected a fanfare of trumpets to herald the curtain coming down on his career in the east end of Glasgow. Instead, there was [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THREE CHEERS: TREBLE No.4 (2016/17)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/three-cheers-treble-no-4-2016-17/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/three-cheers-treble-no-4-2016-17/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T04:05:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS replaced Norwegian Ronny Deila in the summer of 2016 to kick off Celtic’s unbeatable and unstoppable silverware crusade. The Irishman followed in the footsteps of Jock Stein and Martin O’Neill as a Hoops manager to lead the club to total domination of Scottish football. CQN has journeyed back in time to turn the spotlight [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: McSTAY RETURNS, CADETE NO GOAL IBROX STORM: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Seventeen)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-mcstay-returns-cadete-no-goal-ibrox-storm-the-tommy-burns-story-part-seventeen/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-mcstay-returns-cadete-no-goal-ibrox-storm-the-tommy-burns-story-part-seventeen/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-28T04:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE fates appeared to be snarling at Tommy Burns as he experienced extreme turbulence during his third year as Celtic manager during the tempestuous 1996/97 crusade. The fans’ favourite had returned to the club on July 12 1994 and had won the Scottish Cup in his debut campaign. That was followed by a barren term [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic to sign youngster from West Ham on three-year deal]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/report-celtic-to-sign-youngster-from-west-ham-on-three-year-deal/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/report-celtic-to-sign-youngster-from-west-ham-on-three-year-deal/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T22:16:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are set to confirm the signing of highly-promising young central defender Justin Osagie on a three-year deal. The 17-year-old is set to arrive from West Ham United as Celtic’s B Team strengthens for the new season. According to All Nigeria Soccer, Osagie will sign a three-year deal with The Scottish Champions. The player opted Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Set to Land Bonus UEFA Payout]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-set-to-land-bonus-uefa-payout/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-set-to-land-bonus-uefa-payout/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T22:14:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will grab an unexpected UEFA coefficient bonus after Olympiakos were dumped out of the Champions League qualifiers on Wednesday evening. The Greek side were thrashed 4-0 at home in their second leg against Maccabi Haifa, consigning them to failure. It’s great news for Celtic, as explained by the ever knowledgable Moravcik67 on social media […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable source says Celtic to net nearly £1m from Champions League result]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/reliable-source-says-celtic-to-net-nearly-1m-from-champions-league-result/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/reliable-source-says-celtic-to-net-nearly-1m-from-champions-league-result/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T21:44:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UEFA competition can be an extremely confusing and difficult concept to fully grasp due to the rules and sheer volume of teams involved across three competitions. However, fortunately for Celtic supporters, @Moravcik67_ on Twitter is on hand to update as developments across the continent occur. Notably, as Champions League Qualifiers continue tonight one result could Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy still living up to Harry Kewell’s example as he follows hero’s footsteps from high school to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>f15f78bc382588d1fab66f5521452c06</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20582643.aaron-mooy-still-living-harry-kewells-example-follows-heros-footsteps-high-school-celtic/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT is widely known that St Ninian’s High School has provided a conveyor belt of talent for Celtic over the years, but under Ange Postecoglou, there is a school rather further afield that is starting to rival the Kirkintilloch campus for former pupils who now ply their trade at the club.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Moritz Jens is a doubt for Aberdeen clash]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/report-moritz-jens-is-a-doubt-for-aberdeen-clash/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/report-moritz-jens-is-a-doubt-for-aberdeen-clash/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T21:12:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a report, Celtic could be without new signing for this weekend’s Premiership curtain-raiser as Moritz Jenz is now a doubt through injury. The German defender joined on loan with an option to buy from Lorient one year after Celtic’s initial interest in bringing the defender to Paradise. According to Video Celts, Jenz is Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hearts 0 – 3 Celtic FC Women – Larisey double but worrying squad issues remain]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/hearts-0-3-celtic-fc-women-larisey-double-but-worrying-squad-issues-remain/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/hearts-0-3-celtic-fc-women-larisey-double-but-worrying-squad-issues-remain/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T20:42:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic FC Women headed to the capital to face Hearts at Oriam this evening in the Hoops penultimate pre-season match, and the starting line-up and substitute bench was still concerningly devoid of the talents of Sarah Harkes, Jodie Bartle, Liv Chance – and most worryingly 40 goal Charlie Wellings – prior to Celtic going on Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hearts 0 – 3 Celtic FC Women – Larisey double but worrying squad issues remain - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEFwjMaE12z7JrYk3AFkNykMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/hearts-0-3-celtic-fc-women-larisey-double-but-worrying-squad-issues-remain/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T20:42:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hearts 0 – 3 Celtic FC Women – Larisey double but worrying squad issues remain  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stunning footage emerges from season-defining fixture]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/stunning-footage-emerges-from-season-defining-fixture/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/stunning-footage-emerges-from-season-defining-fixture/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T19:52:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stunning footage has emerged from Celtic’s win over Rangers back in February. As the new season begins on Sunday, it is worth looking back to this excellent footage from the main stand before kick-off. I wonder if we’ll have a midweek derby this season? The darkness added to the atmosphere that night & the game Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic not set to participate in latest UEFA safe standing trial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/report-celtic-not-set-to-participate-in-latest-uefa-safe-standing-trial/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/report-celtic-not-set-to-participate-in-latest-uefa-safe-standing-trial/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic won’t be one of the clubs involved in UEFA’s latest safe standing trial set to take place this season, according to the Athletic. Many clubs from across the UK and Europe have started to reintroduce standing at football grounds, with the Hoops really pathing the way for safe standing in this country. The popular ...
The post Report: Celtic not set to participate in latest UEFA safe standing trial appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou looks set to let Celtic player leave - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEC4NYsTaWsPAKkfDsvKqoLcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4KKJCzCv9JoDMICkoAY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2022/07/27/ange-postecoglou-let-celtic-player-leave/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T19:07:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou looks set to let Celtic player leave  The Celtic Bhoys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Potential Celtic exit could showcase what Ange Postecoglou&#039;s next transfer move will be]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/potential-celtic-exit-could-showcase-what-ange-postecoglous-next-transfer-move-will-be/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/potential-celtic-exit-could-showcase-what-ange-postecoglous-next-transfer-move-will-be/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been a busy summer transfer window for Ange Postecoglou and Celtic. The 56-year-old has overseen seven new permanent arrivals, which included three familiar faces who played their part last season. It hasn’t just been about the incomings either, though, and some of Postecoglou’s focus has switched to those heading out the Parkhead door. ...
The post Potential Celtic exit could showcase what Ange Postecoglou&#039;s next transfer move will be appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Osaze Urhoghide seals Celtic transfer exit as defender heads back to Belgium after loan stint last season - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEDskAoKNQKAa3rUgUtQmS_AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-transfer-news/osaze-urhoghide-seals-celtic-transfer-27594475"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T18:02:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Osaze Urhoghide seals Celtic transfer exit as defender heads back to Belgium after loan stint last season  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Adams: Creep pretended to be Celtic scout at boys football games - Irvine Times]]></title>
        <id>CBMiaWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmlydmluZXRpbWVzLmNvbS9uZXdzLzIwNTgzMDcxLmFudGhvbnktYWRhbXMtY3JlZXAtcHJldGVuZGVkLWNlbHRpYy1zY291dC1ib3lzLWZvb3RiYWxsLWdhbWVzL9IBAA</id>
        <link href="https://www.irvinetimes.com/news/20583071.anthony-adams-creep-pretended-celtic-scout-boys-football-games/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T17:45:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Adams: Creep pretended to be Celtic scout at boys football games  Irvine Times]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Osaze Urhoghide completes loan return; transfer option included]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-defender-osaze-urhoghide-completes-loan-return-transfer-option-included/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-defender-osaze-urhoghide-completes-loan-return-transfer-option-included/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T17:22:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Osaze Urhoghide has this evening completed a second loan move to Belgian league side Oostende. The 22-year-old arrived at Parkhead last summer and was one of Ange Postecoglou’s first signings as Celtic manager, joining on a free from Sheffield Wednesday. Despite featuring in the opening stages of pre-season last summer, the versatile defender ...
The post Celtic defender Osaze Urhoghide completes loan return; transfer option included appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer Latest – Osaze Urhoghide joins Oostende on season loan with option to buy]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/transfer-latest-osaze-urhoghide-joins-oostende-on-season-loan-with-option-to-buy/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/transfer-latest-osaze-urhoghide-joins-oostende-on-season-loan-with-option-to-buy/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T17:18:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic this evening have confirmed that defender Osaze Urhoghide has returned to Belgian side Oostende on a season long loan deal. The former Sheffield Wednesday defender spent the second half of last season at Oostende and there was talk of them buying him in the summer, but the suns involved were too high for their Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Osaze Urhoghide heads on loan to KV Oostende]]></title>
        <id>b13b27f49a518a35e0266198a6a09a93</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20583031.celtic-defender-osaze-urhoghide-heads-loan-kv-oostende/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T17:11:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OSAZE URHOGHIDE has left Celtic on loan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confirmed: Celtic Defender Makes Belgium Switch]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/confirmed-celtic-defender-makes-belgium-switch/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/confirmed-celtic-defender-makes-belgium-switch/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T17:09:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OSAZE UROGHIDE has gone back out on loan to Oostende for a second season, it has been announced. The defender had returned to Celtic following a short stint at the Belgian club between January and the end of last season. Oostende were keen to keep Osaze but admitted they didn’t have the funds to secure […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Josh Doig in Celtic transfer what could've been as 'ideal' left-back labelled missed Hoops chance - Glasgow Live]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEDJcacStY_4PHLZFoPTyffoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow96D9CjDOy_QCMKzp0wU</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowlive.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/josh-doig-celtic-transfer-what-24604981"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T16:56:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Josh Doig in Celtic transfer what could've been as 'ideal' left-back labelled missed Hoops chance  Glasgow Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers' brilliant Celtic heart-to-heart with ex Hoops kid revealed as career prediction comes true - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEOp1fZVSYToQqkUVzE9umnsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPPfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/brendan-rodgers-brilliant-celtic-heart-24604479"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T16:56:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers' brilliant Celtic heart-to-heart with ex Hoops kid revealed as career prediction comes true  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Willie Collum the reason Bobby Madden quit Scottish football as former SFA ref reveals 'nowhere to go' chat - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiENZymP8-y97ZyWZRsjtiJEcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/willie-collum-reason-bobby-madden-27593864"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T16:55:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Willie Collum the reason Bobby Madden quit Scottish football as former SFA ref reveals 'nowhere to go' chat  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hibs Chairman Is Talking Garbage About Ibrox’s “Advancement” Of Our Game.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/the-hibs-chairman-is-talking-garbage-about-ibroxs-advancement-of-our-game/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/the-hibs-chairman-is-talking-garbage-about-ibroxs-advancement-of-our-game/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T16:41:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ron Gordon of Hibs is the darling of the Ibrox fan forums. For now. But that man’s comments the other day about how the club over there has done more to “advance Scottish football” than any other in the last couple of years might have the village idiots of Sevconia applauding like seals hoping to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hibs Chairman Is Talking Garbage About Ibrox’s “Advancement” Of Our Game. - TheCelticBlog.com]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEJvzhvv0O9hr4-t9xjOeHPgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowne-jCzDg-bsDMLnLhQc</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/the-hibs-chairman-is-talking-garbage-about-ibroxs-advancement-of-our-game/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T16:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Hibs Chairman Is Talking Garbage About Ibrox’s “Advancement” Of Our Game.  TheCelticBlog.com]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aberdeen boss Jim Goodwin praises his Celtic loanee Liam Scales]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/aberdeen-boss-jim-goodwin-praises-his-celtic-loanee-liam-scales/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/aberdeen-boss-jim-goodwin-praises-his-celtic-loanee-liam-scales/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T16:39:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Goodwin has insisted that the Aberdeen fans have realised the quality and contribution Celtic loanee Liam Scales has brought to the Dons this early in his time at Pittodrie. There were murmurings of discontent amongst the Aberdeen casuals when a banner surfaced online condemning the singing of Scales on-loan from the Scottish Champions. However, Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liam Morrison’s Bayern Munich Setback]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/liam-morrisons-bayern-munich-setback/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/liam-morrisons-bayern-munich-setback/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic academy star, Liam Morrison has suffered an injury setback just after he made the step forward to Bayern Munich’s reserve side.  The 19-year old former Celtic academy star made the switch to Germany in July 2019 as a sixteen year old with a lot of potential. He first played in Bayern’s U17 side […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen McManus Frustrated After B Team Defeat]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/stephen-mcmanus-frustrated-after-b-team-defeat/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/stephen-mcmanus-frustrated-after-b-team-defeat/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T15:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic B coach, Stephen McManus, isn’t happy with the performance of the B side after a frustrating defeat against Berwick Rangers. On Tuesday night, Celtic B played Berwick Rangers in the Lowland League and were beat 1-0 in the end. McManus didn’t take the defeat lightly. The former Celtic captain aware they’d dropped points to […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[International director details why he knew Celtic star was going to be a success]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/international-director-details-why-he-knew-carl-starfelt-was-going-to-be-a-success-at-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/international-director-details-why-he-knew-carl-starfelt-was-going-to-be-a-success-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T15:41:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sweden national team director Stefan Pettersson has explained why he knew that Celtic defender Carl Starfelt was going to be a success in Glasgow. The 26-year-old centre-back was part of Ange Postecoglou’s huge summer recruitment last year, joining from Russian side Ruben Kazan. Starfelt didn’t make the greatest of starts to life at Parkhead, as ...
The post International director details why he knew Celtic star was going to be a success appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s Brilliant Callum McGregor Reveal]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtics-brilliant-callum-mcgregor-reveal/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtics-brilliant-callum-mcgregor-reveal/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T15:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been the story of the week while we await the real football to kick off. The banners outside Celtic Park! The opinions, hot takes and pictures coming on an almost hourly basis showing the progress of the new design outside Celtic Park has kept Celtic social media going. We have watched the Lisbon lion […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Fans Should Embrace Our Champions League Campaign White Knuckle Ride.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/celtic-fans-should-embrace-our-champions-league-campaign-white-knuckle-ride/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/celtic-fans-should-embrace-our-champions-league-campaign-white-knuckle-ride/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T14:56:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before the draw is even made, you would get long odds on Celtic even qualifying for the knockout stages from our Champions League group. The bookies will have as candidates for a spot at the bottom of whichever section we’re in. This is a realistic assessment of where we are, and where we can expect […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yosuke Ideguchi in new injury blow ahead of Celtic’s Flag Day]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/yosuke-ideguchi-in-new-injury-blow-ahead-of-celtics-flag-day/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/yosuke-ideguchi-in-new-injury-blow-ahead-of-celtics-flag-day/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T14:40:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yosuke Ideguchi has suffered another injury set-back, according to a report, in what will be a devastating blow to the Japanese midfielder. Ideguchi suffered the same fate when he first arrived in Glasgow as he was viciously assaulted on the field of play against Alloa back in January. The player was sidelined for some months Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor reflects upon the &#039;important&#039; underappreciated aspect of Celtic&#039;s pre-season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/callum-mcgregor-reflects-upon-the-important-underappreciated-aspect-of-celtics-pre-season/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/callum-mcgregor-reflects-upon-the-important-underappreciated-aspect-of-celtics-pre-season/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic captain Callum McGregor has opened up on the positive aspects for Ange Postecoglou’s squad of going unbeaten in pre-season. With the luxury of no Champions League qualifiers this summer, McGregor and his Celtic teammates were handed the unique opportunity to undergo a fully uninterrupted pre-season. The Bhoys have spent the last four weeks preparing ...
The post Callum McGregor reflects upon the &#039;important&#039; underappreciated aspect of Celtic&#039;s pre-season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor reflects upon the ‘important’ underappreciated aspect of Celtic’s pre-season - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEAFdYATfM0w2iTdIyIDqy0IqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMLbFpgY</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/callum-mcgregor-reflects-upon-the-important-underappreciated-aspect-of-celtics-pre-season/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor reflects upon the ‘important’ underappreciated aspect of Celtic’s pre-season  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic flag day plan revealed as Callum McGregor outlines answer to champions' new season challenges]]></title>
        <id>3784126</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-flag-day-plan-revealed-as-callum-mcgregor-outlines-answer-to-champions-new-season-challenges-3784126"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T14:28:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor has warned his Celtic team-mates new challenges await as the champions prepare to kick-off their cinch Premiership title defence on Sunday afternoon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Oliver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Away Ticket Farce; Ross County Latest]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-away-ticket-farce-ross-county-latest/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-away-ticket-farce-ross-county-latest/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T14:26:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ross County have sent Celtic’s ticket allocation to the Parkhead club ahead of their SPFL tie on August 6 at the Global Energy Stadium. The Scottish Champions have been handed only 1,399 tickets for the game leaving supporters scrambling for a brief. When you look at the parameters set just to simply be put in […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mikey Johnston loan move – Chase heats up]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/mikey-johnston-loan-move-chase-heats-up/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/mikey-johnston-loan-move-chase-heats-up/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T14:24:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As revealed right here on The Celtic Star at the weekend, Mikey Johnston is the subject of interest from former Hoops manager Ronny Deila. The Standard Liege head coach wants to take his old pupil to Belgium this summer as he looks to bolster his squad this year. Johnston is in dire need of a Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The big Rangers questions answered as Gio wrestles with 3 huge dilemmas - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiECSUE36cBbo92VbWICJaZfIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/big-rangers-questions-answered-gio-27592060"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T14:12:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The big Rangers questions answered as Gio wrestles with 3 huge dilemmas  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SPFL chief Neil Doncaster warns fans of severe punishments for misbehaving ahead of new season]]></title>
        <id>3784048</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/spfl-chief-neil-doncaster-warns-fans-of-severe-punishments-for-misbehaving-ahead-of-new-season-3784048"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T13:56:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SPFL chief executive Neil Doncaster has warned Scottish football fans they face being “punished severely” for misbehaving, including pitch invasions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[David Bates set for Aberdeen transfer exit as Legia Warsaw 'close in' on six-figure deal - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEMYPASKtqW1DDd0bfvfOcHwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/david-bates-set-aberdeen-transfer-27591295"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T13:27:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Bates set for Aberdeen transfer exit as Legia Warsaw 'close in' on six-figure deal  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Sets Of Ticketless Fans, And Two Different Ways To Cover The Story.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/two-sets-of-ticketless-fans-and-two-different-ways-to-cover-the-story/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/two-sets-of-ticketless-fans-and-two-different-ways-to-cover-the-story/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T12:59:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This morning, I did a piece on the official club statement at Ross County, which the media took great delight in covering. I thought that statement was crass and over the top and ridiculous, and was yet another attack on the support which has helped pay for a lot of these grounds that we now […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic loanee Conor Hazard suffers early Champions League exit with HJK Helsinki - Celtic Way]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEA-jHkPmVJRoy0uWLSoWKIEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsJStCzC9n8UDMNeMswc</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticway.co.uk/news/20581845.celtic-keepers-temporary-club-blown-away-viktoria-plzen/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic loanee Conor Hazard suffers early Champions League exit with HJK Helsinki  Celtic Way]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen McManus reacts as Celtic B side suffer disappointing defeat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/stephen-mcmanus-reacts-as-celtic-b-side-suffer-disappointing-defeat/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/stephen-mcmanus-reacts-as-celtic-b-side-suffer-disappointing-defeat/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic B side suffered their first loss of the season on Tuesday evening, losing out 1-0 to Berwick Rangers. The young Celtic side made a strong start to their second campaign in the Lowland League last weekend, defeating recently relegated Scottish League Two side Cowdenbeath 3-1. Looking to continue their positive opening to the ...
The post Stephen McManus reacts as Celtic B side suffer disappointing defeat appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen McManus reacts as Celtic B side suffer disappointing defeat - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CBMibGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL2NlbHRpYy15b3V0aC9zdGVwaGVuLW1jbWFudXMtcmVhY3RzLWFzLWNlbHRpYy1iLXNpZGUtc3VmZmVyLWRpc2FwcG9pbnRpbmctZGVmZWF0L9IBcGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL2NlbHRpYy15b3V0aC9zdGVwaGVuLW1jbWFudXMtcmVhY3RzLWFzLWNlbHRpYy1iLXNpZGUtc3VmZmVyLWRpc2FwcG9pbnRpbmctZGVmZWF0Lz9hbXA</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/stephen-mcmanus-reacts-as-celtic-b-side-suffer-disappointing-defeat/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen McManus reacts as Celtic B side suffer disappointing defeat  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic make class Callum McGregor flag day announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-make-class-callum-mcgregor-flag-day-announcement/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-make-class-callum-mcgregor-flag-day-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T11:45:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have this afternoon announced that captain Callum McGregor will be the man to unfurl the league flag before this Sunday’s season opener against Aberdeen. With the Hoops’ pre-season preparations coming to an end last weekend, focus is now firmly on the return of the competitive action. Ange Postecoglou’s side goes into this season as defending ...
The post Celtic make class Callum McGregor flag day announcement appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic make class Callum McGregor flag day announcement - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEJzcnJgYBtPleCXOvDbHJs0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMLbFpgY</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-make-class-callum-mcgregor-flag-day-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T11:45:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic make class Callum McGregor flag day announcement  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: “We need to handle all the challenges that will be thrown at us,” Callum McGregor]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/video-we-need-to-handle-all-the-challenges-that-will-be-thrown-at-us-callum-mcgregor/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-we-need-to-handle-all-the-challenges-that-will-be-thrown-at-us-callum-mcgregor/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T11:40:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Celtic’s hectic pre-season schedule came to an end with Saturday’s 2-0 win over Norwich City, there’s been something of a lull in Celtic related activity this week. There’s no midweek game, instead the team are taking the full week to prepare for the flag day opener on Sunday afternoon when Aberdeen are the visitors Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic captain Callum McGregor opens up on 'honour' of flag-day lead role]]></title>
        <id>b7b5f5ae8ce6e7a3d05ba5518482db48</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20581760.celtic-captain-will-take-centre-stage-ahead-aberdeen-game/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The midfielder will unfurl the league flag at a jam-packed Celtic Park]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hotline transfer tit for tat continues but proof will be in the pudding - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEGXrdR1z2nUG_T84PkzbWaMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/alfredo-morelos-can-rangers-champions-27588615"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T11:13:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hotline transfer tit for tat continues but proof will be in the pudding  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers fans fined over racist songs about Celtic's Kyogo Furuhashi - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CBMiWGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL25ld3Mvc2NvdHRpc2gtbmV3cy9yYW5nZXJzLWZhbnMtZmluZWQtb3Zlci1yYWNpc3QtMjc1ODk1MTjSAQA</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/news/scottish-news/rangers-fans-fined-over-racist-27589518"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T11:08:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers fans fined over racist songs about Celtic's Kyogo Furuhashi  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[&#039;I&#039;m led to believe...&#039; - BBC man drops worrying injury news from Celtic on &#039;excellent player&#039;]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-spl-christopher-jullien-transfer-injury-news-update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-spl-christopher-jullien-transfer-injury-news-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T11:06:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic centre-back Christopher Jullien’s proposed summer exit fell through because of fitness issues, according to ex-Scotland international Alan Hutton. The Lowdown: Jullien’s exit falls through The 29-year-old has suffered huge injury problems for the Hoops in recent times, limiting him to just one appearance in the whole of last season, in all competitions. Jullien was […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 ex-SPFL stars including Celtic and Rangers legends who are still available on free transfers - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEBe2Z7D2tKjQ8Te4SJUTS6QqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPLfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/11-ex-spfl-stars-including-24599172"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T11:04:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[11 ex-SPFL stars including Celtic and Rangers legends who are still available on free transfers  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Portents poor for Ideguchi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/portents-poor-for-ideguchi/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/portents-poor-for-ideguchi/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T11:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The portents are not good for Yosuke Ideguchi, injured again and set to be a spectator for the start of the season. Signings don’t all work, but Ange Postecoglou saw something in him and he did enough to impress Leeds United scouts four years ago. Work permit issues meant he was loaned out on arrival [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Celtic, Rangers, Hearts, Hibs, Aberdeen and Premiership rivals compare on opening day of the season]]></title>
        <id>3783622</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/how-celtic-rangers-hearts-hibs-aberdeen-and-premiership-rivals-compare-on-opening-day-of-the-season-3783622"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T10:55:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2022/23 Scottish Premiership season kicks off this weekend when Livingston host Rangers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer bulletin as Abu Fani gets exit approval and Johnston loan latest - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEIQ3cWcyzp0QcqU4kTX_DNAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/celtic-transfer-bulletin-mohammad-abu-27588891"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T10:45:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer bulletin as Abu Fani gets exit approval and Johnston loan latest  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sean Wallace: Celtic game chance for Dons to make statement - The Press & Journal]]></title>
        <id>CBMifmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnByZXNzYW5kam91cm5hbC5jby51ay9mcC9zcG9ydC9mb290YmFsbC9hYmVyZGVlbi1mYy80NTg2NzAxL3NlYW4td2FsbGFjZS1pZGVhbC1zdGFnZS1hYmVyZGVlbi1zdGF0ZW1lbnQtb2YtaW50ZW50L9IBAA</id>
        <link href="https://www.pressandjournal.co.uk/fp/sport/football/aberdeen-fc/4586701/sean-wallace-ideal-stage-aberdeen-statement-of-intent/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T10:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sean Wallace: Celtic game chance for Dons to make statement  The Press & Journal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Referees for Celtic v Aberdeen, Rangers trip to Livingston and all league games for SPFL opening weekend kick-off]]></title>
        <id>3783571</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/referees-for-celtic-v-aberdeen-rangers-trip-to-livingston-and-all-league-games-for-spfl-opening-weekend-kick-off-3783571"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T10:44:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The big kick-off is finally upon us with the start of the league season across Scotland and the SPFL after a ten week wait.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Oliver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former SPFL boss delivers exciting Aaron Mooy Celtic verdict]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-think-he-fits-into-the-celtic-jigsaw-very-very-well-former-spfl-boss-delivers-exciting-aaron-mooy-celtic-verdict/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-think-he-fits-into-the-celtic-jigsaw-very-very-well-former-spfl-boss-delivers-exciting-aaron-mooy-celtic-verdict/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former St Mirren boss Danny Lennon has insisted that new Celtic signing Aaron Mooy has exactly what it takes to fit into Ange Postecoglou’s squad. The 31-year-old midfielder became the latest arrival at Parkhead this summer, joining the club as a free agent on a two-year deal. Mooy is very familiar was Postecogolou, having worked ...
The post Former SPFL boss delivers exciting Aaron Mooy Celtic verdict appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wolves to face Porto, Valencia, Wolfsburg and Celtic at Molineux - wolves.co.uk]]></title>
        <id>CBMib2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LndvbHZlcy5jby51ay9uZXdzL3VuZGVyLTIxLzIwMjIwNzI3LXdvbHZlcy10by1mYWNlLXBvcnRvLXZhbGVuY2lhLXdvbGZzYnVyZy1hbmQtY2VsdGljLWF0LW1vbGluZXV4L9IBAA</id>
        <link href="https://www.wolves.co.uk/news/under-21/20220727-wolves-to-face-porto-valencia-wolfsburg-and-celtic-at-molineux/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T10:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wolves to face Porto, Valencia, Wolfsburg and Celtic at Molineux  wolves.co.uk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ross County Release Hostile Celtic Statement]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/ross-county-release-strong-celtic-statement/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/ross-county-release-strong-celtic-statement/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T10:32:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ross County have warned that Celtic fans will be refused entry into the stadium if they have purchased home end tickets.  This comes in the wake of the last game in Dingwall in late April when Celtic took another huge step towards the title with goals coming from Kyogo and Jota. With there being a […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mikey Johnston: Another Strange Twist In The Tale Of Celtic’s Unluckiest Player.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/mikey-johnston-another-strange-twist-in-the-tale-of-celtics-unluckiest-player/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/mikey-johnston-another-strange-twist-in-the-tale-of-celtics-unluckiest-player/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T10:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday I said in a piece that Mikey Johnston was being kept around the building mainly because he offered us something in terms of our European registration. Someone pointed out to me that even without Mikey, we meet the criteria. Our home grown players – we need eight, including four trained at the club – […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Context to Bizarre Celtic Japan Post]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/context-to-bizarre-celtic-japan-post/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/context-to-bizarre-celtic-japan-post/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T09:48:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have posted a graphic on the official Celtic FC Japan Twitter account which displays Ange Postecoglou holding a baseball bat with a watermelon wrapped in a Celtic away jersey in front of him.  The account has been a great success since it was created last July after the signing of Kyogo Furuhashi. Celtic have […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Special – Trip down memory lane with Celtic’s oldest living first-team player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/photo-special-trip-down-memory-lane-with-celtics-oldest-living-first-team-player/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/photo-special-trip-down-memory-lane-with-celtics-oldest-living-first-team-player/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T09:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of the Celtic Tour Guide Team, we were delighted to welcome Peter Goldie back to Celtic Park recently. Now a sprightly 88 years young, Peter holds the distinction of being Celtic’s oldest living first-team player. I had the pleasure of speaking with him early last year whilst pulling together a resume of his Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star set for interesting loan move - could 7 team-mates also exit?]]></title>
        <id>3783396</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-star-set-for-interesting-loan-move-could-7-team-mates-also-exit-3783396"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T09:42:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are set to allow Mikey Johnston depart on loan for the season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angus Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic loanee experiences familiar Champions League qualifying disappointment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-loanee-experiences-familiar-champions-league-qualifying-disappointment/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-loanee-experiences-familiar-champions-league-qualifying-disappointment/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic loanee Conor Hazard suffered Champions League qualifying disappointment on Tuesday evening after HJK Helsinki were eliminated from the competition. The 24-year-old shot-stopper is currently spending the season on loan in Finland with the domestic champions, having joined the club in January. So far, the Northern Ireland internationalist has made 15 appearances for his loan ...
The post Celtic loanee experiences familiar Champions League qualifying disappointment appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Suspected Celtic fans' - Ross County issue clear message after staff 'threatened and intimidated']]></title>
        <id>3783347</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/suspected-celtic-fans-ross-county-issue-clear-message-after-staff-threatened-and-intimidated-3783347"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T09:19:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ross County have hit out at “suspected Celtic” fans for trying to buy tickets in the home end for the upcoming Premiership fixture in Dingwall.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angus Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player suffers injury and will miss start of the season - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEAGtTNw2rbkl3yR4QhOHTV0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4KKJCzCv9JoDMICkoAY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2022/07/27/celtic-player-suffers-injury-miss-start/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T09:12:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player suffers injury and will miss start of the season  The Celtic Bhoys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star Matt O'Reily reveals singer dad's influence on his passion for music]]></title>
        <id>d0db2a65f5bf3bf1d2099a677ae64688</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20581268.celtic-star-matt-oreily-reveals-singer-dads-influence-passion-music/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T09:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC star Matt O'Reily has said he has followed in his singer dad's footsteps when it comes to his passion for music as he revealed the artists he loves to listen to.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Caveat; Craigan Makes Morelos Claim]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/kyogo-caveat-craigan-makes-morelos-claim/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/kyogo-caveat-craigan-makes-morelos-claim/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T09:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Furuhashi made an instant impact when he arrived at Celtic last summer and has been tipped to finish the leagues top goalscorer this season by Stephen Craigan.  Having missed a good chunk of the second half of the season, Kyogo still managed to finish with 20 goals in all competitions which is a terrific […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ross County’s Allegation Against “Celtic Fans” Is Serious. We Should Demand They Back It Up.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/ross-countys-allegation-against-celtic-fans-is-serious-we-should-demand-they-back-it-up/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/ross-countys-allegation-against-celtic-fans-is-serious-we-should-demand-they-back-it-up/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T08:53:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How easy it is to smear Celtic fans through the media these days. Ross County has done so today and The Record is only too keen to publish their allegation that their ticket office has been “intimidated and threatened” by our supporters whilst they tried to buy briefs for the wrong end of the ground. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ceri Bowley set for Rangers role as coaching guru bids emotional farewell to City Football Group - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEBLE5CnbaZsmORqJM4gE3WEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/ceri-bowley-set-rangers-role-27587578"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T08:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ceri Bowley set for Rangers role as coaching guru bids emotional farewell to City Football Group  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange January signing suffers fresh injury set-back ahead of Celtic season opener]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/yosuke-ideguchi-suffers-fresh-injury-set-back-ahead-of-celtic-season-opener/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/yosuke-ideguchi-suffers-fresh-injury-set-back-ahead-of-celtic-season-opener/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder Yosuke Ideguchi has suffered a fresh injury setback, which will see the 25-year-old miss the start of the new campaign. The Japanese internationalist was first brought to the club by Ange Postecoglou last January as part of a trio of signings arriving from Asia to bolster the squad. Ideguchi was arguably the most ...
The post Ange January signing suffers fresh injury set-back ahead of Celtic season opener appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yosuke Ideguchi suffers fresh injury set-back ahead of Celtic season opener - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEO7gLBKLL2WfMXTlRHk1mXkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMLbFpgY</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/yosuke-ideguchi-suffers-fresh-injury-set-back-ahead-of-celtic-season-opener/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yosuke Ideguchi suffers fresh injury set-back ahead of Celtic season opener  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One of the more obscure pieces of Celtic history – did East Fife beat Celtic to it?]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/one-of-the-more-obscure-pieces-of-celtic-history-did-east-fife-beat-celtic-to-it/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/one-of-the-more-obscure-pieces-of-celtic-history-did-east-fife-beat-celtic-to-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T08:31:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So did East Fife beat Celtic to it? Conventional wisdom tells us that on 15 August 1903, three significant things happened in Scottish football. One was that Aberdeen FC (as we now know them, the original “Aberdeen” having amalgamated with Victoria and Orion) played their first game, another was that a new club in Fife Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One of the more obscure pieces of Celtic history – did East Fife beat Celtic to it? - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiED4bGC9N4UB9FlNVUE__lecqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/one-of-the-more-obscure-pieces-of-celtic-history-did-east-fife-beat-celtic-to-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T08:31:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the more obscure pieces of Celtic history – did East Fife beat Celtic to it?  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Postecoglou set to sanction loan spell for Celtic fringe star]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/report-postecoglou-set-to-sanction-loan-spell-for-celtic-fringe-star-mikey-johnston/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/report-postecoglou-set-to-sanction-loan-spell-for-celtic-fringe-star-mikey-johnston/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T08:12:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic winger and academy graduate Mikey Johnston is reportedly set to head out on loan this summer. The 23-year-old first broke into the side under former boss Brendan Rodgers in 2017, and big things were expected for the talented youngster after a bright start. However, since his breakthrough, it has been very stop-start for the ...
The post Report: Postecoglou set to sanction loan spell for Celtic fringe star appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sutton backing Celtic to give European elite “bloody nose”]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/sutton-backing-celtic-to-give-european-elite-bloody-nose/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/sutton-backing-celtic-to-give-european-elite-bloody-nose/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T08:08:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton is predicting that Celtic will give as good as they get in European competition this time around. The Hoops – by virtue of winning last year’s Scottish Premiership – will be competing at Europe’s top table this forthcoming campaign and will be looking to get their first win since they defeated Anderlecht in Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ross County issue stern Celtic ticket warning after staff 'threatened and intimidated']]></title>
        <id>2e4f62d192fb19bc8cc162494d9b8789</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20581068.ross-county-issue-stern-celtic-ticket-warning-staff-threatened-intimidated/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T07:56:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ROSS COUNTY have issued a stern warning over tickets for the upcoming match against Celtic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O’Riley’s Support System; Parents Glasgow Move]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/matt-orileys-support-system-parents-glasgow-move/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/matt-orileys-support-system-parents-glasgow-move/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T07:47:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O’Riley has opened up about his taste in music and the eclectic mix of tunes he likes to listen while preparing for a big match.  The 21-year old midfielder made an instant impact when he made the switch north to Glasgow from MK Dons during the January transfer window. His outstanding performances earned him […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Ramsey's Rangers flop spell puzzles Alan Brazil as Celtic diehard 'couldn't work out' Ibrox stance - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEOy7LL9kzVOmrae91943cNcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/aaron-ramseys-rangers-flop-spell-27586819"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T07:38:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Ramsey's Rangers flop spell puzzles Alan Brazil as Celtic diehard 'couldn't work out' Ibrox stance  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yosuke Ideguchi's Celtic injury nightmare continues as midfielder out for start of season]]></title>
        <id>69bfc148cfe5ab0a8e001d645b0efddd</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20581034.yosuke-ideguchis-celtic-injury-nightmare-continues-midfielder-start-season/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T07:37:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC midfielder Yosuke Ideguchi will reportedly miss the start of the season after an injury blow ahead of this weekend's Scottish Premiership curtain-raiser.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rylan poses with Celtic captain Callum McGregor as he jets into Scotland with 'cinched it' quip - Glasgow Live]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEAErFD0dPTTlNXKOcqugRXsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow96D9CjDOy_QCMKzp0wU</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowlive.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/rylan-poses-celtic-captain-callum-24596971"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T07:37:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rylan poses with Celtic captain Callum McGregor as he jets into Scotland with 'cinched it' quip  Glasgow Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans sent Ross County ticket warning after staff 'threatened' over hardline home access stance - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiENyv1buV6C_IhRVm1SGXnBEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/celtic-fans-sent-ross-county-27586853"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T07:09:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans sent Ross County ticket warning after staff 'threatened' over hardline home access stance  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stunning Images of Celtic Park Emerge; New Banners]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/stunning-images-of-celtic-park-emerge-new-banners/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/stunning-images-of-celtic-park-emerge-new-banners/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T06:57:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s been a lot of online debate over the new Celtic Park banners. Watching it come together over the space of the last week reminded me of loading an image on the internet before broadband. Yes, I’m that old! Celtic fans have an opinion on everything and because there’s been no competitive football to discuss […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Danny Lennon on why Celtic new Bhoy Aaron Mooy is not the new Scott Brown, and why he could make difference in Champions League]]></title>
        <id>0bafa6eadd7f4baa6457361ecb1b6ae8</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20580437.danny-lennon-celtic-new-bhoy-aaron-mooy-not-new-scott-brown-make-difference-champions-league/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DANNY LENNON may ultimately not have seen the best of Aaron Mooy when he managed him at St Mirren, but he has a feeling that Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou will ensure his new club’s supporters see a midfielder at the peak of his powers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC STAR INJURY SETBACK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-star-injury-setback/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-star-injury-setback/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T05:19:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UNLUCKY Yosuke Ideguchi will MISS Celtic’s kick-off to the new season. The Japanese international midfielder, who was crocked in only his second appearance for the Hoops, has suffered another setback, according to a report in the Scottish Sun. Ideguchi was not one of the 21 players utilised by Ange Postecoglou in the 2-2 draw against Norwich [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE CLEAR-OUT: JOHNSTON NEXT?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ange-clear-out-johnston-next/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ange-clear-out-johnston-next/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T05:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MIKEY JOHNSTON is poised to join Ange Postecoglou’s Celtic clear-out. The 23-year-old winger will be on his way in a loan deal with the Hoops boss eager for the player to get game time, according to a report in the Scottish Sun. Intriguingly, former Parkhead gaffer Ronny Deila, now in charge of Belgian outfit Standard [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carl Starfelt set for Celtic stage two as Sweden chief insists defender can achieve Champions League stardom - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEPpqQQcnuf53aGaDbaQOdD8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/carl-starfelt-set-celtic-stage-27585230"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carl Starfelt set for Celtic stage two as Sweden chief insists defender can achieve Champions League stardom  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GRIFF: THE GOALS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/griff-the-goals/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/griff-the-goals/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T04:10:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[COLOURFUL and controversial, Leigh Griffiths rode an emotional rollercoaster during his eight years at Celtic. The lively little marksman fired in over a century of goals for the Hoops and may have expected a fanfare of trumpets to herald the curtain coming down on his career in the east end of Glasgow. Instead, there was [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THREE CHEERS: TREBLE No.3 (2000/01)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/three-cheers-treble-no-3-2000-01/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/three-cheers-treble-no-3-2000-01/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T04:05:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MARTIN O’NEILL swept into Celtic in majestic style in season 2000/01 with a spectacular silverware clean sweep in his unforgettable debut campaign CQN has journeyed back in time to turn the spotlight on the Parkhead club’s Magnificent Seven seasons where they have won every prize Scottish football has to offer – the league championship, the Scottish [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: ‘SHEER STUPIDITY’: DI CANIO IN THE WARS: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Sixteen)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-sheer-stupidity-di-canio-in-the-wars-the-tommy-burns-story-part-sixteen/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-sheer-stupidity-di-canio-in-the-wars-the-tommy-burns-story-part-sixteen/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-27T04:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS was experiencing extreme turbulence during his third year as Celtic manager in an explosive 1996/97 crusade. The fans’ favourite had returned to the club on July 12 1994 and had won the Scottish Cup in his debut campaign. That was followed by a barren term and all eyes were on the boss as [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Injury Blow for Celtic Ahead of Aberdeen Opener]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/report-injury-blow-for-celtic-ahead-of-aberdeen-opener/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/report-injury-blow-for-celtic-ahead-of-aberdeen-opener/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T22:02:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to reports on Tuesday evening, Celtic midfielder Yosuke Ideguchi has suffered a new injury setback in his quest to break into Ange Postecoglou’s starting XI. Yosuke came in with Reo Hatate and Daizen Maeda, but an injury on his debut set him back months. The Japanese man was back in pre-season training and looked […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Ange Set to Sanction Celtic Loan Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/report-ange-set-to-sanction-celtic-loan-deal/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/report-ange-set-to-sanction-celtic-loan-deal/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T21:49:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MIKEY JOHNSTON hasn’t had luck at all when it comes to injuries. The winger has picked up some major setbacks ever since trying to make his way through to the first team. The Celtic academy star has the talent, but staying fit and then being afforded a run of games to show what he can […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mikey Johnston set for Celtic transfer exit with Scottish Premiership clubs keen on loan move]]></title>
        <id>118cbceb1a2c10e42e88520d982f7547</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20580544.mikey-johnston-set-celtic-transfer-exit-scottish-premiership-clubs-keen-loan-move/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T21:46:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MIKEY JOHNSTON is set to exit Celtic this summer on loan with a host of European clubs interested, according to reports.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Domestic football nearly back, not long now!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.jerseydoesntshrink.com/2022/7/26/23279688/domestic-football-nearly-back-not-long-now</id>
        <link href="https://www.jerseydoesntshrink.com/2022/7/26/23279688/domestic-football-nearly-back-not-long-now"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T21:37:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Paul Devlin/SNS Group via Getty Images
  

 Ahead of the return of a famous sporting organisation getting ready for THE REAL STUFF on Sunday, we thought we’d take a look back and share some season openers over the years.
But enough about GIGPOD, Celtic are also going to be kicking a ball. 
With the actual football just around the corner, here’s a few curtain raisers we’ve enjoyed over the years, either at Celtic Park, or away from home!
We start with a classic at Tannadice in 1991. Dundee Utd 3-4 Celtic, featuring two absolute screamers from John Collins!

Sunday’s opponents were also involved in a memorable 2-2 draw back in August 1996. This was a game that I went to in an era when I missed no away games, but to this day, it’s one of only three games I have left before the 90 minutes are up, and indeed I never witnessed Thom’s leveller below.

Does it get any better than the win at Tannadice in 2000, for what was the first game of the MON era though?

A decade of opening day dominance after that, generally, other than the occasional away day draw, including this disasterclass in 2005 against Motherwell at Fir Park!

We all remember Patrick McCourt’s virtuoso effort at Inverness in 2010 surely?

Fast forward six years later, Tynecastle 2016. Scott Sinclair’s late winner starts the invincible run under Brendan Rodgers

And while the Neil Lennon regime was hardly inspirational, there was of course the fantastic 7-0 thumping of St Johnstone back in 2019!

Let’s hope for more of the same this weekend!
Here’s some trivia to leave you very confident for the game ahead:


Trawled through records to find out when was the last time we lost a game at Celtic Park on the opening day of the season and it seems to have been; 9th Sep 1950 - Celtic 3-4 Morton. Pub quiz obsessives, you’re welcome!— Stevie ⚪️ (@stevieblock102) July 26, 2022]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ron Gordon teases Deloitte review 'wow' factor as Hibs chairman hails Rangers for 'advancing Scottish football more than any other club']]></title>
        <id>3782966</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/hibs/ron-gordon-teases-deloitte-review-wow-factor-as-hibs-chairman-hails-rangers-for-advancing-scottish-football-more-than-any-other-club-3782966"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scottish football has targeted doubling its revenue within three to five years, with all representatives in Europe expected to play a key role in enhancing the game’s reputation and earning potential.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moira Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As Ibrox Starts To Sweat The Wage Bill, A Player And His Agent Dig In Their Heels.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/as-ibrox-starts-to-sweat-the-wage-bill-a-player-and-his-agent-dig-in-their-heels/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/as-ibrox-starts-to-sweat-the-wage-bill-a-player-and-his-agent-dig-in-their-heels/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T19:11:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ibrox has told five of its fringe player that they have to – note that; have to – find new clubs this summer, as though that was something that they can be forced to do. One of them is Katic, who cost them a tidy sum and is on good wages. Now, we have players […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aberdeen manager admits he tried to sign Celtic star permanently - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>CAIiENV7yqaL_lCwIrDwYfwk9cEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4KKJCzCv9JoDMICkoAY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2022/07/26/aberdeen-manager-celtic-star-permanently/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T19:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aberdeen manager admits he tried to sign Celtic star permanently  The Celtic Bhoys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ronny Deila is looking to sign Celtic player this summer - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>CBMiTGh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljYmhveXMuY29tLzIwMjIvMDcvMjYvcm9ubnktZGVpbGEtc2lnbi1jZWx0aWMtcGxheWVyLXN1bW1lci_SAVBodHRwczovL3RoZWNlbHRpY2Job3lzLmNvbS8yMDIyLzA3LzI2L3Jvbm55LWRlaWxhLXNpZ24tY2VsdGljLXBsYXllci1zdW1tZXIvYW1wLw</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2022/07/26/ronny-deila-sign-celtic-player-summer/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T18:04:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ronny Deila is looking to sign Celtic player this summer  The Celtic Bhoys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Those Calling For Celtic To Implement A Ticket Exchange Scheme Are Right.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/those-calling-for-celtic-to-implement-a-ticket-exchange-scheme-are-right/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/those-calling-for-celtic-to-implement-a-ticket-exchange-scheme-are-right/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T17:50:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of things that fans ask for are silly or unreasonable. A lot of them don’t make much sense. But there are some which make all the sense in the world, and those amongst the Celtic sites calling for us to implement a ticket exchange scheme … that’s smart. It’s hard to believe, if […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion: Standard Liege move could save Mikey Johnston’s Celtic career]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/opinion-standard-liege-move-could-save-mikey-johnstons-celtic-career/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/opinion-standard-liege-move-could-save-mikey-johnstons-celtic-career/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T17:35:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One last throw of the dice. One last throw at the dart board. One last attempt at salvation. Pick any metaphor you like, but when it comes to Mikey Johnston’s Celtic career it all amounts to the same thing: the player must go out on loan to try and rescue his status as an employee Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic loan failure returns to Australia two years later - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>CAIiECShwOlQNY1b7a124zrv1JIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4KKJCzCv9JoDMICkoAY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2022/07/26/celtic-loan-failure-returns-australia/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T17:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic loan failure returns to Australia two years later  The Celtic Bhoys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic in the Strachan Era – Summer Transfer Window, 2005]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-in-the-strachan-era-summer-transfer-window-2005/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-in-the-strachan-era-summer-transfer-window-2005/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T16:04:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There was little excitement in the ranks when news of Gordon Strachan’s first signing as Celtic manager came through. Guinean left-back Mo Camara had spent five years in English football with Wolverhampton Wanderers then Burnley, joining Celtic on a ‘Bosman’ transfer on 22 June 2005, just three days short of his 30th birthday. He had Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['He's not daft': Celtic tipped to learn from Brendan Rodgers' mistakes and bloody nose of Champions League elite]]></title>
        <id>071a250ad73746d6ed3e69e7be619426</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20579946.sutton-believes-postecoglous-celtic-will-remain-true-attacking-style/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T15:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton insists that Ange Postecoglou's side can give the best in Europe a run for their money]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton in Celtic no fear verdict as he reckons Champions League big hitters in for 'a bloody nose' - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEPVcbcjZdfzQ88oag_bLOVwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/chris-sutton-celtic-no-fear-27582535"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T15:01:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton in Celtic no fear verdict as he reckons Champions League big hitters in for 'a bloody nose'  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Park in Billy McNeill tribute as new Parkhead banners pictured in summer makeover - Scottish Daily Express]]></title>
        <id>CAIiELhIaFdP6UFH6-Zie9DDW9MqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowi76vCzCYyccDMK3zuAc</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottishdailyexpress.co.uk/sport/football/celtic-park-billy-mcneill-tribute-27582665"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T15:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Park in Billy McNeill tribute as new Parkhead banners pictured in summer makeover  Scottish Daily Express]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cinched it; Callum McGregor Meets Rylan]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/cinched-it-callum-mcgregor-meets-rylan/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/cinched-it-callum-mcgregor-meets-rylan/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T14:52:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s last season’s banter come to life! Today the SPFL captains met Cinch spokesperson Rylan Clark ahead of the new season and that meant Callum McGregor was on hand to get a photo with the former reality tv star. Towards the end of last season, there were cardboard cut outs of Rylan in Scottish football […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Henrik Larsson on that Barcelona goal against Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/henrik-larsson-on-that-barcelona-goal-against-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/henrik-larsson-on-that-barcelona-goal-against-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T14:52:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During his magnificent seven seasons in Glasgow at Celtic Park, Henrik Larsson became part of the rich tapestry of our club’s history and won a place in the hearts of Hoops fans worldwide. He scored countless goals for the green and white throughout his time here and put Rangers to the sword many times along Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to expect from Celtic this season?]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/what-to-expect-from-celtic-this-season/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/what-to-expect-from-celtic-this-season/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T14:23:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic is clearly the biggest and most successful Scottish football club, with a proud unbroken history, whose ambitions have always been to be Scotland’s leading football club. Since its foundation in 1888, this world famous club, based in the East End of Glasgow has achieved many successes and built its reputation year after year, with Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to expect from Celtic this season? - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEOXdsBfU_FIJd0TK1WNasqAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/what-to-expect-from-celtic-this-season/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T14:23:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What to expect from Celtic this season?  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aberdeen boss Jim Goodwin responds to 'No more Celtic loans' fan request]]></title>
        <id>3782572</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/aberdeen-boss-jim-goodwin-responds-to-no-more-celtic-loans-fan-request-3782572"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T14:07:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aberdeen boss Jim Goodwin has defended the club’s decision to sign Liam Scales on loan from Celtic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer rumours: Draxler to Newcastle, Welsh to Toulouse, Mejbri to West Brom]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sportsmole.co.uk/football/man-utd/transfer-talk/feature/transfer-rumours-draxler-to-newcastle-welsh-to-toulouse-mejbri-to-west-brom_490897.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.sportsmole.co.uk/football/man-utd/transfer-talk/feature/transfer-rumours-draxler-to-newcastle-welsh-to-toulouse-mejbri-to-west-brom_490897.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T13:05:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sports Mole rounds up the latest transfer rumours, including Julian Draxler to Newcastle United, Stephen Welsh to Toulouse and Ben Brereton Diaz to West Ham United.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charlie Nicholas Has Driven Sevconia Tonto Today With His Latest Prediction.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/charlie-nicholas-has-driven-sevconia-tonto-today-with-his-latest-prediction/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/charlie-nicholas-has-driven-sevconia-tonto-today-with-his-latest-prediction/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T11:47:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As regular readers know well, I am not the greatest fan of Charlie Nicholas nor any of the nonsense that pours out of his mouth on a regular basis. That’s why, on days like these, I take such amusement in the anger across the city. And boy, is it fierce. He has said, first, that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers and Celtic referees revealed as SFA confirm appointments for Premiership openers - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEE3Lu22TVo2F-iymPPnP9XIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPPfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/rangers-celtic-referees-revealed-sfa-24590501"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T11:43:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers and Celtic referees revealed as SFA confirm appointments for Premiership openers  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Hendry drops significant update on Celtic links to Fernandinho-esque midfielder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-spl-claudio-gomes-transfer-news-updates/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-spl-claudio-gomes-transfer-news-updates/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T11:40:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic‘s rumoured interest in signing Manchester City defensive midfielder Claudio Gomes this summer is ‘wide of the mark’, according to a significant update from the reliable Mark Hendry. The Lowdown: Gomes linked with Hoops move The Hoops are seemingly still looking to make midfield reinforcements ahead of the start of the new Scottish Premiership season, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charlie Nicholas: Ange will leave Ibrox club empty handed this year]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/charlie-nicholas-ange-will-leave-ibrox-club-empty-handed-this-year/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/charlie-nicholas-ange-will-leave-ibrox-club-empty-handed-this-year/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T11:13:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After winning the cinch Premiership title last season to go along with a League Cup trophy, Ange Postecoglou and his Celtic side left theRangers with just a Scottish Cup to their name – which was celebrated like a Champions League win (Scottish Cup *Champions mind). It was a good night Vienna shot if truth be Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Brown Set For Managerial Bow]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/scott-brown-set-for-managerial-bow/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/scott-brown-set-for-managerial-bow/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T11:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former Celtic captain will take charge of his first game as manager when his Fleetwood side take on Port Vale away from home this Saturday.  Preparations have been coming along well for the Celtic legend with his teams final pre-season fixture culminating in a 2-1 victory over Dundee United. Celtic fans will be keen […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Brown Set For Managerial Bow - CeltsAreHere]]></title>
        <id>CBMiPGh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9zY290dC1icm93bi1zZXQtZm9yLW1hbmFnZXJpYWwtYm93L9IBhQFodHRwczovL2NlbHRzYXJlaGVyZS5jb20vc2NvdHQtYnJvd24tc2V0LWZvci1tYW5hZ2VyaWFsLWJvdy9hbXAvP2ZiY2xpZD1Jd0FSMzV4cHotQXBKXzhhbWt0TXJ1cU9mNGlFUWNCSHhLZWxuZmpKa2EtMzRwV3d3NDhEZnJqOGVqak5F</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/scott-brown-set-for-managerial-bow/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T11:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Brown Set For Managerial Bow  CeltsAreHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Effective players]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/effective-players/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/effective-players/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T11:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We had a family conversation this will about the most effective Celtic players we have seen for each position, not necessarily the best there. I went straight to Alan Thompson. Alan was a hard left-mid when he arrived from Aston Villa in 2000, who became a wing-back under Martin O’Neill. His contribution to that successful [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Goodwin bats away Celtic loan fury from Aberdeen fans after Liam Scales deal - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEHKUIBPFhlvV8E9-IwdRDowqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/jim-goodwin-shoots-celtic-loan-27578692"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T10:28:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Goodwin bats away Celtic loan fury from Aberdeen fans after Liam Scales deal  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As Usual, Pirie’s Latest Celtic Is Article Is All Filler, Fluff And Nonsense.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/as-usual-piries-latest-celtic-is-article-is-all-filler-fluff-and-nonsense/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/as-usual-piries-latest-celtic-is-article-is-all-filler-fluff-and-nonsense/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T10:28:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Pirie thinks Ange has big choices to make ahead of the coming season. He thinks that our manager hasn’t made some of these crucial decisions already. Today in his latest daft column he lists the seven decisions our manager needs to make about the peripheral players in his squad, as though Ange has been […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Has Important Flag Day Decision to Make]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/ange-has-important-flag-day-decision-to-make/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/ange-has-important-flag-day-decision-to-make/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T10:01:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic kick-off their league campaign this Sunday with a home tie against Aberdeen but one of the questions is who will partner Cameron Carter-Vickers in defence.  Carl Starfelt was unfortunate to pick up an injury while away on international duty with Sweden meaning that he has missed out on Celtic’s pre-season. The 27-year old was […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Henrik Larsson on 'stabbing Celtic fans in the heart' and his toughest Rangers opponent - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEBzqLK2Mlya7pcOO9UE6qYsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPPfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/henrik-larsson-stabbing-celtic-fans-24588802"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T09:53:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Henrik Larsson on 'stabbing Celtic fans in the heart' and his toughest Rangers opponent  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tony Mowbray Testimonial, 30 years ago today – Middlesbrough v Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/tony-mowbray-testimonial-30-years-ago-today-middlesbrough-v-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/tony-mowbray-testimonial-30-years-ago-today-middlesbrough-v-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T09:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 1992 I was a 14 year old fitba daft Bhoy from the new town of Livingston in West Lothian. I had followed Celtic for years with my father usually travelling by car home and away and even further afield to England for testimonial games. I had pretty much never been to a match without my Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tony Mowbray Testimonial, 30 years ago today – Middlesbrough v Celtic - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEPBdfy5uzxzT7fjq4RzNvrEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/tony-mowbray-testimonial-30-years-ago-today-middlesbrough-v-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T09:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tony Mowbray Testimonial, 30 years ago today – Middlesbrough v Celtic  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premier Sports Cup schedule confirmed as Celtic and Rangers learn TV slot times for last 16 - Glasgow Live]]></title>
        <id>CAIiECT3MtH2PBEPkIuALpGHerYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow96D9CjDOy_QCMKzp0wU</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowlive.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/premier-sports-cup-schedule-confirmed-24587893"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T09:32:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Premier Sports Cup schedule confirmed as Celtic and Rangers learn TV slot times for last 16  Glasgow Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic loanee Daniel Arzani hooks up with Dwight Yorke in Australia after European nightmare - Celtic Way]]></title>
        <id>CAIiENo0ZmasT61Z7nyb9pqxtxkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsJStCzC9n8UDMNiMswc</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticway.co.uk/news/20578395.23-year-olds-injury-plagued-spell-europe/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T09:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic loanee Daniel Arzani hooks up with Dwight Yorke in Australia after European nightmare  Celtic Way]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Henrik Larsson in Celtic fan confession as he admits Barcelona goal at Parkhead 'stabbed them in the heart' - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiECVysavwe8g-37eHjnwRCZcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/henrik-larsson-celtic-fan-confession-27577697"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T09:21:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Henrik Larsson in Celtic fan confession as he admits Barcelona goal at Parkhead 'stabbed them in the heart'  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic Flop Moves Back Home]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/former-celtic-flop-moves-back-home/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/former-celtic-flop-moves-back-home/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T09:10:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Brendan Rodgers loan signing Daniel Arzani has moved back to Australia to continue his career after a tough few years in Europe. Signed by Manchester City as a 19-year-old, the midfielder was sent out on a two year loan to Celtic. After getting up to speed, Brendan Rodgers brought the Australian on against Dundee […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“It’s good to play with those boys – I hope they feel the same way,” David Turnbull]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/its-good-to-play-with-those-boys-i-hope-they-feel-the-same-way-david-turnbull/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/its-good-to-play-with-those-boys-i-hope-they-feel-the-same-way-david-turnbull/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T09:04:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Turnbull eyes goalscoring competition with Reo Hatate and Matt O’Riley… David Turnbull hit double figures for Celtic last season in terms of his goalscoring exploits and that was despite dropping out of the team after pulling his hamstring during the League Cup Final win over Hibs at Hampden just before Christmas. While out of Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers legend admits 'we have to be honest' - Celtic are title team to beat]]></title>
        <id>420596dda8d26eefef843ee1effb9b40</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20578317.rangers-legend-admits-we-honest---celtic-title-team-beat/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T09:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ibrox hero Brian Laudrup has admitted that Celtic go into the Scottish Premiership campaign as favourites – but has reminded everyone that Rangers were tipped to come up trumps last season under Steven Gerrard and that he expects a closely contended title this time around.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Celtic transfer calls Ange Postecoglou still has to make as the clock ticks on Parkhead’s forgotten men - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEMaSpEbsGMg-FsZzBNLSNUIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/7-celtic-transfer-calls-ange-27576724"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T08:53:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[7 Celtic transfer calls Ange Postecoglou still has to make as the clock ticks on Parkhead’s forgotten men  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OLD BHOY COULD SPOIL FLAG DAY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/old-bhoy-could-spoil-flag-day/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/old-bhoy-could-spoil-flag-day/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T08:44:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic star Jonny Hayes will be one of Aberdeen’s dangermen as they attempt to topple the champions on Flag Day at Parkhead on Sunday. The boyhood Hoops fan saw a dream come true when Brendan Rodgers brought him to the club in June 2017 – ironically after he opened the scoring for the Dons [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Long May it Continue’ – Celtic Midfielder Offers Celtic Squad Insight]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/long-may-it-continue-celtic-midfielder-offers-celtic-squad-insight/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/long-may-it-continue-celtic-midfielder-offers-celtic-squad-insight/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T08:06:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former Motherwell midfielder put the finishing touch to Celtic’s pre-season with a terrific strike against Norwich City and has vowed that there is more to come from Ange Postecoglou’s side.  There will be a sigh of relief amongst many Celtic fans as friendlies are very difficult to judge where a team is it and […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Premiership trophy will remain at Parkhead' - Two reasons given why Celtic will triumph over Rangers]]></title>
        <id>3781684</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/premiership-trophy-will-remain-at-parkhead-two-reasons-given-why-celtic-will-triumph-over-rangers-3781684"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T08:04:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Scotland, Aberdeen and Celtic star Charlie Nicholas believes the Premiership title race will be close but there are two reasons why Ange Postecoglou’s men will retain the title.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>By The Newsroom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charlie Nicholas dismisses 'unknown' Rangers youngsters as he makes Celtic title tip]]></title>
        <id>9469a3f7ebc3a8d3a095a2acca358f4c</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20573312.charlie-nicholas-dismisses-unknown-rangers-youngsters-makes-celtic-title-tip/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T07:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pundit Charlie Nicholas reckons it's Celtic's title to lose - despite Rangers bringing in the seven players he earlier said they needed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charlie Nicholas dismisses 'unknown' Rangers youngsters as he makes Celtic title tip]]></title>
        <id>9469a3f7ebc3a8d3a095a2acca358f4c</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20573312.charlie-nicholas-tips-celtic-title-dismisses-unknown-rangers-youngsters/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T07:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pundit Charlie Nicholas reckons it's Celtic's title to lose - despite Rangers bringing in the seven players he earlier said they needed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How ditching kebabs and studying Leonardo Bonucci helped Celtic new boy Moritz Jenz become 'The Duel Monster']]></title>
        <id>41b1434a85a7fac6dbcb5038a5b793b8</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20571319.ditching-kebabs-studying-leonardo-bonucci-helped-celtic-new-boy-moritz-jenz-become-the-duel-monster/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T07:36:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TO say that the last German centre half who Celtic brought in failed to live up to expectations is something of an understatement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NO ORDINARY JOE: ANGE’S ‘BIG SIGNING’ HOLDS TITLE KEY, EX-CELTIC GOAL HERO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/no-ordinary-joe-anges-big-signing-holds-title-key-ex-celtic-goal-hero/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/no-ordinary-joe-anges-big-signing-holds-title-key-ex-celtic-goal-hero/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T07:17:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART acclaimed the work done by Ange Postecoglou by thanking him for “making an old donkey like me feel young again,” as CQN reported in May. The 35-year-old 75 times-capped England international keeper played down the remarkable part he had contributed in the rejuvenation of Celtic on their way to lifting their tenth title [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three stars Celtic could buy to solve their defensive midfield struggles – opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/three-stars-celtic-could-buy-to-solve-their-defensive-midfield-struggles-opinion/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/three-stars-celtic-could-buy-to-solve-their-defensive-midfield-struggles-opinion/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T06:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are well-stocked in almost every area at the moment at Ange Postecoglou aims to develop his squad ahead of a long, tough, gruelling season. However, there is room for improvement always – and one position that may need a bit of TLC is defensive midfield. Nir Bitton left over the summer, Ismaila Soro is away on Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brian Laudrup fires Celtic title warning in loaded Rangers reminder as he draws 'team to beat' parallel - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEIs6aQwqyJWaioeQFKZeXOUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/brian-laudrup-fires-celtic-title-27576235"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T06:16:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brian Laudrup fires Celtic title warning in loaded Rangers reminder as he draws 'team to beat' parallel  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I’VE STILL GOT A LOT MORE TO COME,’ INSISTS TURNBULL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ive-still-got-a-lot-more-to-come-insists-turnbull/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ive-still-got-a-lot-more-to-come-insists-turnbull/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T06:03:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAVID TURNBULL has warned rivals Celtic will still be as relentless in the new campaign as they were last time out when they won their tenth title in 11 years. The Hoops were dismissed by many going into the previous campaign and three defeats in the first six league outings appeared to emphasise that belief. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charlie Nicholas reckons Rangers doomed to horror season as he predicts Gio van Bronckhorst will win NOTHING - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiECeJ4MXVokst8ITIBvBIZWIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/charlie-nicholas-reckons-rangers-doomed-27574290"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Charlie Nicholas reckons Rangers doomed to horror season as he predicts Gio van Bronckhorst will win NOTHING  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Brown made following Rangers horrible and he was my scourge for nine years says Barry Nicholson - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEKzD8l3nMeJ7UT-8x51zJtMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/scott-brown-made-following-rangers-27572116"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Brown made following Rangers horrible and he was my scourge for nine years says Barry Nicholson  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gio van Bronckhorst in Rangers title vow as he names key battleground that will decide Celtic trophy fight - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEBkA3irIVfB6M2t0kFUQZoYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/gio-van-bronckhorst-rangers-title-27575264"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gio van Bronckhorst in Rangers title vow as he names key battleground that will decide Celtic trophy fight  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THREE CHEERS: TREBLE No.2 (1968/69)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/three-cheers-treble-no-2-1968-69/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/three-cheers-treble-no-2-1968-69/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T04:05:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOCK STEIN achieved the first treble in the club’s history in season 1966/67 – and enjoyed the marvellous experience again two years later when Celtic staged an action replay. CQN has journeyed back in time to turn the spotlight on the Parkhead club’s Magnificent Seven seasons where they have won every prize Scottish football has to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Tuesday July 26: Are We Ready ?]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=17849</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=17849"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T04:03:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That’s the pre season done, and next time out Celtic will begin that tricky second season under manager Ange Postecoglou.   Ordinarily, we’d be talking…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: PIERRE’S PAY ROW, BOSS SEES RED IN OLD FIRM FLARE-UP: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Fifteen)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-pierres-pay-row-boss-sees-red-in-old-firm-flare-up-the-tommy-burns-story-part-fifteen/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-pierres-pay-row-boss-sees-red-in-old-firm-flare-up-the-tommy-burns-story-part-fifteen/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-26T04:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS’ third year as Celtic manager was developing into a rollicking rollercoaster. The fans’ favourite had returned to the club on July 12 1994 and had won the Scottish Cup in his debut campaign. That was followed by a barren term and all eyes were on the boss as a new challenging and testing [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[St Mirren starlet has ‘followed in David Turnbull’s footsteps’, manager claims]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/st-mirren-starlet-has-followed-in-david-turnbulls-footsteps-manager-claims/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/st-mirren-starlet-has-followed-in-david-turnbulls-footsteps-manager-claims/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T23:08:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Turnbull’s failed move to Celtic the year before he actually signed has been used as the blueprint for the reason why St Mirren teen Dylan Reid opted to stay with the Buddies as opposed to a switch to Paradise, according to boss Stephen Robinson. 17-year-old Reidmade his professional debut in Paisley at the age Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scotland hero Kenny McLean waxes lyrical over superb Paradise atmosphere]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/scotland-hero-kenny-mclean-waxes-lyrical-over-superb-paradise-atmosphere/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/scotland-hero-kenny-mclean-waxes-lyrical-over-superb-paradise-atmosphere/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T22:27:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Park’s atmosphere is clear for all to see as one of the better – if not the best ground – in the world when it is on top form. Not many will say that when it comes to friendlies, although some ground can be special in that sense. It wasn’t expected by many to Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Official UEFA’s Celtic Post to 42m Followers]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/official-uefas-celtic-post-to-42m-followers/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/official-uefas-celtic-post-to-42m-followers/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T22:16:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC began Monday by letting fans know it was 25 years to the day that Henrik Larsson signed for the Hoops, and the rest, as they say, is history. The Super Swede’s name will be etched into the fabric of Celtic Football club long after we’re all gone. 242 goals and 8 trophies during a […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Official UEFA’s Celtic Post to 42m Followers - CeltsAreHere]]></title>
        <id>CBMiRWh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9vZmZpY2lhbC11ZWZhcy1jZWx0aWMtcG9zdC10by00Mm0tZm9sbG93ZXJzL9IBSWh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9vZmZpY2lhbC11ZWZhcy1jZWx0aWMtcG9zdC10by00Mm0tZm9sbG93ZXJzL2FtcC8</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/official-uefas-celtic-post-to-42m-followers/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T22:16:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Official UEFA’s Celtic Post to 42m Followers  CeltsAreHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Hoops hero names three players who should seek Celtic exit]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/former-hoops-hero-names-three-players-who-should-seek-celtic-exit/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/former-hoops-hero-names-three-players-who-should-seek-celtic-exit/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T22:02:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is no secret that whilst Ange Postecoglou is looking to add players to his team, there are a plethora of players in the current Hoops squad that face a season without action as they aim – and mostly fail – to force their way into the Aussie’s plans. No less than seven new signings Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kris Commons details why Celtic will be ‘absolutely frightening’ ahead of new campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/kris-commons-details-why-celtic-will-be-absolutely-frightening-ahead-of-new-campaign/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/kris-commons-details-why-celtic-will-be-absolutely-frightening-ahead-of-new-campaign/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T21:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero Kris Commons has detailed why the club will be ‘frightening’ going into next season’s Premiership campaign – claiming that the club hit top gear when they click together – and has backed the Bhoys to finish ahead of theRangers for the eleventh time in twelve years. Postecoglou’s men finished four points ahead of Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hayden Coulson next on Aberdeen transfer list as Jim Goodwin eyes Middlesbrough defender - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEOZy4H68yrC9lwUXz0xRPhQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-transfer-news/hayden-coulson-next-aberdeen-transfer-27574938"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hayden Coulson next on Aberdeen transfer list as Jim Goodwin eyes Middlesbrough defender  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers will win no trophies this season says Charlie Nicholas as he backs Celtic for more title glory - Scottish Daily Express]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEAEiHAkmbnsfJ6ozpUVmraUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowi76vCzCYyccDMKvzuAc</id>
        <link href="https://www.scottishdailyexpress.co.uk/sport/football/rangers-win-no-trophies-says-27571643"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T21:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers will win no trophies this season says Charlie Nicholas as he backs Celtic for more title glory  Scottish Daily Express]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda teases that a new trademark Celtic goal celebration is coming soon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/daizen-maeda-teases-that-a-new-trademark-celtic-goal-celebration-is-coming-soon/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/daizen-maeda-teases-that-a-new-trademark-celtic-goal-celebration-is-coming-soon/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T20:45:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda has been a joy to watch in Celtic colours since he arrived from Yokohama F.Marinos in January. Trusted by Ange Postecoglou to play a crucial role in our push for the Scottish Premiership title last season, Maeda quickly built a reputation as a fierce competitor, lightning-quick attacker and goalscorer. With those goals usually ...
The post Daizen Maeda teases that a new trademark Celtic goal celebration is coming soon appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jota and Carter Vickers branded Celtic 'donkeys' as Rangers fan caller lets rip in transfer rant - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEGoqjpFON2UkRJAR5oYuyM0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/jota-carter-vickers-branded-celtic-27575045"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T20:19:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jota and Carter Vickers branded Celtic 'donkeys' as Rangers fan caller lets rip in transfer rant  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Murdo MacLeod: Henrik was as grounded as they come]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/murdo-macleod-henrik-was-as-grounded-as-they-come/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/murdo-macleod-henrik-was-as-grounded-as-they-come/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T19:58:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the 25th anniversary of Celtic signing the Super Swede, Henrik Larsson, Murdo MacLeod was interviewed by the Sunday Post and gave his take on the modern day Celtic great. MacLeod played for the Glasgow side himself and later returned to be assistant coach when he took over one of the important seasons in our Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[King of Kings Henrik Larsson]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/king-of-kings-henrik/</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/king-of-kings-henrik/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T19:39:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The arrival of the King if Kings Henrik Larsson at Celtic Park came after a protracted wrangle over his contract with former club Feyenoord. New manager Wim Jansen was building a team that he hoped could wrestle the title away from our old rivals on the other side of the city. https://celticfanzine.com/product/annual-magazine-subscription/ Larsson was definitely worth […]
The post King of Kings Henrik Larsson appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Dalglish tips Celtic to win Scottish Premiership yet again]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/kenny-dalglish-tips-celtic-to-win-scottish-premiership-yet-again/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/kenny-dalglish-tips-celtic-to-win-scottish-premiership-yet-again/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T19:39:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic great Kenny Dalglish has backed his old club to do the business again this season and claim two titles on the bounce after Ange Postecoglou won a League and League Cup double in his initial season in charge. Last summer the Hoops were in a shambolic state, as the end of an era came Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Face A Confident Side On Opening Day As Martindale Throws In The Towel.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/celtic-face-a-confident-side-on-opening-day-as-martindale-throws-in-the-towel/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/celtic-face-a-confident-side-on-opening-day-as-martindale-throws-in-the-towel/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T19:38:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The game at the weekend is one we’ve all been looking forward to, and I’m pretty glad that Aberdeen are going into it on a bit of a high, scoring plenty of goals and with confidence soaring. That’s exactly how we want our opponents to be. I hate coming up against teams which offer nothing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: City Group link ruled out as Celtic take transfer breath]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/report-city-group-link-ruled-out-as-celtic-take-transfer-breath/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/report-city-group-link-ruled-out-as-celtic-take-transfer-breath/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T19:16:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are no imminent first-team transfer moves at Celtic this week as the club considers the future of some current squad members, Football Scotland reports. Journalist Mark Hendry has been ahead of the curve on the Celtic transfer front this summer and appears to have some pretty decent sources when it comes to business that ...
The post Report: City Group link ruled out as Celtic take transfer breath appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tory Loony Has An Unhinged Rant About The Unseen Fenian Union Barons.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/tory-loony-has-an-unhinged-rant-about-the-unseen-fenian-union-barons/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/tory-loony-has-an-unhinged-rant-about-the-unseen-fenian-union-barons/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T18:14:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You think you’ve seen it all and then you get a day like today. A Tory MSP has slammed the RMT for organising a rail strike, and then suggested that it was done to disenfranchise Ibrox fans. I mean come on. These Peepul really don’t inhabit the real world. I know what he means, but […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans hit with Aberdeen travel setback as Scotrail staff shortages cause chaos after Premiership opener - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEJ_vqG7pPfS01B1mzl1tZtsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/celtic-fans-hit-aberdeen-travel-27574402"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T18:08:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans hit with Aberdeen travel setback as Scotrail staff shortages cause chaos after Premiership opener  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Celtic's starting 11 for Premiership opener v Aberdeen is hidden in plain sight]]></title>
        <id>3781502</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/why-celtics-starting-11-for-premiership-opener-v-aberdeen-is-hidden-in-plain-sight-3781502"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T18:04:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The clues are always hiding in plain sight when it comes to Celtic’s manager Ange Postecoglou’s intentions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Quality save and 3 classy goals in latest Celtic B highlights]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/video-quality-save-and-3-classy-goals-in-latest-celtic-b-highlights/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/video-quality-save-and-3-classy-goals-in-latest-celtic-b-highlights/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T17:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The club have uploaded highlights of Celtic B’s 3-1 victory over Cowdenbeath at the weekend, with the young Hoops getting off to a great start in the Lowland League. It’s all change for the youths this season. Darren O’Dea and Stephen McManus have taken up coaching duties to more closely align the project with Ange ...
The post Video: Quality save and 3 classy goals in latest Celtic B highlights appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic star relishing his first steps into club management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-icon-scott-brown-relishing-his-first-steps-into-club-management/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-icon-scott-brown-relishing-his-first-steps-into-club-management/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T16:54:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic captain Scott Brown is enjoying his first experience of management at Fleetwood Town and can’t wait to get into the competitive English League One action. Brown’s outfit picked up a 2-1 victory in a closely-fought encounter against Dundee United over the weekend, coming out on top against former teammates such as Charlie Mulgrew, ...
The post Former Celtic star relishing his first steps into club management appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Broony’s thoughts on making his managerial debut – “I can’t wait”]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/broonys-thoughts-on-making-his-managerial-debut-i-cant-wait/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/broonys-thoughts-on-making-his-managerial-debut-i-cant-wait/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T16:47:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend Scott Brown called time on his playing career over the summer, having endured fruitful 20-year career in the Scottish game, making over 540 appearances in the Scottish Premiership and becoming one of the greats. But ‘Broony’ is already back in the footballing industry; this time in the dugout at Fleetwood Town in England’s Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Broony’s thoughts on making his managerial debut – “I can’t wait” - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEKIGoCFB3trByWtuAMrxROEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/broonys-thoughts-on-making-his-managerial-debut-i-cant-wait/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T16:47:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Broony’s thoughts on making his managerial debut – “I can’t wait”  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic SLO provides frustrating Scotrail update for Sunday evening]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-slo-provides-frustrating-scotrail-update-for-sunday-evening/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-slo-provides-frustrating-scotrail-update-for-sunday-evening/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T16:35:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some Celtic fans attending the flag day Scottish Premiership could have a travel headache after the match due to ScotRail’s decision to cut their evening services. Celtic SLO John Paul Taylor this afternoon passed on the news to Celtic supporters after the club received confirmation from ScotRail. “Confirmation that we have been notified by ScotRail Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I wouldn’t get too worked up’ – Sutton Addresses Celtic Pre-Season Concern]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/i-wouldnt-get-too-worked-up-sutton-addresses-celtic-pre-season-concern/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/i-wouldnt-get-too-worked-up-sutton-addresses-celtic-pre-season-concern/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T16:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton has insisted that those inside Celtic Park should focus on their own affairs just like his side did all those years ago.  Sutton arrived in Glasgow under newly appointed Martin O’Neill while large sums of money where being spent elsewhere. He did arrive at the club however with some other big names as […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scotrail confirm travel issue for Celtic supporters on Sunday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/scotrail-confirm-travel-issue-for-celtic-supporters-on-sunday/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/scotrail-confirm-travel-issue-for-celtic-supporters-on-sunday/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T16:10:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scotrail will not be running a train from Dalmarnock after full-time on Sunday, as Celtic take on Aberdeen at Celtic Park. Dalmarnock is a well-used station by Celtic fans on matchdays, with the line running directly into Argyle Street, Glasgow Central and beyond. It is the most convenient train line to the city centre from ...
The post Scotrail confirm travel issue for Celtic supporters on Sunday appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC CUP DATE LIVE TV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-cup-date-live-tv/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-cup-date-live-tv/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:57:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S first defence of their Premier Sports League Cup against Ross County in Dingwall will be shown live on satellite TV. The second round encounter will be played on Wednesday night, August 31, with a 7.45pm kick-off. Ange Postecoglou’s side’s meeting with ex-Celt Malky Mackay’s Highlanders has been chosen by the broadcasters for a live transmission. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Back to the Fixture: French Eddy puts Norwegian side to the sword with slick display]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/back-to-the-fixture-french-eddy-puts-norwegian-side-to-the-sword-with-slick-display/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/back-to-the-fixture-french-eddy-puts-norwegian-side-to-the-sword-with-slick-display/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:42:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There was a running joke amongst Celtic fans that Rosenborg and the Hoops would end up forging a rivalry at some point; with the Eliteserien side being pitted against Celtic in the Champions League for what seemed like year upon year. Despite the first meeting between ourselves and the Norwegian giants landing in 2017 – Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premier Sports select Celtic and Rangers cup fixtures for TV as second round kick-off and dates confirmed]]></title>
        <id>3781294</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/premier-sports-select-celtic-and-rangers-cup-fixtures-for-tv-as-second-round-kick-off-and-dates-confirmed-3781294"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:36:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers and Celtic’s second round fixtures in the Premier Sports Cup will both be shown live, the broadcaster has confirmed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Oliver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[League Cup Draw Hands Celtic Glasgow Derby Disadvantage]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/league-cup-draw-hands-celtic-glasgow-derby-disadvantage/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/league-cup-draw-hands-celtic-glasgow-derby-disadvantage/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:25:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s League Cup tie against Ross County has been pencilled in for the final day in August by Premier Sports. The broadcaster has confirmed the Hoops will take on their fellow SPFL outfit on Wednesday August 31 with a 7:45KO while Rangers cup tie will play 24 hours before, giving them an extra day to […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Davies addresses Celtic transfer chance as he vows to make Rangers his 'home' after Parkhead no-go - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEAOPjJ1QDKXXfNj38Eoj7qcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/ben-davies-addresses-celtic-transfer-27572800"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:22:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Davies addresses Celtic transfer chance as he vows to make Rangers his 'home' after Parkhead no-go  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premier Sports Cup TV picks confirmed with Rangers & Celtic matches live]]></title>
        <id>880f9a7000c13315bd9b45887374a0ac</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20519089.premier-sports-cup-tv-picks-confirmed-rangers-celtic-matches-live/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:14:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PREMIER SPORTS have confirmed both Rangers and Celtic's matches in the second round of the Premier Sports Cup will be broadcast live on TV.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scottish Cricket Got Its Independent Inquiry. Celtic Was Denied One In Football.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/scottish-cricket-got-its-independent-inquiry-celtic-was-denied-one-in-football/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/scottish-cricket-got-its-independent-inquiry-celtic-was-denied-one-in-football/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:13:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am always pleased when those in search of fairness, those who have questions wanting answered, get their victory. It impresses me and inspires me to see that such hard work and commitment to a cause sometimes pays off and gets its just reward. Campaigners got that from Scottish Cricket recently, with their independent inquiry […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scottish Cricket Got Its Independent Inquiry. Celtic Was Denied One In Football. - TheCelticBlog.com]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEDZoPmw3qo21r-de8CQiKUsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowne-jCzDg-bsDMLnLhQc</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/scottish-cricket-got-its-independent-inquiry-celtic-was-denied-one-in-football/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scottish Cricket Got Its Independent Inquiry. Celtic Was Denied One In Football.  TheCelticBlog.com]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic set to buy West Ham youngster, according to reports]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-set-to-buy-west-ham-youngster-according-to-reports/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-set-to-buy-west-ham-youngster-according-to-reports/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic could be set to raid the English Premier League once more this summer under Ange Postecoglou, with reports suggesting that advanced talks are underway for West Ham youngster Justin Osagie. Joe Hart, Cameron Carter-Vickers, James McCarthy and Bosun Lawal were all signed from England’s top-flight last summer in what was a huge rebuild under Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liel Abada Snub]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/liel-abada-snub/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/liel-abada-snub/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic winger Karamoko Dembele has been shortlisted for the Tuttosport Golden Boy award despite having failed to break into Ange Postecoglou’s side at Celtic.  The winger suffered a horrific injury during pre-season last year and following his return from injury, the 19-year old only managed to make just two appearances under Postecoglou. He has […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Claudio Gomes Celtic transfer latest amid Manchester City midfielder links - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEM68lhDwhV0wS8EVFZ7j0m4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPLfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/claudio-gomes-celtic-transfer-latest-24583381"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T14:46:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Claudio Gomes Celtic transfer latest amid Manchester City midfielder links  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fixtures, scores and results as Ange Postecoglou's side take on Aberdeen]]></title>
        <id>b9798b046c1c9f6977bb2d927b94511d</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20518081.celtic-fixtures-scores-results-ange-postecoglous-side-take-aberdeen/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T14:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC begin their defence of the Scottish Premiership title this weekend as Aberdeen head to Parkhead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scottish Premiership state of play - Celtic favourites, Rangers signings, Aberdeen overhaul, Hearts & Hibs confidence]]></title>
        <id>3781037</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/scottish-premiership-state-of-play-celtic-favourites-rangers-signings-aberdeen-overhaul-hearts-hibs-confidence-3781037"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T14:13:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are just five days out until the start of the 2022/23 Scottish Premiership campaign when Rangers travel to Livingston in the season opener.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[25 Years Since Henrik Larsson Joined Celtic He Remains The SPFL's Greatest Import - The Sportsman]]></title>
        <id>CBMid2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRoZXNwb3J0c21hbi5jb20vYXJ0aWNsZXMvMjUteWVhcnMtc2luY2UtaGVucmlrLWxhcnNzb24tam9pbmVkLWNlbHRpYy1oZS1yZW1haW5zLXRoZS1zcGZsLXMtZ3JlYXRlc3QtaW1wb3J00gEA</id>
        <link href="https://www.thesportsman.com/articles/25-years-since-henrik-larsson-joined-celtic-he-remains-the-spfl-s-greatest-import"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T14:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[25 Years Since Henrik Larsson Joined Celtic He Remains The SPFL's Greatest Import  The Sportsman]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic sign up West Ham youth player, pictured at Paradise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/report-celtic-sign-up-west-ham-youth-player/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/report-celtic-sign-up-west-ham-youth-player/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T12:58:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have signed up West Ham United youth player Justin Osagie, journalist Fraser Fletcher has reported today. Fletcher says that the 17-year-old, who can play in defence or midfield, has signed a permanent deal at the Bhoys. The reporter posted a picture of the player at Celtic Park on social media this afternoon, appearing to ...
The post Report: Celtic sign up West Ham youth player, pictured at Paradise appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Sign Young West Ham Defender – Report]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-sign-young-west-ham-defender-report/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-sign-young-west-ham-defender-report/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T12:54:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have signed West Ham defender Justin Osagie from West Ham. BBC Reporter Fraser Fletcher revealed the deal and posted a picture of the 17-year-old holding up a Celtic jersey inside Celtic Park. Osagie signed for the Hammers back in 2020 from Southend. He’s been developing under the Hammers youth system but has been identified […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alfredo Morelos in new Rangers contract talks bombshell as van Bronckhorst reveals star’s 'very positive' - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEChVkaOYR9J5CxB3XVbu1p4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-transfer-news/alfredo-morelos-new-rangers-contract-27570671"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T12:41:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alfredo Morelos in new Rangers contract talks bombshell as van Bronckhorst reveals star’s 'very positive'  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[&#039;Still interest...&#039; - Reliable Sky journo claims &#039;excellent&#039; Celtic man could depart this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-spl-christopher-jullien-transfer-news-updates/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-spl-christopher-jullien-transfer-news-updates/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T12:15:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic centre-back Christopher Jullien still looks likely to complete an exit from Parkhead this summer, according to Sky Sports journalist Anthony Joseph. The Lowdown: Jullien’s injury-plagued career The Frenchman has suffered cruel luck in the injury department in recent years, with his progress hampered hugely by ongoing fitness problems. Jullien made just one appearance for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ange Zoom Call That Sealed January Celtic Transfer]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/the-ange-zoom-call-that-sealed-january-celtic-transfer/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/the-ange-zoom-call-that-sealed-january-celtic-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T11:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda has spoken about his move to Celtic and  his thoughts on manager, Ange Postecoglou. Originally Ange wanted to move the Maeda at the same time as signings like Kyogo and Abada, but Maeda’s loyalty to Yokohama and seeing out the season meant Celtic had to wait. The Japanese international insisted on staying at […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Goodwin faced with Aberdeen problem ahead of trip to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/jim-goodwin-faced-with-aberdeen-problem-ahead-of-celtic-visit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/jim-goodwin-faced-with-aberdeen-problem-ahead-of-celtic-visit/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T11:11:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Goodwin’s Aberdeen are in excellent form this summer and are heading into this weekend’s match against Celtic full of confidence. Unlike other top-flight clubs such as Hibernian, St Mirren and St Johnstone, the Dons sailed through the group stages of the Scottish League Cup against lower league opposition. They won all four games in ...
The post Jim Goodwin faced with Aberdeen problem ahead of trip to Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Goodwin faced with Aberdeen problem ahead of trip to Celtic - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEE6mekdtdOsj9Q3MmvFEl3AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMLbFpgY</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/jim-goodwin-faced-with-aberdeen-problem-ahead-of-celtic-visit/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T11:11:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Goodwin faced with Aberdeen problem ahead of trip to Celtic  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s Other Japanese Striker Might Be Something Of A Secret Weapon For Us.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/celtics-other-japanese-striker-might-be-something-of-a-secret-weapon-for-us/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/celtics-other-japanese-striker-might-be-something-of-a-secret-weapon-for-us/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T11:08:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love the media’s interpretation of what Daizen Maeda did at the start of last season. The way they have interpreted it as a “snub” to Celtic makes me laugh. There are two reasons why, the first of which is that it bears no resemblance to what he actually did. The second is that you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers fans fear major transfer own goal as Alfredo Morelos sent urgent appeal - Hotline - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEKmTPRjLx9ckpdrDJYQaDvEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/rangers-fans-fear-major-transfer-27568838"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T11:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers fans fear major transfer own goal as Alfredo Morelos sent urgent appeal - Hotline  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Title defence tested from the off]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/title-defence-tested-from-the-off/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/title-defence-tested-from-the-off/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T11:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aberdeen played three friendlies, scoring 10 and conceding a goal in each, before their four League Cup group games this month. They scored 12 without conceding in them. Celtic Park on Sunday will be a whole different challenge, but as we remember from even recent times, getting the job done against lower league teams is [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alfie Pond Celtic and Rangers offers 'rejected' as transfer race hots up for rising Exeter City stopper - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEEGQAuiRAZYaNH7wFikgjF0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/alfie-pond-celtic-rangers-offers-27568443"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T10:18:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alfie Pond Celtic and Rangers offers 'rejected' as transfer race hots up for rising Exeter City stopper  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s Latest Stadium Update]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtics-latest-stadium-update/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtics-latest-stadium-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T09:35:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC are currently upgrading the banners at Celtic Park, and as we get closer to the beginning of the new season, it’s taking shape. The banners started going up last week and fans who travelled to the game against Norwich would have got a glimpse of the new design. Over the weekend, only the text […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda snubbed Celtic transfer before rethink as he opens up on father figure Ange Postecoglou - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEINUSisntNINO02wuEGU50AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPPfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/daizen-maeda-snubbed-celtic-transfer-24579182"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T09:29:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda snubbed Celtic transfer before rethink as he opens up on father figure Ange Postecoglou  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Zoom call from Ange Postecoglou that sealed Celtic transfer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/the-zoom-call-from-ange-postecoglou-that-sealed-celtic-transfer/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/the-zoom-call-from-ange-postecoglou-that-sealed-celtic-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T09:12:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda has outlined the reason why he initially said no to Ange Postecoglou when his former manager at Yokohama F.Marinos first offered the forward the chance to join him in Scotland. With unfinished business at Yokohama, Maeda wanted to fulfil his commitments there before looking at a new adventure alongside Ange at Celtic and Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda reveals Celtic transfer rethink, his unbreakable bond with Ange and biggest challenge in Scotland - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEB4m_TI_gg5wGk6a6xS_r4QqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/daizen-maeda-reveals-celtic-transfer-27567546"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T09:09:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda reveals Celtic transfer rethink, his unbreakable bond with Ange and biggest challenge in Scotland  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Celebrate Legendary Hoops Anniversary]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-celebrate-legendary-hoops-anniversary/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-celebrate-legendary-hoops-anniversary/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T09:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC are this morning celebrating ‘25 years of Henrik Larsson’. The club posted out on social media that it’s been 25 years since the Swede signed on at Celtic Park and changed the course of Celtic history. When the striker signed, the Hoops were lagging behind their rivals, in one season, alongside Wim Jansen, Henrik […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[David Martindale says Rangers will be a 'different animal' this season - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEHOkq3LcnDVTvOYZJs6Gq-wqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/rangers-different-animal-verdict-rival-27567391"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T08:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Martindale says Rangers will be a 'different animal' this season  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Before, to be that high, I always thought: Danger, danger. But now I understand the reasons,” Joe Hart]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/before-to-be-that-high-i-always-thought-danger-danger-but-now-i-understand-the-reasons-joe-hart/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/before-to-be-that-high-i-always-thought-danger-danger-but-now-i-understand-the-reasons-joe-hart/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T08:34:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart has been an course and distance winner in many a title race in his long and distinguished career yet he’s probably not had the level of expectation that is always there at Celtic, where the players know that they are expected to win just about every game that they play, particularly in domestic Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Euro move for Celtic defender after loan bid turned down]]></title>
        <id>3780242</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/no-euro-move-for-celtic-defender-after-loan-bid-turned-down-3780242"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T08:33:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have no interest in allowing centre-back Stephen Welsh to depart.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angus Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[David Potter’s mixed memories of Celtic playing Ross County in the League Cup]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/david-potters-mixed-memories-of-celtic-playing-ross-county-in-the-league-cup/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/david-potters-mixed-memories-of-celtic-playing-ross-county-in-the-league-cup/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T07:50:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forgive me if I did not leap about my living room with ecstatic joy when I saw the League Cup draw with the news that Celtic will visit Dingwall at the end of August in the Scottish League Cup. It will be the second time that we will visit Dingwall in August, for we are Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘He’s not going to get a game’ – Centenary Hero Celtic Exit Prediction]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/hes-not-going-to-get-a-game-centenary-hero-celtic-exit-prediction/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/hes-not-going-to-get-a-game-centenary-hero-celtic-exit-prediction/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T07:46:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been another busy transfer window for Ange Postecoglou with seven arrivals at the club alongside a number of players departing with former Celtic striker Frank McAvennie expecting more to head for the exit.  Celtic most recently signed midfielder Aaron Mooy and defender Moritz Jenz with both players getting a little game time during the […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NO-GO WELSH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/no-go-welsh/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/no-go-welsh/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T07:13:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have rejected an initial approach from Toulouse for versatile Stephen Welsh. The Ligue 1 side targeted the former Scotland Under-21s captain in an ambitious swoop on the champions. However, the French outfit will be out of luck with the Hoops not interested in selling the 22-year-old central defender, according to a report in the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brian Laudrup senses Rangers title glory but Kris Commons tips 'frightening' Celtic to outgun rivals - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEBSMR1zHGV-ZJdqre1Lm68cqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/brian-laudrup-senses-rangers-title-27566476"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T07:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brian Laudrup senses Rangers title glory but Kris Commons tips 'frightening' Celtic to outgun rivals  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart Explains Ange Postecoglou Dressing Room Request]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/joe-hart-explains-ange-postecoglou-dressing-room-request/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/joe-hart-explains-ange-postecoglou-dressing-room-request/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T06:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART is still a highly enthusiastic player who feeds off the energy of a top dressing room. The Englishman could have faded into obscurity and picked up a wage just sitting in a bench down south. Instead, Joe came to Celtic and is still writing another great chapter in his career. The goalkeeper’s enthusiasm […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer news LIVE as Celtic and Rangers plus Aberdeen, Hearts and Hibs eye signings - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CBMibmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLXRyYW5zZmVyLW5ld3MvdHJhbnNmZXItbmV3cy1saXZlLWNlbHRpYy1yYW5nZXJzLTI3NTY2MzQ20gFyaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZGFpbHlyZWNvcmQuY28udWsvc3BvcnQvZm9vdGJhbGwvZm9vdGJhbGwtdHJhbnNmZXItbmV3cy90cmFuc2Zlci1uZXdzLWxpdmUtY2VsdGljLXJhbmdlcnMtMjc1NjYzNDYuYW1w</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-transfer-news/transfer-news-live-celtic-rangers-27566346"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T05:20:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer news LIVE as Celtic and Rangers plus Aberdeen, Hearts and Hibs eye signings  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘THAT’S WHY I’M JUST A SOLDIER AND HE’S A GENERAL,’ HART DOESN’T ENVY BOSS ANGE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/thats-why-im-just-a-soldier-and-hes-a-general-hart-doesnt-envy-boss-ange/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/thats-why-im-just-a-soldier-and-hes-a-general-hart-doesnt-envy-boss-ange/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T05:18:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART was the only Celtic player to get the full 90 minutes in the 2-0 win over Norwich City as the champions completed their six-game undefeated work-out programme before the big kick-off. Twenty-one players were utilised as Ange Postecoglou continued to monitor his squad before Aberdeen visit for Flag Day on Sunday. A year [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rangers and Celtic free hits are over amid shifting transfer arms race – Keith Jackson - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEDqnK89ipqoAMsdb3WS8jj8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/rangers-celtic-free-hits-over-27563869"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rangers and Celtic free hits are over amid shifting transfer arms race – Keith Jackson  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THREE CHEERS: TREBLE No.1 (1966/67)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/three-cheers-treble-no-1-1966-67/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/three-cheers-treble-no-1-1966-67/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T04:10:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LEGENDARY manager Jock Stein masterminded Celtic’s first-ever clean sweep of domestic silverware in the memorable season 1966/67. CQN has journeyed back in time to turn the spotlight on the Parkhead club’s Magnificent Seven seasons where they have won every prize Scottish football has to offer – the league championship, the Scottish Cup and the League Cup. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TWENTY-FIVE YEARS AGO TODAY: THE SNAG THAT ALMOST KO’d HENRIK DEAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/twenty-five-years-ago-today-the-snag-that-almost-kod-henrik-deal/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/twenty-five-years-ago-today-the-snag-that-almost-kod-henrik-deal/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T04:05:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HENRIK LARSSON became a genuine Celtic legend during his glorious, mesmerising and breathtaking seven years at the club. But his move from Feyenoord to Paradise exactly 25 years ago almost didn’t take place when an eleventh-hour hitch materialised. Today, in a CQN EXCLUSIVE extract from Davie Hay’s autobiography, ‘The Quiet Assassin’, co-authored by Alex Gordon, we reveal [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: PROBLEM PILE-UP IN PARADISE: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Fourteen)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-problem-pile-up-in-paradise-the-tommy-burns-story-part-fourteen/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-problem-pile-up-in-paradise-the-tommy-burns-story-part-fourteen/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-25T04:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE third year of Tommy Burns’ managerial career at Celtic was not going according to plan. The fans’ favourite had returned to the club on July 12 1994 and had won the Scottish Cup in his debut campaign. That was followed by a barren term and all eyes were on the boss as a new [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reaction to Celtic 2-0 Norwich // Michael Johnston rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.jerseydoesntshrink.com/2022/7/24/23276670/reaction-to-celtic-2-0-norwich-michael-johnston-rumours</id>
        <link href="https://www.jerseydoesntshrink.com/2022/7/24/23276670/reaction-to-celtic-2-0-norwich-michael-johnston-rumours"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T22:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Mikolaj Barbanell/SOPA Images/LightRocket via Getty Images
  

 Yesterday was, thankfully, the last pre season game we’ll be involved in before regular blogs during the season that will be 22-23, and it’s Aberdeen at Celtic Park next weekend.
At long last.
If you missed Daizen Maeda and David Turnbull putting Norwich to the sword, as well as the general highlights, here they are below:

Reaction to the comfortable victory was covered on 67HH too!

Earlier tonight, we had rumours (and that’s all they are) developing regarding Michael Johnston being SHIPPED OUT on loan to Ronald Deila’s Standard Liege. 


Rumours Mikey Johnston off to @Standard_RSCL on loan.— Celticunderground (@celticrumours) July 24, 2022



Would definitely be the best thing for his career, and well within Celtic’s interests to see him getting regular games at another club, so hopefully this isn’t yet another lie from a Twitter account and it actually has a bit of weight to it in the coming days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s Joe Hart reflects on banishing “danger, danger” thoughts as sweeper-keeper during pre-season unlike any in memory]]></title>
        <id>3780033</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtics-joe-hart-reflects-on-banishing-danger-danger-thoughts-as-sweeper-keeper-during-pre-season-unlike-any-in-memory-3780033"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic players simply aren’t allowed to get too snug under Ange Postecoglou.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart reveals Ange Postecoglou's message to Celtic squad ahead of new season]]></title>
        <id>085f553abd71c61002be5641dcdbccfb</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20452422.joe-hart-reveals-ange-postecoglous-message-celtic-squad-ahead-new-season/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART insists that Celtic are ready for the new campaign to begin ahead of Aberdeen’s visit to Parkhead on Sunday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart insists he can hit new heights further up the park for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>5e48b410c448ed256e744ea3f16e2a3b</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20452307.joe-hart-insists-can-hit-new-heights-park-celtic/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT can take a little time to get to grips with Ange Postecoglou’s vision, Joe Hart admits. The Celtic goalkeeper, who recorded a clean sheet in the team’s final pre-season outing against Norwich City on Saturday, has been working under the Greek-Australian for almost a year to the day, yet it’s only now that he feels he fully understands the role his manager wants him to play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend Scott Brown eagerly anticipating managerial debut after five months without matchday buzz]]></title>
        <id>869b80079591c84ae9b5d987d9af22da</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20449874.celtic-legend-scott-brown-eagerly-anticipating-managerial-debut-five-months-without-matchday-buzz/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SCOTT BROWN says he is eagerly anticipating his competitive managerial bow after almost five months missing a matchday buzz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda reveals why he rejected Celtic move last summer - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEBEj3jmDblP4WdgOE78R7AwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4KKJCzCv9JoDMICkoAY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2022/07/24/daizen-maeda-rejected-celtic-move/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T21:06:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda reveals why he rejected Celtic move last summer  The Celtic Bhoys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer state of play on Stephen Welsh, Christopher Jullien, Fausto Vera and Ryan Mmaee - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>1510766726</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/celtic-transfer-state-play-stephen-27565494"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T20:44:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer state of play on Stephen Welsh, Christopher Jullien, Fausto Vera and Ryan Mmaee  Daily Record
Celtic: £20k-a-week star 'still has interest' at Parkhead  GIVEMESPORT
Ange Postecoglou's Celtic transfer update as boss explains 'right one' plan  Celtic Way
Report claims Celtic are not pursuing a striker as it stands  The Celtic Star
View Full coverage on Google News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mikey Johnston linked with move to Ronny Delia’s Standard Liege]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/mikey-johnston-linked-with-move-to-ronny-delias-standard-liege/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/mikey-johnston-linked-with-move-to-ronny-delias-standard-liege/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T20:39:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The big rumour this evening centres around Mikey Johnston who was not involved in either the first team yesterday for the match against Norwich City or the Celtic B Team opener against Cowdenbeath. Maybe that’s what started the gossip but the Celtic Rumours account is suggesting this evening that Mikey Johnston could be on his Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda reveals why he initially turned Celtic down; how Ange convinced him]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/daizen-maeda-reveals-why-he-initially-turned-celtic-down-how-ange-convinced-him/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/daizen-maeda-reveals-why-he-initially-turned-celtic-down-how-ange-convinced-him/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T20:11:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic forward Daizen Maeda has given an extensive interview to Japanese sports magazine Number about his move from Yokohama F.Marinos, international career and experiences of living in Glasgow. Maeda moved from Japan to Scotland back in January and became an instant hit with Celtic supporters. His aggressive pressing and speed, as well as a few ...
The post Daizen Maeda reveals why he initially turned Celtic down; how Ange convinced him appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Karamoko Dembele in post Celtic Golden Boy nomination as he makes final shortlist with 20 MINUTES of football - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEEgf8bdwITjKvUgHalr-nNUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/karamoko-dembele-post-celtic-golden-27565339"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T19:58:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Karamoko Dembele in post Celtic Golden Boy nomination as he makes final shortlist with 20 MINUTES of football  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fran Alonso gives huge update after Glasgow Cup defeat]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/fran-alonso-gives-huge-update-after-glasgow-cup-defeat/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/fran-alonso-gives-huge-update-after-glasgow-cup-defeat/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T19:36:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A little bit of football history was made today when the Glasgow Cup was played for for the first time in the Women’s game with Celtic taking on theRangers at the Penny Cars stadium in Airdrie. The Celtic squad has looked a little sparse this pre-season with five players leaving the club, only a few Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic&#039;s £20m budget and the quest for Champions League credibility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/celtics-20m-budget-and-the-quest-for-champions-league-credibility/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/celtics-20m-budget-and-the-quest-for-champions-league-credibility/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This season, Celtic enter the Champions League group stage automatically for the first time in 13 years and with it, gain the associated financial benefits of guaranteed European revenue. It’s a luxury the club have had to operate without in recent years, operating speculatively when it comes to transfers so as not to be left ...
The post Celtic&#039;s £20m budget and the quest for Champions League credibility appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manager cites Turnbull example to explain why teenager rejected Celtic move]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/manager-cites-turnbull-example-to-explain-why-teenager-rejected-celtic-move/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/manager-cites-turnbull-example-to-explain-why-teenager-rejected-celtic-move/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[St Mirren manager Stephen Robinson has explained why starlet Dylan Reid rebuked a move to Celtic in favour of staying with the Paisley club. A fee was agreed between the two clubs but the 17-year-old rejected the move to prioritise first-team football. As reported by the Daily Record, Robinson said: “I don’t know the finances ...
The post Manager cites Turnbull example to explain why teenager rejected Celtic move appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers claim first-ever City of Glasgow Women's Cup with win over Celtic]]></title>
        <id>df3c22546bce8d1f1dafda307a189449</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20450788.rangers-claim-first-ever-city-glasgow-womens-cup-win-celtic/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T18:06:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RANGERS, who were knocked out of the League Cup and Scottish Cup by Celtic last season, beat their oldest rivals 2-1 to win the first-ever City of Glasgow Women's Cup match at the Excelsior Stadium yesterday. Although Rangers captain Nicola Docherty was presented with the new trophy the game was billed as a showpiece occasion and the competition proper won't start until next pre-season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big calls to be made: The Ange Postecoglou Celtic selection debates vs Aberdeen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/big-calls-to-be-made-the-ange-postecoglou-celtic-selection-debates-vs-aberdeen/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/big-calls-to-be-made-the-ange-postecoglou-celtic-selection-debates-vs-aberdeen/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following a successful and often surprisingly competitive pre-season, Celtic begin the defence of their Scottish Premiership title this coming Sunday at home to Aberdeen. The club have signed six players so far this transfer window – seven if including the obligatory signing of Daizen Maeda from Yokohama F. Marinos, leaving the manager with a deeper ...
The post Big calls to be made: The Ange Postecoglou Celtic selection debates vs Aberdeen appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big calls to be made: The Ange Postecoglou Celtic selection debates vs Aberdeen - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEJvh0Jd5wq4Ss3rbh7Z_pU0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMLbFpgY</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/big-calls-to-be-made-the-ange-postecoglou-celtic-selection-debates-vs-aberdeen/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Big calls to be made: The Ange Postecoglou Celtic selection debates vs Aberdeen  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moritz is fully aware of the pressures playing for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/moritz-is-fully-aware/</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/moritz-is-fully-aware/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T17:39:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The loan with option to buy market has proved to be a successful transfer option so far under the guidance of Ange Postecoglou.  Three first team regulars in Carter-Vickers, Maeda and of course Jota all arrived at Celtic Park. With an option to buy clause at the start of their deal. Latest loan signing Moritz is […]
The post Moritz is fully aware of the pressures playing for Celtic appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Celtic encouragement for Toulouse on Welsh move but Jullien’s a different story]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/no-celtic-encouragement-for-toulouse-on-welsh-move-but-julliens-a-different-story/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/no-celtic-encouragement-for-toulouse-on-welsh-move-but-julliens-a-different-story/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T17:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[French Ligue 1 side Toulouse have made an approach to Celtic to sign our Scotland Under 21 captain Stephen Welsh but have not been given any encouragement from Celtic. The defender, who started in the 2-0 win over Norwich City on Saturday, is part of Ange Postecoglou’s plans for the new season and last year Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[&#039;I&#039;m sure...&#039; - Celtic backed to win transfer race for 23 y/o gem who Mourinho dubbed &#039;amazing&#039;]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-spl-japhet-tanganga-transfer-news-updates/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-spl-japhet-tanganga-transfer-news-updates/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T17:05:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic could pip other clubs to the signing of Tottenham youngster Japhet Tanganga this summer, according to former Scottish top-flight striker Noel Whelan. The Lowdown: Tanganga linked with Celtic Ange Postecoglou may still be eyeing up new signings ahead of the new Premiership season as he looks to make his squad even more formidable. One […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed difficult but thrilling week ahead of first Rangers derby]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-handed-difficult-but-thrilling-week-ahead-of-first-derby/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-handed-difficult-but-thrilling-week-ahead-of-first-derby/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T16:42:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic face a difficult week of action in late August and early September after the draw for the second round of the Scottish League Cup was confirmed this evening. The Bhoys will be travelling to Dingwall to face Ross County away from home on Wednesday 31st August in the tournament, just three days before the ...
The post Celtic handed difficult but thrilling week ahead of first Rangers derby appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed difficult but thrilling week ahead of first derby - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEF_zyfquESmkhpqHf1BUtc4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMLbFpgY</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-handed-difficult-but-thrilling-week-ahead-of-first-derby/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T16:42:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed difficult but thrilling week ahead of first derby  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clean sheet coincides with Cameron Carter-Vickers no complacency assertion]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/clean-sheet-coincides-with-cameron-carter-vickers-no-complacency-assertion/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/clean-sheet-coincides-with-cameron-carter-vickers-no-complacency-assertion/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T16:35:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic sailed to victory over Norwich City this weekend in a very comfortable display. However, one thing that was crucial to the victory was only the second clean sheet we’ve kept this pre-season during friendly matches. The Hoops have been prone to second half collapses in regards to the backline of late, causing some concern Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DINGWALL TEST FOR HOLDERS CELTIC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/dingwall-test-for-holders-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/dingwall-test-for-holders-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T16:09:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC will start the defence of their Premier Sports League Cup with a tricky second round draw against Ross County in Dingwall. Ange Postecoglou’s holders will travel to the Highlands next month, a venue where they won both their Premiership outings last season. It took a goal from Anthony Ralston deep in stoppage time to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Draw Ross County in League Cup]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-draw-ross-county-in-league-cup/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-draw-ross-county-in-league-cup/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T16:06:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have today found out they will begin the defence of their League Cup trophy against Ross County away from home The bhoys won the competition in December last year, coming from a goal behind against Hibernian to win the game 2-1. An injured Kyogo played the game and made the difference with a brace […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confirmed – Celtic face Dingwall test in League Cup defence]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/confirmed-celtic-face-dingwall-test-in-league-cup-defence/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/confirmed-celtic-face-dingwall-test-in-league-cup-defence/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T16:04:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been drawn to face Ross County in the second round of the League Cup. Following Aberdeen’s win over Raith Rovers today, Ange Postecoglou and his team discovered who they would face in their defence of the Premier Sports Cup. It means that the Celtic support will need to travel to the Highlands on Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premier Sports Cup draw: Celtic and Hearts handed Premiership ties as Rangers host League One side]]></title>
        <id>3780029</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/premier-sports-cup-draw-celtic-and-hearts-handed-premiership-ties-as-rangers-host-league-one-side-3780029"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T16:04:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The draw has been made for the last-16 of the Premier Sports Cup with Celtic’s trip to Ross County and Aberdeen facing Annan Athletic the stand-out ties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premier Sports Cup second round draw in full]]></title>
        <id>c9c141511ceea9559782f3e772a2e2df</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20447343.premier-sports-cup-second-round-draw-full/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T16:02:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers vs Queen of the South]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed away trip to Ross County in Premier Sports Cup second round]]></title>
        <id>3ab6ebdfb3951aa4b54d32475bf2b645</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20447298.celtic-handed-away-trip-ross-county-premier-sports-cup-second-round/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T16:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have been handed a trip tie to Dingwall in the Premier Sports Cup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Years Ago Ibrox Ignored COVID Protocols. They’ve Been Out Of Control Ever Since.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/two-years-ago-ibrox-ignored-covid-protocols-theyve-been-out-of-control-ever-since/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/two-years-ago-ibrox-ignored-covid-protocols-theyve-been-out-of-control-ever-since/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T15:59:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two years ago in May, the Ibrox board attempted to bring down Scottish football’s second top governing body, that of the SPFL. The whole game could have been plunged into anarchy as a result of it. But much worse followed two months later. In July of 2020, Scottish football was still struggling with exactly how […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Soul Podcast Returns]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-soul-podcast-returns/</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-soul-podcast-returns/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T15:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic Soul Podcast returns on audio across all platforms and on Celtic Fanzine TV on YouTube. With Celtic continuing to prepare for the new season. https://celticfanzine.com/product/annual-magazine-subscription/ Celtic FC manager, Ange Postecoglou talks about the Tommy Burns Play. While Jota chats about his permanent move to Celtic. Glasgow Poet Erin Boyle joins host Andrew Milne […]
The post Celtic Soul Podcast Returns appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Premier League level’ – Norwich boss Dean Smith praises Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/premier-league-level-norwich-boss-dean-smith-praises-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/premier-league-level-norwich-boss-dean-smith-praises-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T15:53:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Norwich City boss Dean Smith watched on from the sidelines at Parkhead on Saturday afternoon as Ange Postecoglou’s men out his team to the sword. In what was a convincing victory for the lads in green and white, Celtic’s movement and all-round play was too much for the Championship outfit and Smith was effusive in Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 talking points as Aberdeen blow away Raith in final Celtic tune up - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiECzfI3u1c3Hd1nlEAaNfXxYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/3-talking-points-aberdeen-blow-27563425"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T15:50:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[3 talking points as Aberdeen blow away Raith in final Celtic tune up  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Son of former Celtic hero gives insight on Jordan Larsson pressure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/son-of-former-celtic-hero-gives-insight-on-jordan-larsson-pressure/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/son-of-former-celtic-hero-gives-insight-on-jordan-larsson-pressure/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The son of former Celtic hero Johan Mjallby has spoken of the pressure that Jordan Larsson would have felt if he had signed for Celtic. Timothy Mjallby was a youth player at the club whilst his father was assistant manager to the first team, and grew up alongside Jordan. Speaking to The Celtic Way, Mjallby ...
The post Son of former Celtic hero gives insight on Jordan Larsson pressure appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic 1-2 Rangers - Rangers Football Club]]></title>
        <id>CBMiUmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnJhbmdlcnMuY28udWsvYXJ0aWNsZS9yZXBvcnQtY2VsdGljLTEtMi1yYW5nZXJzLzdzcVc0MHh2NVVkbnNWeDdQdVNjY3rSAQA</id>
        <link href="https://www.rangers.co.uk/article/report-celtic-1-2-rangers/7sqW40xv5UdnsVx7PuSccz"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T15:14:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic 1-2 Rangers  Rangers Football Club]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scott McDonald details Harry Kewell traits that will help Celtic; talks up "steal" transfer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/scott-mcdonald-details-harry-kewell-traits-that-will-help-celtic-talks-up-steal-transfer/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/scott-mcdonald-details-harry-kewell-traits-that-will-help-celtic-talks-up-steal-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic star Scott McDonald this week told 67 Hail Hail of his joy at two new Australians joining their fellow countryman Ange Postecoglou at the club this close season. The club recruited Socceroos legend Harry Kewell as a first-team coach and signed current international midfielder Aaron Mooy on a two-year deal after his release ...
The post Scott McDonald details Harry Kewell traits that will help Celtic; talks up "steal" transfer appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premier Sports Cup second round draw RECAP: Rangers play QotS as Celtic face trip to Ross County]]></title>
        <id>c6de4d17e8b62b801e0ab8c6f9ab6d74</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20445233.premier-sports-cup-second-round-draw-recap-rangers-play-qots-celtic-face-trip-ross-county/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T15:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE Premier Sports Cup second round draw takes place this afternoon. Scottish Premiership clubs Celtic, Rangers, Hearts, Dundee United and Motherwell all enter the competition alongside the 11 progressing sides from the group stage. The eight group winners will advance with the three best runner ups also included in the last 16 draw which takes place at the conclusion of Aberdeen against Raith Rovers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toulouse make Stephen Welsh Celtic transfer 'enquiry' over summer move]]></title>
        <id>723eee20280c56154802bd2786e817a6</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20443697.toulouse-make-stephen-welsh-celtic-transfer-enquiry-summer-move/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T14:40:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FRENCH side Toulouse have reportedly made a transfer enquiry to Celtic over the availability of Stephen Welsh.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ligue 1 club make contact with Celtic on 22-year-old star but Bhoys stand firm]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/ligue-1-club-make-enquiry-for-celtic-defender-but-bhoys-stand-firm/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/ligue-1-club-make-enquiry-for-celtic-defender-but-bhoys-stand-firm/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T14:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[French club Toulouse have made an enquiry on the availability of Celtic defender Stephen Welsh, Sky Sports have reported this afternoon. Toulouse are preparing for a season in Ligue 1 having gained promotion as second-tier winners last season. The broadcaster believes Celtic are unwilling to sell as Ange Postecoglou considers Welsh to be part of ...
The post Ligue 1 club make contact with Celtic on 22-year-old star but Bhoys stand firm appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[French Side Make Celtic Defender Enquiry]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/french-side-make-celtic-defender-enquiry/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/french-side-make-celtic-defender-enquiry/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T14:14:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to reports, Celtic Defender Stephen Welsh is the subject to interest from French side Toulouse. However, the Scottish Champions don’t want to sell their defender. Sky Sports journalist Anthony Joseph claims the French side is keen on the Hoops academy player and this is the second but of interest from a side in Europe. […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou&#039;s 60-game Celtic plan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglous-60-game-celtic-plan/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglous-60-game-celtic-plan/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou has emphasised the need for Celtic to have a deeper squad this coming season. The Australian had to make do with shallow pool for much of last season, significantly bolstering it in the January transfer window after relying heavily on a select few players for the first half of the season. ...
The post Ange Postecoglou&#039;s 60-game Celtic plan appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are clear title favourites, Rangers need 'something very special to stop them', claims Parkhead hero]]></title>
        <id>57f91d8c9fb262eb9e9020fb37abe20d</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20441779.celtic-clear-title-favourites-rangers-need--something-special-stop-them-claims-parkhead-hero/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T13:27:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KENNY DALGLISH reckons Celtic are clear favourites for the Scottish Premiership title this season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate responds to hearing his latest Celtic song yesterday; states season intent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/reo-hatate-responds-to-hearing-his-latest-celtic-song-yesterday-states-season-intent/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/reo-hatate-responds-to-hearing-his-latest-celtic-song-yesterday-states-season-intent/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T13:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate was delighted to hear the love of the Celtic support yesterday, with the latest song dedicated to him given an airing throughout the 90 minutes. Fans have repurposed Scooter’s tune ‘Weekend’ to make it all about Hatate with lyrics along the line of: “Hey oh, Reo Hatate, the Celtic get excited when we ...
The post Reo Hatate responds to hearing his latest Celtic song yesterday; states season intent appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scotland’s Gutter Rag Tries To Drag Celtic Fans Into Our Rival’s Latest Cesspit.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/scotlands-gutter-rag-tries-to-drag-celtic-fans-into-our-rivals-latest-cesspit/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/scotlands-gutter-rag-tries-to-drag-celtic-fans-into-our-rivals-latest-cesspit/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T12:56:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You have to hand it to the media; they know how to dredge the gutter. Especially those papers which perennially operate from there. We all know that The Sun is the one most football fans associate with that gutter. It is no surprise to find their Scottish rag swimming in the sewer this morning with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scotland’s Gutter Rag Tries To Drag Celtic Fans Into Our Rival’s Latest Cesspit. - TheCelticBlog.com]]></title>
        <id>CAIiELEBncHjntFKfTiUjosow5EqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowne-jCzDg-bsDMLnLhQc</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/scotlands-gutter-rag-tries-to-drag-celtic-fans-into-our-rivals-latest-cesspit/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T12:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scotland’s Gutter Rag Tries To Drag Celtic Fans Into Our Rival’s Latest Cesspit.  TheCelticBlog.com]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report – Excellent pre-season has Celtic peaking at the perfect time]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/report-excellent-pre-season-has-celtic-peaking-at-the-perfect-time/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/report-excellent-pre-season-has-celtic-peaking-at-the-perfect-time/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T12:51:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After yesterday’s 2-0 win at Parkhead against Norwich City completed what has been an excellent pre-season for Celtic in many different ways, I thought I would give a bit of a synopsis regards the main things we can take away from the past few weeks. In the six matches we have played during our pre-season Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Celtic were labelled 'Premier League team in the making' by Norwich City boss]]></title>
        <id>3779940</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/why-celtic-were-labelled-premier-league-team-in-the-making-by-norwich-city-boss-3779940"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T12:46:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Norwich City boss Dean Smith labelled Celtic a “Premier League team in the making” after seeing his side go down 2-0 to the Scottish champions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One pundit unafraid to back Celtic over Rangers in title race]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kenny-dalglish-gives-celtic-title-advantage-over-rivals/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kenny-dalglish-gives-celtic-title-advantage-over-rivals/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Dalglish has backed Celtic to maintain their dominance in Scotland by bringing the league title home for a second consecutive season. The Celtic legend believes that the Scottish champions have added significantly to the squad that wrestled the title back from Rangers last season, and this will be the difference in next season’s Premiership ...
The post One pundit unafraid to back Celtic over Rangers in title race appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carl Starfelt fitness update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/carl-starfelt-fitness-update/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/carl-starfelt-fitness-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T12:28:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday Celtic ran out 2-0 winners against Dean Smith’s Norwich City, in what was a comprehensive and controlled performance from start to finish. A composed low strike from David Turnbull added to a delicious back heel flick from Daizen Maeda in the first half of the game. Although the score was 2-0 it wasn’t really Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["They are very good"; Norwich midfielder talks up Celtic quality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/they-are-very-good-norwich-midfielder-talks-up-celtic-quality/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/they-are-very-good-norwich-midfielder-talks-up-celtic-quality/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Aberdeen midfielder Kenny McLean has suggested that Celtic wouldn’t struggle in the Premier League following Norwich’s 2-0 pre-season defeat in Paradise yesterday. The Scotland international made the move south in 2018 and has played in the Premier League across two promotions and subsequent relegations with the Canaries. As reported by Eastern Daily Press, he ...
The post "They are very good"; Norwich midfielder talks up Celtic quality appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic hero gets the last laugh after hostile return to Scotland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-hero-gets-the-last-laugh-after-hostile-return-to-scotland/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-hero-gets-the-last-laugh-after-hostile-return-to-scotland/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic hero Fraser Forster laughed off a hostile Rangers reception yesterday as the Englishman helped Tottenham Hotspur secure a 2-1 friendly win at Ibrox. The ex-Celtic keeper joined the Lilywhites in the summer after eight years at Southampton, with a brief return to Glasgow intersecting his time on the south coast. As reported by ...
The post Former Celtic hero gets the last laugh after hostile return to Scotland appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Once Again, Celtic Fans Need To Remind Keevins Readers That He Takes Them For Mugs.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/once-again-celtic-fans-need-to-remind-keevins-readers-that-he-takes-them-for-mugs/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/once-again-celtic-fans-need-to-remind-keevins-readers-that-he-takes-them-for-mugs/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T11:19:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Know what I find infuriating about some of what you read in the Scottish media on a daily basis? The implied insult to the audience. There are people in it who sit there in front of their word processors and know that what they are writing is total nonsense, but they do it anyway. They […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Once Again, Celtic Fans Need To Remind Keevins Readers That He Takes Them For Mugs. - TheCelticBlog.com]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEMD30D9MXylqvh0nrtBrTFIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowne-jCzDg-bsDMLnLhQc</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/once-again-celtic-fans-need-to-remind-keevins-readers-that-he-takes-them-for-mugs/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T11:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once Again, Celtic Fans Need To Remind Keevins Readers That He Takes Them For Mugs.  TheCelticBlog.com]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Rogic Accidentally Photobombs Global Celeb]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/tom-rogic-accidentally-photobombs-global-celeb/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/tom-rogic-accidentally-photobombs-global-celeb/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T11:18:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOM ROGIC has been keeping off the grid since he left Celtic in the summer. The Hoops midfielder spent almost ten years in Glasgow and was part of some famous Celtic sides. His goal in the invincible treble Scottish Cup final is stretched into the very fabric of Celtic’s history. It’s little wonder the Australian […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The big winners from Celtic&#039;s pre-season; 3 more left with uncertain futures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-big-winners-from-celtics-pre-season-3-more-left-with-uncertain-futures/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-big-winners-from-celtics-pre-season-3-more-left-with-uncertain-futures/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic rounded off their pre-season yesterday with a comfortable 2-0 win over Championship side Norwich City in Paradise. It marked the end of a highly competitive set of friendlies, allowing manager Ange Postecoglou ample opportunity to assess his squad ahead of the new season. Here are the players who impressed, and those who really could ...
The post The big winners from Celtic&#039;s pre-season; 3 more left with uncertain futures appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Louis Tomlinson photobombed by Celtic icon as Parkhead fans pick out 'real superstar' in airport pic - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEBhuZo1S8GseI3hg-p-cGsAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/louis-tomlinson-photobombed-celtic-icon-27562535"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T11:04:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Louis Tomlinson photobombed by Celtic icon as Parkhead fans pick out 'real superstar' in airport pic  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opponent left impressed by Ange Postecoglou&#039;s Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglous-celtic-given-ringing-endorsement-by-impressed-opponent/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglous-celtic-given-ringing-endorsement-by-impressed-opponent/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Norwich City boss Dean Smith has offered a ringing endorsement of Ange Postecoglou’s Celtic after the Canaries’ 2-0 defeat at Parkhead yesterday. Celtic saw rounded off their pre-season with a goal in each half from Daizen Maeda and David Turnbull, to secure a farily comfortable win against the recently relegated Championship side. As reported by ...
The post Opponent left impressed by Ange Postecoglou&#039;s Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Refutes Starting XI Decision]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/ange-refutes-starting-xi-decision/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/ange-refutes-starting-xi-decision/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T10:26:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou was asked if the Celtic starting XI vs Norwich on Saturday was indicative of what we can expect from the lineup next Sunday against Aberdeen. The overwhelming thought is Ange decided to play the team he believes should start Celtic’s first SPFL game of the season and gave them all around 60 minutes […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dean Smith in Celtic confession as Angeball leaves Norwich City boss purring over Hatate and Co - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>1509487128</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/dean-smith-celtic-confession-angeball-27562260"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T10:18:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dean Smith in Celtic confession as Angeball leaves Norwich City boss purring over Hatate and Co  Daily Record
Hatate the highlight again as Bhoys beat Canaries; Full verdict on Celtic win  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News
Celtic 2-0 Norwich City – Watch the Goals plus all post match reaction from both clubs  The Celtic Star
Highlights: Celtic FC 2-0 Norwich City in Friendly Game 2022  VAVEL.com
Celtic v Norwich City: Starting line ups confirmed  PinkUn
View Full coverage on Google News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premier Sports Cup draw: where to watch, TV and live stream details]]></title>
        <id>9288bf47da6892e310e0de2c825e1396</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20302446.premier-sports-cup-draw-watch-tv-live-stream-details/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T09:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE draw for the last 16 of the Premier Sports Cup will take place on Sunday as the Premiership's big hitters enter the competition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What channel is the Premier Sports Cup last-16 draw? How to watch & when as Celtic, Hearts & Rangers involved]]></title>
        <id>3779854</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/what-channel-is-the-premier-sports-cup-last-16-draw-how-to-watch-when-as-celtic-hearts-rangers-involved-3779854"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T09:35:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Premier Sports Group stages will come to a conclusion this afternoon when Aberdeen host Raith Rovers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dalglish, Boyd and McGhee differ over Celtic and Rangers title chances - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEAmz9jaopxK2ZNGdb7Uo4HwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/celtic-rangers-win-scottish-premiership-27561928"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T08:49:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dalglish, Boyd and McGhee differ over Celtic and Rangers title chances  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC HERO LAUGHS OFF IBROX JEERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-hero-laughs-off-ibrox-jeers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-hero-laughs-off-ibrox-jeers/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T08:36:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic keeper Fraser Forster LAUGHED OFF the boos and jeers that were directed at him during Spurs’ 2-1 win at Ibrox yesterday. The one-time Hoops fans’ favourite, who joined the London club in the summer as a free agent after leaving Southampton, received a hostile reception as he replaced Hugo Lloris in the second-half. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou: Team has benefited from full pre-season]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/ange-postecoglou-team-has-benefited-from-full-pre-season/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/ange-postecoglou-team-has-benefited-from-full-pre-season/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T08:26:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou spoke to Celtic TV after the Norwich City game today and was please at both the result and the manner in which it was achieved. Celtic played Blackburn Rovers last weekend at home and let the Championship outift survive the game with some questionable defending at the time. Likewise, Legia Warsaw in midweek Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Norwich Boss Dean Smith Delivers Classy Celtic Verdict]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/norwich-boss-dean-smith-delivers-classy-celtic-verdict/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/norwich-boss-dean-smith-delivers-classy-celtic-verdict/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T08:10:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Norwich boss Dean Smith heaped praise on Celtic after watching his side fall to a 2-0 defeat at Celtic Park. The Canaries came to town for the Hoops final pre-season game before the real stuff starts next weekend. The Bhoys looked comfortable and dominated proceedings. Goals from Daizen Maeda and David Turnbull were enough to […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HAPPY HATATE AND THE SONGS OF PRAISE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/happy-hatate-and-the-songs-of-praise/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/happy-hatate-and-the-songs-of-praise/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T08:04:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE admits the Celtic fans singing a song in his honour was music to his ears. The 24-year-old Japanese midfielder caught the eye again with his performance in the 2-0 pre-season win over English Championship side Norwich City at Parkhead yesterday. Hatate put in his usual industrious shift allied with some subtle and skilful [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mooy can be Celtic great just like Rogic says Gavin Rae]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/mooy-can-be-celtic-great-just-like-rogic-says-gavin-rae/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/mooy-can-be-celtic-great-just-like-rogic-says-gavin-rae/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T08:03:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy arrived at Celtic Park this past week and was received by a mixed reaction for the most part over whether he can still deliver at the top level of the game. The ex-Huddersfield midfielder spent the past while in the Chinese Super League and has been shy of match day experience since January Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fraser Forster given hostile reception on return to Glasgow]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/fraser-forster-given-hostile-reception-on-return-to-glasgow/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/fraser-forster-given-hostile-reception-on-return-to-glasgow/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T07:39:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fraser Forster returned to Glasgow this afternoon with Antonio Conte’s Tottenham Hotspur side to take on Giovanni van Bronkhorst and his new-look Ibrox squad. The big stopper signed on the dotted line for Daniel Levy after he became a free agent this summer, as his mammoth financial contract with Southampton finally came to an end. Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carl Starfelt Celtic Return Timeline]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/carl-starfelt-celtic-return-timeline/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/carl-starfelt-celtic-return-timeline/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has provided a major update on Celtic’s biggest injury concern going into the new season. Carl Starfelt has been out injured since being stretchered off for Sweden during the summer. The Celtic defender’s first full cap for his country ended prematurely. Since then, Carl has been fighting back from injury and working with […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whatever happened to Celtic youngster Timothy Mjallby? | Celtic Way - Celtic Way]]></title>
        <id>CBMiXWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmNlbHRpY3dheS5jby51ay9uZXdzLzIwMjk3MzcxLndoYXRldmVyLWhhcHBlbmVkLWNlbHRpYy15b3VuZ3N0ZXItdGltb3RoeS1tamFsbGJ5L9IBAA</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticway.co.uk/news/20297371.whatever-happened-celtic-youngster-timothy-mjallby/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T06:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whatever happened to Celtic youngster Timothy Mjallby? | Celtic Way  Celtic Way]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: COLLINS EXIT – AND TARGET THAT GOT AWAY: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Thirteen)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-collins-exit-and-target-that-got-away-the-tommy-burns-story-part-thirteen/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-collins-exit-and-target-that-got-away-the-tommy-burns-story-part-thirteen/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T06:25:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS was preparing for his third year in charge of Celtic since returning as manager on July 12 1994. A Scottish Cup had been won in his first campaign in the dug-out, but the following term had seen the team fail on the domestic and European fronts. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE series, we chart [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REO GRAND AS ANGE PRAISES ENTIRE SQUAD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/reo-grand-as-ange-praises-entire-squad/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/reo-grand-as-ange-praises-entire-squad/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T06:10:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE is eager to deliver on his promises and the silky midfielder was outstanding in the 2-0 win over Norwich City in the final work-out before the action kicks off a week today. The Japanese international made a breathtaking first impression after joining the Hoops on Hogmanay along with his J-League colleagues Daizen Maeda [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where would Scottish Women's Cup moving to SFA leave SWF? - Alan Campbell]]></title>
        <id>35de405d5d212bd395374a7f0025757f</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20381519.scottish-womens-cup-moving-sfa-leave-swf---alan-campbell/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC'S first-ever Scottish Women's Cup success in May could be one of the last under the auspices of Scottish Women's Football. I understand senior figures at the Scottish FA are keen to bring the national knock out competition into their portfolio.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Rangers and Celtic hunch tells me the game of title pass the parcel is set to continue - Hugh Keevins - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEB1XUUmPtvhls-wUt46akLEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/rangers-celtic-hunch-tells-game-27559664"/>
        <updated>2022-07-24T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My Rangers and Celtic hunch tells me the game of title pass the parcel is set to continue - Hugh Keevins  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>