<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-12-29T22:09:48.136Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diminished Returns]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58583</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/diminished-returns/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T15:57:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dropped points at home and away along with the confirmation of our European wooden spoon wasn’t exactly the start to the festive season we were hoping for. The banning of the green brigade and growing discontent around the lack of ambition from the board doesn’t exactly scream ‘unified front’. Thankfully the Ultras are back […]
The post Diminished Returns appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CCV OUT, GREEN LIGHT FOR WELSH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115826</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ccv-out-green-light-for-welsh/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T15:19:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[STEPHEN WELSH is set to partner Liam Scales in the heart of the Celtic defence in the derby encounter at Parkhead tomorrow. Cameron Carter-Vickers, who limped off early in the second-half of the 3-0 win over Dundee on Boxing Day, is ruled out of the visit from Philippe Clement’s Ibrox side. Welsh came on at [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton senses Celtic tactical switch from Brendan Rodgers vs Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184833</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/chris-sutton-senses-celtic-tactical-switch-from-brendan-rodgers-vs-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker Chris Sutton is intrigued by what the Bhoys’ attack will look like against Rangers in this weekend’s derby, suggesting there could be...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: SEISMIC SWITCH? DON’T MAKE ME LAUGH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115824</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-seismic-switch-dont-make-me-laugh/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T13:01:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FOLK who really should know a lot better have been wittering on about “a seismic shift” in power in Glasgow in recent weeks. That observation is as hysterical as it is hilarious. There has also been talk from a former player of “a little bit of panic” setting in over in the east end of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers' big message to Celtic dressing room ahead of Rangers derby]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184830</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-big-message-to-celtic-dressing-room-ahead-of-rangers-derby/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T12:36:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s final game of 2023 is also one of the biggest of the calendar year – a derby at home to Rangers amidst a fully-ignited...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic must beware arbitrary red card]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115821</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-must-beware-arbitrary-red-card/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T12:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We go into tomorrow’s top of the table clash in better form than we were at the start of the month.  Wins over Livingston and Dundee give Celtic a platform to build on.  These games coincided with a consistency of selection in central midfield; Paulo Bernardo filled the endlessly changed slot in central midfield and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NOT PAYING THE PENALTY: OPEN SEASON ON CELTS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115804</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/not-paying-the-penalty-open-season-on-celts/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T08:57:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CAMERON CARTER-VICKERS must have thought he was involved in a wrestling tag-team event against Dundee in midweek. The Celtic central defender positioned himself on the goal-line in front of keeper Trevor Carson at corner-kicks which is an action which is perfectly legal. The Dens No.1, like every other netminder in football, hardly welcomed the intrusion – [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO AND THE JOY OF SIX]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115036</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kyogo-and-the-joy-of-six-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T07:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO FURUHASHI had to wait until January 2 this year to claim his first goal against Ibrox opposition. The Japanese international striker fired blanks against Celtic’s city foes – then managed by Steven Gerrard – when he made his derby debut in Govan on August 29 2021,  just under a month after his £4.6million arrival [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS v RANGERS (Part Six)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115778</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-v-rangers-part-six/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T06:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS got the Glasgow derby-winning show on the road again when he masterminded the 1-0 triumph at Ibrox on September 3. Following 10 victories, two draws and a solitary loss in his first stint, the Irishman returned to the fixture for the first time following an absence of over four and a half years [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS v RANGERS (Part Five)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111583</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-v-rangers-part-five/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T06:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS was all smiles in September when he watched Kyogo Furuhashi fire a spectacular volley behind Jack Butland to seal Celtic’s derby win at Ibrox – and mark the second time-around Hoops manager’s return to the fixture after an absence of over four and a half years. The 50-year-old Irishman enjoyed phenomenal success against the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…AMIDO BALDE?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=108616</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-amido-balde/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T05:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMIDO BALDE turned out to be another spectacular waste of money for Celtic after he signed for £1.2million from Portuguese outfit Vitoria Guimaraes in June 2013. The towering 22-year-old striker came highly recommended to Neil Lennon after making the breakthrough with his nation’s Under-21 squad the previous year. However, blundering Balde netted a mere three [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Where are they?': Chris Sutton baffled by what has happened to Celtic duo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184815</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-baffled-by-what-has-happened-to-gustaf-lagerbielke-and-maik-nawrocki-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Where are Gustaf Lagerbielke and Maik Nawrocki?  That’s a question Chris Sutton wants the answer to as the duo were absent for Celtic once again...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Sore head': Scott Brown suggests Celtic fringe player could now start against Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184793</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/scott-brown-drops-interesting-selection-claim-about-mikey-johnston-ahead-of-celtic-v-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just when you thought the end was near for Mikey Johnston at Celtic, he comes off the bench and nets a brace. On paper, Celtic...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘He was the best in Scotland’: BBC pundit thinks ‘outstanding’ Celtic star could now be replaced]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184776</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-legend-speaks-about-greg-taylors-future-ahead-of-january-transfer-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are so many areas of the pitch that Celtic could look to enhance during the January transfer window from centre-back to the striker department....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You don’t get to be Racist and a Celt]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58578</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/you-dont-get-to-be-racist-and-a-celt/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T16:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the early nineties and I am a wide eyed young Bhoy on the way home from Paradise on the Naomh Padraig C.S.C bus. Supporters club legend Ger Brady passes by me as I am leafing through the match day programme after another disappointing result and slaps a “Celtic Fans against fascism” sticker in […]
The post You don’t get to be Racist and a Celt appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I just don’t see it’: Pat Bonner thinks £2.5m ace is yet to prove his worth to Celtic dressing room]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184758</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/pat-bonner-delivers-a-critical-viewpoint-of-hyeongyu-ohs-time-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pat Bonner has stated that he still can’t see what Hyeongyu Oh is bringing to the table and thinks he is yet to prove his...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No excuses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115785</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/no-excuses/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T12:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s unfortunate that our next opponents had a clear midweek while we played on Tuesday, but we’re not ones for excuses around here.  We have the strongest squad in the country and should have more than enough in the tank to get through our next two games. Cameron Carter-Vickers’ fitness well be a concern for [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TWO AREAS WHERE CELTIC MUST STRENGTHEN: LEGEND’S VERDICT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115786</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/two-areas-where-celtic-must-strengthen-legends-verdict/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T11:47:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEIL LENNON has identified two positions where Celtic urgently need strengthening in the January Sales. The former Hoops boss believes Brendan Rodgers will be looking for a defensive-minded midfielder to take some of the burden off skipper Callum McGregor. And Lennon, who had two stints as the man in charge at Parkhead, insists back-up frontman [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kris Boyd needs to be put in his place after bonkers claim about Celtic star Kyogo on Sky last night]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184737</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kris-boyd-needs-a-reality-check-after-claim-about-celtics-kyogo-furuhashi-hearts-star-lawrence-shankland/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘Kyogo couldn’t finish like that’ were the words uttered by Kris Boyd about Celtic’s talisman during Hearts’ 1-0 win over Hibernian on Wednesday night. Lawrence...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘A red herring’: Celtic told Rodgers could spring a surprise by starting £1.4m star v Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184719</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-told-brendan-rodgers-might-spring-possible-surprise-with-reo-hatate-against-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T09:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate is back in training just in time for Celtic’s all-important clash against Rangers on Saturday. The 26-year-old has been back on the training...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘He does it against big teams’: John Hartson says Celtic would 'love' to sign 16-goal star]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184701</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-told-they-would-love-to-sign-hearts-star-lawrence-shankland-as-he-nets-edinburgh-derby-winner/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That price-tag on Lawrence Shankland’s head seems to be growing by the game and John Hartson thinks he would be a worthy signing for Celtic....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘ABSENT’ HARRY HEADS FOR HOOPS EXIT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115777</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/absent-harry-heads-for-hoops-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T06:53:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HARRY KEWELL edged closer to the Celtic exit when he missed the 3-0 win over Dundee at Dens Park on Boxing Day. The first-team coach was given time off by the Hoops hierarchy as the Australian legend put the finishing touches to his move to Yokohama F. Marinos. Ex-Leeds United and Liverpool winger is formalising [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS v RANGERS (Part Four)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111571</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-v-rangers-part-four/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T06:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS celebrated his return to the rarified atmosphere of a Glasgow derby this season after an absence of over four and a half years. The second time-around Celtic boss was all smiles as he watched Kyogo Furuhashi volley in the only goal of the encounter at Ibrox in early September to seal his comeback. Rodgers [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS v RANGERS (Part Three)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111506</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-v-rangers-part-three/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T06:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is preparing for Saturday’s second derby of the season on the back of the 1-0 success at Ibrox in September when Kyogo Furuhashi was acclaimed as the matchwinner. That was the Irishman’s return to the fixture following an absence of over four and a half years. The second time-around Hoops gaffer enjoyed phenomenal [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…DORUS DE VRIES?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=108610</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-dorus-de-vries/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T05:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS produced a surprise signing in mid-August 2016 when he unveiled 35-year-old keeper Dorus de Vries as his latest recruit. The Dutchman, who had been at Swansea when the new Hoops gaffer was in charge of the Welsh club, joined from Nottingham Forest and went straight into the first team for the Premiership game [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘He misses Reo Hatate’: BBC pundit says he has noticed Celtic 28-year-old is ‘frustrated’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184680</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/pat-bonner-shares-what-he-has-noticed-about-celtic-star-kyogo-furuhashi-under-brendan-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T19:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The big game against Rangers is coming up and the hope is that Celtic’s star man, Kyogo Furuhashi will be back to his best. That...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Doesn’t fit it’: Pat Bonner thinks Celtic duo need replacing, calls for January transfer action]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184656</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/doesnt-fit-it-pat-bonner-thinks-celtic-duo-need-replacing-calls-for-january-replacement/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You could argue that Celtic need strength in depth across the pitch ahead of the January transfer window opening. Brendan Rodgers has been pretty vocal...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S 8-POINT INCENTIVE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115768</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtics-8-point-incentive/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T14:33:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have the opportunity to go into 2024 with an EIGHT-POINT advantage at the Premiership pinnacle. The champions restored their five-point lead following the 3-0 win over Dundee at Dens Park which left Philippe Clement’s side five points adrift. The Hoops’ nearest challengers hoped to cut that to two with a victory over Ross County [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gig Review  Jamie Webster  Glasgow O2 Academy]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58575</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/gig-review-jamie-webster-glasgow-o2-academy/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T14:27:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes, just sometimes, the stars align and for a minute or two and you feel like the luckiest guy on the planet.  Well, that was me, that was how I felt walking out of The Glasgow O2 Academy at about half ten on Friday the 10th November.  A blistering night of music and stories […]
The post Gig Review  Jamie Webster  Glasgow O2 Academy appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘What’s this all about’: BBC pundit ‘surprised’ by Hyeongyu Oh's actions in Celtic warm-up v Dundee]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184640</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/bbc-pundit-surprised-by-hyeongyu-ohs-actions-in-celtic-warm-up-questions-whats-this-all-about/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pat Bonner reacted to Hyeongyu Oh’s unique way of warming up for Celtic games, as he proved again on Boxing Day against Dundee.  Celtic romped...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paulo clicks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115701</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/paulo-clicks/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T12:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It wasn’t Celtic at their devastating best, but there was enough on show to reassure us that the malaise which had afflicted the champions in recent weeks is easing. Brendan Rodgers chopped and changed who accompanied Callum McGregor and Matt O’Riley in midfield, before handing Paulo Bernardo consecutive starts – and the team the change [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN’S BOXING DAY ANGUISH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115764</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/brendans-boxing-day-anguish/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T11:46:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE game was edging towards the half-hour mark with Celtic dominating the flow of play against Dundee at Dens Park. It was a one-sided Boxing Day encounter, but the champions had yet to be rewarded for their supremecy as they pushed the hosts onto the back-foot right from the kick-off in a must-win contest. In [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘THE CHALLENGE FOR MIKEY,’ BRENDAN’S VERDICT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115699</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-challenge-for-mikey-brendans-verdict/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T10:09:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MIKEY JOHNSTON will figure in Brendan Rodgers’ matchday squad for the crucial clash with Phillipe Clement’s Ibrox side at Parkhead on Saturday. However, Celtic’s two-goal star in the 3-0 win over Dundee at Dens Park is being given no guarantees by his manager as he prepares for the second derby of the campaign following the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forgotten man Gustaf Lagerbielke sends 2-word message to Celtic midfielder after win over Dundee]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184622</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/forgotten-man-gustaf-lagerbielke-sends-2-word-message-to-celtic-midfielder-after-win-over-dundee/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T09:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many Celtic players have been in and out of the side under Brendan Rodgers this season, no more so than forgotten man, Gustaf Lagerbielke, as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I NEED TO IMPROVE,’ MIKEY’S VERDICT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115687</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-need-to-improve-mikeys-verdict/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T08:26:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MIKEY JOHNSTON fired a timely reminder to Brendan Rodgers with his double salvo in the 3-0 Boxing Day triumph over Dundee at Dens Park. The champions were dominating the Tayside encounter following Paulo Bernardo’s first strike for the club shortly after the turnaround, but there was always the possibility of the hosts pinching a dreaded [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘He didn’t’: Chris Sutton says £2.5m Celtic star 'lacking belief' despite win over Dundee]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184600</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/chris-sutton-shares-hyeongyu-oh-concern-despite-celtics-3-0-win-over-dundee/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyeongyu Oh is still trying to fight to prove his worth at Celtic following his £2.5 million transfer last January. On Boxing Day, Celtic recorded...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Magic’: Shane Duffy & Paulo Bernardo wowed by Celtic star’s display against Dundee]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184583</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/shane-duffy-and-paulo-bernardo-wowed-by-celtic-stars-display-after-3-0-win-over-dundee/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That was a moment Mikey Johnston has been waiting for in Celtic colours and his latest performance was applauded by Shane Duffy and Paulo Bernardo. ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS v RANGERS (Part Two)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111476</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-v-rangers-part-two/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T06:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is preparing for the second derby since his return to Celtic in June after enjoying a 1-0 success at Ibrox earlier in the campaign. In his first stint, the Hoops gaffer enjoyed phenomenal success against the city rivals in his first spell between May 2016 and February 2019. Rodgers faced the Govan club [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS v RANGERS: DERBY DEBUT RAMPAGE (Part One)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111451</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-v-rangers-derby-debut-rampage-part-one/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T06:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS faced Ibrox opposition 13 times in his first stint as Celtic manager. The elite coach enjoyed TEN wins along with two draws and a solitary loss. Rodgers watched the Hoops hammer THIRTY-ONE goals into their rivals’ net with only seven conceded. The Hoops gaffer got his second coming off to a perfect start [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…ISLAM FERUZ?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=108605</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-islam-feruz/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T05:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ONE-TIME Celtic wonderkid Islam Feruz quit football at the age of 24 in April 2020 – to set up his own clothing brand. The forward, once tipped to go all the way to the top by former manager and mentor Tommy Burns, walked out on the Hoops at the age of 16 to join Chelsea. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic take pleasing January transfer window stance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184578</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-take-pleasing-january-transfer-window-stance/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T20:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic aren’t interested in selling midfielder Matt O’Riley in the upcoming January transfer window, according to a new report. In addition, it’s stated that the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers indicates future role for Celtic fringe player]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184573</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-indicates-mikey-johnstons-future-role-at-celtic-after-dundee-double/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T19:49:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers was impressed with the performance of Mikey Johnston against Dundee as the winger netted a double to rack up a 3-0...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers issues promising Reo Hatate and Liel Abada news ahead of Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184566</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-issues-promising-reo-hatate-and-liel-abada-news-ahead-of-derby/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T19:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liel Abada and Reo Hatate are in contention to make the weekend match squad for Celtic’s massive derby at home to Rangers. Brendan Rodgers delivered...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton delivers verdict on Celtic display against Dundee after sharp recent criticism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184569</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/chris-sutton-delivers-verdict-on-celtic-display-against-dundee-after-sharp-recent-criticism/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T18:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton has pulled no punches with his criticism of Celtic in recent weeks, so it says a lot for the Bhoys’ performance away to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CCV: DERBY WAITING GAME]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115677</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ccv-derby-waiting-game/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T18:22:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS admits he is in the dark regarding Cameron Carter-Vickers’ chances of playing in the crucial derby at Parkhead on Saturday. The rugged centre-back came off in the 55th minute of Celtic’s 3-0 win over Dundee at Dens Park where Mikey Johnston notched a double to add to Paulo Bernardo’s breakthrough strike. Carter-Vickers, who [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers provides update on Cameron Carter-Vickers after big Celtic injury concern]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184560</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-provides-update-on-cameron-carter-vickers-after-big-celtic-injury-concern/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T17:20:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cameron Carter-Vickers limped out of Celtic’s 3-0 win over Dundee this afternoon, sparking a big injury concern ahead of the weekend’s crucial derby. The Bhoys...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DUNDEE 0 CELTIC 3: IT’S MIKEY – AT THE DOUBLE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115668</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/dundee-0-celtic-3-its-mikey-at-the-double/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T17:11:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DUNDEE 0 CELTIC 3   MIKEY JOHNSTON went over FOUR YEARS without scoring a goal for Celtic. The winger came off the substitutes’ bench to score two in EIGHT MINUTES as the champions overcame Dundee at Dens Park this afternoon to restore their five-point advantage at the Premiership pinnacle. Johnston made his appearance in the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worrying injury issue, unlikely hero; The 3 big talking points as Celtic beat Dundee]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184555</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/worrying-injury-issue-unlikely-hero-the-3-big-talking-points-as-celtic-beat-dundee/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T16:59:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic continued their winning ways during the Christmas period with a 3-0 win over Dundee at Dens Park on Boxing Day. Paulo Bernardo was the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dundee v Celtic, GG Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115666</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/dundee-v-celtic-gg-live-updates/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T14:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 15.00]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: SAME AGAIN CELTS, NO HATATE IN SQUAD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115024</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-same-again-celts-no-hatate-in-squad/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T13:53:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has given a vote of confidence to the team that started against Livingston at the weekend by saying same again for Dundee at Dens Park this afternoon. It means on-loan Benfica midfielder Paulo Bernardo once again gets the nod ahead of David Turnbull while Daizen Maeda continues on the wing after his comeback [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James McClean – an Irish Centurion]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58568</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/james-mcclean-an-irish-centurion/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T11:49:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A late November friendly International match between the Republic and New Zealand was hardly likely to create a lot of interest especially when it came after a disappointing Euro qualifying campaign for the Irish which ended with the manager Stephen Kenny relinquishing his post.  New Zealand, unlike their famous counterparts, the All Blacks, sit […]
The post James McClean – an Irish Centurion appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's Christmas Day sacrifice to prepare for Dundee]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184548</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtics-christmas-day-sacrifice-to-prepare-for-dundee/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T09:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While most of us were enjoying Christmas dinner and the usual festive celebrations yesterday, the Celtic squad were busy preparing for today’s trip to Dens...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic team news and Predicted XI for Boxing Day Dundee clash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184543</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-news-and-predicted-xi-for-boxing-day-dundee-clash/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T08:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s festive season continues in a 3pm Boxing Day match away to Dundee in the Scottish Premiership and it’s another crucial encounter. The Bhoys have...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TWO FOR THE ROAD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115661</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/two-for-the-road/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T08:25:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YOSUKE IDEGUCHI will kick off Celtic’s feverish transfer activity in the January window by sealing a permanent return to the J-League. The midfielder, whose career at the Hoops stalled through injury shortly after his arrival from Gamba Osaka in January 2022, will confirm a deal with Vissel Kobe within the next fortnight. Ideguchi is currently on [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[O’RILEY: NO DEAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115659</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/oriley-no-deal/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T07:48:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY will NOT be moving to Inter Milan next month. News leaked last week the Serie A outfit were about to firm up their interest in Celtic’s in-form midfielder. However, as CQN forecast at the time, the champions will not be interested in selling the 23-year-old midfielder who has scored nine goals and had eight assists in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…DERK BOERRIGTER?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=108585</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-derk-boerrigter/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T07:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DERK BOERRIGTER lived up to his nickname of ‘Sicknote’ after joining Celtic from £3million from Ajax on July 30 2013. The Dutch winger was 26 when Neil Lennon splashed the cash for the player who had earned the unwanted moniker after missing so many games for the Amsterdam giants. It didn’t augur well when Boerrigter [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BOXING DAY CHEERS 2022: CELTIC GOAL ROUT IN THE CAPITAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115021</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/boxing-day-cheers-2022-celtic-goal-rout-in-the-capital/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T06:05:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HIBS 0 CELTIC 4: December 28 2022 AARON MOOY scored his first goal for Celtic – and his first in Scottish football in ELEVEN years – as the champions routed Hibs at Easter Road to enjoy a belated Boxing Day triumph. The Aussie midfielder enjoyed the experience so much he repeated the feat in the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BOXING DAY CHEERS 2021: ABADA DOUBLE SEALS THE DEAL IN PERTH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115020</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/boxing-day-cheers-2021-abada-double-seals-the-deal-in-perth/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T06:04:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ST JOHNSTONE 1 CELTIC 3: Boxing Day 2021 LIEL ABADA struck twice within 22 first-half minutes to guide the visitors to victory over St Johnstone in Perth as Ange Postecoglou celebrated his first six months as Celtic manager. The Israeli international winger looked to have had the much-changed Hoops coasting to three crucial points, but [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BOXING DAY CHEERS 2020: EDOUARD LIFT-OFF AT HAMILTON]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115019</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/boxing-day-cheers-2020-edouard-lift-off-at-hamilton/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T06:03:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HAMILTON ACCIES 0 CELTIC 3: Boxing Day 2020 CELTIC relied on the old one-two of Odsonne Edouard and Leigh Griffiths to make sure the points weren’t gone with the wind at Hamilton. The double-act, who went into this game with a total of 15 goals in their nine outings together, took the total to 17 [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BOXING DAY CHEERS 2019: LATE SCARE IN PAISLEY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115018</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/boxing-day-cheers-2019-late-scare-in-paisley/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T06:02:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ST MIRREN 1 CELTIC 2: Boxing Day 2019 CELTIC racked up their ELEVENTH successive Premiership triumph at Paisley, but were given a late scare on their way to the three points. Callum McGregor and James Forrest struck in the first-half and it appeared the Hoops were in cruise control and easing towards their third successive [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BOXING DAY CHEERS 2018: PANDEMONIUM AT PITTODRIE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115017</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/boxing-day-cheers-2018-pandemonium-at-pittodrie/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T06:01:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ABERDEEN 3 CELTIC 4: Boxing Day 2018 IT was pandemonium at Pittodrie as Scott Sinclair fired in a brilliant hat-trick and Celtic emerged with three points from a dramatic seven-goal thriller. The frantic confrontation see-sawed in remarkable fashion as referee Kevin Clancy awarded the Dons two dodgy penalty-kicks to keep the outcome in the balance [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BOXING DAY CHEERS 2017: DENS PARK DELIGHT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115016</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/boxing-day-cheers-2017-dens-park-delight/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T06:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DUNDEE 0 CELTIC 2: Boxing Day 2017 BRENDAN RODGERS celebrated his second Christmas as Celtic manager in the anticipated manner – a win and three precious Premiership points. It was lively winger James Forrest who got the show on the road with the opening strike in the eighth minute to ease the pressure on the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DUNDEE v CELTIC: 5-MINUTE QUIZ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114965</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/dundee-v-celtic-5-minute-quiz/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T05:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC play their SEVENTH successive Boxing Day away game when they face Dundee at Dens Park in today’s 3pm showdown. Brendan Rodgers has already experienced the festive fixture on Tayside. Back in 2017, the Hoops celebrated a 2-0 triumph with James Forrest and Leigh Griffiths on target. Now the champions are looking to complete a magnificent [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Predicting 2023/24 Celtic outcomes as title race heats up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184083</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/predicting-2023-24-celtic-outcomes-as-title-race-heats-up/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-25T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These last few weeks might not have gone the way Celtic fans would have liked, but 2023 overall has served the club very well. Ange...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The incredible value found from Celtic's 3 best players in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184196</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-incredible-value-found-from-celtics-3-best-players-in-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-25T14:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From winning the League Cup final at Rangers’ expense to watching Ange Postecoglou ball in full flow, it has been a year of more dominance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Merry Christmas]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58565</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/merry-christmas-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-25T11:35:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to all our readers and sponsors fo the continued support enjoy your day with family and friends
The post Merry Christmas appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's Player of the Season so far... and there is only one winner]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=184041</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/there-is-only-one-winner-when-it-comes-to-celtics-player-of-the-season-so-far/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-25T11:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A piece of footballing art = Matthew Sean O’Riley of Celtic. The stylistic and easy-on-the-eye nature of Matt O’Riley’s game is what makes him such...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic want to sign £4 million-rated player in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45945</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-4-million-player-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T23:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The defeat at the hands of Lazio was further proof of Celtic’s need to strengthen in the January transfer window. The club might have brought in nine new faces in the summer but a lot of people feel that the team has taken a step back since last season, when they breezed past the competition […]
Celtic want to sign £4 million-rated player in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers sends clear message Celtic board must not ignore]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45941</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/brendan-rodgers-message-celtic-board/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T21:35:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s fate in Europe for this season is sealed after their 2-0 defeat at the hands of Lazio. The result means that the Hoops are guaranteed to finish bottom of their group in the UEFA Champions League. That also means that they will not be dropping down to the Europa League, something that should have […]
Brendan Rodgers sends clear message Celtic board must not ignore - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton publicly criticises Celtic after loss to Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45938</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/chris-sutton-celtic-loss-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T20:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic lost 2-0 away in Rome to Lazio. The Hoops were in the match for a long time before Ciro Immobile came off the bench to score a brace and put the game to bed. The result means that not only are Brendan Rodgers’ side out of the Champions League following the group stages but […]
Chris Sutton publicly criticises Celtic after loss to Lazio - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed £7 million Jeremie Frimpong windfall news]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45933</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-jeremie-frimpong-windfall-news/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremie Frimpong’s rise at Bayer Leverkusen has been fascinating, to say the least. The Dutchman had shown a lot of quality going forward at Celtic as well but not many could have foreseen him becoming one of the most prolific wingbacks in Europe just a few years later. That is exactly what has happened under […]
Celtic handed £7 million Jeremie Frimpong windfall news - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic told 29-goal striker is good enough amid links]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45930</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-told-29-goal-striker-good-enough/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T13:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to add to their options up top this January. Kyogo has done well once again but he is not scoring as frequently as he was last season. On the other hand, Oh Hyeon-gyu has been inconsistent as well and is not at the level required to start for the Hoops right now. There […]
Celtic told 29-goal striker is good enough amid links - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anderlecht consider making offer for Celtic standout in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45927</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/anderlecht-offer-celtic-standout-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T11:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have not had the greatest campaign till now. They were eliminated early from the Scottish League Cup and while they do lead the Premiership, their performances and results have been somewhat inconsistent. Almost half a season on, it feels like the Hoops are still finding their feet under the management of Brendan Rodgers and […]
Anderlecht consider making offer for Celtic standout in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serie A club want to sign Celtic player amid contract worry]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45907</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/serie-club-want-celtic-player-contract/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T22:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic fans hope for more quality players arriving there could be a problem with others heading for the exit door. It seems pretty clear that Brendan Rodgers wants to make the size of the squad more manageable over the next couple of transfer windows and departures are expected. But there is a risk of […]
Serie A club want to sign Celtic player amid contract worry - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur step up bid to sign Celtic-linked player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45918</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/tottenham-hotspur-bid-sign-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur made a fantastic start to the season under the management of Ange Postecoglou. With Harry Kane leaving the club in the summer for Bayern Munich, most expected them to struggle. Instead, they appeared to be putting up an unlikely title challenge and were sitting atop the Premier League table not too long ago. […]
Tottenham Hotspur step up bid to sign Celtic-linked player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boost in race to sign £11 million Real Madrid player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45914</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/celtic-boost-real-madrid-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to sign a goalkeeper in the near future. It is quite clear that Joe Hart is not the long-term solution between the posts. The Englishman’s performances have been criticised lately. Also, he is set to turn 37 years of age before this season comes to an end. So, while he has done a […]
Celtic boost in race to sign £11 million Real Madrid player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio boss Maurizio Sarri makes fantastic Celtic claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45910</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/lazio-boss-maurizio-sarri-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T18:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By now, Celtic fans have accepted that Brendan Rodgers’ side are most probably not going through or even finishing third in their group in the UEFA Champions League. It would be a positive step to get a win in the competition though. It has been quite some time since the Hoops won at this level. […]
Lazio boss Maurizio Sarri makes fantastic Celtic claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic tipped to go for 28-year-old Premiership striker]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45904</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/celtic-tipped-go-premiership-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T12:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans breathed a sigh of relief as the Rangers dropped points at the weekend against Aberdeen. In fact, it took a late penalty for them to even come out with a draw from the game. That means that the Hoops will maintain their strong position at the top of the Scottish Premiership table. That […]
Celtic tipped to go for 28-year-old Premiership striker - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£7.5 million Mathias Kvistgaarden to Celtic transfer update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45900</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/mathias-kvistgaarden-celtic-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T10:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to sign a striker in January. On one hand, we have seen the club struggle for goals in some games this season. When the opposition puts up a resolute defence, the Hoops do not appear to have a lot of answers other than Kyogo, Matt O’Riley or Luis Palma. On the other hand, […]
£7.5 million Mathias Kvistgaarden to Celtic transfer update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur have been eyeing Celtic superstar]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45896</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/tottenham-hotspur-eyeing-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T23:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou made the move to Tottenham Hotspur in the summer and it was only a matter of time before the Australian was linked with a reunion with some Celtic players. The manager enjoyed a lot of success at Parkhead, even though he was at the club for just two seasons, and won five trophies […]
Tottenham Hotspur have been eyeing Celtic superstar - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John McGinn claims he spoke to Celtic players about manager]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45890</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/john-mcginn-spoke-celtic-players/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T21:35:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most Celtic fans will remember how the club missed out on the opportunity to sign John McGinn some years back. The Scot grew up supporting the Hoops but a move to Parkhead failed to materialise even though it had looked close and he ended up moving down south to join Aston Villa. McGinn has risen […]
John McGinn claims he spoke to Celtic players about manager - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic must consider signing striker from Premiership rivals]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45886</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-signing-striker-premiership-rivals/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T20:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there is one position where Celtic need to strengthen during the upcoming January transfer window, it is striker. The Hoops have been pretty inconsistent in front of goal this season so far. Of course, there are games when they can go out and score six times. But then, on days they are having a […]
Celtic must consider signing striker from Premiership rivals - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend takes dig at Rangers player for diving]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45884</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-legend-rangers-player-diving/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T18:35:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Celtic drew 1-1 against Motherwell, the Rangers were handed a major chance to get back into the title race. All they needed to do was win their games in hand and they would be just three points behind the Hoops in the league table. We have seen the Ibrox side not perform at their […]
Celtic legend takes dig at Rangers player for diving - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player criticised after draw against Motherwell]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45881</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-player-criticised-draw-motherwell/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T12:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Titles are not decided this early in the season. That has been proven once again. Not too long ago, Celtic were sitting seven points clear at the top of the Premiership table and most fans felt that the league was pretty much in the bag with the Rangers struggling for any kind of form.  It […]
Celtic player criticised after draw against Motherwell - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgio Chiellini makes superb claim about Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45874</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/giorgio-chiellini-claim-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T10:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Giorgio Chiellini is one of the best defenders of all time and he had some pretty positive comments about Celtic Park recently. The 39-year-old spent the majority of his career playing for Juventus and won more silverware there than one should try to count. Overall, he made more […]
Giorgio Chiellini makes superb claim about Celtic Park - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s problem is very clear and needs solving quick]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45870</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/celtic-problem-needs-solving-quick/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T19:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two more dropped points mean that Celtic have well and truly allowed the Rangers to get back into the title race. A lead which once stood at seven points, could be reduced to three if Philippe Clement’s side are able to win their games in hand. And the sad thing is that the Hoops have […]
Celtic’s problem is very clear and needs solving quick - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic problem after draw]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45866</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/brendan-rodgers-celtic-problem-draw/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T18:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was not the result Celtic were looking for, as they dropped two valuable points against Motherwell. David Turnbull’s goal appeared to have won it for the Hoops but the visitors equalised in the 90th minute and it ended 1-1. That means that if the Rangers win their games in hand, the gap will be […]
Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic problem after draw - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hollywood superstar pictured wearing Celtic jersey]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45861</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/hollywood-pictured-wearing-celtic-jersey/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T12:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Celtic have their fair share of famous fans. Rod Stewart is the first name that comes to most people’s minds, one of the best-selling music artists in history. Lewis Capaldi is another popular musician known to support the Hoops. And several A-list celebrities like Gerard Butler, Snoop Dogg, […]
Hollywood superstar pictured wearing Celtic jersey - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic pushing for priority signing in January window]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45859</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/celtic-priority-signing-january-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T09:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s January transfer window is expected to be a busy one. The club might have made nine signings in the summer, seven arriving on a permanent basis and two on loan, but there are still holes in Brendan Rodgers’ squad that need to be filled. On the other hand, there are way too many players […]
Celtic pushing for priority signing in January window - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable source offers Sydney van Hooijdonk to Celtic update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45854</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/reliable-sydney-van-hooijdonk-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T22:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are believed to be on the lookout for a striker in the January transfer window. There might be a few reasons behind that. Firstly, both Kyogo and Oh Hyeon-gyu might be unavailable for a considerable length of time early next year due to the AFC Asian Cup. They are the club’s two options to […]
Reliable source offers Sydney van Hooijdonk to Celtic update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou claims Celtic success gets dismissed]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45852</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/ange-postecoglou-claims-celtic-success/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T21:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has proven to be a major success in the Premier League since swapping Celtic for Tottenham Hotspur. Of course, a lot of fans were not happy to see him depart after just two years at Parkhead. But he has been very respectful about the club even after leaving. And it is hard not […]
Ange Postecoglou claims Celtic success gets dismissed - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>