<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-12-01T00:54:23.393Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aberdeen Women hit for unlucky thirteen as Celtic Women complete a record-breaking scoreline]]></title>
        <id>https://celticunderground.net/?p=6691</id>
        <link href="http://celticunderground.net/aberdeen-women-hit-for-unlucky-thirteen-as-celtic-women-complete-a-record-breaking-scoreline/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T22:18:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thirteen goals, eight scorers and two hat-tricks as Celtic completed a historic feat at the Excelsior Stadium. This is Aberdeen’s biggest ever defeat, and this is the biggest win of the season for any top-flight team. Amy Gallacher took her goals tally up to 15 for the season with a hat-trick and Murphy Agnew scored […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ethan Barlow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Let me finish': Danny Murphy shuts down claims about Celtic from talkSPORT pundit Simon Jordan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=182159</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/danny-murphy-shuts-down-claims-about-celtic-from-talksport-pundit/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Danny Murphy has defended Celtic’s Champions League run which has seen them finish bottom of Group E. As of this moment, Celtic are on one...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant urges Celtic to hand 'exceptional' star a new contract after 'question marks']]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=182125</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/peter-grant-sends-contract-message-about-liam-scales-after-question-marks-about-celtic-star/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T17:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant has urged Celtic to hand Liam Scales a new contract after his strong performances this season.  Before a ball could be kicked this...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['It has to': Neil Lennon sends Celtic board blunt message that fans have been crying out for]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=182142</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/neil-lennon-sends-celtic-board-blunt-transfer-message-after-european-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T16:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon says Celtic need to focus on the January transfer window after getting knocked out of Europe. Brendan Rodgers and his players faced a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘He belongs in this side’: James McFadden impressed by surprise package Celtic star this season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=182109</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/james-mcfadden-says-what-many-celtic-fans-are-thinking-of-liam-scales/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T13:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James McFadden handed Liam Scales his flowers for his performances in Celtic colours this season.  If it wasn’t for injuries at the start of the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Doesn’t tell the truth’: Alan Brazil and Ally McCoist are in agreement about Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=182088</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alan-brazil-and-ally-mccoist-in-agreement-about-celtic-and-express-what-doesnt-tell-the-truth/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alan Brazil and Ally McCoist were in agreement that Celtic shot themselves in the foot at home in the Champions League this season. Brendan Rodgers’...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Historic Vatican visit represents us all]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114756</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/historic-vatican-visit-represents-us-all/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T12:10:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I like David Turnbull, when given a chance, he does a job for Celtic and he has a role to play in this season’s title race.  But talk about AC Milan being interested in him is surely fanciful.  Scots have done well in Italy recently, David could thrive there, but the demands at Milan would [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOUL PLAY: LIAM SCALES’ BRUTAL LEARNING CURVE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114754</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/foul-play-liam-scales-brutal-learning-curve/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T10:03:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIAM SCALES played his seventeenth first-team game this season in Celtic’s 2-0 loss against Lazio in Rome. The Republic of Ireland international defender has been involved in every minute of the team’s ill-fated Champions League crusade which started in Rotterdam, moved to Parkhead against the Serie A outfit and then the double-header against Atletico Madrid. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£2.75m CELT’S DAYS ARE NUMBERED]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114750</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/2-75m-celts-days-are-numbered/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T08:53:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT LOOKS as though David Turnbull’s days as a Celtic player are numbered after a series of snubs from Brendan Rodgers. The latest came in the midweek Champions League exit to Lazio in Rome when the Hoops boss again elected to start with on-loan Benfica midfielder Paulo Bernardo. Turnbull, a £2.75million recruit by Neil Lennon [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I would still': Barry Ferguson still can't hide Celtic envy even after Champions League exit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=182068</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/barry-ferguson-still-cant-hide-celtic-envy-even-after-champions-league-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T08:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Barry Ferguson says he would still ‘rather be in Celtic’s position’ in the Scottish Premiership table after Brendan Rodgers watched his side crash out of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Give us more money': Simon Jordan drops harsh realities after Celtic crash out of Europe again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=182046</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/simon-jordan-drops-harsh-realties-after-celtic-crash-out-of-europe-again/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T07:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Simon Jordan referenced how Celtic need to be spending more in the transfer market after crashing out of Europe in a sorry way once again....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SILVERWARE HEAVEN IN GOVAN FOR HENRIK, WIM AND CO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=100362</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/silverware-heaven-in-govan-for-henrik-wim-and-co/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T06:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TODAY marks the 26th anniversary of a significant silverware success that is almost overshadowed in Celtic history. On a pulsating Sunday afternoon on November 30 1997 in front of 49,305 fans at Ibrox, goals from Marc Rieper, Henrik Larsson and Craig Burley defeated Dundee United 3-0 in the League Cup Final – then in the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE BERTIE AULD: PART SIXTEEN: ‘OUR LISBON SECRET’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=72659</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-unforgettable-bertie-auld-part-sixteen-our-lisbon-secret/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T05:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bertie Auld was rated the team’s most influential player by many onlookers, club legend Davie Hay among them, when Celtic conquered Europe on May 25 1967. CQN are celebrating the life and incredible times of the Hoops great in an EXCLUSIVE series with extracts from his best-selling autobiography, ‘A Bhoy Called Bertie‘, co-authored by [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Sells himself': Neil Lennon slams Celtic duo after Champions League defeat to Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=182027</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/neil-lennon-offers-honest-thoughts-on-cameron-carter-vickers-liam-scales-after-celtic-defeat-to-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T20:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon was critical of Cameron Carter-Vickers and Liam Scales for the role they played during Celtic’s 2-0 defeat to Lazio. Heading into the final...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What John Hartson said about Mikey Johnston just five minutes after coming on for Celtic at Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=182009</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/what-john-hartson-said-about-mikey-johnston-just-five-minutes-after-coming-on-for-celtic-at-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T18:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not many things went right for Celtic against Lazio, there weren’t many positives to shout about for Brendan Rodgers. But one positive was Mikey Johnston,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['No': Micah Richards defends Celtic star after Jamie Carragher questions him after Lazio defeat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181986</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/micah-richards-reacts-to-jamie-carragher-questioning-joe-hart-after-celtic-defeat-to-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Micah Richards has defended Joe Hart for the role he played in Celtic’s 2-0 defeat to Lazio in the UEFA Champions League. The former Manchester...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pundit notes what will disappoint Brendan Rodgers most after Celtic defeat to Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181946</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/pundit-notes-what-will-disappoint-brendan-rodgers-most-after-celtic-defeat-to-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T17:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic defender Mark Wilson has revealed that he believes a lack of cutting edge upfront  cost Celtic against Lazio last night.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant has issues with Brendan Rodgers’ Celtic team selection vs Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181874</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/peter-grant-has-issues-with-brendan-rodgers-celtic-team-selection-vs-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T17:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic midfielder Peter Grant has spoken about Brendan Rodgers’ team selection against Lazio. Celtic crashed out of the Champions League for the second consecutive...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[’The biggest surprise’: James McFadden says Celtic star ‘barely touched the ball’ v Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181949</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/james-mcfadden-delivers-paulo-bernardo-verdict-as-celtic-suffer-champions-league-defeat-at-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The selection and performance of Paulo Bernardo during Celtic’s 2-0 defeat to Lazio in the UEFA Champions League was a big talking point for James...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I don't': Michael Stewart dishes out a dose of Celtic reality to Rangers regarding winning title]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181920</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/michael-stewart-dishes-out-a-dose-of-celtic-reality-to-rangers-regarding-winning-the-title/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Stewart says Brendan Rodgers’ Celtic will beat Rangers to the Premiership title this season. Not only does Michael Stewart think that Celtic will win...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE POPE’S WORDS OF CONSOLATION FOR CELTIC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114739</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-popes-words-of-consolation-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T14:16:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS and his Celtic players were given words of consolation after their 2-0 loss to Lazio in Rome from a very special person this morning. Pope Francis met the manager, chairman Peter Lawwell, the club’s directors and entire playing squad at the Vatican in the aftermath of the Parkhead side’s disappointing exit from Europe [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC RECORD-BREAKER SPOTS EURO WEAKNESS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114736</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-record-breaker-spots-euro-weakness/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T13:35:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART dismissed a personal milestone to focus on the disappointment of the 2-0 defeat to Lazio in Rome. The 36-year-old 75 times-capped international became the first English keeper to notch 50 appearances in the Champions League last night. However, the record sequence was not on Hart’s mind after the Hoops’ loss meant there would be [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘INCREDIBLE,’ BOSS BRENDAN PRAISES PLAYERS AND FANS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114723</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/incredible-boss-brendan-praises-players-and-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T13:19:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS praised his players for their “effort and commitment”, despite the 2-0 loss to Lazio in Rome firing Celtic into Euro oblivion for another season. The Hoops conceded two late goals in another disappointing collapse in the Champions League – their fourth in five games – to make the final Group E match against [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Competitive but results tell the whole story]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114687</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/competitive-but-results-tell-the-whole-story/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T12:08:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Midway through the second half, I chastised myself for being so downbeat about our prospects last night.  For 81 minutes, the game was there to be won.  Neither team was at full strength, but if Celtic had a little of Maeda’s industry, or Hatate’s control, the outcome could have been different. As it was, the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I know': John Hartson names 2 Celtic players who will get 'better' as a result of European exit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181855</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/john-hartson-names-two-celtic-players-who-will-get-better-as-a-result-of-getting-knocked-out-of-europe/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T10:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Hartson thinks Hyunjun Yang and Hyeongyu Oh will get ‘better’ from Celtic getting knocked out of the Champions League by Lazio. It was another...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘WE NEED TO GET TO GRIPS,’ INSISTS McGREGOR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114679</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/we-need-to-get-to-grips-insists-mcgregor/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T09:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CALLUM McGREGOR must have felt as though he had stepped into a time warp in Rome last night. Heading towards the 82nd minute, it was goalless in the Champions League encounter with Lazio at the Stadio Olimpico and the visitors had possession. The ball was worked to Kyogo Furuhashi in the middle of the pitch [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Absolute joke’: Alan Brazil slams Lazio star’s actions during Celtic defeat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181824</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/alan-brazil-blasts-ciro-immobiles-absolute-joke-actions-during-celtics-defeat-to-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alan Brazil wasn’t best pleased with Ciro Immobile’s ’time-wasting’ as Celtic crashed out of Europe at the hands of Lazio on Tuesday night. To the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘GLARING’: RODGERS ADMITS LACK OF QUALITY AS HE TARGETS NEW WIDE BHOY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114670</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/glaring-rodgers-admits-lack-of-quality-as-he-targets-new-wide-bhoy/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T08:59:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS admitted Celtic’s need to add quality to the squad is “glaring” following the late collapse against Lazio in Rome. The Hoops conceded two goals in three minutes to substitute Ciro Immobile to to leave them with just one point from a possible 15 in Champions League Group E with next month’s game against [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[X-CERTIFICATE CELTS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114666</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/x-certificate-celts-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T08:20:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have hit a new low after the 2-0 loss to Lazio in the Olimpico Stadium last night extinguished any lingering hopes of European football after Christmas. Brendan Rodgers’ side toppled out of the Champions League with four defeats and a draw from their five games, an x-certificate sequence that renders next month’s Group E final [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘It is odd’: Maurizio Sarri reacts to Lazio dumping sorry Celtic out of Europe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181802</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/maurizio-sarri-reacts-to-lazio-dumping-sorry-celtic-out-of-europe/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T07:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not the game Celtic wanted. Another Champions League game. Another game on the road. Another defeat. And now out of Europe pre-Christmas once again.  What’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Under Ange’: Neil Lennon makes his feelings clear on Celtic’s style of play under Brendan Rodgers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181755</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/neil-lennon-makes-his-feelings-clear-on-celtics-style-of-play-under-brendan-rodgers-compared-to-ange-postecoglou/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T06:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon thinks Celtic are moving the ball slower under Brendan Rodgers in comparison to Ange Postecoglou. As Celtic fans know too well and as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE BERTIE AULD: PART FIFTEEN: ‘IF IT CAME TO A FIGHT, WE COULD GIVE AS GOOD AS WE GOT’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=54073</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-unforgettable-bertie-auld-part-fifteen-if-it-came-to-a-fight-we-could-give-as-good-as-we-got/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T05:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bertie Auld never lost his affection for Celtic or the supporters long after he had kicked his last ball for the club on an emotional afternoon on May 1 1971 when the curtain came down on the Lisbon Lions. It was the final appearance of the most celebrated team in Parkhead history and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic want to sign £4 million-rated player in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45945</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-4-million-player-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T23:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The defeat at the hands of Lazio was further proof of Celtic’s need to strengthen in the January transfer window. The club might have brought in nine new faces in the summer but a lot of people feel that the team has taken a step back since last season, when they breezed past the competition […]
Celtic want to sign £4 million-rated player in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers sends clear message Celtic board must not ignore]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45941</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/brendan-rodgers-message-celtic-board/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T21:35:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s fate in Europe for this season is sealed after their 2-0 defeat at the hands of Lazio. The result means that the Hoops are guaranteed to finish bottom of their group in the UEFA Champions League. That also means that they will not be dropping down to the Europa League, something that should have […]
Brendan Rodgers sends clear message Celtic board must not ignore - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star owns up with "same old story" assessment of Lazio defeat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181796</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/callum-mcgregor-owns-up-with-same-old-story-celtic-assessment-of-lazio-defeat/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T21:27:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic captain Callum McGregor lamented the “same old story” for the Bhoys in Europe on Tuesday night after succumbing to a 2-0 defeat at the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Familiar message from Brendan Rodgers as Celtic boss reacts to Lazio defeat and European exit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181787</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/the-repeating-message-from-brendan-rodgers-as-celtic-boss-reacts-to-lazio-defeat-and-european-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T20:49:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has reiterated his desire for real ‘quality’ in the Celtic squad after watching his Bhoys team lose to Lazio 2-0 in the UEFA...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LAZIO 2  CELTIC 0: HOOPS EXIT IN LATE, LATE WOE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114662</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/lazio-2-celtic-0-hoops-exit-in-late-late-woe/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T20:01:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LAZIO 2 CELTIC 0  CELTIC failed yet again to respond to the challenge at the highest level and there will be no European football at Parkhead after Christmas yet again. Brendan Rodgers’ men went into the encounter at the Olimpico Stadium knowing a victory was an absolute must if they had a chance of keeping [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton publicly criticises Celtic after loss to Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45938</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/chris-sutton-celtic-loss-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T20:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic lost 2-0 away in Rome to Lazio. The Hoops were in the match for a long time before Ciro Immobile came off the bench to score a brace and put the game to bed. The result means that not only are Brendan Rodgers’ side out of the Champions League following the group stages but […]
Chris Sutton publicly criticises Celtic after loss to Lazio - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton delivers damning verdict as Celtic crash out of Europe with defeat to Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181776</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/chris-sutton-delivers-damning-verdict-as-celtic-crash-out-of-europe-with-defeat-to-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T19:41:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been knocked out of European football for the 2023/24 season after losing 2-0 away to Lazio on Tuesday night. Brendan Rodgers’ side needed...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed £7 million Jeremie Frimpong windfall news]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45933</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-jeremie-frimpong-windfall-news/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremie Frimpong’s rise at Bayer Leverkusen has been fascinating, to say the least. The Dutchman had shown a lot of quality going forward at Celtic as well but not many could have foreseen him becoming one of the most prolific wingbacks in Europe just a few years later. That is exactly what has happened under […]
Celtic handed £7 million Jeremie Frimpong windfall news - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio v Celtic, GG Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114655</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/lazio-v-celtic-gg-live-updates/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T16:45:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 17:45.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: FORREST, BERNARDO GET NOD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114635</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-forrest-bernardo-get-nod/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T16:40:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has turned to evergreen James Forrest to solve his winger problem gainst Lazio in the Olimpico Stadium tonight. The experienced wide Bhoy has been given the nod to face the Italians in the must-win Champions League Group E confrontation with Liel Abada, Luis Palma and Daizen Maeda all absent through injury and suspension. On-loan [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic XI confirmed: 3 changes, big attack call, global TV details, instant reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181748</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-vs-lazio-confirmed-3-changes-global-tv-details-instant-reaction/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T16:36:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manager Brendan Rodgers has named his Celtic team vs Lazio for tonight’s UEFA Champions League encounter in Rome. The full match squad is as follows:...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic enjoy superb UEFA Youth League win away to Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181742</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/celtic-enjoy-superb-uefa-youth-league-win-away-to-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T14:53:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic U19s have secured their first win of this season’s UEFA Youth League campaign with a 2-0 result away to Lazio this afternoon. The youth...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 changes, winger dilemma; Celtic team news, suspensions and Predicted XI for big Lazio clash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181733</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/3-changes-winger-dilemma-celtic-team-news-suspensions-and-predicted-xi-for-big-lazio-clash/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T13:45:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic travel to Rome this evening to take on Lazio on matchday five of the UEFA Champions League. Needing a victory to keep their hopes...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic told 29-goal striker is good enough amid links]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45930</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-told-29-goal-striker-good-enough/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T13:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to add to their options up top this January. Kyogo has done well once again but he is not scoring as frequently as he was last season. On the other hand, Oh Hyeon-gyu has been inconsistent as well and is not at the level required to start for the Hoops right now. There […]
Celtic told 29-goal striker is good enough amid links - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Options may dictate experimental formation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114649</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/options-may-dictate-experimental-formation/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T12:01:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Celtic were at full strength, I would fancy them tonight.  As it is, we will be able to select our normal defensive lineup, midfield will be without our fulcrum Reo Hatate, and a lengthening list of wingers are absent from the forward line. Along with the rest of the team, Yang did not set [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[’That’s basically it’: Liam Scales says what every Celtic fan wants to hear]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181716</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/liam-scales-says-what-every-celtic-fan-wants-to-hear-ahead-of-champions-league-clash-against-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T11:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liam Scales was in a buoyant mood ahead of Celtic’s must-win clash against Lazio in the Champions League on Tuesday. Overall, the Champions League campaign...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anderlecht consider making offer for Celtic standout in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45927</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/anderlecht-offer-celtic-standout-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T11:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have not had the greatest campaign till now. They were eliminated early from the Scottish League Cup and while they do lead the Premiership, their performances and results have been somewhat inconsistent. Almost half a season on, it feels like the Hoops are still finding their feet under the management of Brendan Rodgers and […]
Anderlecht consider making offer for Celtic standout in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘He is available’: Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic star to return for Lazio clash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181696</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-delivers-james-forrest-news-ahead-of-celtics-champions-league-clash-at-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has confirmed that James Forrest will return to the Celtic squad for the Champions League showdown against Lazio.  The 32-year-old was absent for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC STAR WHO WON’T BE PUT ON THE SPOT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114638</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-star-who-wont-be-put-on-the-spot/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T09:42:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE, David Turnbull and Luis Palma have all been spot-kick sinners for Celtic this season. The Honduran international winger joined the other two culprits when he saw his effort pushed away by Motherwell keeper Liam Kelly in the 1-1 draw at Parkhead at the weekend. Both Hatate and Turnbull clattered the woodwork with their [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[’There are problems’: Neil Lennon predicts Celtic’s Champions League tie at Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181678</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/neil-lennon-predicts-celtics-champions-league-tie-against-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon says he is ‘sticking his neck out’ and backing Brendan Rodgers’ Celtic to beat Lazio in the Champions League on Tuesday.  Celtic are...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN WARNS AGAINST ANOTHER OFF NIGHT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114624</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/brendan-warns-against-another-off-night/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T07:43:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS insists Celtic have a chance against Lazio in Rome tonight – if none of his players sees red. The Hoops’ hopes of progress in Europe are hanging by a thread after three losses and a draw in their ill-fated Champions League quest this time out. The warning signs were flashing after the first [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘WE’LL DEFINITELY HAVE A RIGHT GO,’ SCALES IN RALLYING CALL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114622</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/well-definitely-have-a-right-go-scales-in-rallying-call/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T07:14:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIAM SCALES has played every single minute of Celtic’s Champions League adventure this season. The Republic of Ireland international defender has watched the team concede 12 goals in four games – including the 6-0 mauling in Madrid last time out – and are still looking for their first win in Group E. And as Scales [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['He has grown on me': Barry Ferguson backs Celtic to sign thriving 24-year-old Aberdeen star]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181646</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/barry-ferguson-backs-celtic-to-secure-transfer-of-aberdeen-28-year-old/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Barry Ferguson has backed Brendan Rodgers’ Celtic to sign Aberdeen hitman, Bojan Miovski. The 24-year-old, who has 11 goals in all competitions this season, scored...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HART SICK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114610</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hart-sick/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T06:15:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART must be sick and tired of retrieving the ball from the back of his net when Celtic embark upon the European trail. The 36-year-old 75 rimes-capped England international keeper was helpless when Atletico Madrid ran amok in the Spanish capital three weeks ago as they crammed six goals past him. The Hoops were [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS: MISSION IMPROBABLE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114605</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-mission-improbable/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T06:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS will take charge of Celtic for the 47th time in European competition against Lazio in Rome this evening. The Hoops boss knows he needs to achieve his first win in Champions League Group E after losing three and drawing one while the team have  conceded TWELVE goals in four games with only three in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LAZIO v CELTIC: 5-MINUTE QUIZ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114614</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/lazio-v-celtic-5-minute-quiz/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T05:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEIL LENNON celebrated when Celtic beat Lazio home and away in the Europa League in the space of a fortnight in season 2019/20. On both occasions, the Hoops gaffer had witnessed his side come from behind to win 2-1 to secure famous victories over the Italian aces, the first at Parkhead on October 24 2019 [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE BERTIE AULD: PART FOURTEEN: ‘OLD FIRM LAUGH-IN’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=54024</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-unforgettable-bertie-auld-part-fourteen-old-firm-laugh-in/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T05:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bertie Auld liked nothing better than “strutting his stuff” in front of the fans he always insisted were “the best supporters in the world”. CQN are celebrating the life and incredible times of the Celtic legend in an EXCLUSIVE series with extracts from his best-selling autobiography, ‘A Bhoy Called Bertie’, co-authored by his friend [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serie A club want to sign Celtic player amid contract worry]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45907</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/serie-club-want-celtic-player-contract/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T22:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic fans hope for more quality players arriving there could be a problem with others heading for the exit door. It seems pretty clear that Brendan Rodgers wants to make the size of the squad more manageable over the next couple of transfer windows and departures are expected. But there is a risk of […]
Serie A club want to sign Celtic player amid contract worry - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic set to step up search for new goalkeeper]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181603</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-set-to-step-up-search-for-new-goalkeeper-in-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are set to step up their search for a new goalkeeper in January.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interest in Mathias Kvistgaarden is heating up after Celtic reports]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181495</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/interest-in-mathias-kvistgaarden-is-heating-up-after-celtic-reports/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are set to face competition to sign Mathias Kvistgaarden in January, with clubs across Europe reportedly also interested in the Danish forward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur step up bid to sign Celtic-linked player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45918</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/tottenham-hotspur-bid-sign-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur made a fantastic start to the season under the management of Ange Postecoglou. With Harry Kane leaving the club in the summer for Bayern Munich, most expected them to struggle. Instead, they appeared to be putting up an unlikely title challenge and were sitting atop the Premier League table not too long ago. […]
Tottenham Hotspur step up bid to sign Celtic-linked player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio star Pedro makes it clear what he thinks of Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181592</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/lazio-star-pedro-makes-it-clear-what-he-thinks-of-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T20:54:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio winger Pedro was full of praise for Celtic ahead of tomorrow night's Champions League Group E fixture.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boost in race to sign £11 million Real Madrid player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45914</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/celtic-boost-real-madrid-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to sign a goalkeeper in the near future. It is quite clear that Joe Hart is not the long-term solution between the posts. The Englishman’s performances have been criticised lately. Also, he is set to turn 37 years of age before this season comes to an end. So, while he has done a […]
Celtic boost in race to sign £11 million Real Madrid player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio boss Maurizio Sarri makes fantastic Celtic claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45910</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/lazio-boss-maurizio-sarri-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T18:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By now, Celtic fans have accepted that Brendan Rodgers’ side are most probably not going through or even finishing third in their group in the UEFA Champions League. It would be a positive step to get a win in the competition though. It has been quite some time since the Hoops won at this level. […]
Lazio boss Maurizio Sarri makes fantastic Celtic claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I don't know what he is doing': Chris Sutton isn't happy with one Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181620</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-shares-his-honest-thoughts-on-joe-hart-after-another-questionable-celtic-performance/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T17:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton was critical of Joe Hart for the role he played in Motherwell’s equalising goal against Celtic on Saturday. The Celtic legend was reviewing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo's isolation and creative woes shown in data from Celtic draw with Motherwell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181508</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kyogos-isolation-and-creative-woes-shown-in-data-from-celtic-draw-with-motherwell/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T17:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic suffered a disappointing 1-1 draw with Motherwell on Saturday, and the data reveals that the Hoops were wasteful in front of goal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon makes bold European Celtic prediction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181577</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/neil-lennon-tips-celtic-to-break-european-glass-ceiling/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T16:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic manager Neil Lennon has revealed he believes that Celtic could win another European trophy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maurizio Sarri delivers verdict on Celtic ahead of Lazio Champions League clash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181584</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/maurizio-sarri-delivers-verdict-on-celtic-ahead-of-lazio-champions-league-clash/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T16:21:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maurizio Sarri has shared that he is mindful of the challenge Celtic will present to his Lazio side despite a win in the reverse fixture....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic tipped to go for 28-year-old Premiership striker]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45904</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/celtic-tipped-go-premiership-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T12:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans breathed a sigh of relief as the Rangers dropped points at the weekend against Aberdeen. In fact, it took a late penalty for them to even come out with a draw from the game. That means that the Hoops will maintain their strong position at the top of the Scottish Premiership table. That […]
Celtic tipped to go for 28-year-old Premiership striker - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Mark of Losers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114601</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-mark-of-losers/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T12:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are no longer suffering the emotional trauma from the 90s, that decade has been more than compensated for since the dawning of the new century, but old wounds are still there.  Back then, it was difficult to live with that ‘loser’ feeling.  We knew that our wins were fragile and our ‘greatest’ triumphs often [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BBC pundit suggests one Celtic star ‘doesn’t understand’ Brendan Rodgers’ system]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181541</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/bbc-pundit-suggests-one-celtic-star-doesnt-understand-brendan-rodgers-system/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T11:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Callum Davidson thinks Hyunjun Yang ‘doesn’t understand’ Brendan Rodgers’ system after Celtic dropped points at home to Motherwell on Saturday.  It was a frustrating afternoon...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘He is that big of a talisman’: Celtic tipped to sign 28-yr-old Scotland star after Motherwell draw]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181510</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-tipped-to-sign-28-year-old-scotland-star-who-is-that-big-of-a-talisman/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Stewart has backed Brendan Rodgers’ Celtic to sign Hearts striker Lawrence Shankland after dropped points against Motherwell on Saturday.  When Kyogo Furuhashi isn’t firing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£7.5 million Mathias Kvistgaarden to Celtic transfer update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45900</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/mathias-kvistgaarden-celtic-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T10:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to sign a striker in January. On one hand, we have seen the club struggle for goals in some games this season. When the opposition puts up a resolute defence, the Hoops do not appear to have a lot of answers other than Kyogo, Matt O’Riley or Luis Palma. On the other hand, […]
£7.5 million Mathias Kvistgaarden to Celtic transfer update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROME, SWEET ROME? CCV HOPES FOR ‘A BIT MORE QUALITY’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114599</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rome-sweet-rome-ccv-hopes-for-a-bit-more-quality/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T09:57:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CAMERON CARTER-VICKERS insists it will be EASIER for Celtic against Lazio in Rome tomorrow night that it was in the 1-1 stalemate with Motherwell in Glasgow on Saturday. The USA World Cup centre-back is convinced there will be a lot more space for his team-mates to show their qualities in the Olimpico Stadium than there [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Rangers have won nothing’: Celtic legend Chris Sutton puts Kris Boyd in his place on Sky Sports]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181483</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-legend-chris-sutton-brutally-shuts-down-kris-boyd-on-sky-after-recent-claim/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton put Kris Boyd in his place yesterday following his comments after Celtic thrashed Aberdeen before the international break. Kris Boyd seemingly suggested that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXPLAIN THIS, Mr DALLAS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114587</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/explain-this-mr-dallas/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T08:09:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VAR – and Andrew Dallas – have once again left football fans baffled and bewildered this morning. It’s not just Celtic supporters who will have been left mystified by a decision which presented Rangers with a stoppage-time penalty-kick at Pittodrie as they trailed 1-0 to Aberdeen. Time was running out as a corner-kick was sent [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE BERTIE AULD: PART THIRTEEN: ‘RANGERS DIDN’T KNOW WHAT HIT THEM’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=100291</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-unforgettable-bertie-auld-part-thirteen-rangers-didnt-know-what-hit-them/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T05:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bertie Auld was the most irrepressible performer in Jock Stein’s team of all stars who conquered all before them in the sixties. CQN are celebrating the life and incredible times of the club legend in an EXCLUSIVE series with extracts from his best-selling autobiography, ‘A Bhoy Called Bertie‘, co-authored by his friend and writer [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur have been eyeing Celtic superstar]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45896</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/tottenham-hotspur-eyeing-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T23:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou made the move to Tottenham Hotspur in the summer and it was only a matter of time before the Australian was linked with a reunion with some Celtic players. The manager enjoyed a lot of success at Parkhead, even though he was at the club for just two seasons, and won five trophies […]
Tottenham Hotspur have been eyeing Celtic superstar - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John McGinn claims he spoke to Celtic players about manager]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45890</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/john-mcginn-spoke-celtic-players/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T21:35:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most Celtic fans will remember how the club missed out on the opportunity to sign John McGinn some years back. The Scot grew up supporting the Hoops but a move to Parkhead failed to materialise even though it had looked close and he ended up moving down south to join Aston Villa. McGinn has risen […]
John McGinn claims he spoke to Celtic players about manager - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic must consider signing striker from Premiership rivals]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45886</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-signing-striker-premiership-rivals/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T20:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there is one position where Celtic need to strengthen during the upcoming January transfer window, it is striker. The Hoops have been pretty inconsistent in front of goal this season so far. Of course, there are games when they can go out and score six times. But then, on days they are having a […]
Celtic must consider signing striker from Premiership rivals - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SCOTTISH CUP: CELTIC HOME TO BUCKIE THISTLE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114580</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/scottish-cup-celtic-home-to-buckie-thistle/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T19:58:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC will  face Buckie Thistle at Parkhead in the Scottish Cup fourth round after this evening’s ballot. It will be a first for the Hoops, who have won the competition a record 41 times. They have never before met Buckie in competitive football. Coincidentally, the holders took on Highland opposition in their previous encounter in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend takes dig at Rangers player for diving]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45884</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-legend-rangers-player-diving/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T18:35:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Celtic drew 1-1 against Motherwell, the Rangers were handed a major chance to get back into the title race. All they needed to do was win their games in hand and they would be just three points behind the Hoops in the league table. We have seen the Ibrox side not perform at their […]
Celtic legend takes dig at Rangers player for diving - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Italian media said about Lazio after shock defeat ahead of Champions League clash against Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181462</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-italian-media-said-about-lazio-after-shock-defeat-ahead-of-champions-league-clash-against-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not the result or performance Celtic fans wanted yesterday, especially ahead of a crucial Champions League showdown against Lazio. Let’s be honest, it was deserved...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers blow big chance vs Aberdeen as Celtic end weekend 8 points clear]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181452</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/rangers-blow-big-chance-vs-aberdeen-as-celtic-end-weekend-8-points-clear/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T14:03:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have ended the Scottish Premiership weekend eight points clear of Rangers after the Ibrox club failed to win away to Aberdeen at Pittodrie on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player criticised after draw against Motherwell]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45881</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-player-criticised-draw-motherwell/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T12:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Titles are not decided this early in the season. That has been proven once again. Not too long ago, Celtic were sitting seven points clear at the top of the Premiership table and most fans felt that the league was pretty much in the bag with the Rangers struggling for any kind of form.  It […]
Celtic player criticised after draw against Motherwell - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgio Chiellini makes superb claim about Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45874</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/giorgio-chiellini-claim-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T10:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Giorgio Chiellini is one of the best defenders of all time and he had some pretty positive comments about Celtic Park recently. The 39-year-old spent the majority of his career playing for Juventus and won more silverware there than one should try to count. Overall, he made more […]
Giorgio Chiellini makes superb claim about Celtic Park - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s problem is very clear and needs solving quick]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45870</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/celtic-problem-needs-solving-quick/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T19:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two more dropped points mean that Celtic have well and truly allowed the Rangers to get back into the title race. A lead which once stood at seven points, could be reduced to three if Philippe Clement’s side are able to win their games in hand. And the sad thing is that the Hoops have […]
Celtic’s problem is very clear and needs solving quick - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic problem after draw]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45866</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/brendan-rodgers-celtic-problem-draw/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T18:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was not the result Celtic were looking for, as they dropped two valuable points against Motherwell. David Turnbull’s goal appeared to have won it for the Hoops but the visitors equalised in the 90th minute and it ended 1-1. That means that if the Rangers win their games in hand, the gap will be […]
Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic problem after draw - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hollywood superstar pictured wearing Celtic jersey]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45861</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/hollywood-pictured-wearing-celtic-jersey/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T12:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Celtic have their fair share of famous fans. Rod Stewart is the first name that comes to most people’s minds, one of the best-selling music artists in history. Lewis Capaldi is another popular musician known to support the Hoops. And several A-list celebrities like Gerard Butler, Snoop Dogg, […]
Hollywood superstar pictured wearing Celtic jersey - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic pushing for priority signing in January window]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45859</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/celtic-priority-signing-january-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T09:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s January transfer window is expected to be a busy one. The club might have made nine signings in the summer, seven arriving on a permanent basis and two on loan, but there are still holes in Brendan Rodgers’ squad that need to be filled. On the other hand, there are way too many players […]
Celtic pushing for priority signing in January window - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable source offers Sydney van Hooijdonk to Celtic update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45854</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/reliable-sydney-van-hooijdonk-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T22:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are believed to be on the lookout for a striker in the January transfer window. There might be a few reasons behind that. Firstly, both Kyogo and Oh Hyeon-gyu might be unavailable for a considerable length of time early next year due to the AFC Asian Cup. They are the club’s two options to […]
Reliable source offers Sydney van Hooijdonk to Celtic update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou claims Celtic success gets dismissed]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45852</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/ange-postecoglou-claims-celtic-success/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T21:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has proven to be a major success in the Premier League since swapping Celtic for Tottenham Hotspur. Of course, a lot of fans were not happy to see him depart after just two years at Parkhead. But he has been very respectful about the club even after leaving. And it is hard not […]
Ange Postecoglou claims Celtic success gets dismissed - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>