<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-08-09T04:12:00.514Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic target Gustaf Lagerbielke outshines Carl Starfelt in two areas]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43256</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/08/celtic-gustaf-lagerbielke-carl-starfelt/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T22:34:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carl Starfelt’s exit is still to be finalised but Celtic appear to be moving rapidly with an eye on replacing him in their squad. If rumours are accurate, then it seems as though Brendan Rodgers has his eye on another Swedish centre-back to take his place. There have even been suggestions that a £3 million […]
Celtic target Gustaf Lagerbielke outshines Carl Starfelt in two areas - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Journalist hands summer transfer blow to Celtic fans]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43272</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/08/journalist-hands-transfer-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T21:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a pretty stacked squad at the moment, but they could do with a few reinforcements. Most feel that the club have not properly replaced Jota, who left for Al-Ittihad earlier this summer. On the other hand, Carl Starfelt seems to be headed out as well and the Hoops will need to bring in […]
Journalist hands summer transfer blow to Celtic fans - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic must sign Real Madrid goalkeeper this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43267</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/08/celtic-must-sign-real-madrid-goalkeeper/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T19:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is no secret that Celtic could do with another goalkeeper at this point in time. Joe Hart is the number one for the Hoops at the moment and the Englishman deserves credit for the job that he has done since arriving in the summer of 2021. But at the same time, there are clear […]
Celtic must sign Real Madrid goalkeeper this summer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Furuhashi speaks about the affection shown to him by Celtic supporters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170398</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kyogo-furuhashi-speaks-about-the-affection-shown-to-him-by-celtic-supporters/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Kyogo Furuhashi signed his new contract at Celtic this summer, the supporters were overjoyed at the news. There was a fear that he could...
The post Kyogo Furuhashi speaks about the affection shown to him by Celtic supporters appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["We did some workshops"; Brendan Rodgers on the important relationships being built at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170417</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/we-did-some-workshops-brendan-rodgers-on-the-important-relationships-being-built-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has offered some insight in to some behind-the-scenes work Celtic carried out this summer. It’s been a busy old period for the first-team...
The post "We did some workshops"; Brendan Rodgers on the important relationships being built at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Club official confirms Celtic interest in £3 million player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43264</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/08/club-official-confirms-celtic-interest/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T18:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic must find a replacement for Carl Starfelt. It has become quite clear over the past week that the Swedish centre-back is on his way out of Parkhead. He has been a regular starter for the Hoops for the previous two seasons though and it does not feel like the club have anyone in their […]
Club official confirms Celtic interest in £3 million player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers' next matchday squad could be telling for one Celtic star]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170373</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/brendan-rodgers-next-matchday-squad-could-be-telling-for-one-celtic-star/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that the season is well and truly underway, the Celtic fans will be looking forward to every weekend with more gusto than they did...
The post Brendan Rodgers' next matchday squad could be telling for one Celtic star appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swedish football expert's glowing appraisal of reported Celtic target Gustaf Lagerbielke]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170394</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/swedish-football-experts-glowing-appraisal-of-reported-celtic-target-gustaf-lagerbielke/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s pursuit of Gustaf Lagerbielke is now well and truly underway. With the club reportedly already made an offer for the Swedish defender, it looks...
The post Swedish football expert's glowing appraisal of reported Celtic target Gustaf Lagerbielke appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The key Brendan Rodgers message that has offered fresh hope to unfancied Celtic stars]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170410</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-key-brendan-rodgers-message-that-has-offered-fresh-hope-to-unfancied-celtic-stars/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T16:18:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has been making a key point to his Celtic stars in his initial weeks at the club. Rodgers is firmly back in the...
The post The key Brendan Rodgers message that has offered fresh hope to unfancied Celtic stars appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[History repeats itself at the start of a new season for former Celtic ace Tom Rogic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170401</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/history-repeats-itself-at-the-start-of-a-new-season-for-former-celtic-ace-tom-rogic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T15:13:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic favourite Tom Rogic is still without a club as a brand new season gets underway. The Aussie magician, a modern-day icon at Celtic,...
The post History repeats itself at the start of a new season for former Celtic ace Tom Rogic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Exciting prospects"; Chris Sutton's verdict on two Celtic summer signings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170340</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/exciting-prospects-chris-suttons-verdict-on-two-celtic-summer-signings/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been extremely busy in this summer’s transfer window. With five new faces already added to the squad, we have had fleeting glimpses in...
The post "Exciting prospects"; Chris Sutton's verdict on two Celtic summer signings appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The latest on Celtic pursuit of Gustaf Lagerbielke as Elfsborg chief has his say]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170383</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/the-latest-on-celtics-pursuit-of-gustaf-lagerbielke-as-elfsborg-chief-has-his-say/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More details have emerged about Celtic’s interest in Swedish centre-back Gustaf Lagerbielke. We first heard of the Elfsborg defender on Monday evening, with an Expressen...
The post The latest on Celtic pursuit of Gustaf Lagerbielke as Elfsborg chief has his say appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic make enquiries for two players to replace Carl Starfelt]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43257</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/08/celtic-enquiries-two-players-starfelt/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T12:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This summer transfer window is proving to be a tough one for Celtic. The Hoops have already lost one starter in Jota, with the Portuguese winger leaving for Al-Ittihad last month. And now, the club seem to be on the verge of losing another key player from the Ange Postecoglou era, as Carl Starfelt is […]
Celtic make enquiries for two players to replace Carl Starfelt - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Furuhashi shares story of rallying support from his Celtic teammates after World Cup pain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170367</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kyogo-furuhashi-shares-story-of-rallying-support-from-his-celtic-teammates-after-world-cup-pain/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The story of Kyogo Furuhashi not making Japan’s World Cup squad for Qatar dominated the headlines in Scotland last winter. The Japanese striker was widely...
The post Kyogo Furuhashi shares story of rallying support from his Celtic teammates after World Cup pain appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Backfill defender first]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110825</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/backfill-defender-first/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T11:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers was a bit too relaxed looking when announcing the probable departure of Carl Starfelt this week.  You could interpret this as a sign the ‘news’ was not news to him and that a plan to accommodate was at a mature state. Reports from Sweden yesterday suggest we are interested in Gustaf Lagerbielke (23), [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic make enquiries for two centre-backs as Carl Starfelt exit nears]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170362</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-make-enquiries-for-two-centre-backs-as-carl-starfelt-exit-nears/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T10:58:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have made enquiries for two centre-backs with Carl Starfelt’s departure from the club nearing. The Swedish central-defender is set to join Spanish side Celta...
The post Report: Celtic make enquiries for two centre-backs as Carl Starfelt exit nears appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic man Olivier Ntcham finds new club after unsavoury weekend scenes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170343</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-man-olivier-ntcham-finds-new-club-after-unsavoury-weekend-scenes/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic midfielder Olivier Ntcham has found his next club. The French midfielder departed the Hoops for Swansea City right at the end of the...
The post Former Celtic man Olivier Ntcham finds new club after unsavoury weekend scenes appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confirmed: Match officials announced for Aberdeen v Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170345</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/confirmed-match-officials-announced-for-aberdeen-v-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T09:42:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s opening day 4-2 win over Ross County at Parkhead got Brendan Rodgers’ SPFL campaign off to a winning start at the weekend. A double...
The post Confirmed: Match officials announced for Aberdeen v Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Tuesday August 8: Getting Wind Of Change]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18447</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18447"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T09:29:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a few weeks without the pressure of having to qualify for the UCL, manager Brendan Rodgers seems to be ready to make the changes…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Malph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic eye transfer move for West Ham United striker]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43251</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/08/celtic-transfer-west-ham-united-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T09:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a couple of great options up top right now. Kyogo Furuhashi is the main man for the Hoops, coming off a 34-goal 2022/23 campaign. He has already opened his account this time around with a strike against Ross County on Flag Day. Oh Hyeon-gyu has been impressive as well, as he looks to […]
Celtic eye transfer move for West Ham United striker - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Gustaf Lagerbielke has said about his playing style as Celtic make their move]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170334</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/what-gustaf-lagerbielke-has-said-about-his-playing-style-as-celtic-make-their-move/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s reported interest in Gustaf Lagerbielke will have left the fans reaching for their phones and laptops in a bid to find out more about...
The post What Gustaf Lagerbielke has said about his playing style as Celtic make their move appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIRTHDAY BHOY AT CROSSROADS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110820</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/birthday-bhoy-at-crossroads/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T08:13:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIAM SCALES celebrates his 25th birthday today with his Celtic career at the crossroads. The versatile Republic of Ireland defender admitted he was in the dark about his immediate future at the treble winners, as CQN reported last month. Scales spent all of last season on loan at Aberdeen, coincidentally the Hoops’ Premiership opponents in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin O'Neill comments on Rodgers' Parkhead reception with words of advice to the Celtic boss]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170327</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/martin-oneill-comments-on-rodgers-parkhead-reception-with-words-of-advice-to-the-celtic-boss/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers’ first SPFL fixture since he returned to Celtic was one that was highly anticipated for two reasons. The first is that the fans...
The post Martin O'Neill comments on Rodgers' Parkhead reception with words of advice to the Celtic boss  appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC TREBLE TITLE-WINNER ON LOOK-OUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110813</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-treble-title-winner-on-look-out/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T07:32:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic treble title winner Gary Mackay-Steven is on the look-out for a new club – at the age of 32. The one-time Scotland international winger – capped twice – has been without a club since leaving Hearts at the end of his contract in May. A foot injury forced the tricky, ball-playing forward onto [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jan Aage Fjortoft explains how a Celtic legend helped mould his career]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170307</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/jan-aage-fjortoft-explains-how-celtic-legend-david-hay-moulded-his-career/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan Aage Fjortoft has opened up on how Celtic legend, David Hay, helped to mould his career when he was just a fresh-faced teenager. The...
The post Jan Aage Fjortoft explains how a Celtic legend helped mould his career appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Man of the match; first goal for new club, ex-Celtic youth delights his new manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170301</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/man-of-the-match-first-goal-for-new-club-ex-celtic-youth-delights-his-new-manager/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T06:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic youngster, Ewan Otoo got his season at his new club off to a flyer at the weekend with a Man of the Match...
The post Man of the match; first goal for new club, ex-Celtic youth delights his new manager appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£3m SWEDE ON THE BRINK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110809</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/3m-swede-on-the-brink/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T05:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have made a £3million offer for Swedish international centre-back Gustaf Lagerbielke, according to reports. The 23-year-old Elfsborg defender has been targeted by Brendan Rodgers as a replacement for Carl Starfelt who is expected to seal his exit this week in a £5million move to Celta Vigo. Lagerbielke is seen as one of Sweden’s top prospects [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Champions League side enquire about former Celtic man Kieran Tierney]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170316</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/champions-league-side-enquire-about-former-celtic-man-kieran-tierney/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T05:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A fresh report has linked former Celtic defender Kieran Tierney with a Champions League move. The Scotland international is set to enter European football’s premier...
The post Report: Champions League side enquire about former Celtic man Kieran Tierney appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Carl Starfelt's agent makes Sunday appearance for Celtic's benefit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170304</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/carl-starfelts-agent-makes-sunday-appearance-for-celtics-benefit/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T05:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic want to sign defender Gustaf Lagerbielke and Carl Starfelt’s agent has had a part to play, according to a report. On Monday evening, Swedish...
The post Report: Carl Starfelt's agent makes Sunday appearance for Celtic's benefit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIG YOGI AND LISBON: THE TRUTH (Part Five)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=95307</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/big-yogi-and-lisbon-the-truth-part-five/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-08T04:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE name of John Hughes was missing when Jock Stein named his Celtic line-up for the European Cup Final against Inter Milan in Lisbon on May 25 1967. The giant forward, lovingly known as ‘Yogi’ to his legions of fans, had played in five of the club’s eight ties during their great adventure to propel [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic submit £3 million bid for Carl Starfelt replacement]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43248</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/07/celtic-submit-bid-starfelt-replacement/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T22:34:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As news broke out that Carl Starfelt was set to leave the club this summer, Celtic seem to be wasting no time in trying to find a replacement for him. And it looks like the Hoops could be trying to replace the 28-year-old centre-back this summer with one of his Swedish international teammates. Starfelt has […]
Celtic submit £3 million bid for Carl Starfelt replacement - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player granted permission to complete Parkhead exit]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43243</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/07/celtic-player-permission-parkhead-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T21:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are expected to make a few more additions to Brendan Rodgers’ squad before the summer transfer window slams shut. On the other hand, players are continuing to leave the club as well. Some departures have gone under the radar while others have grabbed the headlines, like Jota leaving for Al-Ittihad. Unfortunately, it looks like […]
Celtic player granted permission to complete Parkhead exit - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic linked with move for Leicester City centre-back]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43238</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/07/celtic-leicester-city-centre-back/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T19:35:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are on the verge of losing one of their starting centre-backs in the form of Carl Starfelt. The Swede has been a nailed-on starter for the club over the past two seasons, playing his part in winning five trophies over that time. His run at Parkhead looks set to come to an end soon […]
Celtic linked with move for Leicester City centre-back - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Early days but recent arrival has made a positive Celtic impression; weekend moment - opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170282</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/early-days-but-maik-nawrocki-has-made-a-positive-celtic-impression-telling-weekend-moment/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maik Nawrocki may only have played 110 minutes for Celtic so far, but we’ve still learned a bit about him. The Polish defender made his...
The post Early days but recent arrival has made a positive Celtic impression; weekend moment - opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic interested in another Manchester City player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43235</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/07/celtic-interested-manchester-city-player-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T18:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quite a few players have made the move from Manchester City to Celtic over the years, either on loan or on a permanent basis. Even this summer, there have been several of the Treble winners’ youngsters, who have been linked with a switch to Parkhead. And now, it looks like it is time to add […]
Celtic interested in another Manchester City player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's early season schedule and 2022 inspiration offers a big opportunity - opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170292</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/celtics-early-season-schedule-and-2022-inspiration-offers-a-big-opportunity/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic won’t have to play two matches per week until the middle of September. With Champions League qualification already in the bag, and a return...
The post Celtic's early season schedule and 2022 inspiration offers a big opportunity - opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Get the whole place buzzing"; Celtic's unseen footage captures class Callum McGregor moment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170288</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/get-the-whole-place-buzzing-celtics-unseen-footage-captures-class-callum-mcgregor-moment/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whoever comes up with these ideas for Celtic should get a pay rise. The club have been heavily involved in giving fans some brilliant social...
The post "Get the whole place buzzing"; Celtic's unseen footage captures class Callum McGregor moment appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An interesting few weeks are ahead for Reo Hatate and Celtic - opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170268</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/an-interesting-few-weeks-are-ahead-for-reo-hatate-and-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It will be interesting to see how things go for both Reo Hatate and Celtic over the coming weeks. The Japan international was a surprise...
The post An interesting few weeks are ahead for Reo Hatate and Celtic - opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton praises 'brave' Brendan Rodgers for Celtic return; addresses weekend fan reception]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170265</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-praises-brave-brendan-rodgers-for-celtic-return-addresses-weekend-fan-reception/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers’ Celtic return was one that came out of the blue for many supporters and one that still touched a raw nerve. Even for...
The post Chris Sutton praises 'brave' Brendan Rodgers for Celtic return; addresses weekend fan reception appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic 'interested' in talented England u21 international]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170249</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-hold-interest-in-talented-manchester-city-youth-prospect/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T13:44:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been listed with a number of clubs in England as holding an interest in young England u21 international, Jason McAtee. At just 20...
The post Report: Celtic 'interested' in talented England u21 international appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic the major contributors as the SPFL release good news from opening weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170248</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-the-major-contributors-as-the-spfl-release-more-good-crowd-news/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were the major contributors as the SPFL released some more good crowd news after the opening weekend of the season. The Premiership, Championship, League...
The post Celtic the major contributors as the SPFL release good news from opening weekend appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BULLY FOR YOU, DAVID]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110806</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/bully-for-you-david/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T13:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAVID TURNBULL celebrated his first start for Celtic in nine months with two goals in the 4-2 opening-day win over Ross County at Parkhead at the weekend. Matt O’Riley is not surprised by the impact of his team-mate who claimed the champions’ first goal of the new campaign with a sweetly-taken penalty-kick in the 17th [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SPFL newcomer's intriguing comments on family link with ex-Celtic hero Artur Boruc]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170235</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/spfl-newcomers-intriguing-comments-on-family-link-with-ex-celtic-hero-artur-boruc/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Max Boruc signed for Hibs earlier this summer, a lot was made in the media about his family link to former Celtic star, Artur...
The post SPFL newcomer's intriguing comments on family link with ex-Celtic hero Artur Boruc appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Champions League picture becomes clearer after Monday draw]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170231</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-champions-league-picture-becomes-clearer-as-qualifying-draw-is-completed/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The draw for UEFA Champions League qualification was concluded on Monday morning, as Celtic continue to watch on. As you’ll know, Celtic have already secured...
The post Celtic Champions League picture becomes clearer after Monday draw appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC 13 SECONDS FROM PERFECT GOAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110801</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-13-seconds-from-perfect-goal/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T12:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BLINK and you might have missed Celtic just failing to claim a contender for Goal of the Season just 86 minutes into the new campaign. The champions were leading 4-1 at the time courtesy of a double from David Turnbull – the first from the penalty spot – and others from Kyogo Furuhashi and Matt [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic keeper assessed after winning debut at new club]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170221</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/conor-hazards-debut-assessed-as-ex-celtic-keeper-gets-off-to-a-winning-start-at-new-club/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic goalkeeper, Conor Hazard, made his debut for Plymouth Argyle this weekend. The Northern Ireland international got off to a winning start and impressed...
The post Ex-Celtic keeper assessed after winning debut at new club appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Celtic require from the final four weeks of the transfer window - opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170224</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/what-celtic-require-from-the-final-four-weeks-of-the-transfer-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T11:44:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The transfer window has just shy of four weeks to run, and Celtic have business to do. The club have signed five new players so...
The post What Celtic require from the final four weeks of the transfer window - opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic goalkeeper completes eventful one-game loan]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43229</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/07/celtic-goalkeeper-one-game-loan/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T11:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a stacked squad at this point in time. Naturally, not everyone is expected to get first-team chances. For some, it is best to leave the club on a permanent basis. On the other hand, for youngsters, loan moves away can be beneficial for their future and help them come to grips with the […]
Celtic goalkeeper completes eventful one-game loan - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo, Maik, Carl]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110800</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kyogo-maik-carl/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T11:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was quite a fascinating weekend in the Scottish Premiership.  Celtic started the action by labouring before taking the lead and moving into cruise control against Ross County.  St Mirren bookended the action by scoring a 95th minute winner at Easter Road.  Motherwell rode their luck to earn a point at Dundee, St Johnstone continued [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New summer signing's absence being felt as former manager makes Celtic admission]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170216</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/maik-nawrockis-absence-being-felt-as-former-manager-makes-celtic-admission/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The signing of Maik Nawrocki this summer already seems like a great piece of business by Brendan Rodgers. The Polish defender already seems to have...
The post New summer signing's absence being felt as former manager makes Celtic admission appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HARTACHE? KEEPER FACES MAKE-OR-BREAK 24 DAYS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110797</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hartache-keeper-faces-make-or-break-24-days/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T09:46:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART has provided a fair bit of ammunition for the snipers who believe he should be replaced as the No.1 Celtic keeper. The 36-year-old 75 times-capped England international was not convincing in the champions’ 4-2 opening-day victory over Ross County at the weekend. Hart will not need CQN or anyone else to emphasise that point. A [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Irony alert as Ibrox figure talks up away fans at Celtic derbies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170205</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/irony-alert-as-ibrox-figure-talks-up-away-fans-at-celtic-derbies/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Bisgrove has amusingly been talking up the importance of away supporters at Celtic vs Rangers matches. The Ibrox chief executive has been in the...
The post Irony alert as Ibrox figure talks up away fans at Celtic derbies appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O'Riley star explains the Kyogo 'adaptation' that Celtic's midfield are exploiting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170202</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/matt-oriley-explains-the-kyogo-tweak-that-celtics-midfield-are-exploiting/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Flag Day opening win for Celtic over Ross County was literally a game of two halves, in the first half! In the opening 20...
The post Matt O'Riley star explains the Kyogo 'adaptation' that Celtic's midfield are exploiting appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O'Riley predicts a big season ahead for rejuvenated Celtic midfielder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170198</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/matt-oriley-predicts-a-big-season-ahead-for-rejuvenated-celtic-midfielder/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Turnbull’s return to a Celtic shirt this preseason and for the SPFL curtain raiser has been a sight for sore eyes for this Hoops...
The post Matt O'Riley predicts a big season ahead for rejuvenated Celtic midfielder appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic plan to replace Carl Starfelt]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43225</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/07/brendan-rodgers-celtic-replace-starfelt/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T08:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past few days, it has become pretty clear that Carl Starfelt will be on his way out of Celtic this summer. The Swede has been a key part of this team since he arrived in 2021 and was a major part of their successes under the management of Ange Postecoglou, winning five out […]
Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic plan to replace Carl Starfelt - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Young Celtic prospect praised despite emergency loan debut defeat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170191</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/young-celtic-prospect-josh-clarke-praised-despite-emergency-loan-debut-defeat/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T07:42:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic got back into the swing of things with their 4-2 win over Ross County at Celtic Park on Flag Day to get the defence...
The post  Young Celtic prospect praised despite emergency loan debut defeat appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HAKSABANOVIC MYSTERY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110792</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/haksabanovic-mystery-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T07:38:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SEAD HAKSABANOVIC was the Celtic matchwinner the last time Ross County featured at Parkhead in November last year. This time around, there was no sign of the Montenegro international winger as the champions claimed an opening-day 4-2 triumph. Haksabanovic, who arrived in a cut-price £1.8million switch from Rubin Kazan in August last year, wasn’t even [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I am grateful"; Celtic star thinks Brendan Rodgers is now playing him in his best position and role]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170187</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/matt-oriley-grateful-brendan-rodgers-is-now-playing-him-in-his-favourite-celtic-position-and-role/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last couple of months, no one has sounded happier with Brendan Rodgers coming into the club than Matt O’Riley and that trend has...
The post "I am grateful"; Celtic star thinks Brendan Rodgers is now playing him in his best position and role appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I NEED TO BE A BIT MORE SELFISH,’ O’RILEY IGNORES PASS MARKS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110788</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-need-to-be-a-bit-more-selfish-oriley-ignores-pass-marks/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T06:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY almost uprooted the net and goalposts with his pulverising piledriver that left Ross County keeper Ross Laidlaw motionless as he sealed Celtic’s opening-day 4-2 triumph. It was an emphatic finish from the midfield mastermind’s so-called weaker foot and was one of the highlights as Brendan Rodgers’ men got their bid for a twelfth [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Monday August 7: Monday Morning Sure Looks Fine]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18443</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18443"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T06:21:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And we’re off.     Scottish football roared back onto the scene over the weekend, and as is usually the case, there were a few…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Malph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What referee told Ross County star about Celtic Park penalty flashpoint]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170182</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/what-referee-nick-walsh-told-ross-county-star-about-celtic-park-penalty-flashpoint/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T06:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ross County forward Simon Murray is convinced he should have had a penalty against Celtic, despite replays showing that he was barely touched by goalkeeper...
The post What referee told Ross County star about Celtic Park penalty flashpoint appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I am happy for him"; Celtic star addresses imminent teammate exit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170177</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/me-carl-and-jota-were-quite-close-matt-oriley-addresses-celtic-transfer-exits/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T05:30:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder Matt O’Riley is experiencing his closest friends leaving the club but reckons change is part of football and has to be embraced. Jota...
The post "I am happy for him"; Celtic star addresses imminent teammate exit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIG YOGI AND LISBON: THE TRUTH (Part Four)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=95194</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/big-yogi-and-lisbon-the-truth-part-four/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T04:45:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOHN ‘YOGI’ HUGHES played in five of Celtic’s eight ties during their great adventure that took Jock Stein’s team to the European Cup Final against Inter Milan in Lisbon on the unforgettable date of May 25 1967. The non-appearance of the iconic Hoops forward has been the subject of conjecture ever since. The goalscoring winger [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou signing linked with Celtic exit already]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43201</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/06/ange-postecoglou-linked-celtic-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T22:40:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As it looks like Carl Starfelt is set to exit from Celtic, there are question marks over who else may be about to make a move away before the summer transfer window closes. One player, in particular, may have to act quickly if he is to secure more playing time with the Hoops or elsewhere. […]
Ange Postecoglou signing linked with Celtic exit already - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports man confirms Serie A club want Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43217</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/06/sky-sports-man-serie-club-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T20:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already lost an incredibly key player in Jota this summer and Carl Starfelt is expected to leave the club this week too. Their departures will have surely weakened the squad and the Hoops need to make sure that they bring in proper replacements. On the other hand, highly-rated youngsters are being linked with […]
Sky Sports man confirms Serie A club want Celtic player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Stewart talks up Celtic's "sign of intent"; what Rodgers is about to remind everyone of]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170165</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/michael-stewart-talks-up-celtics-sign-of-intent-what-rodgers-is-about-to-remind-everyone-of/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been a juggernaut in Scottish football over the last 23 years or so. The club’s domination of Scottish football was kickstarted by Martin...
The post Michael Stewart talks up Celtic's "sign of intent"; what Rodgers is about to remind everyone of appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans unhappy with rumoured Carl Starfelt replacement]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43212</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/06/celtic-fans-carl-starfelt-replacement/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T19:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last two days, it has become pretty clear that Carl Starfelt is on his way out of Celtic Park this summer. One would expect the move to be completed over the coming week or so and Spain seems like his most likely destination at this point in time. The Swedish defender has been […]
Celtic fans unhappy with rumoured Carl Starfelt replacement - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The new Celtic song that got an airing vs Ross County; tune and lyrics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170164</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-new-celtic-song-that-got-an-airing-vs-ross-county-tune-and-lyrics/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T18:40:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New season, new Celtic songs. There was a vibrant atmosphere at Paradise on Saturday for the, what now seems to be annual, Flag Day festivities....
The post The new Celtic song that got an airing vs Ross County; tune and lyrics appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Odin Thiago Holm on the major draw of signing for Celtic; sets sights high]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170155</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/odin-thiago-holm-discusses-one-of-the-reasons-why-he-joined-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New summer signing, Odin Thiago Holm has opened up on one of the reasons he left Norway to come to Glasgow and join Celtic. Holm...
The post Odin Thiago Holm on the major draw of signing for Celtic; sets sights high appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bargain transfer fee named for Carl Starfelt’s Celtic exit]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43209</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/06/transfer-fee-carl-starfelt-celtic-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T17:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carl Starfelt leaving Celtic is a blow for the club without a shadow of a doubt. The Swedish centre-back has often not gotten the credit that he deserves for what he has brought to the table for the Hoops. But no one can deny that he has been a nailed-on starter in the heart of […]
Bargain transfer fee named for Carl Starfelt’s Celtic exit - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shades of 2016 as Brendan Rodgers explains key Celtic decision vs Ross County]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170151</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/shades-of-2016-as-brendan-rodgers-explains-key-celtic-decision-vs-ross-county/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has returned to Celtic and in his first league game has made one of the biggest calls of his second tenure as the...
The post Shades of 2016 as Brendan Rodgers explains key Celtic decision vs Ross County appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton's message to Celtic over Carl Starfelt's imminent exit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170129</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-suttons-message-to-celtic-over-carl-starfelts-imminent-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems like the Carl Starfelt transfer out of the club is one that is going to be concluded over the course of the next...
The post Chris Sutton's message to Celtic over Carl Starfelt's imminent exit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Carl Starfelt wants to leave Celtic this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43204</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/06/carl-starfelt-wants-leave-celtic-summer/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T14:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carl Starfelt seems to be closing in on a Celtic exit this summer. The Swedish centre-back has been a regular starter for the Hoops since arriving in the summer of 2021. But now, it looks like his run at Parkhead might be set to come to an end very soon. A move to Celta Vigo […]
Why Carl Starfelt wants to leave Celtic this summer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BBC pundit explains why Celtic fringe player is set for more appearances under Brendan Rodgers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170143</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/pat-bonner-explains-why-james-forrest-is-set-for-more-celtic-appearances-under-brendan-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Forrest is undoubtedly a legend at Celtic. In a career that has spanned over two decades, Forrest has picked up 22 winners medals at...
The post BBC pundit explains why Celtic fringe player is set for more appearances under Brendan Rodgers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ballpark transfer fee being discussed for Carl Starfelt's Celtic exit; negotiations continue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170132</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/the-ballpark-transfer-fee-being-discussed-for-carl-starfelts-celtic-exit-negotiations-continue/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T12:30:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Carl Starfelt is closing in on a move to Celta Vigo in La Liga and it could all be finalised early this week....
The post The ballpark transfer fee being discussed for Carl Starfelt's Celtic exit; negotiations continue appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The three players that could benefit from Carl Starfelt’s Celtic exit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170125</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-three-players-that-could-benefit-from-carl-starfelts-celtic-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The imminent exit of Carl Starfelt at Celtic is normally would be one that would concern me. Don’t get me wrong, I’m a huge fan...
The post The three players that could benefit from Carl Starfelt’s Celtic exit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Let's be honest"; Matt O'Riley's brilliant show of support to Celtic teammate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170121</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/lets-be-honest-matt-orileys-brilliant-show-of-support-to-celtic-teammate/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Turnbull has enjoyed what looks like a resurgence at Celtic under the new manager, Brendan Rodgers. Having spent a full season in the wilderness...
The post "Let's be honest"; Matt O'Riley's brilliant show of support to Celtic teammate appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I'm surprised": Ex-Celtic hero's verdict on latest transfer update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170102</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/im-surprised-stan-petrovs-verdict-on-celtics-latest-transfer-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T09:42:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Brendan Rodgers confirming that Celtic defender, Carl Starfelt, will leave the club over the next few days, the news would have possibly come as...
The post "I'm surprised": Ex-Celtic hero's verdict on latest transfer update  appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers may need to address one more position for Celtic in the transfer window]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170096</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/brendan-rodgers-may-need-to-address-one-more-position-for-celtic-in-the-transfer-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has already had a busy summer for Celtic in the transfer window. With five new additions already donning the green and white hoops,...
The post Brendan Rodgers may need to address one more position for Celtic in the transfer window appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UNIQUE ANGLE: HIGHLAND FLING ACTION REPLAY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110715</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/unique-angle-highland-fling-action-replay/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T08:54:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE more things change, the more they stay the same. Celtic kicked off the new season yesterday in an identical manner to the way they brought down the curtain on the previous campaign. On June 3 in Glasgow – Hampden to be exact – the Hoops enjoyed a two-goal margin of success in their 3-1 [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic stars head to Instagram after Flag Day win vs Ross County]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170087</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-stars-head-to-instagram-after-flag-day-win-vs-ross-county/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Finally, the season is up and running and the Celtic supporters can got to see their heroes in the flesh. After what seems like an...
The post Celtic stars head to Instagram after Flag Day win vs Ross County appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player set to join Championship side on loan]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43198</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/06/celtic-player-set-join-championship-side/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T08:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One issue that Celtic have faced in recent years is their inability to bring through their most highly-rated youth players into the senior team. Callum McGregor is the only regular starter in the current team, who has come through the ranks at the club. Other than that, Anthony Ralston is the backup right-back while Stephen […]
Celtic player set to join Championship side on loan - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DEAL OR NO DEAL: RODGERS CHALLENGE TO TURNBULL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110706</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/deal-or-no-deal-rodgers-challenge-to-turnbull/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T08:16:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has thrown down the gauntlet to David Turnbull after the comeback Celt’s two-goal performance in the 4-2 win over Ross County yesterday. The 24-year-old midfielder, who made only five starts last season, was in the line-up for the kick-off against the Highlanders and responded with a double, the opener coming from the penalty [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tactical switch, two devastating sides to Kyogo; Celtic share Unique Angle footage of 4-goal win]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170078</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/tactical-switch-two-devastating-sides-to-kyogo-celtic-share-unique-angle-footage-of-opening-win/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T08:11:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new Celtic season is here and everyone is waking up to another joyful day to be a supporter after a pleasing weekend of Scottish...
The post Tactical switch, two devastating sides to Kyogo; Celtic share Unique Angle footage of 4-goal win appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘A CASE OF GIVING YOUR ALL,’ INSISTS COMEBACK CELT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110704</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/a-case-of-giving-your-all-insists-comeback-celt/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T07:54:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAVID TURNBULL set an unwanted Celtic record last season when he made a remarkable TWENTY-EIGHT appearances as a substitute. That’s an all-time high for a Hoops player coming off the bench in a solitary campaign and it is not a landmark the gifted midfielder wants to replicate. Turnbull, in fact, made only five starts, the last in November, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic talent heading to Championship side on loan after impressing in pre-season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170067</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-talent-heading-to-championship-side-on-loan-after-impressing-in-pre-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic talent Ben McPherson is heading to Scottish Championship side Queen’s Park on loan for the season, journalist Alan Nixon has reported this weekend. McPherson...
The post Report: Celtic talent heading to Championship side on loan after impressing in pre-season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["We all have the same agent"; Former Celtic stars helped convince new signing to join Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170060</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/we-all-have-the-same-agent-former-celtic-stars-helped-convince-holm-to-join-bhoys/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Odin Thiago Holm made his competitive debut for Celtic on Saturday and is hoping to become a firm fixture in Brendan Rodgers matchday squad moving...
The post "We all have the same agent"; Former Celtic stars helped convince new signing to join Bhoys appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Serie A side want to sign Celtic talent; Bhoys have big decision to make]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170053</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/serie-a-side-want-to-sign-celtic-talent-rocco-vata-contract-and-agent-situation/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T06:12:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serie A side Torino are showing interest in signing young Celtic talent Rocco Vata. The Sunday Mail [06/08 print edition, page 61] reports that the...
The post Report: Serie A side want to sign Celtic talent; Bhoys have big decision to make appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Impressive performer ready to earn Celtic contract; Rodgers really likes him]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170048</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/david-turnbull-makes-celtic-intentions-clear-with-less-than-12-months-left-on-contract/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T05:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Turnbull is ready to rise to the challenge Brendan Rodgers set to forge a long-term future at Celtic. Turnbull was very impressive on Saturday...
The post Impressive performer ready to earn Celtic contract; Rodgers really likes him appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIG YOGI AND LISBON: THE TRUTH (Part Three)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=95076</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/big-yogi-and-lisbon-the-truth-part-three/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-06T04:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC great John ‘Yogi’ Hughes was missing from Jock Stein’s Lisbon line-up for the history-making triumph on May 25 1967. The non-appearance of the iconic Hoops forward has been the subject of conjecture ever since. Hughes played in five of the eight games leading up to the European Cup Final, but the nearest he got [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Furuhashi makes beautiful claim about Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43153</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/05/kyogo-furuhashi-beautiful-claim-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T23:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic kicked off a new season, Kyogo Furuhashi is back scoring again with a goal in the first match. There were rumours surrounding his future this summer, but the Japanese superstar went on to put them to bed by signing a new contract. Thus, fans would be hoping he is here to stay for […]
Kyogo Furuhashi makes beautiful claim about Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss looking to sign Manchester City midfielder]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43190</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/05/celtic-boss-manchester-city-midfielder/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T21:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already added a couple of midfielders to their ranks this summer in the form of Odin Thiago Holm and Kwon Hyeok-kyu. On top of that, they already had a stacked midfield with players like Callum McGregor, Matt O’Riley, Reo Hatate, Tomoki Iwata and David Turnbull, all expected to be in the mix. That […]
Celtic boss looking to sign Manchester City midfielder - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers fans unhappy as Celtic already lead title race]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43187</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/05/rangers-fans-celtic-title-race/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T20:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is safe to say that the Rangers fans were pretty confident coming into the league season, despite having finished trophyless the last time around. Now, to be fair to them, the club have made more high-profile signings than Celtic this summer till now. But they already find themselves trailing the Hoops by three points, […]
Rangers fans unhappy as Celtic already lead title race - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers addresses David Turnbull's expiring Celtic contract situation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170042</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-addresses-david-turnbulls-expiring-celtic-contract-situation/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T19:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Turnbull looks rejuvenated under Brendan Rodgers at Celtic this summer and he played a starring role in the opening Scottish Premiership victory of the...
The post Brendan Rodgers addresses David Turnbull's expiring Celtic contract situation appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic looking at Manchester City midfielder as summer transfer option]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170033</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-looking-at-manchester-city-midfielder-as-summer-transfer-option/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T18:51:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are showing interest in Manchester City midfielder Tommy Doyle this month, as Brendan Rodgers looks to add more quality to his Bhoys squad. The...
The post Report: Celtic looking at Manchester City midfielder as summer transfer option appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player agrees personal terms to leave this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43182</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/05/celtic-player-agrees-terms-leave-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T18:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already lost one key starter this summer in the form of Jota. And now, it looks like they are set to lose another one. He has been linked with a move away from Parkhead for a while already and now, it looks like Carl Starfelt is pretty much on the verge of leaving […]
Celtic player agrees personal terms to leave this summer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers dropping points already as Celtic end opening day top of Scottish Premiership]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170027</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/rangers-dropping-points-already-as-celtic-end-opening-day-top-of-scottish-premiership/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T18:07:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have started the Scottish Premiership as they ended it in May, top of the table and looking down on the opposition. The Bhoys’ 4-2...
The post Rangers dropping points already as Celtic end opening day top of Scottish Premiership appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and BBC row latest after Saturday events clear up coverage stance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170020</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-and-bbc-row-latest-after-saturday-events-clear-up-coverage-stance/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has become clear Celtic won’t be excluding BBC Scotland from match coverage at Celtic Park, after the broadcaster had a full team at the...
The post Celtic and BBC row latest after Saturday events clear up coverage stance appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic will enter transfer market to replace wantaway star]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170022</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-confirms-celtic-will-enter-transfer-market-to-replace-wantaway-star/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T15:10:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has confirmed Celtic will be in the market for a new defender if Carl Starfelt ends up leaving the Bhoys as expected. The...
The post Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic will enter transfer market to replace wantaway star appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STARFELT’S STRIKING FAREWELL?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110698</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/starfelts-striking-farewell/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T14:50:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CARL STARFELT could have marked his final Celtic appearance at Parkhead with a goal. Unfortunately, for the Swedish central defender the goal was for Ross County, but it didn’t prevent the champions from gaining all three points in a 4-2 victory on Flag Day at Parkhead. Starfelt, who arrived at the club in a £4.2million [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms key Celtic player could leave]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43178</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/05/brendan-rodgers-key-celtic-player-leave/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T14:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were nowhere near perfect on Flag Day. But they were good enough to get a 4-2 win over Ross County and kick off the new league season with a win. David Turnbull got an unexpected start on the day and justified his place in the team with a brace. Kyogo and Matt O’Riley opened […]
Brendan Rodgers confirms key Celtic player could leave - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["There are reasons why"; Rodgers confirms another Celtic regular could leave shortly]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170016</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/there-are-reasons-why-rodgers-confirms-carl-starfelt-celtic-exit-could-happen-quickly/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T14:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bhoys boss Brendan Rodgers has confirmed there’s something in the recent reports linking Carl Starfelt with a move away from Celtic this summer. Various outlets...
The post "There are reasons why"; Rodgers confirms another Celtic regular could leave shortly appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC 4 ROSS COUNTY 2: WELCOME BACK, BRENDAN AND TWO-GOAL TURNBULL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110684</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-4-ross-county-2-welcome-back-brendan-and-two-goal-turnbull/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T13:54:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC 4 ROSS COUNTY 2 COMEBACK Bhoy David Turnbull marked his first start in NINE months with a double and a Man-of-the-Match award as the champions got their assault on the Premiership underway at a rocking Parkhead on Flag Day. The smooth midfielder was given the nod by Brendan Rodgers to start ahead of Reo [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC 4 ROSS COUNTY 2: WELCOME BACK, BRENDAN AND TWO-GOAL TURNBULL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110684</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-4-ross-county-0-welcome-back-brendan-and-two-goal-turnbull/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T13:54:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC 4 ROSS COUNTY 2 COMEBACK Bhoy David Turnbull marked his first start in NINE months with a double and a Man-of-the-Match award as the champions got their assault on the Premiership underway at a rocking Parkhead on Flag Day. The smooth midfielder was given the nod by Brendan Rodgers to start ahead of Reo [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Lighting this place up"; BBC Sportsound and 5Live pundits rave about "superb" Celtic performer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170011</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/bbc-sportsound-and-5live-pundits-rave-about-superb-celtic-performer-vs-ross-county/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T13:51:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have kicked off the Scottish Premiership season in comfortable fashion, taking care of Ross County at Paradise by a 4-2 margin. Goals from David...
The post "Lighting this place up"; BBC Sportsound and 5Live pundits rave about "superb" Celtic performer appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nawrocki verdict, Kyogo's new role; 3 things we learned as Celtic beat Ross County]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169999</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/nawrocki-verdict-kyogos-new-role-3-things-we-learned-as-celtic-beat-ross-county/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T13:29:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic surged to a comfortable 4-2 victory over visitors Ross County on Saturday, getting the season off to a solid start in front of a...
The post Nawrocki verdict, Kyogo's new role; 3 things we learned as Celtic beat Ross County appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: NAWROCKI’S QUICKFIRE DEBUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110680</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-nawrockis-quickfire-debut/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T10:38:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MAIK NAWROCKI will partner comeback Bhoy Cameron Carter-Vickers as the Pole makes his competitive debut when Celtic take on Ross County on Flag Day at Parkhead this afternoon. The 22-year-old centre-back joined from Legia Warsaw in a £4.3million switch and makes a quickfire first appearance for the champions against Malky Mackay’s Highlanders in the 12.30pm [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic v Ross County, GG Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110670</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-ross-county-gg-live-updates/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T10:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 12:30.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic XI confirmed: Midfield surprise, big debut, global TV details, instant reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169996</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-vs-ross-county-confirmed-midfield-surprise-big-debut-global-tv-details-instant-reaction/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T10:21:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manager Brendan Rodgers has confirmed his Celtic team vs Ross County for today’s Scottish Premiership opener at Celtic Park. The full matchday squad is as...
The post Celtic XI confirmed: Midfield surprise, big debut, global TV details, instant reaction appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S CROWNING GLORIES: 5-MINUTE QUIZ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110678</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtics-crowning-glories-5-minute-quiz/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T10:20:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MARTIN O’NEILL guided Celtic to a silverware clean sweep in his managerial debut campaign in 2000/01. The Irishman came in with the force of a hurricane after the Hoops had limped through the previous league season and had been knocked out of the Scottish Cup following the infamous 3-1 home loss to Inverness Caley Thistle. Rookie [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers sends defiant message ahead of Celtic season opener]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169993</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-sends-defiant-message-ahead-of-celtic-season-opener/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T09:48:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers says he’s been ‘belittled and disrespected’ throughout his coaching career, so question marks surrounding his return to the Bhoys are nothing...
The post Brendan Rodgers sends defiant message ahead of Celtic season opener appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC CLEAR-OUT: FOUR DOWN, SIX TO GO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110671</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-clear-out-four-down-six-to-go/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T09:37:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ISMAILA SORO is poised to quit Celtic and join French second tier outfit Valenciennes at the beginning of next week. The £2million midfield misfit, who still has 12 months to run on his contract, is ready to sign for the Ligue 2 club, despite recent links to Israeli top-flight duo Beitar Jerusalem and Hapoel Be’er [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic must try to sign superb Chelsea striker on loan]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43171</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/05/celtic-must-sign-chelsea-striker-loan/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T08:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a couple of very good options at striker right now. Kyogo is coming off a 34-goal season. On the other hand, Oh Hyeon-gyu appears to be finding his feet in Glasgow as well. He scored consistently towards the end of last season and has impressed in pre-season as well. That being said, the […]
Celtic must try to sign superb Chelsea striker on loan - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strongest midfield, potential debuts; Team news and Celtic Predicted XI vs Ross County]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169986</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/strongest-midfield-potential-debuts-team-news-and-celtic-predicted-xi-vs-ross-county/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T08:28:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Football is finally back. Celtic kick-off their Scottish Premiership campaign this Saturday lunchtime with a match against Malky Mackay’s Ross County at Celtic Park. With...
The post Strongest midfield, potential debuts; Team news and Celtic Predicted XI vs Ross County appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: RUNNING SCARED OF RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110668</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-running-scared-of-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T07:45:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OUR chums across the Clyde are running scared of Brendan Rodgers. Actually, terrified might be a more appropriate expression. It’s not exactly outwith the bounds of imagination and expectancy to believe Celtic could present their fans with an early Christmas gift by emerging victorious in the Viaplay League Cup Final at Hampden on Sunday December [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Nothing to hide"; Celtic watch on as SFA address wild Rangers streak and transparency issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169981</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/nothing-to-hide-celtic-watch-on-as-sfa-address-wild-rangers-penalty-streak-and-transparency-issues/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T06:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scottish FA referee John Beaton has described Rangers’ streak of not conceding a penalty in the league as an ‘anomaly’ ahead of the season starting...
The post "Nothing to hide"; Celtic watch on as SFA address wild Rangers streak and transparency issues appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Potential bidding war can only be a good thing for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169976</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/potential-bidding-war-can-only-be-a-good-thing-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T06:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems the interest in Celtic defender Carl Starfelt is pretty intense this month, meaning it may well be the best time to sell the...
The post Potential bidding war can only be a good thing for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pleasing Cameron Carter-Vickers update ahead of Celtic season opener vs Ross County]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169970</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/pleasing-cameron-carter-vickers-update-ahead-of-celtic-season-opener-vs-ross-county/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T05:40:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has been talking up the quality of Cameron Carter-Vickers ahead of Celtic’s opening Scottish Premiership fixture against Ross County. Carter-Vickers was out for...
The post Pleasing Cameron Carter-Vickers update ahead of Celtic season opener vs Ross County appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN IN THE BEGINNING: HOW THE SCOTTISH CUP WAS WON]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110647</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/brendan-in-the-beginning-how-the-scottish-cup-was-won/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T05:03:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS completed an extraordinary clean sweep of Scotland’s silverware when Tom Rogic claimed a stoppage-time winner in the 2-1 Scottish Cup Final triumph over Aberdeen at Hampden on the Saturday afternoon of May 27 2017. The Irishman, in his debut campaign, led the club to an unprecedented 47-game unbeaten sequence against domestic opposition – [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN IN THE BEGINNING: HOW THE LEAGUE CUP WAS WON]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110646</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/brendan-in-the-beginning-how-the-league-cup-was-won/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T05:02:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS guided the Hoops to their 3-0 League Cup Final success over Aberdeen on November 27 2016 with the club achieving historic acclaim at Hampden. The players were hailed as Celtic Centurians after they picked up their 100th piece of major silverware in a thoroughly well-merited and professional manner as they dismantled the Dons. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN IN THE BEGINNING: HOW THE LEAGUE WAS WON]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110643</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/brendan-in-the-beginning-how-the-league-was-won/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T05:01:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TO SAY Celtic romped to the Premiership title in Brendan Rodgers’ debut 2016/17 campaign would be taking understatement to the extreme. The Hoops sealed their sixth successive championship with a rollicking, one-sided 5-0 triumph over Hearts on April 2 2017 at Tynecastle, coincidentally the venue where the league bid kicked off back on August 7 [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN IN THE BEGINNING: BIRTH OF THE INVINCIBLES]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110641</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/brendan-in-the-beginning-birth-of-the-invincibles/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T05:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE Celtic fans among the 16,777 crowd on a sunny afternoon at Tynecastle on August 7 2016 didn’t realise it, but they were witnessing the birth of the team that would be acclaimed as The Invincibles at the end of the season. Brendan Rodgers was taking his bow in a competitive domestic game for the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIG YOGI AND LISBON: THE TRUTH (Part Two)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=95034</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/big-yogi-and-lisbon-the-truth-part-two/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T04:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MYSTERY has surrounded the non-appearance of Celtic great John ‘Yogi’ Hughes from Jock Stein’s Lisbon line-up ever since that memorable, history-making day in the Portuguese capital on May 25 1967. The iconic Hoops star played in five of the eight games leading up to the European Cup Final, but the nearest he got to the action [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘SURE AS GOD, I’VE NOT DONE ANYTHING TO MAKE ME WANT TO WALK OUT THE BACK DOOR’: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Twenty-five)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=94863</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/sure-as-god-ive-not-done-anything-to-make-me-want-to-walk-out-the-back-door-the-tommy-burns-story-part-twenty-five/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-05T04:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE third season of Tommy Burns’ turbulent time in charge of Celtic ended abruptly when he was fired. The Scottish Cup semi-final replay exit against First Division Falkirk on April 23 1997 brought down the curtain on the fans’ favourite dug-out involvement just before the completion of an explosive, topsy-turvy 1996/97 campaign. Burns had returned [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss drops Cameron Carter-Vickers fitness hint]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43167</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/04/celtic-boss-cameron-carter-vickers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T22:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the major talking points ahead of Celtic’s Premiership opener against Ross County this weekend is the fitness status of Cameron Carter-Vickers. The American made a somewhat unexpected return to the pitch, as Brendan Rodgers started him in the final pre-season friendly against Athletic Bilbao. Carter-Vickers might not have played a game in months, […]
Celtic boss drops Cameron Carter-Vickers fitness hint - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player agrees to join Ligue 2 club this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43163</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/04/celtic-player-agrees-ligue-2-club/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T21:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are quite a few players at Celtic right now, who are not expected to be contending for first-team minutes moving forward. For them, leaving the club this summer might be the best step. And it remains to be seen if exits end up transpiring before the ongoing transfer window slams shut. One player who […]
Celtic player agrees to join Ligue 2 club this summer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flag day tifos prepared for both ends of Celtic Park on Saturday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169955</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/flag-day-tifos-prepared-for-both-ends-of-celtic-park-on-saturday/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T20:46:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We may not be treated to a full-stadium tifo display for tomorrow’s Scottish Premiership opener between Celtic and Ross County at Paradise, but a vibrant...
The post Flag day tifos prepared for both ends of Celtic Park on Saturday appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BBC release on-air statement as Celtic shut out continues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169952</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/bbc-release-on-air-statement-as-celtic-shut-out-continues/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T19:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BBC Scotland are still being refused access to Celtic press conferences, a statement read out on Reporting Scotland has confirmed. The broadcaster were famously shut...
The post BBC release on-air statement as Celtic shut out continues appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon’s son signs for Celtic’s Premiership rivals]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43160</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/04/neil-lennon-son-signs-celtic-premiership/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T19:32:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The manner in which Neil Lennon’s run as Celtic manager ended up disappointing, to say the least. With 10IAR up for grabs, the Hoops’ 2020/21 campaign went completely off the tracks. They ended up finishing trophyless and 25 points behind the Rangers in the league. And the Northern Irish manager would walk away in the […]
Neil Lennon’s son signs for Celtic’s Premiership rivals - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I don't want to say too much"; McGregor and Rodgers on tactical changes coming to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169939</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-dont-want-to-say-too-much-mcgregor-and-rodgers-on-tactical-changes-coming-to-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T19:15:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Both manager Brendan Rodgers and Callum McGregor have been discussing the tactical switches coming to Celtic for the new season. The Scottish Premiership champions start...
The post "I don't want to say too much"; McGregor and Rodgers on tactical changes coming to Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers – Down to Business]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58221</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/brendan-rodgers-down-to-business/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T19:08:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s board of directors didn’t spend too much time deliberating over a successor to Ange Postecoglou and it was no surprise that they turned to Brendan Rogers as he was free after leaving Leicester City. Not everyone was happy with this appointment and I suppose I can understand this in that many people feel […]
The post Brendan Rodgers – Down to Business appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer insider hints at marquee signing for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43156</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/04/transfer-insider-marquee-signing-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T18:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic find themselves in a good position right now. They are looking to defend the domestic treble this season. On top of that, Brendan Rodgers’ side will surely want to make their presence felt in the UEFA Champions League as well. Overall, they have a very solid squad and not much need for reinforcements. There […]
Transfer insider hints at marquee signing for Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic hero's son makes big career breakthrough; could play the Hoops this season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169944</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-heros-son-makes-big-career-breakthrough-could-play-the-hoops-this-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T17:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gallagher Lennon — the son of Hoops hero Neil — could play at Celtic Park this season. That’s because he has signed a deal with...
The post Report: Celtic hero's son makes big career breakthrough; could play the Hoops this season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player posts back to work message but his future isn't at the club]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169931</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/out-of-favour-midfielder-posts-back-to-work-message-but-his-future-wont-be-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player Ismaila Soro has posted a back to work message. The out-of-favour midfielder seems to have been given extra time off this summer, judging...
The post Celtic player posts back to work message but his future isn't at the club appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>