<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-12-12T16:12:47.377Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A team with a hunted look to them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115267</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/a-team-with-a-hunted-look-to-them/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T12:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a bad defeat, would you rather a difficult game against a Champions League team at Celtic Park, or an awkward visit to a Premiership side playing 10 men behind the ball?  Neither seems a great prospect, but in a tight league race, the latter is definitely not a desired option. A big performance and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS PURSUES PERSONAL TREBLE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115256</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-pursues-personal-treble/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T09:21:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is searching for a personal treble when Celtic face Feyenoord at Parkhead tomorrow night. Remarkably, the Irishman has won only TWO games in the Champions League in his managerial career at the Hoops and Liverpool. Rodgers has endured an x-certificate excursion through Europe’s elite competition with an alarming sequence that shows a meagre two wins, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘A year ago he was gone’: Pat Bonner makes his feelings clear on Celtic star who started v Killie]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183244</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/pat-bonner-delivers-honest-verdict-on-mikey-johnston-12-months-after-he-was-gone-from-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was an afternoon to forget for Celtic on Sunday at Kilmarnock, with not a single player able to hold their head high. In recent...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC RETURN? ‘MY TIME HAS BEEN, IT’S GONE,’ INSISTS BROONY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115252</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-return-my-time-has-been-its-gone-insists-broony/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T08:12:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SCOTT BROWN insists his Celtic past would not prevent him from managing another club in Scotland. The Hoops legend won a remarkable TWENTY-TWO honours in his 14 glorious years at Parkhead and has been linked with a return – if first-team coach Harry Kewell quits for the manager’s role at Ange Postecoglou’s former J-League side [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I have seen him live': Neil Lennon tips Celtic to secure the transfer of 'really good player']]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183222</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/neil-lennon-delivers-a-defiant-message-about-celtics-transfer-links-with-aberdeens-bojan-miovski/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have some big calls to make ahead of the January transfer window opening. Not only are the Celtic fans expecting high-quality players to be...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE BERTIE AULD: PART TWENTY-EIGHT: ‘BIG TG – THE BEST IN THE WORLD’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=45946</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-unforgettable-bertie-auld-part-twenty-eight-big-tg-the-best-in-the-world/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T05:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bertie Auld was just one of Jock Stein’s diamonds who sparkled so brilliantly in the all-star squad of the sixties. CQN are celebrating the life and incredible times of the Celtic legend in an EXCLUSIVE series with extracts from his best-selling autobiography, ‘A Bhoy Called Bertie‘, co-authored by his friend and writer Alex Gordon. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Celtic fans don't rate him highly': Andy Walker delivers critical eye on 24-year-old Bhoys star]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183204</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/andy-walker-names-celtic-player-who-fans-dont-rate-highly-amid-brendan-rodgers-comments/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been a challenging few weeks for Celtic after indifferent performances, which was topped off by losing to Kilmarnock on Sunday.  One man who...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['It's tough': Scott Brown and James McFadden sympathise with Celtic 26-year-old]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183189</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/scott-brown-and-james-mcfadden-deliver-honest-verdict-on-liverpool-loanee-nat-phillips-after-celtic-defeat/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This Nat Phillips loan spell from Liverpool isn’t going the way Celtic or the player himself wanted.  The 26-year-old joined Celtic in the summer on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic 7-0 Spartans: Celtic hit magnificent seven as The Spartans are thrashed]]></title>
        <id>https://celticunderground.net/?p=6702</id>
        <link href="http://celticunderground.net/celtic-7-0-spartans-celtic-hit-magnificent-seven-as-the-spartans-are-thrashed/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T18:31:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a stalemate at halftime, The Celts managed seven second half goals to take all the points in their final home match of the year. Goals from Gallacher, Smith, Goldie, Barclais, Agnew and a Caitlin Hayes double kept Celtic one point behind league leaders Rangers, who won 5-0 at Motherwell. Here are some of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ethan Barlow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Tremendous': Pundit blown away by Celtic player who has a 'rare' quality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183171</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/pundit-states-what-is-rare-about-celtic-captain-callum-mcgregor/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor has been ‘Mr Consistent’ for Celtic over the years and is a key player for the club. That fresh-faced youngster, who played alongside...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['For sure': Scott Brown sends clear message on Celtic defeat, states what Brendan Rodgers will do]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183154</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/scott-brown-delivers-verdict-as-celtic-suffer-kilmarnock-defeat-states-what-brendan-rodgers-will-do/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Brown was pretty bullish about Celtic after the 2-1 defeat to Kilmarnock on Sunday. Whilst on paper, it was only the first league defeat...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['That is something you haven't seen in a long time': Andy Walker shocked by Celtic transfer rumour]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183139</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/andy-walker-reacts-to-suggestion-celtic-might-have-to-pay-brondby-8-5m-for-mathias-kvistgaarden/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The disappointment of Kilmarnock is only going to further engulf the flames within the Celtic fanbase for more quality to be added in the January...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC INVINCIBLE IN BOSS LINK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115241</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-invincible-in-boss-link/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T12:44:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC Invincible Scott Brown could be set for a return to the dug-out – just over three months after leaving Fleetwood Town. The Hoops great, who was Brendan Rodgers’ onfield leader during the memorable unbeaten season of 2016/17 that brought in a silverware treble, has been linked with Queen’s Park. The ambitious Championship side are [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic suffer inexplicable collapse]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115232</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-suffer-inexplicable-collapse/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T12:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At halftime during our game at Kilmarnock yesterday, I said, “This is the best we have played in weeks”.  The only concern was that we were only the single goal ahead.  What transpired throughout the second half is inexplicable. Kilmarnock pressed Celtic high up the field for the entire game, a refreshing change to the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I don’t think anyone would stand in his way’: Pundit thinks Celtic man could leave amid rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183115</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/andy-walker-delivers-verdict-on-harry-kewells-celtic-future-amid-yokohama-f-marinos-interest/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andy Walker thinks Harry Kewell might be heading out of Celtic amid interest in his coaching services. The links tie in with Ange Postecoglou’s former...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NINETEEN DEVASTATING SECONDS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115233</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/nineteen-devastating-seconds/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T10:39:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ALISTAIR JOHNSTON and Celtic paid a heavy price for an aimless delivery into the Kilmarnock box at Rugby Park yesterday. The encounter was stalemated at 1-1 in the 87th minute when the Hoops right-back was presented with a wonderful opportunity to carve an opening in the home side’s penalty area. The Canadian World Cup defender [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMAZING STATS: BRENDAN’S KILLING FIELDS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115206</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/amazing-stats-brendans-killing-fields/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T08:52:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has now lost FOUR times at Rugby Park over his two spells as Celtic manager. Remarkably, the 50-year-old Irishman has only sampled defeat to Scottish opposition at four other grounds – Tynecastle (twice), Easter Road (twice), Ibrox (once) and Parkhead (once). Rodgers, of course, steered the Hoops to a phenomenal domestic silverware clean [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ally McCoist reacts to Celtic defeat, states what is ’strange’ about upcoming Rangers game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183095</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/ally-mccoist-reacts-to-celtic-defeat-states-what-is-strange-about-upcoming-rangers-game/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The pressure has just intensified on Brendan Rodgers and Celtic after that defeat to Kilmarnock on Sunday. Chris Sutton didn’t hold back on his criticism...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘BULLIED’, ‘SLOPPY’, ‘WE CAN’T REALLY MAKE EXCUSES’: O’RILEY OPENS UP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115204</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/bullied-sloppy-we-cant-really-make-excuses-oriley-opens-up/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T07:10:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY didn’t bother searching for excuses after Celtic’s lamentable second-half performance at Rugby Park. The stylish midfielder shot the champions into the lead with his ninth strike of the season, but an alarmingly feeble display saw them outfought by Kilmarnock as they surrendered two goals and also their unbeaten Premiership record. The Hoops got lost [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE BERTIE AULD: PART TWENTY-SEVEN: ‘YES, I THINK THERE WAS A BIT OF BIAS AGAINST CELTIC’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=85261</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-unforgettable-bertie-auld-part-twenty-seven-yes-i-think-there-was-a-bit-of-bias-against-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T05:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bertie Auld was pivotal to Celtic’s overwhelming success at Celtic after Jock Stein has returned to Parkhead in March 1965. CQN are celebrating the life and incredible times of the club legend in an EXCLUSIVE series with extracts from his best-selling autobiography, ‘A Bhoy Called Bertie‘, co-authored by his friend and writer Alex Gordon. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Fantastic’: Scott Brown praises Celtic duo amid defeat to Kilmarnock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183076</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/what-scott-brown-said-about-callum-mcgregor-and-matt-oriley-during-celtic-defeat-at-kilmarnock/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T20:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There wasn’t much, if anything, for Celtic to cheer about as Brendan Rodgers suffered his first league defeat since returning to the club at Kilmarnock...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Brendan Rodgers spoke about in Celtic dressing room after defeat to Kilmarnock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183074</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/what-brendan-rodgers-and-celtic-players-spoke-about-in-dressing-room-after-defeat-to-kilmarnock/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T19:52:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s first Scottish Premiership defeat of the season was a sore one to take. The Bhoys were not good enough in Ayrshire on Sunday and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The latest on Cameron Carter-Vickers Celtic injury after Nat Phillips disappoints vs Kilmarnock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183071</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-latest-on-cameron-carter-vickers-celtic-injury-after-nat-phillips-disappoints-vs-kilmarnock/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T19:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cameron Carter-Vickers didn’t make the starting line-up for Celtic’s trip to Kilmarnock on Sunday with Brendan Rodgers instead opting to play Nat Phillips. Carter-Vickers was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘WE DIDN’T RESPOND,’ ADMITS RODGERS AFTER DISMAL LOSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115162</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/we-didnt-respond-admits-rodgers-after-dismal-loss/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T16:21:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS accepted Celtic had only themselves to blame for their dismal 2-1 loss against Kilmarnock at rain lashed Rugby Park. The champions, leading at the interval, didn’t respond to the challenge of Derek McInnes’ side in the second period and meekly surrendered to their first league defeat of the campaign at the same venue where [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Brown and Chris Sutton shut down Kris Boyd's bizarre Celtic vs Kilmarnock penalty claim]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183043</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/scott-brown-and-chris-sutton-shut-down-kris-boyds-bizarre-celtic-vs-kilmarnock-penalty-claim/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Brown was quick to shut down Kris Boyd after he questioned why Kilmarnock weren’t awarded a penalty in the first half of their clash...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports pundit doesn't hold back with scathing summation of Celtic vs Kilmarnock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183066</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/chris-sutton-doesnt-hold-back-with-scathing-verdict-on-celtic-vs-kilmarnock/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T15:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker Chris Sutton has declared that the second-half performance vs Kilmarnock on Sunday was one of the worst he’s seen from the Bhoys....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers reacts to dismal Celtic display vs Kilmarnock and first league defeat of season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183061</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-reacts-to-dismal-celtic-display-vs-kilmarnock-and-first-league-defeat-of-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T14:33:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has been giving his reaction to a very poor afternoon for Celtic after losing 2-1 to Kilmarnock at Rugby Park. Celtic found themselves...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KILMARNOCK 2 CELTIC 1: BHOYS IN BLUNDERLAND]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115152</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kilmarnock-2-celtic-1-bhoys-in-blunderland/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T14:20:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KILMARNOCK 2 CELTIC 1  CARELESS Celtic collapsed to a shocker of a defeat after an alarming and absymal second-half performance against fired-up Kilmarnock at Rugby Park this afternoon. The champions got lost in a blunderland as they threw away a first-half advantage to present the points to the Ayrshire club after they failed to match [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kilmarnock v Celtic, GG Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115150</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kilmarnock-v-celtic-gg-live-updates/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T11:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 12.00.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: JOHNSTON, PHILLIPS IN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115110</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-johnston-phillips-in/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T10:53:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has given the nod to Nat Phillips to start in central defence as the Celtic boss takes no risks with Cameron Carter-Vickers on Kilmarnock’s plastic pitch at Rugby Park in today’s noon showdown. Mikey Johnston gets another opportunity to impress the Hoops gaffer with evergreen James Forrest on the substitutes’ bench. South Korean [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Kyogo call: Celtic XI confirmed, one change, global TV details, instant reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183039</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-vs-kilmarnock-confirmed-kyogo-call-one-change-global-tv-details-instant-reaction/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T10:53:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manager Brendan Rodgers has named his Celtic team vs Kilmarnock for today’s Scottish Premiership clash at Rugby Park. The full match squad is as follows:...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHILLIPS’ £7.3m PUZZLER]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115145</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/phillips-7-3m-puzzler/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T10:17:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NAT PHILLIPS is poised to line up alongside Liam Scales against Kilmarnock in today’s noon kick-off at Rugby Park. Brendan Rodgers is unlikely to take a risk with Cameron Carter-Vickers on the Ayrshire club’s articial surface after the USA World Cup defender was kept in at the interval in the 4-1 midweek win over Hibs [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I’M TRYING TO TAKE EVERY STEP I CAN,’ JOHNSTON’S RESPONSE TO RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115142</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/im-trying-to-take-every-step-i-can-johnstons-response-to-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T09:32:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DETERMINED Mikey Johnston is a man on a mission as he aims to show Brendan Rodgers he has a future at Celtic. The manager threw down the gauntlet to the 24-year-old winger when he insisted the Republic of Ireland international “needed to do more” after his first start in the top side in 22 months [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['He is really hungry': Andy Walker backs 22-year-old to start for Celtic at Kilmarnock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183018</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/andy-walker-backs-22-year-old-to-start-for-celtic-at-kilmarnock-says-he-is-really-hungry/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Life isn’t easy when you are playing as a back-up striker, but Hyeongyu Oh has always remained grounded and now he is getting his rewards....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I can see him playing for Celtic': Brendan Rodgers tipped to sign top-flight's team 'best player']]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183000</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-tipped-to-sign-24-year-old-who-has-more-goals-than-kyogo-furuhashi-this-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That January transfer window door is set to open in less than a month and there is talk of Celtic looking to be busy.  One...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KILMARNOCK v CELTIC: 5-MINUTE QUIZ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115100</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kilmarnock-v-celtic-5-minute-quiz-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T06:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS suffered his first domestic Cup defeat as Celtic manager at the 25th hurdle against Kilmarnock in the Viaplay Cup at Rugby Park in August. An off-colour Hoops side, with new Bhoys Maik Nawrocki, Gustaf Lagerbielke, Odin Holm and Yang Hyun-jun making early appearances after their summer arrivals, just never got started against the home [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE BERTIE AULD: PART TWENTY-SIX: ‘BLAME GAME IN MILAN’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=71524</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-unforgettable-bertie-auld-part-twenty-six-blame-game-in-milan/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T05:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bertie Auld was a player possessed when he turned on the magic in Jock Stein’s team of all-stars in the sixties. CQN are celebrating the life and incredible times of the Celtic legend in an EXCLUSIVE series with extracts from his best-selling autobiography, ‘A Bhoy Called Bertie‘, co-authored by his friend and writer Alex [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The big money on the line for Celtic vs Feyenoord on Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=182995</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-big-money-on-the-line-for-celtic-vs-feyenoord-on-wednesday/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T21:48:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feyenoord manager Arne Slot has refuted claims that his upcoming match against Celtic is meaningless, pointing out it’s worth a lot of money for both...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic star in line to make return from career-threatening injury against the Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=182990</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-star-in-line-to-make-return-from-career-threatening-injury-against-the-bhoys/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T20:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic winger Gary Mackay-Steven is on the brink of a return from injury that has kept him out of action for over a year...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers' judgement on Nat Phillips loan as Liverpool return looms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=182985</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-verdict-on-nat-phillips-celtic-loan-as-liverpool-return-looms/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T19:49:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers says Nat Phillips has been “fantastic” for the Bhoys since arriving on loan, despite not getting much game time in green...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers delivers update on Celtic transfer ins and outs this January as Miovski pops up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=182980</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-delivers-update-on-celtic-transfer-ins-and-outs-this-january-as-miovski-pops-up/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T18:36:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers wouldn’t be drawn on speculation linking Celtic to Bojan Miovski this January but has stated he wants the club to get their business...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star speaks out against assumption on Rodgers tactics after Ange Postecoglou exit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=182975</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-star-speaks-out-against-assumption-on-rodgers-tactics-after-ange-postecoglou-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T17:51:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Greg Taylor reckons the tactical instructions given to him aren’t all that different to when Ange Postecoglou was at the club, despite a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's Sunday task after Saturday Scottish Premiership results]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=182971</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtics-sunday-task-after-saturday-scottish-premiership-results/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T17:03:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will be playing to restore an eight-point advantage at the top of the Scottish Premiership tomorrow after Saturday afternoon’s results. Brendan Rodgers’ Bhoys return...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘UNDER NO ILLUSIONS,’ TAYLOR WARNS OF KILLIE THREAT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115131</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/under-no-illusions-taylor-warns-of-killie-threat/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T10:57:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC continue the countdown to the winter break with tomorrow’s tricky trip to Rugby Park, the venue of their only domestic loss this season. Brendan Rodgers’ men take on their Viaplay League Cup conquerors Kilmarnock in the High Noon shoot-out in the first of seven fixtures before the curtain comes down on the first half [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHY RODGERS MUST TEAM UP KYOGO AND OH: SUTTON’S VERDICT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115125</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/why-rodgers-must-team-up-kyogo-and-oh-suttons-verdict/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T08:43:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CHRIS SUTTON has urged Brendan Rodgers to team up Kyogo Furuhashi and Oh Hyeon-gyu against Kilmarnock tomorrow. The Hoops boss’ usual formation has one up front, almost exclusively the prolific Japanese striker, but the team’s former goal hero believes the South Korean could also get the nod to play on the “monstrosity” of a pitch [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S CATHOLIC HERITAGE]]></title>
        <id>http://celticunderground.net/?p=6698</id>
        <link href="http://celticunderground.net/celtics-catholic-heritage/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T08:28:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Celtic supporting acquaintance of mine once told me the story of how he was talking to a work mate in England. His friend told him he had decided to be a Chelsea fan at the age of 10, after watching them defeat Leeds in the 1970 FA cup final on TV. A good choice […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>St Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: RUTHLESS RODGERS AND LESSONS FROM THE PAST]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115112</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-ruthless-rodgers-and-lessons-from-the-past/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T06:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JIMMY JOHNSTONE’S glittering career stalled in season 1974/75, but, at the age of 30, most onlookers were convinced he still had a lot to offer Celtic. Jock Stein didn’t agree and handed a P45 to the little showman. It mattered not a jot the mercurial genius had illuminated the east end of Glasgow and various other [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE BERTIE AULD: PART TWENTY-FIVE: ‘OLE AND ADIOS IN MADRID’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=72897</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-unforgettable-bertie-auld-part-twenty-five-ole-and-adios-in-madrid/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T05:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bertie Auld was a mastermind in the Celtic midfield as Jock Stein’s all-stars illuminated football in the sixties and early seventies. CQN are celebrating the life and incredible times of the club legend in an EXCLUSIVE series with extracts from his best-selling autobiography, ‘A Bhoy Called Bertie‘, co-authored by his friend and writer Alex [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stiff asking price set for Celtic transfer target as 'game' develops between clubs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=182965</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/stiff-asking-price-set-for-celtic-striker-target/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T21:10:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will have to negotiate well to bring Mathias Kvistgaarden to the club in January with reports in Denmark suggesting Brondby will set a high...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 9 prime candidates to leave Celtic in January after Brendan Rodgers comments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=182962</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/the-9-prime-candidates-to-leave-celtic-in-january-after-brendan-rodgers-comments/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T19:43:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has made no secret of the fact he feels the Celtic squad is bloated and far too large for his needs. In comments...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers hints barely used Celtic player is about to feature much more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=182957</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-noises-coming-out-of-celtic-training-about-tomoki-iwata-bode-well/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T18:33:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers looks set to give Tomoki Iwata more starting opportunities at Celtic after being left impressed by his performances in training and matches. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Derek McInnes says he has "a real concern" ahead of Celtic as crisis hits Kilmarnock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=182952</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/derek-mcinnes-says-he-has-a-real-concern-ahead-of-celtic-as-injury-crisis-hits-kilmarnock/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T17:54:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Derek McInnes says he could be missing up to six Kilmarnock players for the visit of Celtic on Sunday, noting that his midfield is looking...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["He's not a baby"; Brendan Rodgers' honest message to Celtic star hoping for more starts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=182947</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-gets-honest-with-mikey-johnston-after-lennoxtown-chat/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T17:16:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has spoken extensively about the situation of winger Mikey Johnston today after criticising his performance against Hibernian on Wednesday night. Rodgers...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has one eye on the weather forecast ahead of Celtic trip to Kilmarnock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=182944</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-has-one-eye-on-the-weather-forecast-ahead-of-celtic-trip-to-kilmarnock/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T16:44:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers is expecting a stiff challenge from Kilmarnock in this weekend’s Scottish Premiership clash at Rugby Park. Derek McInnes’ Killie side remain...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers backs potential SPFL rule change]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=182941</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-backs-potential-spfl-rule-change/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T16:13:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has welcomed the possibility of the SPFL enforcing the use of grass pitches in the Scottish Premiership. It was reported by...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic team news ahead of Kilmarnock as Brendan Rodgers confirms key player is a doubt]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=182931</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-news-vs-kilmarnock-as-bhoys-left-waiting-on-cameron-carter-vickers-issue/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T15:42:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are waiting on the availability of defender Cameron Carter-Vickers after he was substituted at half-time during Wednesday night’s 4-1 win over Hibernian. Carter-Vickers was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALL-CHANGE CELTS: RODGERS WARNS RIVALS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115115</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/all-change-celts-rodgers-warns-rivals/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T15:38:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has warned Kilmarnock they will face a different Celtic team on Sunday from the one they dumped out of the Viaplay League Cup in August. The Irishman suffered his first domestic Cup defeat in 25 games as Hoops gaffer when they lost 1-0 at Rugby Park in only his third game since returning [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Many reasons not to play Carter-Vickers on Sunday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115109</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/many-reasons-not-to-play-carter-vickers-on-sunday/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cameron Carter-Vickers was rested for the second half against Hibs due to a tight hamstring.  Were we not two goals ahead, he might well have played on, but there was no point taking chances.  The same argument holds for Kilmarnock on Sunday. Nat Phillips is more than capable of stepping into the defensive leadership role.  [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘IDEAL FOOTBALLER’: BRENDAN HAILS CELTIC’S MAN FOR ALL REASONS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115106</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ideal-footballer-brendan-hails-celtics-man-for-all-reasons/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T08:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CALLUM McGREGOR has emerged as Celtic’s man for all reasons as he continues to earn praise from Brendan Rodgers. The second time-around manager is just as convinced of his skipper’s all-round talents today as he was when he first arrived at the club in May 2016. The sheer versatility of the 30-year-old Glaswegian has Rodgers [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THANKS FOR THE MEMORY, FRASER]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=68730</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/thanks-for-the-memory-fraser/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T06:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EUPHORIA will never fade from the recollection of Fraser Forster’s majestic and triumphant goalkeeping exhibition at Hampden on Sunday, December 8 2019. The awesome shotstopper was simply unbeatable as he stubbornly refused to yield a solitary goal in the victory that earned Celtic their tenth successive domestic honour. Forster dived, twisted, blocked, parried and held [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE BERTIE AULD: PART TWENTY-FOUR: ‘VICTORY FOR THE GOOD GUYS’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=100635</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-unforgettable-bertie-auld-part-twenty-four-victory-for-the-good-guys/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T05:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bertie Auld was simply outstanding as he turned in a spellbinding performance on the biggest day in Celtic’s history. CQN are celebrating the life and incredible times of the club legend in an EXCLUSIVE series with extracts from his best-selling autobiography, ‘A Bhoy Called Bertie‘, co-authored by his friend and writer Alex Gordon. The [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic want to sign £4 million-rated player in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45945</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-4-million-player-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T23:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The defeat at the hands of Lazio was further proof of Celtic’s need to strengthen in the January transfer window. The club might have brought in nine new faces in the summer but a lot of people feel that the team has taken a step back since last season, when they breezed past the competition […]
Celtic want to sign £4 million-rated player in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers sends clear message Celtic board must not ignore]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45941</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/brendan-rodgers-message-celtic-board/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T21:35:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s fate in Europe for this season is sealed after their 2-0 defeat at the hands of Lazio. The result means that the Hoops are guaranteed to finish bottom of their group in the UEFA Champions League. That also means that they will not be dropping down to the Europa League, something that should have […]
Brendan Rodgers sends clear message Celtic board must not ignore - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton publicly criticises Celtic after loss to Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45938</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/chris-sutton-celtic-loss-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T20:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic lost 2-0 away in Rome to Lazio. The Hoops were in the match for a long time before Ciro Immobile came off the bench to score a brace and put the game to bed. The result means that not only are Brendan Rodgers’ side out of the Champions League following the group stages but […]
Chris Sutton publicly criticises Celtic after loss to Lazio - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed £7 million Jeremie Frimpong windfall news]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45933</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-jeremie-frimpong-windfall-news/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremie Frimpong’s rise at Bayer Leverkusen has been fascinating, to say the least. The Dutchman had shown a lot of quality going forward at Celtic as well but not many could have foreseen him becoming one of the most prolific wingbacks in Europe just a few years later. That is exactly what has happened under […]
Celtic handed £7 million Jeremie Frimpong windfall news - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic told 29-goal striker is good enough amid links]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45930</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-told-29-goal-striker-good-enough/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T13:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to add to their options up top this January. Kyogo has done well once again but he is not scoring as frequently as he was last season. On the other hand, Oh Hyeon-gyu has been inconsistent as well and is not at the level required to start for the Hoops right now. There […]
Celtic told 29-goal striker is good enough amid links - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anderlecht consider making offer for Celtic standout in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45927</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/anderlecht-offer-celtic-standout-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T11:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have not had the greatest campaign till now. They were eliminated early from the Scottish League Cup and while they do lead the Premiership, their performances and results have been somewhat inconsistent. Almost half a season on, it feels like the Hoops are still finding their feet under the management of Brendan Rodgers and […]
Anderlecht consider making offer for Celtic standout in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serie A club want to sign Celtic player amid contract worry]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45907</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/serie-club-want-celtic-player-contract/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T22:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic fans hope for more quality players arriving there could be a problem with others heading for the exit door. It seems pretty clear that Brendan Rodgers wants to make the size of the squad more manageable over the next couple of transfer windows and departures are expected. But there is a risk of […]
Serie A club want to sign Celtic player amid contract worry - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur step up bid to sign Celtic-linked player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45918</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/tottenham-hotspur-bid-sign-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur made a fantastic start to the season under the management of Ange Postecoglou. With Harry Kane leaving the club in the summer for Bayern Munich, most expected them to struggle. Instead, they appeared to be putting up an unlikely title challenge and were sitting atop the Premier League table not too long ago. […]
Tottenham Hotspur step up bid to sign Celtic-linked player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boost in race to sign £11 million Real Madrid player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45914</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/celtic-boost-real-madrid-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to sign a goalkeeper in the near future. It is quite clear that Joe Hart is not the long-term solution between the posts. The Englishman’s performances have been criticised lately. Also, he is set to turn 37 years of age before this season comes to an end. So, while he has done a […]
Celtic boost in race to sign £11 million Real Madrid player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio boss Maurizio Sarri makes fantastic Celtic claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45910</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/lazio-boss-maurizio-sarri-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T18:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By now, Celtic fans have accepted that Brendan Rodgers’ side are most probably not going through or even finishing third in their group in the UEFA Champions League. It would be a positive step to get a win in the competition though. It has been quite some time since the Hoops won at this level. […]
Lazio boss Maurizio Sarri makes fantastic Celtic claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic tipped to go for 28-year-old Premiership striker]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45904</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/celtic-tipped-go-premiership-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T12:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans breathed a sigh of relief as the Rangers dropped points at the weekend against Aberdeen. In fact, it took a late penalty for them to even come out with a draw from the game. That means that the Hoops will maintain their strong position at the top of the Scottish Premiership table. That […]
Celtic tipped to go for 28-year-old Premiership striker - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£7.5 million Mathias Kvistgaarden to Celtic transfer update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45900</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/mathias-kvistgaarden-celtic-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T10:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to sign a striker in January. On one hand, we have seen the club struggle for goals in some games this season. When the opposition puts up a resolute defence, the Hoops do not appear to have a lot of answers other than Kyogo, Matt O’Riley or Luis Palma. On the other hand, […]
£7.5 million Mathias Kvistgaarden to Celtic transfer update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur have been eyeing Celtic superstar]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45896</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/tottenham-hotspur-eyeing-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T23:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou made the move to Tottenham Hotspur in the summer and it was only a matter of time before the Australian was linked with a reunion with some Celtic players. The manager enjoyed a lot of success at Parkhead, even though he was at the club for just two seasons, and won five trophies […]
Tottenham Hotspur have been eyeing Celtic superstar - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John McGinn claims he spoke to Celtic players about manager]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45890</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/john-mcginn-spoke-celtic-players/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T21:35:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most Celtic fans will remember how the club missed out on the opportunity to sign John McGinn some years back. The Scot grew up supporting the Hoops but a move to Parkhead failed to materialise even though it had looked close and he ended up moving down south to join Aston Villa. McGinn has risen […]
John McGinn claims he spoke to Celtic players about manager - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic must consider signing striker from Premiership rivals]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45886</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-signing-striker-premiership-rivals/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T20:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there is one position where Celtic need to strengthen during the upcoming January transfer window, it is striker. The Hoops have been pretty inconsistent in front of goal this season so far. Of course, there are games when they can go out and score six times. But then, on days they are having a […]
Celtic must consider signing striker from Premiership rivals - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend takes dig at Rangers player for diving]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45884</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-legend-rangers-player-diving/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T18:35:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Celtic drew 1-1 against Motherwell, the Rangers were handed a major chance to get back into the title race. All they needed to do was win their games in hand and they would be just three points behind the Hoops in the league table. We have seen the Ibrox side not perform at their […]
Celtic legend takes dig at Rangers player for diving - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player criticised after draw against Motherwell]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45881</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-player-criticised-draw-motherwell/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T12:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Titles are not decided this early in the season. That has been proven once again. Not too long ago, Celtic were sitting seven points clear at the top of the Premiership table and most fans felt that the league was pretty much in the bag with the Rangers struggling for any kind of form.  It […]
Celtic player criticised after draw against Motherwell - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgio Chiellini makes superb claim about Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45874</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/giorgio-chiellini-claim-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T10:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Giorgio Chiellini is one of the best defenders of all time and he had some pretty positive comments about Celtic Park recently. The 39-year-old spent the majority of his career playing for Juventus and won more silverware there than one should try to count. Overall, he made more […]
Giorgio Chiellini makes superb claim about Celtic Park - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s problem is very clear and needs solving quick]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45870</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/celtic-problem-needs-solving-quick/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T19:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two more dropped points mean that Celtic have well and truly allowed the Rangers to get back into the title race. A lead which once stood at seven points, could be reduced to three if Philippe Clement’s side are able to win their games in hand. And the sad thing is that the Hoops have […]
Celtic’s problem is very clear and needs solving quick - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic problem after draw]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45866</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/brendan-rodgers-celtic-problem-draw/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T18:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was not the result Celtic were looking for, as they dropped two valuable points against Motherwell. David Turnbull’s goal appeared to have won it for the Hoops but the visitors equalised in the 90th minute and it ended 1-1. That means that if the Rangers win their games in hand, the gap will be […]
Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic problem after draw - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hollywood superstar pictured wearing Celtic jersey]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45861</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/hollywood-pictured-wearing-celtic-jersey/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T12:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Celtic have their fair share of famous fans. Rod Stewart is the first name that comes to most people’s minds, one of the best-selling music artists in history. Lewis Capaldi is another popular musician known to support the Hoops. And several A-list celebrities like Gerard Butler, Snoop Dogg, […]
Hollywood superstar pictured wearing Celtic jersey - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic pushing for priority signing in January window]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45859</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/celtic-priority-signing-january-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T09:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s January transfer window is expected to be a busy one. The club might have made nine signings in the summer, seven arriving on a permanent basis and two on loan, but there are still holes in Brendan Rodgers’ squad that need to be filled. On the other hand, there are way too many players […]
Celtic pushing for priority signing in January window - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable source offers Sydney van Hooijdonk to Celtic update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45854</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/reliable-sydney-van-hooijdonk-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T22:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are believed to be on the lookout for a striker in the January transfer window. There might be a few reasons behind that. Firstly, both Kyogo and Oh Hyeon-gyu might be unavailable for a considerable length of time early next year due to the AFC Asian Cup. They are the club’s two options to […]
Reliable source offers Sydney van Hooijdonk to Celtic update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou claims Celtic success gets dismissed]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45852</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/ange-postecoglou-claims-celtic-success/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T21:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has proven to be a major success in the Premier League since swapping Celtic for Tottenham Hotspur. Of course, a lot of fans were not happy to see him depart after just two years at Parkhead. But he has been very respectful about the club even after leaving. And it is hard not […]
Ange Postecoglou claims Celtic success gets dismissed - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>