<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-09-13T10:10:48.566Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maik Nawrocki news doesn't appear to be good after Celtic squad announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174101</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/maik-nawrocki-news-doesnt-appear-to-be-good-after-celtic-squad-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic man Maik Nawrocki appears to be some way from making his return from injury, judging by developments on Tuesday. The Polish central defender, signed...
The post Maik Nawrocki news doesn't appear to be good after Celtic squad announcement appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers making a mistake not playing Celtic ace]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44152</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/13/brendan-rodgers-mistake-celtic-ace/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T10:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers’ return to Celtic Park has been up-and-down till now. The Hoops made a questionable start to the season for sure and are already out of the Scottish League Cup. But then, the win over the Rangers away at Ibrox has settled a lot of nerves and convinced the doubters that the Northern Irishman […]
Brendan Rodgers making a mistake not playing Celtic ace - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic round-up; Callum McGregor vs England verdict as Bernardo, Holm and Kyogo all feature]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174107</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-round-up-callum-mcgregor-vs-england-verdict-as-bernardo-holm-and-kyogo-all-feature/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tuesday was a busy day for some of Celtic’s stars as the international programme drew to a close. The first break of the season arrived...
The post Celtic round-up; Callum McGregor vs England verdict as Bernardo, Holm and Kyogo all feature appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GREEN LIGHT FOR HATATE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111883</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/green-light-for-hatate/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T08:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE is poised to make his return from injury against Dundee at Parkhead on Saturday as the champions continue their quest for Premiership points. The influential Japanese midfielder has been missing since a 25-minute second-half cameo in the 3-1 win over Aberdeen at Pittodrie exactly a month ago. Hatate suffered a muscular injury that [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers is bullish; thinks Celtic have already encountered major moment this season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174117</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-is-bullish-thinks-celtic-have-already-had-their-gibraltar-moment-this-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers had plenty of interesting things to say about Celtic on Tuesday. As we’ve already covered, the Hoops boss offered a pretty positive injury...
The post Brendan Rodgers is bullish; thinks Celtic have already encountered major moment this season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss shares great Reo Hatate news that extends beyond positive injury update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174083</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-shares-great-reo-hatate-news-that-extends-beyond-positive-injury-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers has shared some great news about Reo Hatate. The Japanese midfielder — arguably our most talented player — has endured a...
The post Celtic boss shares great Reo Hatate news that extends beyond positive injury update appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Irish outlet rave about Celtic youngster as he steals the show in midweek]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174135</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/irish-outlet-rave-about-rocco-vata-as-celtic-man-steals-the-show-in-midweek/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic youngster Rocco Vata was the standout performer for the Republic of Ireland’s under-21s on Tuesday evening. The young Irish side kept up their 100%...
The post Irish outlet rave about Celtic youngster as he steals the show in midweek appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers shares positive injury update but two Celtic stars not mentioned by name]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174090</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-shares-positive-injury-update-but-two-celtic-stars-not-mentioned-by-name/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers shared a largely positive injury update on Tuesday. It’s been a challenging few weeks for the Hoops with a number of...
The post Brendan Rodgers shares positive injury update but two Celtic stars not mentioned by name appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing produces in overnight international; Hoops debut soon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174125</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/luis-palma-produces-in-overnight-honduras-clash-celtic-are-next/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summer Celtic signing Luis Palma was among the goalscorers in an emphatic midweek win for Honduras. The Central American country were in CONCACAF Nations League...
The post New Celtic signing produces in overnight international; Hoops debut soon appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE JOCK STEIN YEARS (Part Three)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=55150</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-jock-stein-years-part-three/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T04:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Jock Stein made an extraordinary immediate impact on the Parkhead club when he returned as manager in March 1965. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE series, author Alex Gordon, who has written fifteen books on Celtic, has opened his publication files on the Parkhead great. Today, in Part Three of our fascinating look back at [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JOHNNY DIVERS: GREAT UNCAPPED CELTS (Part Nine)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.cqnmagazine.com/?p=5054</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/johnny-divers-great-uncapped-celts-part-nine/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T04:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CQN is turning the spotlight again on the Celtic players who never had the honour of playing for their country. Johnny Divers was a goalscoring phenomenon who netted the first goal in a 4-0 win over Dundee United at Tannadice in August 1965 that kicked off the historic first nine in row. He had been [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic tipped to sign another Liverpool player amid links]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44148</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/12/celtic-sign-another-liverpool-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T22:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already signed one player from Liverpool recently in the form of Nat Phillips, who arrived on loan for the first half of the season. It was a move made out of necessity more than anything else. Celtic have players like Cameron Carter-Vickers, Stephen Welsh and Maik Nawrocki out for the foreseeable future. So, […]
Celtic tipped to sign another Liverpool player amid links - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OFF NIGHT FOR SCOTS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111872</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/off-night-for-scots/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T21:13:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SCOTLAND were off colour, off target and off the pace as they lost 3-1 to England in the 150th Anniversary Match at Hampden this evening. There was also bad news from Norway where the hosts beat Georgia 2-1 in the Scots’ Euro group in the game in which a draw would have seen Steve Clarke’s [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou makes emotional claim about Celtic fans]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44144</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/12/ange-postecoglou-claim-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T20:31:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou is one of the most popular Celtic managers in recent memory. Not only did the Australian win over the fans with wins, trophies and the style of football that his team played but also with his conduct off the pitch as well. A cheeky one-liner was never far away and he seemed to […]
Ange Postecoglou makes emotional claim about Celtic fans - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou explains why he left Celtic for Tottenham]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44140</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/12/ange-postecoglou-left-celtic-tottenham/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T19:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were dealt a blow when Ange Postecoglou left the club, merely days after winning a domestic treble with the Hoops, in order to join Tottenham Hotspur. The lead-up to the Scottish Cup final had been dominated by rumours of his potential exit and the fans’ worst fears soon came true. Postecoglou had proven himself […]
Ange Postecoglou explains why he left Celtic for Tottenham - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms major Celtic injury boost]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44137</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/12/brendan-rodgers-celtic-injury-boost/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T17:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There has been very little good news for Celtic when it comes to the injury front. One player after another has gone down with fitness issues at the start of the season, leaving Brendan Rodgers with limited options to pick his team from. That contributed to the stumbling start they made to the campaign, even […]
Brendan Rodgers confirms major Celtic injury boost - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Paulo Bernardo state of play as Celtic debut comes in to focus]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174021</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-paulo-bernardo-state-of-play-as-celtic-debut-comes-in-to-focus/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paulo Bernardo could make his Celtic debut this weekend against Dundee. The midfielder joined us on a season-long loan from Benfica on the final day...
The post The Paulo Bernardo state of play as Celtic debut comes in to focus appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou signing must leave after Celtic decision]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44135</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/12/ange-postecoglou-signing-leave-celtic-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T15:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A change in managers is always an interesting time for a club and the players, and Celtic certainly are going through a transitional phase right now. Ange Postecoglou left at the end of last season in order to join Tottenham Hotspur while Brendan Rodgers has been brought in as the Australian’s replacement. Of course, Rodgers’ […]
Ange Postecoglou signing must leave after Celtic decision - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic set for big billing in Champions League opener as new television era begins]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173999</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-set-for-big-billing-in-champions-league-opener-as-the-tnt-sports-era-begins/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic get their UEFA Champions League campaign underway next Tuesday. It may not feel like it right now, with international football dominating the headlines, but...
The post Celtic set for big billing in Champions League opener as new television era begins appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: NAWROCKI OUT OF EURO SQUAD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111868</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-nawrocki-out-of-euro-squad/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T14:48:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has been forced to leave crocked Maik Nawrocki out of Celtic’s 25-man Champions League squad . The £4.3million centre-back who arrived from Legia Warsaw in the summer suffered a hamstring problem during the Hoops’ 1-0 Viaplay League Cup loss to Kilmarnock at Rugby Park just over three weeks ago. It was announced Nawrocki [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[€5 million Celtic player left out of Champions League squad]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44132</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/12/5-million-celtic-champions-league-squad/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T13:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will be kicking off their Champions League campaign in a week when they take on Feyenoord away in the Netherlands. The Hoops were not able to win a single game in Europe’s elite competition last season despite putting in a few impressive performances and finished bottom of their group as a result. They will […]
€5 million Celtic player left out of Champions League squad - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The potential for at least one Celtic debut this weekend; problem area looking better]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174006</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/the-potential-for-at-least-one-celtic-debut-this-weekend-centre-back-situation-improves/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic centre-back situation will already have improved by the time Saturday’s clash against Dundee rolls around. The Hoops are back in Premiership action against...
The post The potential for at least one Celtic debut this weekend; problem area looking better appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Right at the top': Ange Postecoglou shares what he 'tells everyone' about Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174056</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/right-at-the-top-ange-postecoglou-shares-what-he-tells-everyone-about-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has shared that he ‘keeps saying to everyone’ that Celtic should be ‘top’ of the bucket list of clubs you want to be...
The post 'Right at the top': Ange Postecoglou shares what he 'tells everyone' about Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Park's unlikely starring role the last time Scotland faced England in a friendly]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173990</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-parks-unlikely-starring-role-the-last-time-scotland-faced-england-in-a-friendly/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scotland face England in a friendly on Tuesday evening at Hampden Park. The match is uncompetitive by definition, yet it is sure to be a...
The post Celtic Park's unlikely starring role the last time Scotland faced England in a friendly appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor’s five mountains in five weeks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111867</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/callum-mcgregors-five-mountains-in-five-weeks/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T11:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If results to their way, Scotland will tonight become the first team to qualify for the Euro 2024 in Germany next summer.  Norway and Georgia are both on four points.  A draw would see them move to five, 10 behind Scotland with three games remaining. Either way, automatic qualification is inevitable, as, with Spain remaining [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I don't': Sutton mentions Callum McGregor & says England star doesn't get into Scotland XI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174035</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-dont-sutton-mentions-callum-mcgregor-says-england-star-doesnt-get-into-scotland-xi/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton name-dropped Celtic captain Callum McGregor whilst stating that England star Jordan Henderson doesn’t get into Scotland’s XI. Celtic’s main man in the middle...
The post 'I don't': Sutton mentions Callum McGregor & says England star doesn't get into Scotland XI appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic influence already clear to see as Luis Palma shares photo from Honduras]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174028</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-influence-already-clear-to-see-as-luis-palma-shares-photo-from-honduras/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T09:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic influence is already clear to see as Luis Palma shared a photograph from Honduras. The recent Hoops signing is back in his homeland...
The post Celtic influence already clear to see as Luis Palma shares photo from Honduras appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHEN HARRY MET BROONY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111858</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/when-harry-met-broony/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T08:22:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC hero Scott Brown came face to face with rival skipper Harry Kane before the Scotland v England Euro 2018 qualifier at a sunkissed Hampden on the afternoon of June 10 2017. It turned out to be an epic confrontation between the opposite onfield leaders during a thrilling 2-2 stalemate after the hosts had fought [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic youngster shares Rodgers hope for next season as surprise midfield talk emerges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174014</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/bosun-lawal-shares-brendan-rodgers-hope-for-next-season-surprise-celtic-midfield-option-emerges/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bosun Lawal still seems to be hopeful about a future career at Celtic. The 20-year-old has played a handful of games for the Hoops since...
The post Celtic youngster shares Rodgers hope for next season as surprise midfield talk emerges appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HEARD THE ONE ABOUT HAMPDEN’S HEROES AND VILLAINS? CELTIC HERO REVEALS ALL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111839</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/heard-the-one-about-hampdens-heroes-and-villains-celtic-hero-reveals-all/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T07:39:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JUST over six years and three months ago, Leigh Griffiths sent two soaring long-range free-kicks beyond the grasping fingers of Joe Hart at Hampden Park in a crucial Euro 2018 qualifier. A late goal from Harry Kane gave England a 2-2 draw with Scotland, a loss of two points that went a long way to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic leave former Ibrox man feeling "a little bit silly" after glorious derby triumph]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173983</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-leave-former-ibrox-man-feeling-a-little-bit-silly-after-glorious-derby-triumph/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s over a week since Celtic silenced the doubters with a glorious derby win at Ibrox. With multiple injuries to contend with, and no supporters...
The post Celtic leave former Ibrox man feeling "a little bit silly" after glorious derby triumph appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo braced for big Japan chance after an injury that will interest Celtic fans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173976</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kyogo-furuhashi-braced-for-big-japan-chance-after-an-injury-that-will-interest-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Furuhashi could be set for his big opportunity to impress in a Japan shirt on Tuesday. The in-form Hoops forward was an unused substitute...
The post Kyogo braced for big Japan chance after an injury that will interest Celtic fans appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Joe Hart and Leigh Griffiths scenes that reached Celtic circles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173961</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-joe-hart-and-leigh-griffiths-banter-that-reached-celtic-circles/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart and Leigh Griffiths had plenty of chat to catch up on when they first met at Celtic in the summer of 2021. The...
The post The Joe Hart and Leigh Griffiths scenes that reached Celtic circles appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Hibernian boss credits Celtic move which opened doors to Scottish football]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173968</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/new-hibernian-boss-credits-celtic-move-which-opened-doors-to-scottish-football/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Hibernian manager Nick Montgomery has credited a move Celtic made in 2021 with opening doors from Australian to Scottish football. The move in question...
The post New Hibernian boss credits Celtic move which opened doors to Scottish football appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE JOCK STEIN YEARS (Part Two)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=55147</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-jock-stein-years-part-two/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T04:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Jock Stein made an extraordinary immediate impact on the Parkhead club when he returned as team boss in March 1965. The 38th anniversary of the passing of the Hoops great, at the age of 62, was marked by CQN on Sunday. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE,  author Alex Gordon, who has had fifteen Celtic works published, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TOM McADAM: GREAT UNCAPPED CELTS (Part Eight)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.cqnmagazine.com/?p=4982</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/tom-mcadam-great-uncapped-celts-part-eight/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T04:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CQN is turning the spotlight again on the Celtic players who never had the honour of playing for their country. Club legend Billy McNeill converted Tom McAdam from striker to centre-back – and the player was consistently immense following the dramatic career switch. He became a key man for the Hoops and a fans’ favourite [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aiden McGeady makes questionable claim about Celtic fans]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44128</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/11/aiden-mcgeady-makes-questionable-claim-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T22:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Celtic decided to bring back Brendan Rodgers to replace Ange Postecoglou in the Parkhead hot seat, the reaction of the fans was always going to be a major talking point. After all, the Northern Irishman had left a bitter taste in the mouths of many by leaving in the middle of the season to […]
Aiden McGeady makes questionable claim about Celtic fans - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers hero makes U-turn after Celtic win at Ibrox]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44125</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/11/rangers-hero-celtic-win-ibrox/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T21:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are just four games into the league season and nothing is even close to being settled. Yet, the mood in the camps of the two Glasgow giants are completely opposite. Celtic must be delighted following their win at Ibrox, a result that not many saw coming and has acted as a major confidence boost […]
Rangers hero makes U-turn after Celtic win at Ibrox - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star set for elite test at int'l level ahead of Champions League campaign; how to watch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173956</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-star-set-for-elite-test-at-international-level-ahead-of-champions-league-campaign-how-to-watch/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T20:20:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic captain Callum McGregor will go through excellent preparation for the Bhoys’ upcoming Champions League group stage with an appearance for Scotland on Tuesday night....
The post Celtic star set for elite test at int'l level ahead of Champions League campaign; how to watch appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feyenoord handed major problem for Celtic match]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44122</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/11/feyenoord-handed-problem-celtic-match/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T19:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will kick off their Champions League group stage campaign a little over a week later with an away trip to take on Feyenoord. Of course, the Hoops are the only Scottish club in Europe’s elite competition this season after the Rangers failed to make it, having been knocked out from the qualifiers by another […]
Feyenoord handed major problem for Celtic match - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 big changes Brendan Rodgers could make to Celtic team]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173953</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/4-big-changes-brendan-rodgers-could-make-to-celtic-team-vs-dundee/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T18:20:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re not far away from Celtic returning to action after the international break and everyone remains on a high from last week’s derby win. A...
The post 4 big changes Brendan Rodgers could make to Celtic team appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liverpool player tipped to join Celtic permanently in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44118</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/11/liverpool-player-join-celtic-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T17:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were busy during the summer transfer window even though they received quite a bit of criticism for the moves they did make. The club opted to go for highly rated youngsters rather than going for established and experienced names, even though there had been rumours about high-profile signings following the reappointment of Brendan Rodgers […]
Liverpool player tipped to join Celtic permanently in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Buzzing" £25m man explains his transfer decision after summer of Celtic rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173948</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/buzzing-kieran-tierney-explains-his-la-liga-decision-after-summer-of-celtic-and-arsenal-rumours/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T15:34:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kieran Tierney has spoken about his move to La Liga this season and the decision to leave Arsenal on loan, after a summer of rumours...
The post "Buzzing" £25m man explains his transfer decision after summer of Celtic rumours appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player completes transfer to Sheffield United]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44115</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/11/celtic-player-transfer-sheffield-united/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T13:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have continued to add talented youngsters to their side, in hopes that they would develop into first-team stars and eventually be transferred for much bigger fees. That is the strategy that the Hoops have followed for a long time now and it would come as a surprise to anyone who has supported the club […]
Celtic player completes transfer to Sheffield United - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revolving medical door, A-League coup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111838</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/revolving-medical-door-a-league-coup/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T11:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There appears to be a revolving door on the Lennoxtown medical room.  Just as we hoped to see players return from injury, Liel Abada picked up a strain on international duty with Israel and is expected to be out of action for a month.  We are not short of wingers in the squad, but we [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BROONY GUESSING GAME ENDS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111834</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/broony-guessing-game-ends/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T09:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SPECULATION that Scott Brown could be in the running for the Hibs manager’s job has finally come to an end. The Easter Road club issued a statement this morning confirming the appointment of Nick Montgomery as their new boss on a three-year contract. The 41-year-old head coach has left Aussie outfit Central Coast Mariners to replace [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports man names key signing Celtic failed to make]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44112</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/11/sky-sports-man-signing-celtic-failed/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T09:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were pretty active over the summer transfer window even if most fans were not happy that the club did not bring in any established and high-profile names. Instead, they continued to sign highly-rated youngsters with the potential to develop into key players at Parkhead. Let’s see if the strategy pays off or not. It […]
Sky Sports man names key signing Celtic failed to make - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘GOD WILLING, MATT SIGNS A NEW DEAL,’ CELTIC HERO REVEALS WISH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111831</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/god-willing-matt-signs-a-new-deal-celtic-hero-reveals-wish/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T07:23:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC hero Peter Grant hopes his old club make Matt O’Riley an offer he can’t refuse. The former Hoops midfield battler is an enthusiastic admirer of the Londoner after their time together at Fulham. Grant was in charge of youth development at the Craven Cottage club and had no hesitation in upgrading 15-year-old O’Riley to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NIGHT CELTIC HIT TEN – WITH ONLY TWO GOALSCORERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=96209</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/night-celtic-hit-ten-with-only-two-goalscorers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T04:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC hit hapless Hamilton Accies with a ten-goal hurricane exactly FIFTY-FIVE years ago as Bobby Lennox and Stevie Chalmers went on the rampage in an unforgettable evening in the east end of Glasgow. Jock Stein’s all-conquering Hoops heroes were unstoppable in a League Cup encounter as they annihilated their shell-shocked opponents with the lightning-swift raiders each [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE JOCK STEIN YEARS (Part One)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=55137</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-jock-stein-years-part-one/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T04:15:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE 38th anniversary of the passing of Celtic legend Jock Stein, at the age of 62, was marked by CQN yesterday. In an exciting in-depth analysis, CQN will spotlight the astounding Celtic managerial years of Big Jock, his extraordinary impact on the club and his remarkable legacy. Author Alex Gordon, who has written fifteen publications on [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HARRY HOOD: GREAT UNCAPPED CELTS (Part Seven)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.cqnmagazine.com/?p=4932</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/harry-hood-great-uncapped-celts-part-seven/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T04:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CQN is turning the spotlight once again on the Celtic players who never had the honour of playing for their country. Harry Hood was Jock Stein’s fourth major signing for the club – following Joe McBride, Willie Wallace and Tommy Callaghan – when he arrived from Clyde in 1969. He became a key player for [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero takes dig at Kris Boyd for hilarious miss]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44088</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/10/celtic-hero-kris-boyd-miss/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T23:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a not great time for Rangers fans and former players like Kris Boyd. They have been defeated again by a Celtic side and Chris Sutton couldn’t resist a joke on the occasion. The Hoops had a team of past stars entering the revived Scottish Masters alongside the Ibrox club, Hibernian and Hearts at […]
Celtic hero takes dig at Kris Boyd for hilarious miss - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Old comments go viral as Michael Beale on brink after losing to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44104</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/10/comments-michael-beale-losing-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T21:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Beale currently finds himself in an unenviable situation at Ibrox. He saw his side lose at home to an out-of-form Celtic last weekend, thanks to a superb strike from Kyogo Furuhashi. And the result, combined with their 7-3 aggregate loss to PSV in the UEFA Champions League qualifiers, appears to have left the manager […]
Old comments go viral as Michael Beale on brink after losing to Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Bargains of the millennium’ – Kenny Dalglish on Celtic signing]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44100</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/10/bargains-kenny-dalglish-celtic-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T19:30:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been pretty impressive when it comes to identifying talents in recent years. Of course, a large part of that credit has to go to Ange Postecoglou. The Australian’s arrival as manager in 2021 changed the transfer methods of the club to a club extent and they have spread their networks further and wider […]
‘Bargains of the millennium’ – Kenny Dalglish on Celtic signing - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday columns show Celtic have put Beale under severe pressure even a full week after derby win]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173943</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/sunday-columns-show-celtic-have-put-michael-beale-under-severe-pressure-even-a-full-week-after-derby-win/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T19:14:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s derby win last week has prompted an outcry across the city akin to their season-ending. A solitary goal from Kyogo Furuhashi has sent rival...
The post Sunday columns show Celtic have put Beale under severe pressure even a full week after derby win appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moussa Dembele shares beautiful Celtic throwback]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44096</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/10/moussa-dembele-shares-celtic-throwback/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T18:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moussa Dembele is one of the best players that Celtic have had in recent years. He was absolutely brilliant during his time at Parkhead and became an absolute fan favourite. He was a stalwart from Brendan Rodgers’ first stint as the manager of the club and continues to show his love for the Hoops to […]
Moussa Dembele shares beautiful Celtic throwback - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Like Rodgers has a new £10m player"; Chris Sutton excited by potential resurgence at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173940</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/like-rodgers-has-a-new-10m-player-chris-sutton-excited-by-potential-resurgence-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T16:38:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton is looking forward to seeing Reo Hatate back in the Celtic line-up after the international break, feeling he could take the Bhoys midfield...
The post "Like Rodgers has a new £10m player"; Chris Sutton excited by potential resurgence at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic icon Scott Brown replaced by sacked Hibs boss at Fleetwood; two Bhoys loanees impacted]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173925</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-icon-scott-brown-replaced-by-sacked-hibs-boss-at-fleetwood-two-bhoys-loanees-impacted/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T15:41:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fleetwood Town have announced that Lee Johnson, recently sacked by Hibernian, will be taking charge of the club following the departure of Scott Brown. Celtic...
The post Celtic icon Scott Brown replaced by sacked Hibs boss at Fleetwood; two Bhoys loanees impacted appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic pair rested as international demolition prompts managerial sacking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173920</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-pair-rested-as-international-demolition-prompts-managerial-sacking/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T15:11:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic duo Daizen Maeda and Kyogo Furuhashi only had a place on the bench for Japan’s victory over Germany this weekend, but got a close-up...
The post Celtic pair rested as international demolition prompts managerial sacking appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Ledley makes superb claim about Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44092</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/10/joe-ledley-claim-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T15:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have made an up-and-down start to this campaign. They won their first two games but the performances left a lot to be desired. Those were followed by a loss and a draw, which caused the fans to worry heading into the Glasgow Derby. But then, Brendan Rodgers’ side rose to the occasion and won […]
Joe Ledley makes superb claim about Celtic player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic hero finds a spark to pile misery on Rangers pundits and their nightmare week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173915</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-hero-finds-a-spark-to-pile-misery-on-rangers-pundits-and-their-nightmare-week/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T14:43:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not been a great week for those of a Rangers persuasion, has it? Celtic’s fine work in last Sunday’s derby, won by a Kyogo...
The post Former Celtic hero finds a spark to pile misery on Rangers pundits and their nightmare week appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Dalglish says Celtic got "one of the transfer bargains of the millennium" from £4m deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173907</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kenny-dalglish-says-celtic-got-one-of-the-transfer-bargains-of-the-millennium-from-4m-deal/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T13:54:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend Kenny Dalglish has lauded striker Kyogo Furuhashi after scoring yet another derby goal last weekend. The Japanese forward now has six goals in...
The post Kenny Dalglish says Celtic got "one of the transfer bargains of the millennium" from £4m deal appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic urged to bring back former striker on free transfer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44085</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/10/celtic-urged-bring-back-former-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T12:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic could do with another striker at this point in time. There were suggestions that the club were looking for one towards the end of the summer transfer window but an addition up top was not made. Luis Palma is capable of playing in a more central role as well though, so perhaps he could […]
Celtic urged to bring back former striker on free transfer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CROCKED CELT ‘SEEMS TO BE ANGRY’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111825</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/crocked-celt-seems-to-be-angry/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T09:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIEL ABADA has joined the growing Celtic injury list – and he could face a MONTH on the sidelines to add to Brendan Rodgers’ woes. The Israeli wing ace has been sent home from his country’s international squad after sustaining a knock in training. The Hoops medical staff will check the extent of the problem, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JOCK STEIN: ‘THE BIG MAN, ME AND GOING ON STRIKE’: DAVIE HAY LOOKS BACK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=54271</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/jock-stein-the-big-man-me-and-going-on-strike-davie-hay-looks-back/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T04:32:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAVIE HAY mourned the loss of a good friend and mentor when Jock Stein passed away 38 years ago today. However, the Celtic legend recalls a time when he and the Hoops gaffer were at loggerheads. Here is an extract from Davie’s autobiography, ‘The Quiet Assassin,‘ co-authored by Alex Gordon and published by Black and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JOCK STEIN: TOP TEN QUOTES]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=54260</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/jock-stein-top-ten-quotes/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T04:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WHEN Jock Stein talked, others listened. Here are 10 of some his most notable quotes: “Football is nothing without fans.” *** “Cups are not won by individuals, but by men in a team who put their club before personal prestige.” *** “Unlike many other Celts, I cannot claim that Celtic was my first love … [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JOCK STEIN: ‘WHEN WILL WE SEE YOUR LIKE AGAIN?’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=54252</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/jock-stein-when-will-we-see-your-like-again/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T04:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LEGENDARY Celtic manager Jock Stein, at the age of 62, passed away on this day 38 years ago. This is an extract from author Alex Gordon’s ‘Lisbon Lions: 40th Anniversary Celebration‘ publication which paid tribute to the Big Man. JOCK STEIN had his back turned to the pitch when West German referee Kurt Tschenscher put the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY CALLAGHAN: GREAT UNCAPPED CELTS (Part Six)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.cqnmagazine.com/?p=4894</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/tommy-callaghan-great-uncapped-celts-part-six/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T04:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CQN is turning the spotlight once again on the Celtic players who never had the honour of playing for their country. Tommy Callaghan was Jock Stein’s third signing for the club – following Joe McBride and Willie Wallace – when he arrived from Dunfermline in 1968. He became a key player for Big Jock and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player earns praise from Jurgen Klinsmann after debut]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44031</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/09/celtic-player-jurgen-klinsmann-debut/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T22:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Playing for Celtic can help your international career. That’s pretty clear from this break with one Hoops ace even making his debut for his national team. There have been some question marks at times about whether playing in the Scottish Premiership could hurt such prospects. Especially when both Kyogo Furuhashi and Reo Hatate missed out […]
Celtic player earns praise from Jurgen Klinsmann after debut - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heartbreak for Celtic after dramatic Saturday night UWCL 11-10 penalties defeat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173900</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/heartbreak-for-celtic-after-dramatic-saturday-night-uwcl-11-10-penalties-defeat/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T21:03:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic FC Women are out of the UEFA Women’s Champions League after a dramatic penalty shoot-out defeat against Valerenga in Norway. Celtic lost a very...
The post Heartbreak for Celtic after dramatic Saturday night UWCL 11-10 penalties defeat appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Beale on brink of sack after losing to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44077</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/09/michael-beale-brink-sack-losing-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T21:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Michael Beale arrived as the manager of the Rangers, he came in with a lot of expectations and many of their fans believed that he was the man to topple Celtic. After all, he was a part of Steven Gerrard’s coaching staff at Ibrox and was believed to be the mastermind behind the team […]
Michael Beale on brink of sack after losing to Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sead Haksabanovic makes questionable Celtic claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44074</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/09/sead-haksabanovic-makes-celtic-claim/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T19:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Haksabanovic left Celtic on Deadline Day to join Stoke City on a season-long loan. It was a move that made sense for all parties involved. The player certainly was not getting a lot of chances at Parkhead and did not seem to be particularly happy with his situation, judging from his social media activity before […]
Sead Haksabanovic makes questionable Celtic claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating goals they didn't score; hilarious Celtic Rangers video emerges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173894</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celebrating-goals-they-didnt-score-hilarious-celtic-rangers-video-emerges/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T18:32:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every time Celtic win a derby match against Rangers it’s satisfying for a number of different reasons. It gives the club an obvious sporting advantage...
The post Celebrating goals they didn't score; hilarious Celtic Rangers video emerges appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed injury boost ahead of Champions League]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44070</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/09/celtic-handed-injury-champions-league/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T18:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will take on Dundee FC right after the international break. But fans cannot be blamed for already having half an eye on the upcoming Champions League campaign. The Hoops are set to face Feyenoord away at De Kuip in their opening game of the group stage of Europe’s elite competition. Of course, Celtic were […]
Celtic handed injury boost ahead of Champions League - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend Scott Brown releases lengthy statement on Instagram after Fleetwood Town sacking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173889</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-legend-scott-brown-releases-lengthy-statement-on-instagram-after-fleetwood-town-sacking/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T16:59:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic captain Scott Brown has had his say after leaving his position as Fleetwood Town manager last weekend. The English League One side parted...
The post Celtic legend Scott Brown releases lengthy statement on Instagram after Fleetwood Town sacking appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World-famous musician shares picture with Celtic man]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44066</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/09/world-famous-musician-celtic-man/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T16:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic certainly do have their fair share of world-famous supporters. The likes of Rod Stewart and Lewis Capaldi have never hidden their love for the club. Snoop Dogg has also been seen wearing the Hoops on more than one occasion. And it looks like we might have to add another name to that list very […]
World-famous musician shares picture with Celtic man - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic injury worries deepen as scan results provide bad news; major doubt for Champions League]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173884</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-injury-worries-deepen-after-liel-abada-scan-results-major-doubt-for-champions-league-opener/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T15:53:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The news from Bucharest on Liel Abada isn’t positive after the Celtic winger limped out of Israel training ahead of their match against Romania. Israeli...
The post Celtic injury worries deepen as scan results provide bad news; major doubt for Champions League appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[91% pass rate, defensive importance; Celtic star shines alongside expensive midfield at int'l level]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173879</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/91-pass-rate-defensive-importance-celtic-hero-shines-alongside-expensive-midfield-at-intl-level/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T15:10:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It may have been Scott McTominay and John McGinn who stole the headlines in Scotland’s midfield on Friday night, but Celtic captain Callum McGregor was...
The post 91% pass rate, defensive importance; Celtic star shines alongside expensive midfield at int'l level appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exciting new Celtic Bhoy cited as part of "generational change" for his country by national boss]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173874</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/new-celtic-bhoy-cited-as-part-of-generational-change-for-his-country-by-national-boss/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T14:37:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyunjun Yang made his debut for South Korea on Thursday night and although he only got a few minutes of action, he already has an...
The post Exciting new Celtic Bhoy cited as part of "generational change" for his country by national boss appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["It's obvious"; Joe Ledley left very impressed by Celtic star's progress since Rodgers came in]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173869</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/its-obvious-joe-ledley-impressed-as-celtic-star-ups-his-game-from-last-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T13:42:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic midfielder Joe Ledley has given a big thumbs up to Matt O’Riley and his progress working under Brendan Rodgers this season. O’Riley has...
The post "It's obvious"; Joe Ledley left very impressed by Celtic star's progress since Rodgers came in appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player ruled out for a month in fresh injury blow]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44062</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/09/celtic-player-fresh-injury-blow/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T13:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been struggling with injury problems at the start of the 2023/24 campaign. Brendan Rodgers’ side were able to get a win away at Ibrox last weekend but that does not mean that they are in good form at the moment. It was their first victory in three games. This team needs to build […]
Celtic player ruled out for a month in fresh injury blow - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can it really be 45 years ?]]></title>
        <id>http://celticunderground.net/?p=6639</id>
        <link href="http://celticunderground.net/can-it-really-be-45-years/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T09:36:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks the 45th anniversary of one of my favourite Celtic games of all time. In an excerpt taken from the book, Ten Men Won The League, we take a look back at a memorable game from 1978. These were still the days of drinking alcohol in the ground and open terracings. A more violent, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>St Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton is concerned about one Celtic star's big game ability but new Bhoy gets good review]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173864</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-has-concerns-about-david-turnbull-at-celtic-but-new-signing-gets-positive-review/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T09:21:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton has been running the rule over Brendan Rodgers’ midfield options at Celtic during the international break, as the Bhoys prepare for a very...
The post Chris Sutton is concerned about one Celtic star's big game ability but new Bhoy gets good review appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: ‘NO BAD FOR AN EFFIN’ LINSEMAN, EH, WALTER?’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111790</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-no-bad-for-an-effin-linseman-eh-walter/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T04:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AS a veteran of way too many Hampden and Wembley skirmishes – and I’ve got the scars to prove it – I am looking forward to Tuesday’s 150th anniversary match between Scotland and England at “Celtic’s second home,” as Bertie Auld used to call our national stadium. Contrary to popular belief, I was not among [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JOHN FALLON: GREAT UNCAPPED CELTS (Part Five)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.cqnmagazine.com/?p=4885</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/john-fallon-great-uncapped-celts-part-five/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T04:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CQN is turning the spotlight once again on the Celtic players who never had the honour of playing for their country. Goalkeeper John Fallon played an important part in Celtic winning the Scottish Cup when they overcame Dunfermline 3-2 in April 1965 – the club’s first silverware in eight years. He was in Jock Stein’s [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing Luis Palma was close to joining Portuguese club]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44039</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/08/celtic-signing-luis-palma-portuguese/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T22:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many Celtic fans were unhappy with the club’s summer business, with no star names arriving at Parkhead despite the Scottish champions making a number of signings. One of those was Luis Palma, who signed a 5-year contract with the Hoops after joining from Greek side Aris FC for a transfer fee believed to be around […]
New Celtic signing Luis Palma was close to joining Portuguese club - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Wyatt-Hupton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>