<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-07-15T04:13:01.279Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liverpool’s Fabinho transfer update is great for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42624</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/14/liverpool-fabinho-transfer-update-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T22:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are expected to make plenty of signings in this summer transfer window, and hopefully a few marquee ones as well. At the same time, it will also be important for the club to hold onto their best players as well. We have already seen Jota make the move to Al-Ittihad and several others have […]
Liverpool’s Fabinho transfer update is great for Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic suffer €9 million Dominik Livakovic transfer blow]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42620</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/14/celtic-dominik-livakovic-transfer-blow/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T20:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are expected to strengthen their squad this summer, as they aim to retain all three domestic titles next season and also have their eyes set on making an impact in the Champions League group stages, following the appointment of Brendan Rodgers as the manager of the club for the second time. And one area […]
Celtic suffer €9 million Dominik Livakovic transfer blow - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Current Celtic star posts a throwback to the day it all started]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167231</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/liel-abada-posts-a-celtic-throwback-ahead-of-an-interesting-summer/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liel Abada has shared a throwback to his first day at Celtic, exactly two years on. On 14 July 2021 the Israel international was signed from Maccabi Petah Tikva on a five-year deal. Abada was the first proper signing of the summer after a number of youth deals had been sealed. Few knew a great ...
The post Current Celtic star posts a throwback to the day it all started appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic submit €1 million offer for defensive midfielder]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42617</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/14/celtic-1-million-offer-midfielder/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T19:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been excellent in recent times when it comes to identifying top talents from leagues all over the world and bringing them to Glasgow. That is one of the biggest reasons that they have been successful in winning five out of the last six domestic competitions in Scotland, when you consider that situation that […]
Celtic submit €1 million offer for defensive midfielder - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dinamo Zagreb receive substantial offer for Dominik Livakovic but it's not from Celtic yet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167238</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/dinamo-zagreb-receive-substantial-offer-for-dominik-livakovic-but-its-not-from-celtic-yet/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fenerbahce look to be the main rivals to Celtic on any move for Dinamo Zagreb goalkeeper Dominik Livakovic, if reports coming out of Turkey today are accurate. It was reported by Sky Sports earlier that the Bhoys are closely monitoring the well-regarded Croatian international, with the goalkeeping position a priority to the recruitment staff at ...
The post Dinamo Zagreb receive substantial offer for Dominik Livakovic but it's not from Celtic yet appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Brendan Rodgers has said about Joe Hart as exciting Celtic transfer link emerges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167230</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/what-brendan-rodgers-has-said-about-joe-hart-as-exciting-celtic-transfer-link-emerges/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans have been waiting a while for a box office transfer rumour this summer, so the links to Dominik Livakovic have understandably caught the imagination of many. Sky Sports have reported that the Bhoys are ‘closely monitoring’ the Croatian international goalkeeper, whose arrival would be a box office statement signing. Clearly, there is a ...
The post What Brendan Rodgers has said about Joe Hart as exciting Celtic transfer link emerges appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic want to sign Croatia’s superstar at World Cup]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42613</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/14/celtic-croatia-superstar-world-cup/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T17:30:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are expected to make a few big signings in this summer transfer window in order to make sure that Brendan Rodgers’ squad is ready to defend all three titles next season and also can make an impact in the Champions League, which they failed to do in the previous campaign. And a few positions […]
Celtic want to sign Croatia’s superstar at World Cup - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic squad is being taken to the limit in Portugal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167210</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-celtic-squad-is-being-taken-to-the-limit-in-portugal/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T17:19:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has hailed the intensity and quality of his squad’s pre-season work in Portugal, stating that the heat and schedule are bringing the players to some “uncomfortable” places. Celtic have been at the state-of-the-art Campus facility on the Algarve since Sunday and depart this weekend before making a trip to Japan for ...
The post The Celtic squad is being taken to the limit in Portugal appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Saudi Comes they GO – Jota no longer on the wing]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58091</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/when-saudi-comes-they-go-jota-no-longer-on-the-wing/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T17:06:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We had Jota on the wing, he was a pleasure to watch from the stands. Celtic’s recruitment has been excellent over the past 2 seasons and the Portuguese winger was one of the stand out players alongside Kyogo and Carter Vickers. One season on loan before he signed a permanent deal. Little did Celtic know […]
The post When Saudi Comes they GO – Jota no longer on the wing appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic closely monitoring goalkeeper who dazzled at the World Cup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167219</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/report-celtic-closely-monitoring-goalkeeper-dominik-livakovic-dazzled-at-the-world-cup/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T16:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are closely monitoring Croatia goalkeeper Dominik Livakovic, according to a report. Sky Sports journalist Anthony Joseph has shared an update on the club’s transfer intentions, with the goalkeeping position seemingly high on the agenda. Joseph tweeted on Friday evening, saying: “Celtic are in the market for a goalkeeper this summer. “It’s understood one target ...
The post Report: Celtic closely monitoring goalkeeper who dazzled at the World Cup appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic dodge a bullet as Asian Games squad is announced]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167215</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-dodge-a-bullet-as-south-korea-announce-their-asian-games-squad/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T16:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have received some good news in the form of the South Korea squad for the Asian Games. The Koreans announced their 22 player selection for the competition that will take place in China from September 19 to October 7. The Asian Games are not to be confused with the Asian Cup — which takes ...
The post Celtic dodge a bullet as Asian Games squad is announced appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers may be about to get wish from first Celtic media day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167209</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-may-be-about-to-get-wish-from-first-celtic-media-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers may be about to get an important wish at Celtic. The Hoops boss will still be in the process of evaluating his new squad. The first-team are currently in Portugal, and will travel to Japan next week as they step-up preparations for the new season. Recruitment will continue to be a major topic ...
The post Brendan Rodgers may be about to get wish from first Celtic media day appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic announce fixture change as tricky early season test is selected by Sky Sports]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167204</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-announce-fixture-change-as-difficult-early-season-test-is-selected-by-sky-sports/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T14:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As expected, Celtic’s match away to Livingston in the Scottish Premiership this September has been selected by Sky Sports, meaning Brendan Rodgers’ team face another lunchtime kick-off in the opening weeks of the season. The game away to David Martindale’s side had been scheduled in for 3pm on Saturday 23rd September, but will now kick-off ...
The post Celtic announce fixture change as tricky early season test is selected by Sky Sports appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rodgers talks Kennedy and Kewell; explains how Celtic training will be different]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167198</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/rodgers-talks-kennedy-and-kewell-explains-how-celtic-training-will-be-different/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T13:43:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers has praised John Kennedy and explained his role in training. The first-team squad are currently in Portugal, being put through their paces as they prepare for the new season. It’s still very early on in Rodgers‘ second spell at the club, but the early signs are positive with standards already high. ...
The post Rodgers talks Kennedy and Kewell; explains how Celtic training will be different appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic player involved as women's match makes unlikely headlines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167191</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-player-involved-as-womens-match-makes-unlikely-headlines/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T12:46:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently departed Celtic player Claire O’Riordan has been caught up in some strange goings-on. The Republic of Ireland international is busy preparing for her country’s tilt at the 2023 FIFA Women’s World Cup in Australia and New Zealand. Ireland have had plenty of warm-up matches, with their most recent a closed-door clash against Colombia. The ...
The post Former Celtic player involved as women's match makes unlikely headlines appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic look set to sign midfielder compared to Rodri]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42607</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/14/celtic-sign-midfielder-compared-rodri/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T12:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a fantastic record in recent years, when it comes to identifying the right talents from around the world. The club have brought in the likes of Kyogo, Jota, Reo Hatate, Cameron Carter-Vickers, Josip Juranovic, Alistair Johnston, Matt O’Riley and many more superb players, just over the past couple of seasons. Thus, fans would […]
Celtic look set to sign midfielder compared to Rodri - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Encouraging signs as Brendan Rodgers names two Celtic stars who have set early standards]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167183</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/encouraging-signs-as-brendan-rodgers-names-two-celtic-stars-who-have-set-early-standards/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T12:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has praised the international contingent for bringing added quality to Celtic training. It’s been a staggered start to pre-season over the past few weeks. Sessions started at Lennoxtown without Celtic‘s international players, before they joined up for work in Portugal. Rodgers reckons they have brought some additional quality to proceedings, as he named ...
The post Encouraging signs as Brendan Rodgers names two Celtic stars who have set early standards appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC KOREAN SWOOP – AT THE DOUBLE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109840</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-korean-swoop-at-the-double/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T11:14:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC are on the brink of a daring double swoop for South Korean pair Yang Hyun-Jun and Kwon Hyeok-kyu. The Hoops have been chasing Yang for over a month and the £2.1million deal is about to be sealed, according to a report in local media outlet Sports Chosun. The 21-year-old highly-rated winger has insisted in recent weeks [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summer signing shares what everyone has been telling him about Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167175</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/marco-tilio-shares-what-everyone-has-been-telling-him-about-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marco Tilio couldn’t even make it out of the airport before being told about Celtic Park. The Australian arrived in Glasgow last week after signing from Melbourne City seven days earlier. Since then he has been thrust into the media spotlight, flown out to Portugal with his team-mates and confirmed to be missing the first ...
The post Summer signing shares what everyone has been telling him about Celtic Park appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why we might need a pool of 7 wingers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109839</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/why-we-might-need-a-pool-of-7-wingers/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T11:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[News from Korea today suggests we have agreed the transfer of Yang Hyun-jun from Gangwon.  The player turned 21 two days before our last league game of the season against Aberdeen.  Gangwon have won only two of their 22 league games and sit well adrift of safety in the relegation zone. He is young and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic's Asian influence to grow further as December interest pays off]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167167</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-asian-influence-to-grow-further-as-december-interest-pays-off/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T10:14:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are set to complete two more signings from South Korea, according to a report. Korean daily newspaper The Chosun Ilbo report that deals for Hyun-jun Yang and Kwon Hyeok-kyu have been completed. They include some quotes from an “official in the transfer market” who says: “Yang Hyun-jun’s transfer to Celtic has been confirmed. After ...
The post Report: Celtic's Asian influence to grow further as December interest pays off appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic agree £2.1 million deal for third summer signing]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42604</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/14/celtic-agree-deal-third-summer-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T09:35:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After completing moves for Odin Thiago Holm and Marco Tilio early on in the summer transfer window, things have moved a bit slowly for Celtic over the past few days. Now though, it looks like a third signing is not far away either and the Hoops appear to have agreed a deal, as they continue […]
Celtic agree £2.1 million deal for third summer signing - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘FOOTBALL’S MAD,’ INSISTS HART]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109834</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/footballs-mad-insists-hart/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T09:20:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART has gone into overdrive as he prepares for yet another campaign as a new season looms into view. The 36-year-old 75 times-capped England international keeper has seen it all before at Manchester City and his stops at Shrewsbury, Burnley and Spurs while he experienced it, too, in Italy during a loan season at [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘FIGHT FOR OUR LIVES,’ CELTIC BOSS IN EURO VOW]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109825</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/fight-for-our-lives-celtic-boss-in-euro-vow/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T08:07:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DETERMINED Brendan Rodgers insists Celtic “will fight for our lives in the Champions League”. However, the manager is savvy enough to realise that success in the group stages of Europe’s elite competition may be a step too far for his team at the moment. European football after the turn of the year is crucial to the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘THAT DOESN’T BOTHER ME ONE BIT,’ SCOFFS RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109823</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/that-doesnt-bother-me-one-bit-scoffs-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T07:31:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS scoffs at the old adage of never going back. The Irishman returned to Celtic last month after leaving the champions over four-and-a-half years earlier in abrupt fashion to take over Leicester City in February 2019. However, Rodgers, 50, had no hesitation in coming back to Parkhead to succeed Spurs-bound Ange Postecoglou when the call [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SALES TALK: RODGERS REMAINS FOCUSED]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109822</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/sales-talk-rodgers-remains-focused/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T07:15:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is remaining focused amid transfer speculation as the Premiership looms into view with the big kick-off due on Flag Day against Ross County at Parkhead three weeks tomorrow. The returning Celtic boss will be without three of the stars who helped the club make world history with an eighth treble last season. Canada [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS BACKS ‘UNDERVALUED’ CELT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109819</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-backs-undervalued-celt/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T06:17:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has given veteran keeper Joe Hart a massive vote of confidence – for the time being. The returning Celtic manager has been assessing the squad of players he inherited from Ange Postecoglou to compile the strongest group for the rigours that lie ahead. Portuguese maverick Filipe Jota has already quit the treble winners for [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers sets out 3 basic rules as he shares what Celtic formations and tactics to expect]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167163</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-sets-out-3-basic-rules-as-he-shares-what-celtic-formation-and-tactics-to-expect/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T06:11:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic supporters are pretty well accustomed to the kind of football Brendan Rodgers plays, but there are still a few tactical unknowns heading into the new season – primarily how the existing squad built by Ange Postecoglou fit into those plans. From an approach standpoint, however, it seems not much will change from Rodgers’ first ...
The post Brendan Rodgers sets out 3 basic rules as he shares what Celtic formations and tactics to expect appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[McCarthy and fringe players discussed by Brendan Rodgers; strength of Celtic squad is assessed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167160</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/mccarthy-and-fringe-players-discussed-by-brendan-rodgers-strength-of-celtic-squad-is-assessed/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T05:42:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers is using this initial period on his return to Celtic to assess the strength of the squad, from its top stars to the fringe players who have struggled to get a look in under Ange Postecoglou. Amongst those being put through their paces in Portugal are James McCarthy and Liam Scales, both signed ...
The post McCarthy and fringe players discussed by Brendan Rodgers; strength of Celtic squad is assessed appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC TRIPLE SETBACK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109815</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-triple-setback/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T05:31:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MARCO TILIO has joined Alistair and Mikey Johnston on the Celtic crocked list who will miss the start of the new season. The Canada World Cup right-back could be out for six to eight weeks after undergoing an ankle operation. Johnston was injured playing for his nation against America where he was forced to limp off [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers provides disappointing update on new Celtic signing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167157</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-provides-disappointing-update-on-new-celtic-signing-marco-tilio/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T05:11:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans will have to wait to see Marco Tilio in action after Brendan Rodgers revealed he is suffering from an injury that will keep him out of the first few weeks of the season. Tilio signed from Melbourne City on a five-year deal earlier this month and it was hoped he could start to ...
The post Brendan Rodgers provides disappointing update on new Celtic signing appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…MIKU?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109796</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-miku/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T05:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEIL LENNON reckoned he had pulled off a signing coup when he brought Venezualan striker Miku to Celtic on loan on the last day of the transfer window on August 31 2012. The 27-year-old frontman was surprisingly allowed to leave Spanish outfit Getafe where he had been their top scorer in La Liga the previous [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FRUGAL McCANN AND BIG PIERRE: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Three)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=93609</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/frugal-mccann-and-big-pierre-the-tommy-burns-story-part-three/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T04:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS had to revive Celtic after their sensational penalty-kick loss to Raith Rovers in the League Cup Final at Ibrox on the fateful Sunday afternoon of November 27 1994. The shock waves reverberated around the whole of football and Parkhead and the manager realised he would have to spend big money to help turn [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable journalist offers Donny van de Beek to Celtic news]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42600</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/13/journalist-donny-van-de-beek-celtic-news/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T22:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with quite a few big names in recent times, as rumours have suggested that the club are interested in making a few marquee signings this summer. One player who would fall under that category is Donny van de Beek. The Manchester United midfielder is someone the Hoops are rumoured to hold […]
Reliable journalist offers Donny van de Beek to Celtic news - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player ruled out for three months with new injury]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42597</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/13/celtic-player-three-months-injury/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T20:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers’ start to his second stint as Celtic manager has not been the smoothest at all. The club have already lost arguably their most creative player in the form of Jota. Alistair Johnston has undergone a surgery as well, which means that he looks set to miss the start of next season. And now, […]
Celtic player ruled out for three months with new injury - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart's telling insight on behind-closed-doors Celtic match and 6-a-side training tournament]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167153</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/joe-harts-telling-insight-on-behind-closed-doors-celtic-match-and-6-a-side-training-tournament/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T20:18:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been delivering regular video and social media content from the club’s training camp in Portugal; tonight it was Joe Hart’s turn to face the cameras and give supporters an update. Hart was one of the players involved in Wednesday’s 0-0 bounce game against Portuguese top-flight side Portimonense and also took part in a ...
The post Joe Hart's telling insight on behind-closed-doors Celtic match and 6-a-side training tournament appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 6 Celtic players who won Thursday's Portugal training tournament]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167150</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-6-celtic-players-who-won-thursdays-portugal-training-tournament/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T19:42:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic players are hard at work in Portugal preparing for the new season, but they’re also having plenty of fun too, if the club’s social media updates are anything to go by. The official Celtic Twitter account posted this evening that the squad took part in a six-a-side training tournament at ‘The Campus’ centre on ...
The post The 6 Celtic players who won Thursday's Portugal training tournament appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers gives 17-year-old Celtic chance after interest from Newcastle and Spurs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167131</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/brendan-rodgers-gives-17-year-old-celtic-chance-after-interest-from-newcastle-and-spurs/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic prospect Mitchel Frame is one of the Bhoys prospects getting a big chance in Portugal this week as Brendan Rodgers takes a look at talents from all levels at the club. Earlier this week we brought you seven names who were spotted in training pictures including Rocco Vata, Ben Summers, Josh Dede and Daniel ...
The post Brendan Rodgers gives 17-year-old Celtic chance after interest from Newcastle and Spurs appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic offered superb Kieran Tierney transfer boost]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42594</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/13/celtic-kieran-tierney-transfer-boost/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T19:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody would have expected Kieran Tierney to be linked with a return to Celtic this summer, even though he is expected to leave Arsenal. It was in 2019 that he had left his boyhood club in order to join the Premier League giants in a Scottish record £25 million move. A lot has happened since […]
Celtic offered superb Kieran Tierney transfer boost - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upcoming coverage after a strange start; the Celtic TV situation for the rest of pre-season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167056</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/upcoming-coverage-after-a-strange-start-the-celtic-tv-situation-for-the-rest-of-pre-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic supporters should be able to see more of the team in action later this pre-season. The Hoops played their first organised match on Wednesday evening as things got off to a strange start. There was no video, audio or text coverage of the clash against Portimonense. Numerous score applications have the result down as ...
The post Upcoming coverage after a strange start; the Celtic TV situation for the rest of pre-season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steven Gerrard wants ex-Celtic star who terrorised Rangers; Fabrizio Romano update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167126</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/steven-gerrard-wants-ex-celtic-star-who-terrorised-rangers-fabrizio-romano-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T18:11:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker, Moussa Dembele has been approached by Saudi Arabain club, Al Ettifaq according to Italian transfer specialist, Fabrizio Romano. The Saudi club have recently hired former Rangers manager, Steven Gerrard as their manager. The Frenchman is still a free agent after leaving Lyon when his contract expired at the end of the season. ...
The post Steven Gerrard wants ex-Celtic star who terrorised Rangers; Fabrizio Romano update appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking forward to getting back to see Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58086</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/looking-forward-to-getting-back-to-see-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T18:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s nice to be back writing about Celtic after the summer break. We look forward to another season following Celtic home and away. Thanks to everyone who bought the latest More than 90 Minutes. The print edition is heading for another sell out with less than 5 copies left as I write. Work will begin […]
The post Looking forward to getting back to see Celtic appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers states the achievable UEFA Champions League goal for Celtic this season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167121</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-states-the-achievable-uefa-champions-league-goal-for-celtic-this-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T17:40:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the hype around Brendan Rodgers’ return to Celtic last month, there were some pretty big claims and ambitions being reported by journalists around Scotland about the manager’s expectations of the future. One columnist suggested that Rodgers’ private aim was to bring the Bhoys to a European final. Publicly, the Celtic boss is never going ...
The post Brendan Rodgers states the achievable UEFA Champions League goal for Celtic this season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic starter undergoes surgery and out for 6-8 weeks]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42591</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/13/celtic-starter-surgery-6-8-weeks/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T17:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are just days into pre-season training and there is already worrying injury news for Celtic. But the club have faced fitness issues for some time now and that has not stopped them from being successful on the pitch. They are coming off of a treble-winning campaign after all. This is not the start that […]
Celtic starter undergoes surgery and out for 6-8 weeks - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Got to give respect to Ronny" - Rodgers brings up Deila in Celtic media response]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167111</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/got-to-give-respect-to-ronny-rodgers-brings-up-deila-in-celtic-media-response/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ronny Deila got a mention from Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers at Thursday’s press conference. The current Hoops boss was speaking to the media from Portugal where his first-team stars are being put through their paces. Rodgers returned to Celtic almost a month ago, over four years on from his first spell at the club. At ...
The post "Got to give respect to Ronny" - Rodgers brings up Deila in Celtic media response appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tomoki Iwata's encouraging, self-critical Celtic appraisal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167071</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/tomoki-iwatas-encouraging-but-pretty-harsh-celtic-appraisal/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tomoki Iwata is the latest Celtic player to speak to club media in Portugal. As we’ve been covering over the past few days, a number of the first-team squad have been put in front of the Celtic TV cameras for a chat. The likes of Daizen Maeda, Carl Starfelt and Daniel Kelly have all given ...
The post Tomoki Iwata's encouraging, self-critical Celtic appraisal appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The three positions Celtic must strengthen in the summer transfer window - Opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167097</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-three-positions-celtic-must-strengthen-in-the-summer-transfer-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Celtic already adding two names to the squad this summer (three if you count Tomoki Iwata), the club are, seemingly, still looking to add more bodies as Brendan Rodgers looks to strengthen for the season ahead. The club have been linked to a variety of names so far but are temporary loan deals for ...
The post The three positions Celtic must strengthen in the summer transfer window - Opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers’ update on Cameron Carter-Vickers will delight the Celtic support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167104</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-update-on-cameron-carter-vickers-will-delight-the-celtic-support/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today has been a day for bad news on the injury front for Celtic. With Mikey Johnston and Alistair Johnston both confirmed as mid to long-term injuries today by Brendan Rodgers, the Celtic support must be massaging their temples with worry at the recent updates from the club. But there is good news on the ...
The post Brendan Rodgers’ update on Cameron Carter-Vickers will delight the Celtic support appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decisions must be looming on Celtic stars contracted until 2024 - Opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167080</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/decisions-must-be-looming-on-celtic-stars-contracted-until-2024/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have made some brilliant headway over the last two weeks by tieing up Callum McGregor, Daizen Maeda and Kyogo Furuhashi into new contracts. The club are clearly looking to make a statement of intent after the disappointing loss of Ange Postecoglou to Spurs and Jota to Al-Ittihad. And whilst many fans are looking to ...
The post Decisions must be looming on Celtic stars contracted until 2024 - Opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The latest on potential Celtic signings as Brendan Rodgers has his say on high-profile departure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167092</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-latest-on-potential-celtic-signings-as-brendan-rodgers-has-his-say-on-jota-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T14:36:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers has updated the media on the latest situation with potential signings. Celtic have signed Odin Thiago Holm and Marco Tilio so far this summer, while Tomoki Iwata’s permanent move was also confirmed by the club on Thursday. Jota and Aaron Mooy are the two big departures, and fans are keen to ...
The post The latest on potential Celtic signings as Brendan Rodgers has his say on high-profile departure appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers clears up Alistair Johnston injury but the news could be better]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167079</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-clears-up-alistair-johnston-injury-but-the-news-could-be-better/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T14:01:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has cleared up the situation with Alistair Johnston and an injury. Last night, a report suggested that Johnston could miss the start of the season. Sadly, it seems like that is an inevitability, with the Canadian recovering. Johnston first injured his ankle in our Scottish Cup semi-final win over Rangers in ...
The post Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers clears up Alistair Johnston injury but the news could be better appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic player's heartfelt farewell message after ending 9 year stay at the club]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167068</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/conor-hazard-pens-heartfelt-farewell-message-after-celtic-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Celtic making some positive movements in the transfer window with the acquisitions of Odin Thiago Holm and Macro Tilio, inevitably players will have to move on. And one such player that has been moved on is Conor Hazard. The Northern Ireland international joined Plymouth Argyle this week on a three-year deal as he looks ...
The post Former Celtic player's heartfelt farewell message after ending 9 year stay at the club appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IWATA REVEALS HOOPS TARGETS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109809</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/iwata-reveals-hoops-targets/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T13:34:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMOKI IWATA won three medals in only 18 appearances for Celtic after arriving from Yokohama F Marinos in January. His spectacular silverware achievement is matched by Canadian World Cup right-back Alistair Johnston and South Korean international striker Oh Hyeon-gyu who arrived at Parkhead at the same time. It’s been a whirlwind start for the new [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELT FACES THREE-MONTH LAY-OFF]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109804</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celt-faces-three-month-lay-off/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T12:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MIKEY JOHNSTON’S hopes of impressing Brendan Rodgers in the early games of the new season have been obliterated. The winger, who spent last term on loan at Portuguese club Vitoria Guimaraes, will miss the kick off to the 2023/24 campaign with a back injury and could be out for THREE months. It’s a hammer blow [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers announces latest injury blow for Celtic attacker; comments on future]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167061</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-announces-latest-mikey-johnston-injury-blow-comments-on-celtic-future/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T12:14:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mikey Johnston will miss the first few months of the season, Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has announced. The Hoops winger spent last season on loan in Portugal with Vitoria Guimaraes, and would have hoped to hit the ground running on his return to Celtic. Rodgers handed Johnston has big Celtic chance in his first spell ...
The post Brendan Rodgers announces latest injury blow for Celtic attacker; comments on future appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic permanent transfer finally announced officially]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42588</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/13/celtic-transfer-announced-officially/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T12:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ange Postecoglou era at Celtic might be over, after the Australian manager decided to leave the club in order to take the Tottenham Hotspur job this summer. His influence still continues to be felt at Parkhead though and the club have signed a player on a permanent basis, who was brought in on loan […]
Celtic permanent transfer finally announced officially - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and an Aviva Stadium free-for-all; intriguing Wolves ticket arrangements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167040</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-and-an-aviva-stadium-free-for-all-intriguing-wolves-ticket-arrangements/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans are set for a free-for-all when buying tickets for the upcoming friendly against Wolves. The Hoops will face the Premier League side at the Aviva Stadium in Dublin on Saturday 29 July. The match will kick-off at 2pm and act as an additional warm-up fixture ahead of the start of both side’s competitive ...
The post Celtic and an Aviva Stadium free-for-all; intriguing Wolves ticket arrangements appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star reacts as loan move is officially made permanent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167046</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/tomoki-iwata-reacts-as-yokohama-f-marinos-make-celtic-transfer-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tomoki Iwata’s move from Yokohama F Marinos to Celtic has been made official after an announcement by the Japanese club. No fee or contract details have been released. Iwata spent the second half of last season on loan at Celtic where he helped the club win their world-record eighth domestic treble. Although used sparingly, Iwata ...
The post Celtic star reacts as loan move is officially made permanent appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full back tales, tall ones and worrying ones]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109795</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/full-back-tales-tall-ones-and-worrying-ones/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m struggling to find anything viable in newspaper stories linking Kieran Tierney returning to Celtic.  He has been the outstanding left back of the last 20 years, but I don’t see the fit.  He is 26 years old, has three years left on his Arsenal contract and is currently earning three times our top salary. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Odsonne Edouard sends Moussa Dembele a message and reminds us of some glorious Celtic days]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167033</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/odsonne-edouard-sends-moussa-dembele-a-message-and-reminds-us-of-some-glorious-celtic-days/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Odsonne Edouard has sent Moussa Dembele a birthday message and reminded us of some glorious Celtic days. Dembele turned 27 yesterday, in news that may make you feel a little older. The Frenchman was just 19 when he joined Celtic in the summer of 2016 — right at the start of the first Brendan Rodgers ...
The post Odsonne Edouard sends Moussa Dembele a message and reminds us of some glorious Celtic days appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The latest on Kieran Tierney and Celtic reunion; wage concession, Rodgers' stance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167029</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-latest-on-kieran-tierney-and-celtic-reunion-wage-concession-rodgers-stance/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Kieran Tierney to Celtic story is one that is not going away anytime soon it seems. The former Celtic defender has found it difficult to break into the Arsenal first team and now seems keen on finding first-team football next season. Newcastle are also said to be interested in the Scotland fullback but it ...
The post The latest on Kieran Tierney and Celtic reunion; wage concession, Rodgers' stance appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mixed feelings as entire new Adidas Celtic training range hits shelves]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167024</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/mixed-feelings-as-entire-new-adidas-celtic-training-range-hits-shelves/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T09:17:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The full new Adidas Celtic training range has been released online and in stores. The first-team are currently in Portugal gearing up for the new season, and they’ve been sporting some new gear in the process. Fans got a first glimpse of the new Adidas gear when training resumed at Lennoxtown a fortnight ago. The ...
The post Mixed feelings as entire new Adidas Celtic training range hits shelves appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic suffer injury blow with key player out of action]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42583</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/13/celtic-suffer-injury-blow-key-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T09:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Returning for his second spell in the Celtic Park hot seat, Brendan Rodgers surely would have wanted to have his best players available from the get go in order to make a bright start to the campaign. But it looks like one of the Hoops’ key stars could end up missing the beginning of the […]
Celtic suffer injury blow with key player out of action - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Mikael Lustig's comments on Brendan Rodgers should excite the Celtic fans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167019</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/why-mikael-lustigs-comments-on-brendan-rodgers-should-excite-the-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T08:41:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new Brendan Rogers era is now underway at Celtic. The Celtic manager is well into his preparations in the Portugal training camp. 67 Hail Hail covered a story yesterday that gave a glimpse into how Rodgers was working and communicating with the Celtic players on the training ground. The Celtic manager looked calm, composed ...
The post Why Mikael Lustig's comments on Brendan Rodgers should excite the Celtic fans appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confirmed: The amount Celtic and Scottish clubs received from FIFA for 2022 World Cup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167014</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/confirmed-the-amount-celtic-and-scottish-clubs-received-from-fifa-for-2022-world-cup/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T08:05:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will receive a six-figure fee from FIFA for player participation in the 2022 World Cup, it has been confirmed by the global body today. After every World Cup, FIFA pay clubs around the world a per day fee for their players taking part in the tournament, shared between all of the clubs who held ...
The post Confirmed: The amount Celtic and Scottish clubs received from FIFA for 2022 World Cup appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston injury update; the key Celtic fixtures defender could miss]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167011</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alistair-johnston-injury-update-the-key-celtic-fixtures-defender-could-miss/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston looks set to miss the start of the season for Celtic a report from The Sun has claimed. The Celtic right-back suffered a foot injury in the Scottish Cup semi-final against Rangers in April of this year. The Canadian had seemed to have made a full recovery after appearing in the final against ...
The post Alistair Johnston injury update; the key Celtic fixtures defender could miss appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ticket prices not the big issue; the expensive reality of Celtic's latest pre-season trip]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166954</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ticket-prices-not-the-big-issue-the-expensive-reality-of-celtics-latest-trip-to-dublin/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T06:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are heading for Dublin again later this month, with a friendly against Wolves now confirmed. The club made the announcement on Wednesday morning, with the fixture taking place at the Aviva Stadium at 2pm on Saturday 29 July. It’s the team’s first visit to Dublin since 2018 and our first at the home of ...
The post Ticket prices not the big issue; the expensive reality of Celtic's latest pre-season trip appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘FUN BHOY’ WHO GOT THE BOOT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109785</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/fun-bhoy-who-got-the-boot/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T06:27:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FUN-LOVING Boli Bolingoli broke strict Government Covid regulations for a hush-hush break with his girlfriend to Spain in August 2020. The blundering Belgian’s secret sunshine trip was exposed AFTER a cameo appearance in the 1-1 draw with Kilmarnock at Rugby Park in the second Premiership game of the club’s disastrous quest for a historic tenth [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Celtic should avoid Kieran Tierney loan move but must strengthen key left-back position]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166977</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/why-celtic-should-avoid-kieran-tierney-loan-move-but-must-strengthen-key-left-back-position/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T06:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There has been a decent amount of chatter over the last few weeks about the possibility of Celtic making the return of Kieran Tierney to Paradise a reality. The current Arsenal defender has found it difficult to break into Mikel Arteta’s first team and whilst rumours have been rife that he could be about to ...
The post Why Celtic should avoid Kieran Tierney loan move but must strengthen key left-back position appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UEFA relax home nation knockout rules; the earliest Celtic could face Scottish rivals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166964</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/uefa-relax-home-nation-knockout-rules-the-earliest-celtic-could-face-scottish-rivals/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T05:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic could come in to contact with other Scottish clubs earlier than ever before in new UEFA proposals. European football’s governing body have been releasing more details about what the Champions League, Europa League and Conference League will look like from season 2024/25. As we told you yesterday, the knockout rounds of the competitions are ...
The post UEFA relax home nation knockout rules; the earliest Celtic could face Scottish rivals appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘CROCKED’ JOHNSTON SETBACK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109776</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/crocked-johnston-setback/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T05:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC right-back Alistair Johnston is struggling to be fit in time for the season’s kick-off against Ross County at Parkhead on Saturday August 5. The Canadian World Cup defender has yet to begin training with Brendan Rodgers’ squad after returning from international duty with an injury. Johnston started his nation’s games against Panama and the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…THOMAS ROGNE?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109746</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-thomas-rogne/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T05:15:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THOMAS ROGNE was seen as one for the future when he was signed by Tony Mowbray on a free from Norwegian club Stabaek in January 2010. The 19-year-old 6ft 4in centre-back agreed a three-and-a-half-year deal at the Parkhead side and was unexpectedly handed a first-team appearance only three weeks after arriving in Scotland. Rogne made [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE DESPERATE HOURS: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Two)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=93539</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-desperate-hours-the-tommy-burns-story-part-two/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T04:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS travelled to Ibrox on the Sunday afternoon of November 27 1994 with the opportunity of winning the League Cup – just four months after his return to Celtic as manager. Raith Rovers, from the First Division, stood in the way of the club’s iconic midfielder and fans’ favourite lifting his first piece of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jota faces potential ban after leaving Celtic for Al-Ittihad]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42563</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/12/jota-faces-ban-celtic-al-ittihad/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T22:05:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The transfer of Jota from Celtic to Al-Ittihad was quite an eye opening deal in many ways. It was no surprise that the Portuguese winger was wanted by another club. He had made a tremendous impact for the Hoops over the past couple of seasons. But his destination was perhaps a major surprise to most […]
Jota faces potential ban after leaving Celtic for Al-Ittihad - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic told they don’t need to sign £16 million free agent]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42575</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/12/celtic-told-need-free-agent/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T20:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are expected to bring in several fresh faces this summer in an attempt to strengthen Brendan Rodgers’ squad for the upcoming season. Till now, they have signed Odin Thiago Holm and Marco Tilio. Both are very highly-rated talents and might go on to become superstars at Parkhead but at the same time, they are […]
Celtic told they don’t need to sign £16 million free agent - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wolves marketing figure references Celtic disappointment after South Korea shambles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166998</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/wolves-marketing-figure-shares-celtic-disappointment-after-south-korea-shambles/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T20:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A key marketing figure at Wolves has been talking up his side’s upcoming clash against Celtic. It was announced on Wednesday that Brendan Rodgers’ men will face the Premier League team in Dublin on Saturday 29 July. The game will take place at the glorious Aviva Stadium, with kick-off at 2pm. The Hoops were originally ...
The post Wolves marketing figure references Celtic disappointment after South Korea shambles appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The two former Celtic Treble winners still looking for a club]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167008</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-two-former-celtic-treble-winners-still-looking-for-a-club/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T19:45:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The transfer window is a part of the season that all football fans love. The excitement of new players coming in coupled with the possibility of the club raking in millions whenever one of our top players are sold makes what would be a boring part of the year with no football that little bit ...
The post The two former Celtic Treble winners still looking for a club appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Odin Thiago Holm just getting started as Celtic begin with slow-mo hype]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166994</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/odin-thiago-holm-just-getting-started-as-celtic-begin-with-slow-mo-hype-another-star-absent/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic started their hype of summer signing Odin Thiago Holm on Wednesday. It’s three weeks since the Norwegian was signed from Valerenga on a five-year contract. The Celtic first-team were on holiday at that stage, and have since returned with the squad now in Portugal. Over the past few weeks while the players have been ...
The post Odin Thiago Holm just getting started as Celtic begin with slow-mo hype appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[€20 million Celtic target confirms he wants summer move]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42570</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/12/20-million-celtic-target-wants-move/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T19:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with plenty of high profile names in recent times, as it is believed that the club could be targeting a few marquee signings in the ongoing summer transfer window. It remains to be seen how things play out. The likes of Scott McTominay, Donny van de Beek, Kieran Tierney and a […]
€20 million Celtic target confirms he wants summer move - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fresh Donny van de Beek news should worry Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42566</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/12/donny-van-de-beek-news-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T17:35:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rumours have suggested that Celtic could try to pull off a few marquee signings this summer in order to strengthen Brendan Rodgers’ squad, as they look to defend their treble and also make an impact in the Champions League. And one player that they have been linked with lately is Manchester United midfielder, Donny van […]
Fresh Donny van de Beek news should worry Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic manager Neil Lennon lays out the unenviable task ahead for Michael Beale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166991</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-manager-neil-lennon-lays-out-the-unenviable-task-ahead-for-michael-beale/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new season ahead brings fresh optimism for every supporter base of every club. Only two teams can win the league but all teams go into the new season believing that they can, at least, win a cup of some sort. Well, that’s if Celtic stop hoovering them all up at the rate of knots ...
The post Former Celtic manager Neil Lennon lays out the unenviable task ahead for Michael Beale appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why this is the summer of opportunity for Celtic's former POTY; it could start tonight]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166985</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/why-this-is-the-summer-of-opportunity-for-celtics-david-turnbull-it-could-start-tonight/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is something about David Turnbull that makes me warm to him as a Celtic player. Now, I don’t know if it was because in that instantly forgettable COVID season he was the one shining light in what was a pretty shocking year for the club. Or maybe it’s because I love to see Scottish ...
The post Why this is the summer of opportunity for Celtic's former POTY; it could start tonight appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A rare media treat; Daizen Maeda makes one thing clear about Celtic in Japan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166967</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/a-rare-media-treat-daizen-maeda-makes-one-thing-clear-about-celtic-in-japan/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic attacker Daizen Maeda has given a rare interview to club media in Portugal. The Japanese attacker is part of the Celtic squad being put through their paces by manager Brendan Rodgers. The Hoops are due to face Portuguese side Portimonense this evening although the game will be a very low-key affair. Maeda may feature ...
The post A rare media treat; Daizen Maeda makes one thing clear about Celtic in Japan appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Darren O'Dea credits backroom man for Celtic B progress despite defeat to Sligo Rovers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166969</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/darren-odea-credits-backroom-man-for-celtic-b-progress-despite-defeat-to-sligo-rovers/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not just Brendan Rodgers’ men that are preparing for the new season ahead. The youngsters in the Celtic B team have also started their preparations for another year in the Lowland League. The young Hoops took part in a friendly in Ireland against Sligo Rovers last night ahead of the new season kick-off in ...
The post Darren O'Dea credits backroom man for Celtic B progress despite defeat to Sligo Rovers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic favourites to sign €20 million Brazilian winger]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42558</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/12/celtic-favourites-sign-brazilian-winger/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T12:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are rumoured to be looking to bring in some marquee players this summer in order to strengthen Brendan Rodgers’ squad. One area where they certainly need reinforcements at the moment is on the wings. They have seen a nailed on starter like Jota leave recently, leaving a big gap there. Jota arrived at the […]
Celtic favourites to sign €20 million Brazilian winger - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Willie Miller names versatile Celtic defender to fill priority position at Aberdeen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166953</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/willie-miller-names-versatile-celtic-defender-to-fill-priority-position-at-aberdeen/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic had a number of players out on loan last season and whilst many of them had successful seasons, there are others that did struggle to make a name for themselves. One that did impress was Liam Scales. The Celtic defender spent a full season on loan at Aberdeen. After a shaky start to his ...
The post Willie Miller names versatile Celtic defender to fill priority position at Aberdeen appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Returning loan player and an interesting midfield; Celtic Predicted XI vs Portimonense]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166938</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/returning-loan-player-and-an-interesting-midfield-celtic-predicted-xi-vs-portimonense/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are back in action on Wednesday evening against Portuguese side Portimonense. It’s 39 days since we clinched our latest treble with a 3-1 Scottish Cup final victory over Inverness Caledonian Thistle at Hampden. To say that a lot has changed since then would be an understatement. Ange Postecoglou has departed the club and been ...
The post Returning loan player and an interesting midfield; Celtic Predicted XI vs Portimonense appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summer fitness claims never stack up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109774</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/sumer-fitness-claims-never-stack-up/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T11:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a week of hard training, Celtic take to the field for their first preseason friendly today when they face Portimonense this evening.  The Portuguese side finished 15th in the topflight last season, a comfortable 8 points above relegation, although only one spot above the play-offs. We face the same side on Saturday before flying [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic are the main contenders to sign Brazilian winger]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166939</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-are-the-main-contenders-to-sign-brazilian-winger-tete/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been named as one of the main contenders to sign Shakhtar Donetsk winger, Tete. A report from Ukrainian outlet Sport Novyny has said that the 23-year-old intends to leave the club due to fears for his safety due to the ongoing conflict in the region. Tete joined Donetsk in 2019 as a product ...
The post Report: Celtic are the main contenders to sign Brazilian winger appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[€5 million Celtic flop closes in on move to Swansea City]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42555</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/12/5-million-celtic-flop-swansea-city/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T10:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been very good with their signings in recent times. That was not always the case though. In fact, one of the biggest reasons behind their struggles in the 2020/21 campaign was the terrible summer transfer window that they had that time around. Not one player that was brought in during those few months […]
€5 million Celtic flop closes in on move to Swansea City - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A pleasing sight from Celtic training and Brendan Rodgers gets a mic'd up moment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166933</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/pleasing-kyogo-furuhashi-sight-in-celtic-training-as-brendan-rodgers-gets-a-micd-up-moment/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T09:47:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Furuhashi has been seen back in training with Celtic in Portugal. Brendan Rodgers‘ side are in the Algarve as preparations step up ahead of the new season. The team are due to face Portuguese top-flight side Portimonense this evening, although that match will be played behind closed doors. The team have been training in ...
The post A pleasing sight from Celtic training and Brendan Rodgers gets a mic'd up moment appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic TV interviews in Portugal take a different turn; rising star put in front of the mic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166924</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-celtic-tv-interviews-in-portugal-take-a-different-turn-rising-star-put-in-front-of-the-mic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T09:13:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rising star Daniel Kelly is the latest player to speak to Celtic TV in Portugal. The Hoops first-team squad are in the Algarve, where they will will face Primeira Liga outfit Portimonense later on Wednesday. The likes of Callum McGregor, Daizen Maeda and Reo Hatate could all feature in the fixture but Celtic‘s stars of ...
The post The Celtic TV interviews in Portugal take a different turn; rising star put in front of the mic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Boyle talks up Brendan Rodgers’ summer signing; exciting times ahead for the Celtic fans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166918</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/martin-boyle-talks-up-brendan-rodgers-summer-signing-exciting-times-ahead-for-the-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T08:44:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic fans may well still be lamenting the loss of Jota this summer. The Portuguese winger was a huge fan favourite over his two years at the club but finally ended his brief, but successful, stay in Glasgow with a move to Al-Ittihad in Saudi Arabia. Jota’s trickery on the wing will be missed ...
The post Martin Boyle talks up Brendan Rodgers’ summer signing; exciting times ahead for the Celtic fans appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Brendan Rodgers must offer a new Celtic deal to 25-year-old international]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166916</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/why-brendan-rodgers-must-offer-a-new-celtic-deal-to-25-year-old-international/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All the excitement over Celtic offering new deals to the likes of Kyogo Furuhashi, Daizen Maeda and Callum McGregor did two things over the last two weeks. For one, it offset the disappointment of losing Portuguese winger Jota to Al-Ittihad and secondly, it put to bed the speculation that former Celtic manager, Ange Postecoglou could ...
The post Why Brendan Rodgers must offer a new Celtic deal to 25-year-old international appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A TALE OF TWO KEEPERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109763</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/a-tale-of-two-keepers/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T07:17:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S £4.5million misfit Vasilis Barkas is on the brink of joining English Championship side Swansea City. And the Greek flop could face former Hoops glove rival Conor Hazard in the new season after the Irishman signed for newly-promoted Plymouth Argyle. Both keepers had dropped down the ranks at the champions behind first-choice Joe Hart and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conor Hazard love extends far and wide; Celtic stars from multiple eras react to departure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166898</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/conor-hazard-love-extends-far-and-wide-celtic-stars-from-multiple-eras-react-to-departure/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T06:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic stars from multiple eras have been reacting after Conor Hazard departed the club. The Northern Irish goalkeeper has signed for Plymouth Argyle, for an undisclosed fee. Hazard took to Instagram on Tuesday evening to share a post of him in the Home Park side’s colours, with an accompanying message reading: “Delighted to sign at ...
The post Conor Hazard love extends far and wide; Celtic stars from multiple eras react to departure appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New name but a familiar look; Jacynta finds her next club after Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166904</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/new-name-but-a-familiar-look-jacynta-finds-her-next-club-after-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T06:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic FC Women star Jacynta Galabadaarachchi has found her next club. The attacker departed Celtic around a week ago after an enjoyable two-and-a-half year spell in Glasgow. Jacynta tormenting SWPL defenders in the hoops was a sight to behold, and something similar may occur next season, in a funny way. That’s because she had ...
The post New name but a familiar look; Jacynta finds her next club after Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic rearrange pre-season friendly; tickets on presale today]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166909</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-pre-season-friendly-rearranged-tickets-on-presale-today/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T05:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s pre-season friendly with English Premier League side Wolves has been rearranged and tickets go on pre-sale today on Ticketmaster. The original match that was organised in South Korea as part of the Asia Tour later this month but was cancelled due to Wolves pulling out of the fixture stating that the tour organisers failed ...
The post Celtic rearrange pre-season friendly; tickets on presale today appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…LASSAD NOUIOUI?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109739</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-lassad-nouioui/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T05:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LASSAD NOUIOUI signed a two-year deal at Celtic on September 2 2012 as a free agent after quitting Spanish top-flight club Deportivo La Coruna. Expectation levels were high for the French-born striker, who won two international caps for his adopted nation Tunisia, after he had performed for three years in La Liga. Peter Lawwell, then [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC v WOLVES IN DUBLIN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109758</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-wolves-in-dublin/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T05:09:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC will play Wolves at the Aviva Stadium on Saturday July 29 with a 2pm kick-off. The clubs were due to face each other in South Korea a fortnight today, but the match was scrapped with both sides withdrawing due to “financial and logistical” issues with organisers. Brendan Rodgers’ men are scheduled to take on [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC CONFIDENTIAL: FANS EUPHORIC AND ENRAGED AFTER TITLE WIN: DAVIE HAY REVEALS ALL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=75485</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-celtic-fans-euphoric-and-enraged-after-title-win-davie-hay-reveals-all/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T05:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Davie Hay concludes his inside tales during an eventful and ultimately successful 1997/98 season. The former player and manager had been chief scout for most of Wim Jansen’s solitary campaign as Hoops boss that saw the Parkhead men derail Rangers’ bid for 10 in a row – and go on and lift the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WELCOME BACK TO CELTIC: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part One)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=93495</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/welcome-back-to-celtic-the-tommy-burns-story-part-one/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T04:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS returned to his beloved Celtic as manager EXACTLY twenty-nine years ago today. It was an emotional and controversial homecoming for the Hoops legend as he left Kilmarnock in acrimonious circumstances to take over from the sacked Lou Macari. Celtic were accused of ‘tapping’ the boss while he was in charge at the Ayrshire [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic must avoid high-profile Premier League loan deals]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42533</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/11/celtic-premier-league-loan-deals/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T22:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a few potential loan deals Celtic are being linked with this summer. They are mainly English Premier League players looking for a fresh opportunity and it would raise serious questions about the Hoops’ planning if any of them end up happening. In the long run, they would help the club at all. Three […]
Celtic must avoid high-profile Premier League loan deals - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£2.6 million Celtic transfer target joins FC Midtjylland]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42547</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/11/celtic-transfer-target-joins-midtjylland/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T21:05:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have two great options up top right now in the form of Kyogo and Oh Hyeon-gyu. The Japanese forward has been the main man for the Hoops in recent times, and found the back of the net on 34 occasions last season. On the other hand, the South Korean striker has impressed as well, […]
£2.6 million Celtic transfer target joins FC Midtjylland - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano’s £35 million update is great news for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42543</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/11/fabrizio-romano-35-million-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T19:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Celtic appointed Brendan Rodgers as manager for a second stint in the Parkhead hot seat, rumours had suggested that the Northern Irishman had been promised a significant transfer budget in order to reshape the squad. Since then, we have seen Jota leave in a £25 million move to Al-Ittihad. And now, it looks like […]
Fabrizio Romano’s £35 million update is great news for Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic comments that feel particularly pertinent as more away fans are shut out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166840</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-joe-hart-comments-that-feel-particularly-pertinent-as-more-celtic-away-fans-are-shut-out/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart doesn’t seem to be the biggest fan of Celtic receiving a small allocation for Tynecastle. The Hoops received just over 1,200 tickets for trips to Hearts last season, but that number will be almost halved in the coming campaign. The Jambos are said to be reducing our allocation due to “high season ticket ...
The post The Celtic comments that feel particularly pertinent as more away fans are shut out appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Brendan Rodgers hype is real as yet another Ange favourite talks up Celtic boss]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166890</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-brendan-rodgers-hype-is-real-as-yet-another-postecoglou-favourite-talks-up-celtic-boss/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T17:45:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carl Starfelt is the latest Celtic player to speak positively about Brendan Rodgers. It’s been an intriguing few weeks as we see our first-team stars return to training under their new boss. The vast majority of the squad were brought to the club by former Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou, and it’s been particularly interesting to ...
The post The Brendan Rodgers hype is real as yet another Ange favourite talks up Celtic boss appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Celtic player completes Parkhead exit this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42539</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/11/another-celtic-player-completes-exit-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T17:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already seen Jota leave Parkhead this summer, in a £25 million move to Al-Ittihad. The Portuguese winger departing is a major blow without doubt and he will need to be replaced. Now, another club hero has headed out of the exit door as well, but his departure is not as high profile and […]
Another Celtic player completes Parkhead exit this summer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UEFA confirm even more big Champions League changes are coming Celtic's way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166885</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/uefa-confirm-even-more-big-champions-league-changes-are-coming-celtics-way/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T16:52:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More big changes are coming to the UEFA Champions League from 2024/25 and Celtic will be affected. As you’ll know by now, European football’s premier club competition is undergoing a major revamp from next season. The new Champions League format will see the traditional group stage ditched in favour of a new single league phase ...
The post UEFA confirm even more big Champions League changes are coming Celtic's way appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former EPL 'keeper tells how Martin O'Neill 'disappeared' and scuppered his move to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166867</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-epl-keeper-tells-how-martin-oneill-disappeared-and-scuppered-his-move-to-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former West Ham United and Newcastle goalkeeper, Shaka Hislop has spoken out about how Celtic were looking to sign him back in 2002 when Martin O’Neill was the manager. The former Trinidad and Tobago international goalkeeper revealed on ESPN’s YouTube podcast how the then-goalkeeping coach, Terry Gennoe was speaking to him about the move and ...
The post Former EPL 'keeper tells how Martin O'Neill 'disappeared' and scuppered his move to Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic exit confirmed as backup player joins English Championship side]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166875</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-exit-confirmed-as-backup-player-joins-english-championship-side/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conor Hazard has finally ended his nine-year affiliation with Celtic after penning a three-year deal with English Championship side, Plymouth Argyle. The Northern Ireland international underwent a medical yesterday and it seems all has gone well as Plymouth announced the move on their official website this afternoon. Hazard signed for Celtic back in 2014 from ...
The post Celtic exit confirmed as backup player joins English Championship side appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The vague SPFL rule that allows clubs to cut Celtic allocation; what can be done]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166857</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-vague-spfl-rule-that-allows-hearts-and-rangers-to-cut-celtic-allocation-what-can-be-done/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will receive just 650 tickets for league matches away to Hearts next season. The BBC say that the Tynecastle club are cutting away allocations next season for every team other than rivals Hibernian. The move is said to be a result of large season ticket sales in Gorgie, but it will continue to squeeze ...
The post The vague SPFL rule that allows clubs to cut Celtic allocation; what can be done appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['They are very important to me' - Kyogo Furuhashi pays tribute to the Celtic supporters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166858</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/they-are-very-important-to-me-kyogo-furuhashi-pays-tribute-to-the-celtic-supporters/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Furuhashi has paid tribute to the Celtic support in an interview with Celtic TV. The Hoops striker was asked how important the fans were in helping him settle at the club when he signed and into home life in Scotland when he revealed just how important the supporters are to him. Kyogo said [Celtic ...
The post 'They are very important to me' - Kyogo Furuhashi pays tribute to the Celtic supporters appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I WANT TO SEE THEIR SMILES,’ KYOGO AIMS TO PLEASE THE FANS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109749</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-want-to-see-their-smiles-kyogo-aims-to-please-the-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T14:08:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MASTER marksman Kyogo Furuhashi is determined to make sure Celtic are smiles better in the new season. The Japanese international striker, who has fired in 54 goals in his 83 appearances spread over two seasons at Parkhead, delighted the Hoops fans when he signed a new four-year deal a week ago, as CQN reported. Kyogo [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers reaffirms fringe player's importance to Celtic's first-team squad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166853</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-reaffirms-james-forrests-importance-to-celtics-first-team-squad/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic continue their preparations for the new season ahead at their training camp in Portugal, Brendan Rodgers took time out to praise James Forrest as the Celtic legend’s testimonial date approaches. The Celtic manager paid tribute to Forrest and urged fans to fill the stadium on the 1st of August and after speaking about ...
The post Brendan Rodgers reaffirms fringe player's importance to Celtic's first-team squad appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano tells of Jeremie Frimpong’s transfer ‘priority’; what it could mean for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166848</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/fabrizio-romano-tells-of-jeremie-frimpongs-transfer-priority-what-it-could-mean-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s all gone quiet on the Celtic transfer front over the last few days. Yes, as 67 Hail Hail highlighted last night, there has been sporadic rumours of interest in some players but nothing really concrete since the signing of Marco Tilio. But that doesn’t mean our transfer interests end there. Celtic still holds a ...
The post Fabrizio Romano tells of Jeremie Frimpong’s transfer ‘priority’; what it could mean for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carlos Borges to Celtic transfer update amid rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42532</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/11/carlos-borges-celtic-transfer-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T12:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have made moves for some highly-rated youngsters this summer. They have brought in Odin Thiago Holm from Valerenga and Marco Tilio from Melbourne City FC. Rumours have suggested that they might be closing in on a move for South Korean youth international, Yang Hyun-jun of Gangwon FC. Another superb young talent that they have […]
Carlos Borges to Celtic transfer update amid rumours - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind-the-scenes video offers fascinating insight in to Celtic star's role in training]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166828</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/behind-the-scenes-celtic-video-offers-fascinating-insight-in-to-joe-harts-role-in-training/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart is Celtic’s number-one goalkeeper but he may have another important role at the club. The Englishman has produced plenty of big moments over the past two years, helping the team to five domestic trophies under Ange Postecoglou. Now, with Brendan Rodgers in charge, the expectation is that Hart will continue between the sticks ...
The post Behind-the-scenes video offers fascinating insight in to Celtic star's role in training appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Tynecastle a more difficult place to visit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109743</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/making-tynecastle-a-more-difficult-place-to-visit/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T11:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why are Hearts proposing to limit the number of away fans to a few hundred, a move which would have consequence for only Celtic and Newco?  It will allow them to sell more season tickets, which would bring in more money.  It would also tip the competitive balance in their favour – no massed ranks [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: No approach from Celtic for Carlos Borges despite City Football Group links]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166842</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/no-approach-from-celtic-for-carlos-borges-despite-city-football-group-links/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are not in for Manchester City teenager Carlos Borges right now, according to a report. The attacker’s name has been on the lips of many Celtic supporters so far this summer, even though there has never been a concrete report linking us with him. As we covered yesterday, the name of Borges and Young ...
The post Report: No approach from Celtic for Carlos Borges despite City Football Group links appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic major contributors as SWPL chief talks up 'unimaginable' numbers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166830</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/celtic-major-contributors-as-swpl-chief-talks-up-unimaginable-numbers/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fran Alonso’s Celtic really captured the imagination of the Celtic fans last season. The Women had us all on the crest of a wave as they kept the challenge of the league title going to the last day of the season. Celtic did look out of it at one point, especially after a defeat to ...
The post Celtic major contributors as SWPL chief talks up 'unimaginable' numbers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star shares family post as injury intrigue continues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166809</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alistair-johnston-shares-family-image-as-injury-intrigue-continues/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Alistair Johnston has shared an amusing family post as intrigue over his fitness continues. The Canadian has been a complete revelation since his January switch from CF Montréal. He’s won the hearts and minds of virtually every Celtic supporter, as well as a hat-trick of trophies. Johnston became an important player for Ange ...
The post Celtic star shares family post as injury intrigue continues appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon tips Manchester United player to join Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42527</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/11/neil-lennon-manchester-united-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T09:30:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are rumoured to be eyeing a few marquee signings this summer in order to boost Brendan Rodgers’ squad ahead of another campaign in the UEFA Champions League group stage and the Hoops have three trophies to defend as well. We have already seen them being linked with one Manchester United player in the form […]
Neil Lennon tips Manchester United player to join Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Darren O'Dea is cautious ahead of Celtic B friendly; Sligo manager recognises club bond]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166820</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/why-darren-odea-is-cautious-ahead-of-celtic-b-friendly-sligo-manager-recognises-club-bond/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic prepare for their upcoming season in Portugal, the B team head to Ireland to face Sligo Rovers in a pre-season friendly. The youngsters will be without the likes of Rocco Vata, Bruno Davidson and Tobi Oluwayemi and Darren O’Dea has highlighted that whilst he has been delighted with the preparations so far, he ...
The post Why Darren O'Dea is cautious ahead of Celtic B friendly; Sligo manager recognises club bond appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Maybe Celtic’s that place for him” - Neil Lennon on recent links with international midfielder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166795</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/maybe-celtics-that-place-for-him-neil-lennon-on-recent-links-with-donny-van-de-beek/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T07:51:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s recent link with Manchester United’s Donny Van De Beek yesterday was a bit of a surprising one. As 67 Hail Hail discussed on the site yesterday, any potential move is likely to be a loan move but should the club pull this one off, it would be an incredible piece of transfer business. Van ...
The post “Maybe Celtic’s that place for him” - Neil Lennon on recent links with international midfielder appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Europa League side weighing up offer for Celtic talent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166789</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/report-celtic-talent-matt-oriley-subject-of-transfer-interest-4-clubs-potential-offer-ahead/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T06:16:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the big-money sale of Jota to Al-Ittihad, Celtic are doubtful keen on the exit of other important talents from last year’s treble-winning squad but it seems they could soon be contending with bids for midfielder Matt O’Riley. The Scottish Daily Mail [11/07 print edition] reports that several sides are showing interest in the Danish ...
The post Report: Europa League side weighing up offer for Celtic talent appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘HE’S ABSOLUTELY THE RIGHT MAN, MATE,’ ANGE’S VERDICT ON RODGERS’ RETURN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109675</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hes-absolutely-the-right-man-mate-anges-verdict-on-rodgers-return/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T06:11:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU had no hesitation in endorsing the merits of Brendan Rodgers as the Irishman continues his preparation for his second stint as Celtic manager. Asked about the qualities of his successor as he returns to the job after an absence of over four years, the Greek-Australian gaffer said: “He’s absolutely the right man, mate. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic youngster set for crucial UEFA Champions League match tonight]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166785</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/celtic-youngster-set-for-crucial-uefa-champions-league-match-tonight/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T05:40:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Believe it or not, the 2023/24 UEFA Champions League kicks off tonight with the first qualifying round – as teams go through the knockout gauntlet for a place in the money-spinning group stages of the competition. Celtic don’t enter the competition until September, with the draw for those all-important groups coming at the end of ...
The post Celtic youngster set for crucial UEFA Champions League match tonight appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…BERAM KAYAL?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109671</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-beram-kayal/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T05:15:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BERAM KAYAL became one of Neil Lennon’s best signings for Celtic first time around when the 22-year-old midfielder arrived in July 2010. The Israel international, who cost £1.25million from Maccabi Haifa, could be relied upon to put in a solid display in the engine room of the team with the ability to win challenges and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["He was constantly messaging me"; Postecoglou on interactions with Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166781</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/he-was-constantly-messaging-me-postecoglou-on-interactions-with-celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T05:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur manager Ange Postecoglou has shared that he and Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers have had many interactions since he departed Japan for Glasgow. Rodgers has replaced the Australian in the Celtic hot seat, with Postecoglou taking part in his first Spurs press conference since being appointed in London. He went over a variety of ...
The post "He was constantly messaging me"; Postecoglou on interactions with Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC CONFIDENTIAL: TITLE IN SIGHT – AND SACKED AGAIN: DAVIE HAY REVEALS ALL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=75444</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-confidential-title-in-sight-and-sacked-again-davie-hay-reveals-all/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T04:45:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Davie Hay continues his inside stories of Wim Jansen’s successful title-winning debut season in 1997/98. The former Hoops player and manager was a right-hand man and chief scout in the Dutchman’s backroom team as the Parkhead club were handed the task of preventing Rangers from claiming the historic 10 in a row. In [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans will be delighted with Marco Tilio’s claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42481</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/10/celtic-fans-marco-tilio-claim/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T22:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic get their preparations for next season underway with a return to training, one player will be hoping to get off to his usual fast start. Marco Tilio joined the club from Melbourne City FC recently and is getting settled to life in Scotland. He does though have a history of making a quick […]
Celtic fans will be delighted with Marco Tilio’s claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic suffer blow in race for Manchester City talent]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42519</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/10/celtic-blow-manchester-city-talent/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T21:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are expected to strengthen their squad this summer in preparation for another Champions League group stage campaign, while they have a treble to defend as well. There have been rumours about some marquee signings but till now, the Hoops have focused on signing highly-rated young talents. Odin Thiago Holm and Marco Tilio have already […]
Celtic suffer blow in race for Manchester City talent - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic contract theory that paves the way for big signings - opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166778</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-celtic-contract-theory-that-paves-the-way-for-big-signings/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T20:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s notable that two of Celtic’s biggest stars have had their contracts renewed recently, despite there being no major rush to do so. Both captain Callum McGregor and talismanic striker Kyogo Furuhashi have committed years more to Celtic – neither renewal was likely to have come cheaply. There’s no great source when it comes to ...
The post The Celtic contract theory that paves the way for big signings - opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers shares how Ange regular can improve under his watch at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166774</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/how-brendan-rodgers-aims-to-improve-daizen-maeda-further-under-his-watch-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T19:46:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has hailed the qualities that Daizen Maeda brings to the Celtic team but reckons the coaching staff can help him improve even further next season. Maeda is one of the players to have recently signed a new contract at the Bhoys, alongside Kyogo Furuhashi and Callum McGregor. The attacker has signed on until ...
The post Brendan Rodgers shares how Ange regular can improve under his watch at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[La Liga giants want to sign Celtic player this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42516</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/10/la-liga-giants-celtic-player-summer/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T19:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been very successful in recent seasons, winning five of the last six domestic competitions. One of the biggest reasons behind that is their superb record when it comes identifying and signing the right players. That also means though, that clubs from abroad will be keeping an eye on them. We have already seen […]
La Liga giants want to sign Celtic player this summer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The EA Sports and Celtic Park situation as club share new game promo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166767</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-ea-sports-and-celtic-park-situation-as-club-share-new-game-promo/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have shared a promotional image for the new EA Sports football video game. On Monday afternoon, the club retweeted a cover image from EA FC 24 to their 900,000 followers on Twitter. The image is a major promo for the new football simulation that will follow on from the immensely popular FIFA series when ...
The post The EA Sports and Celtic Park situation as club share new game promo appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic players we're still waiting to see back in training; image of fan favourite]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166758</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-celtic-players-were-still-waiting-to-see-back-in-training-club-share-image-of-fan-favourite/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic first-team are currently in Portugal continuing their preparations for the new season. For the majority, it’s the start of the second week of training, while our international stars are enjoying (or enduring) their first day back. The players underwent two sessions in the Algarve on Monday, with the official Twitter account describing the ...
The post The Celtic players we're still waiting to see back in training; image of fan favourite appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou makes superb Celtic claim despite leaving]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42512</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/10/ange-postecoglou-celtic-claim-leaving/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T18:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou arrived at Celtic as pretty much an unknown in the European game, despite of his successes in Japan and Australia. It did not take the manager too long to become a fan favourite though and he guided the Hoops to five trophies in his two seasons in the Parkhead hot seat. Postecoglou would […]
Ange Postecoglou makes superb Celtic claim despite leaving - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 7 youngsters spotted getting a big chance in Celtic's Portugal training camp pictures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166756</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/the-7-youngsters-spotted-getting-a-big-chance-in-celtics-portugal-training-camp-pictures/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A number of last season’s Celtic B regulars have made the trip with the senior squad for this week’s training camp in Portugal, per pictures published over the last couple of days. Brendan Rodgers has promised to ramp up the intensity of pre-season preparations over the next fortnight and these young prospects are getting a ...
The post The 7 youngsters spotted getting a big chance in Celtic's Portugal training camp pictures appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carlos Borges, Fabian Rieder and the curious summer Celtic transfer window]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166746</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/carlos-borges-fabian-rieder-and-the-curious-summer-celtic-transfer-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There have been plenty of speculative headlines about Celtic interest in names such as Carlos Borges of Manchester City and Young Boys midfielder Fabian Rieder this summer, but in a curious twist from the usual rumour mill, the original links to this pair didn’t come from the press. Both Borges’ and Rieder’s names came up ...
The post Carlos Borges, Fabian Rieder and the curious summer Celtic transfer window appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Callum McGregor has said about finishing his career at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166747</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-callum-mcgregor-has-said-about-finishing-his-career-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor has spoken previously about planning to finish his playing career at Celtic. The Hoops captain has signed a contract extension at the club, tying him down until the summer of 2028. By then McGregor will be 35 years old and in the latter stages of his career. At that stage, it would seem ...
The post What Callum McGregor has said about finishing his career at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>