<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2024-04-02T14:09:45.658Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I like him': Ally McCoist says he's a big fan of ‘fantastic’ player who's been linked to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193820</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ally-mccoist-is-a-big-fan-of-fantastic-player-who-has-been-linked-to-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not even close to the end of the season and Celtic are being linked to players as Brendan Rodgers looks to build for the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen McGinn explains why ‘very talented’ SPFL midfielder would appeal to Celtic this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193835</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/stephen-mcginn-explains-why-very-talented-spfl-midfielder-would-appeal-to-celtic-this-summer/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers will be aware that the shape of his squad may change during the summer transfer window. Citing the obvious, the Bhoys...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic winger Nicolas Kuhn lifts lid on how he will deal with Glasgow Derby pressure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193814</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-winger-nicolas-kuhn-lifts-lid-on-how-he-will-deal-with-glasgow-derby-pressure/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic take on Rangers at Ibrox this weekend in what could prove to be a vital match in the context of their Scottish Premiership title...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘My understanding’: Anthony Joseph on what’s really going on with Celtic’s Ibrox ticket allocation next season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193823</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/anthony-joseph-shares-whats-really-happening-with-celtics-ibrox-ticket-allocation-next-season/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the hype builds up on Celtic’s trip to Rangers this weekend, there is a genuine sense of excitement surrounding the upcoming Glasgow Derby. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Focus on Hatate paid dividends]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119218</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/focus-on-hatate-paid-dividends/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T11:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday we discussed how best to reintroduce Callum McGregor and Reo Hatate into the side after injury.  I wrote that starting both against Livingston was too much of a risk, but, “Reo is the man I would concentrate on.  Start him alongside Matt O’Riley with Tomoki Iwata in the holding role.” Let’s put some [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BEATON IN CHARGE AT IBROX]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119217</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/beaton-in-charge-at-ibrox/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T10:08:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOHN BEATON will be in charge of Celtic’s visit to Ibrox on Sunday for the third derby of the season. The referee was the VAR official at the centre of the recent controversy surrounding the champions’ 2-0 loss to Hearts at Tynecastle last month. Brendan Rodgers labelled the performance of Beaton and onfield whistler Don [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Officials and VAR confirmed as Celtic travel to face Rangers at Ibrox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193817</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/officials-and-var-confirmed-as-celtic-travel-to-face-rangers-at-ibrox/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T10:07:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans will be excited that Glasgow Derby week is finally upon us as we await what will be a showpiece occasion at Ibrox on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic battling Premier League trio in pursuit of former England Under-21 international]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193806</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-battling-premier-league-trio-in-pursuit-of-former-england-under-21-international/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers will be keen to reshuffle his squad once the summer window rolls around at Parkhead. In the January market period, the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: ‘BRENDAN’S BOYS MUST STAND UP TO THE IBROX BULLIES’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119211</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-brendans-boys-must-stand-up-to-the-ibrox-bullies/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T08:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC players MUST stand up to be counted at Ibrox on Sunday. Govan will be no place for the fainthearted and it’s the perfect occasion for the champions to put down a marker with only seven games to play in the quest for the twelfth title in 13 years. There is absolutely no way anyone in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Unsung hero’: BBC pundit admits Celtic have a ‘quality’ player who deserves more credit this season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193801</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kevin-thomson-admits-celtic-have-an-unsung-hero-who-deserves-more-credit/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have enjoyed immense domestic success over the last two and a half decades. A second nine-in-a-row and a Quadruple Treble has made this period...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's John Kennedy gets honest on Callum McGregor's chances of playing in Glasgow Derby]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193796</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-john-kennedy-gets-honest-on-callum-mcgregors-chances-of-playing-in-glasgow-derby/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic take on Rangers at Ibrox this weekend in a match that could define Brendan Rodgers’ side’s season this Sunday at 12 pm. The Bhoys...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Biggest quality’: Jackie McNamara blown away by ‘deceivingly quick’ Celtic player this season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193798</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/jackie-mcnamara-blown-away-by-the-pace-of-deceivingly-quick-celtic-player-this-season/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T07:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The buildup to the Glasgow Derby is well and truly underway this week after Celtic took care of business at Livingston on Sunday. The 3-0...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GREAT EXPECTATIONS: CELTIC NEW BHOY AND THE IBROX INSIDER]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119205</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/great-expectations-celtic-new-bhoy-and-the-ibrox-insider/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T06:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEW BHOY Nicolas Kuhn already has inside knowledge of what to expect in the white-hot atmosphere of a Glasgow derby. The £3million recruit from Rapid Vienna in January knows to expect thanks to his former RANGERS agent and manager Christian Nerlinger who was instrumental in the German winger joining the champions. Khun is beginning to show glimpses of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former SFA Grade 1 referee delivers verdict on big Celtic call at Livingston]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193765</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/des-roache-celtic-livingston-kyogo-furuhashi-penalty/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T06:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s win over Livingston yesterday afternoon tees up next weekend’s Glasgow Derby nicely as Brendan Rodgers’ side reclaimed top spot in the league. A win...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS v RANGERS: DERBY DEBUT RAMPAGE: Part One]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111451</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-v-rangers-derby-debut-rampage-part-one/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T05:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is preparing for his third derby encounter since his return to Celtic when he takes the champions to Ibrox on Sunday. The Irishman has enjoyed back-to-back successes in this campaign and got his second coming off to a perfect start in Govan on September 3 last year when Kyogo Furuhashi flashed in the only [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['He's always': Former Celtic hero nails it with his view on why Reo Hatate is better than Paulo Bernardo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193788</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/pat-bonner-nails-it-with-his-view-on-why-reo-hatate-is-better-than-paulo-bernardo-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The biggest dilemma Brendan Rodgers has had at Celtic this season was dealing with the injury to Reo Hatate. The Japanese international has missed an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘The important thing’: Chris Sutton delivers Ibrox message to Celtic star who has ‘grown’ in confidence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193776</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-delivers-important-ibrox-message-to-celtic-star-who-has-grown-in-confidence/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic seem to finding their groove in the Scottish Premiership now that they are starting to get some of their big players back from injury....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC FC EASTER 1916]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58756</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-fc-easter-1916-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T17:12:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The approach of Easter in 1916 probably did not mean much to the average Celtic supporter in Glasgow. The only real difference was that Easter Monday (April 24) would be a Holiday (a rare event in wartime Britain) and that Celtic would be playing Third Lanark, after they had played Hearts on the Saturday. […]
The post CELTIC FC EASTER 1916 appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Interesting': Pat Bonner left impressed with John Kennedy’s ‘important’ Rangers message to the Celtic players]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193781</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/john-kennedys-interesting-rangers-message-to-the-celtic-players-left-pat-bonner-really-impressed/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Brendan Rodgers serving a one game ban for Celtic’s game against Livingston yesterday, it was left to John Kennedy to complete the media duties...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['It was a big deal': Nicolas Kuhn opens up on his illness and how it really affected his start at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193784</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/nicolas-kuhn-opens-up-on-his-illness-and-how-it-really-affected-his-start-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A £3m January window but, Nicolas Kuhn arrived at Celtic with the hope that he was the quality signing that Brendan Rodgers was really looking...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Vouched for me’: David Martindale shares how two former Celtic men played a pivotal role in Livingston hire]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193772</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/david-martindale-shares-how-two-former-celtic-men-played-a-pivotal-role-in-livingston-appointment/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Martindale has shared how two former Celtic men played a huge part in him getting his big break into football at Livingston. Martindale has...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['A beauty': SPFL show appreciation for a moment of brilliance from Celtic in win at Livingston]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193768</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/spfl-show-appreciation-for-a-moment-of-beauty-from-celtic-in-win-at-livingston/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic returned to long-awaited domestic action this week after a two-week international break that has the supporters waiting to see their heroes in the green...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The decision is made: Celtic will not win the league]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119204</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-decision-is-made-celtic-will-not-win-the-league/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T11:04:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you were comforted by what happened at Livingston yesterday you are a fool.  A 0-3 win for Celtic on a difficult pitch is irrelevant in light of what happened with the scores at 0-0. Kyogo received the ball inside the Livingston box.  Livi captain, Mikey Devlin, clattered into the Japanese striker’s standing leg, bringing [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WATCH AGAIN: THREE CHEERS FOR THE CHAMPIONS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119201</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/watch-again-three-cheers-for-the-champions/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T10:35:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT WAS trebles all round for Celtic in West Lothian yesterday as three goals from Paulo Bernardo, Matt O’Riley and Jamie Brandon (og) made sure three points were secured in a potentially dodgy fixture. The Hoops celebrated their third win over Livingston this season, following the 3-0 victory at the same venue in September and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Kennedy provides an update on Celtic captian Callum McGregor's fitness ahead of this week's Glasgow Derby]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193761</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/john-kennedy-provides-an-update-on-callum-mcgregors-fitness-ahead-of-this-weeks-glasgow-derby/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that the win over Livingston has been done and dusted, full focus for Celtic now shifts to preparing for the Rangers game at Ibrox...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Really good’: Pat Bonner says one Celtic player proved him and the BBC pundits wrong in win vs Livingston]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193757</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/pat-bonner-says-one-celtic-player-proved-him-and-the-bbc-pundits-wrong-in-win-vs-livingston/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pat Bonner says he was proven wrong by one Celtic player in the 3-0 win over Livingston yesterday. A trio of second-half goals claimed the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘To be honest’: John Kennedy shares how the Celtic dressing room is feeling ahead of Ibrox Glasgow Derby]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193754</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/john-kennedy-shares-honest-thoughts-on-how-the-celtic-players-feel-ahead-of-ibrox-glasgow-derby/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Kennedy has shared how the Celtic dressing room is really feeling ahead of the big Ibrox Glasgow Derby game against Rangers next week. Yesterday’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘WE’LL BE READY,’ KENNEDY’S IBROX RALLYING CALL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119154</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/well-be-ready-kennedys-ibrox-rallying-call/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T07:20:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOHN KENNEDY insists Celtic will be ready for Ibrox on Sunday after safely manoeuvring the Livingston minefield. Strikes from Paulo Bernardo and Matt O’Riley plus an own goal from Jamie Brandon saw the champions ease to a 3-0 victory over David Martindale’s scrappers following a scoreless first-half. Kennedy, taking over the touchline duties with manager [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Kyogo Furuhashi thought of the tackle that VAR said wasn't a Celtic penalty vs Livingston]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193748</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-kyogo-furuhashi-thought-of-the-tackle-that-var-said-wasnt-a-celtic-penalty-vs-livingston/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T06:45:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s 3-0 win over Livingston takes Brendan Rodgers’ side back to the top of the Scottish Premiership ahead of the Ibrox Glasgow Derby next week....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[APRIL FOOLS? WRITTEN-OFF CELTIC HAVE LAST LAUGH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=89720</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/april-fools-written-off-celtic-have-last-laugh/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T05:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ON April 1 1970, Celtic travelled to Elland Road with many so-called experts predicting failure in their European Cup semi-final first leg encounter against Leeds United. The Hoops had been written off and were expected to be bit-part players in Yorkshire. Celtic refused to play ball as they went out that evening with a point to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Stewart notes 'the big surprise' about botched Celtic penalty call vs Livingston]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193742</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/michael-stewart-notes-the-big-surprise-about-botched-celtic-penalty-call-vs-livingston/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T19:10:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Celtic hadn’t picked up their second-half performance against Livingston on Sunday then another refereeing and VAR drama could have easily become big news again...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRING ON THE RANGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58753</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/bring-on-the-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T18:44:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans were in fine voice after the 3-0 win on the road earlier today. It could have been more if Celtic had been awarded a penalty for a foul on Kyogo. Once again we are talking about a referee getting it wrong this time the culprit is Don Robertson and who ever was […]
The post BRING ON THE RANGERS appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate has Celtic fans all saying the same thing after display vs Livingston]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193733</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/reo-hatate-has-celtic-fans-all-saying-the-same-thing-after-display-vs-livingston/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T18:25:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the big frustrations for Celtic this season has been the inability to keep several key players in the squad fit and healthy. Cameron...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hugh Keevins gets it all wrong on Celtic and Rangers ticket issue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193705</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/hugh-keevins-gets-it-all-wrong-on-celtic-and-rangers-ticket-issue/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T16:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recent headlines surrounding the Glasgow Derby ticket allocation took centre stage at the end of this week as Celtic and Rangers both come to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton pinpoints reason why Celtic are now looking "far better off"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193724</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-says-celtic-have-a-player-so-good-its-boring-talking-about-him/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s win over Livingston today puts the team back on top of the league ahead of next week’s Glasgow Derby. In the 3-0 win, Brendan...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘It’s massive’: James McFadden says the return of one Celtic player today is vital for Rangers game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193709</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/james-mcfadden-says-the-return-of-important-celtic-player-is-massive-for-rangers-game-next-week/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that the Livingston game is out of the way, Celtic and Brendan Rodgers can now start preparing for the Glasgow Derby at Ibrox next...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Come on': Chris Sutton and Robert Snodgrass shut down Kris Boyd on another Celtic penalty shocker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193714</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kris-boyds-bizarre-view-on-celtic-penalty-claim-shot-down-by-chris-sutton-and-robert-snodgrass/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T13:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s win over Livingston puts Brendan Rodgers’ team back on top of the Scottish Premiership this afternoon. And the timing of the win couldn’t be...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LIVINGSTON 0 CELTIC 3: TREBLE TOPS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119142</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/livingston-0-celtic-3-treble-tops/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T13:21:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIVINGSTON 0 CELTIC 3 IT WAS three cheers for champions Celtic as they powered back to the Premiership pinnacle with a well-earned victory over Livingston this afternoon. Brendan Rodgers watched from the stand as his side hit three second-half goals for their third successive 3-0 win in West Lothian. After a stuttering, unconvincing first-half, the visitors [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate return verdict, another VAR farce... 3 things we learned as Celtic punish Livingston]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193722</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/reo-hatate-return-verdict-another-var-farce-3-things-we-learned-as-celtic-punish-livingston/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T13:01:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have returned to the top of the Scottish Premiership after a comfortable 3-0 victory over Livingston on Sunday. A returning Reo Hatate was heavily...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Livingston v Celtic, Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119141</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/livingston-v-celtic-live-updates-9/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T09:57:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 12.00.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: HATATE RETURNS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119103</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-hatate-returns/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T09:50:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE makes his long-awaited return to the Celtic midfield for the High Noon showdown against Livingston in West Lothian today. The Japanese playmaker has played for only 21 minutes this year following a cameo appearance in the 3-0 win over St Mirren in Paisley on January 2. Hatate, who has been stricken by hamstring [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['They say': Mark Guidi shares what former Celtic players have told him about Cameron Carter-Vickers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193701</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/mark-guidi-shares-what-former-celtic-players-have-told-him-about-cameron-carter-vickers/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic prepare to face Livingston this afternoon they do so knowing that Cameron Carter-Vickers is available to face David Martindale’s side. The US international...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['A country mile': BBC pundit concedes that Celtic have two players who are the best in Scotland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193694</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kevin-thomson-concedes-that-celtic-have-two-players-who-are-the-best-in-scotland-by-a-country-mile/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has a number of extremely talented players at his disposal at Celtic that he can call upon to change a game if required....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS ‘HAD EVERY RIGHT TO BE ANGRY,’ INSISTS CELTIC LEGEND]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119126</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-had-every-right-to-be-angry-insists-celtic-legend/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T08:24:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Kenny Dalglish insists Brendan Rodgers “had every right to be angry” after having his say on the performances of the SFA officials following the champions’ controversial loss at Tynecastle on March 3. Yang Hyun-jun was red-carded in the 14th minute after a bewildering about-turn by referee Don Robertson following an intervention by VAR [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[English Championship star only has good things to say about Celtic after hitting big milestone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193689</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/stuart-armstrong-only-has-good-things-to-say-about-celtic-after-hitting-big-career-milestone/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic star Stuart Armstrong has been reflecting on his career journey after winning his 50th cap with Scotland during the international break. The midfielder...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[David Martindale goes against the grain with verdict on Livingston's Celtic supporter policy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193687</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/david-martindale-goes-against-the-grain-with-verdict-on-livingstons-celtic-supporter-policy/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic head to Livingston today knowing that a win against David Martindale’s Livingston will propel them back to the top of the Scottish Premiership. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ABADA DEBUT HIT BY LATE SPOILER]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119122</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/abada-debut-hit-by-late-spoiler/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T07:13:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIEL ABADA’S hopes of a winning debut for Charlotte FC were scuppered when Cincinnati struck a stoppage-time equaliser last night. The former Celtic winger moved in an £8million switch to the MLS club earlier this month and had be patient as he waited for his first appearance for his new team. The 22-year-old Israeli international [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I'll be honest': Michael Stewart's verdict on who's got the stronger squad for title race - Celtic or Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193680</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/michael-stewart-delivers-honest-verdict-on-whos-stronger-for-the-title-race-celtic-or-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Stewart has shared who he believes has the strongest squad for the title run-in as Celtic prepare to face Livingston this afternoon. Celtic will...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artur Boruc makes a big Celtic and Rangers title race prediction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193678</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/artur-boruc-makes-a-big-celtic-and-rangers-title-race-prediction/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T06:37:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a brave person to be calling the outcome of the Scottish Premiership title race between Celtic and Rangers at this stage of proceedings. There...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Dalglish nails the SFA with furious verdict after their Celtic decision]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193675</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kenny-dalglish-nails-the-sfa-with-furious-verdict-after-their-celtic-decision/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T06:07:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend Kenny Dalglish isn’t happy at all with the Scottish FA’s decision to haul Brendan Rodgers into Hampden for a disciplinary hearing. Rodgers has...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LIVINGSTON v CELTIC: 5-MINUTE QUIZ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119099</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/livingston-v-celtic-5-minute-quiz-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T04:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have a 100 per cent record this season against Livingston as they prepare to face them for a fourth time in the High Noon showdown in West Lothian today. In an eventful afternoon on the hosts’ treacherous pitch in September, the champions won 3-0 in a true grit display. That was followed by a 2-0 [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton says one player would have had Celtic 'streets ahead' of Rangers in title race]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193669</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-reckons-one-player-would-have-had-celtic-streets-ahead-of-rangers-in-title-race/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-30T20:27:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are gearing up for a final push in the Scottish Premiership and Scottish Cup with the expectation that it’ll be fine margins that decide...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers' communication plan to get around touchline ban vs Livingston]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193665</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-communication-plan-to-work-around-touchline-ban-vs-livingston/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-30T19:07:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers isn’t too perturbed by his ban for Sunday’s match away to Livingston and has shared he will have lines of communication...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers miss out, Hatate decision: Celtic Predicted XI vs Livingston after latest squad update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193660</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/wingers-miss-out-hatate-decision-celtic-predicted-xi-vs-livingston-after-latest-squad-update/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-30T18:09:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic face Livingston in the Scottish Premiership on Sunday and it’s another big game for the Bhoys in this title race. After Rangers defeated Hibernian...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Joe Hart wasn't happy with popular viral Celtic video clip]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193657</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/why-joe-hart-wasnt-happy-with-popular-viral-celtic-video-clip/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-30T17:39:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Celtic go on to win the Scottish Premiership this season then the clip of Joe Hart celebrating with passion away to Livingston back in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's title race mission after Saturday Scottish Premiership results; goal difference situation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193651</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-title-race-mission-after-saturday-scottish-premiership-results-goal-difference-situation/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-30T17:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will be playing to return to the top of the Scottish Premiership against Livingston on Sunday after another afternoon of drama in the top...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch Celtic prospect become a derby hero out on loan with latest goal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193646</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/watch-celtic-prospect-become-a-derby-hero-out-on-loan-with-latest-goal/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-30T16:19:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have sent many players out on loan to various clubs around the world this season; naturally, some garner more attention than others. Mikey Johnston,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic v Livi Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58748</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-v-livi-preview/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-30T16:14:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I spent the international break watching Ireland v Belgium and Switzerland. Both Mikey Johnstone and Adam Idah took part in both matches in Dublin. But now all our thoughts turn to Livingston away on Easter Sunday. On a week when we found out Celtic fans will be allocated tickets for Ibrox next season and likewise […]
The post Celtic v Livi Preview appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton questions SFA treatment of Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers compared to Clement & company]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193641</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-questions-sfa-treatment-of-celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-compared-to-philippe-clement-and-company/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-30T13:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After facing Hearts at Tynecastle, Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers didn’t say anything about Scottish refereeing and the use of VAR that wasn’t true. The roll-out...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CALMAC CONUNDRUM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119119</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/calmac-conundrum/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-30T11:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CALLUM McGREGOR faces a week-long guessing game as the burning question follows him all the way to the midday kick-off at Ibrox a week tomorrow. Will the inspirational Celtic captain be fit to play in what will be a vital derby encounter in the champions’ quest for their twelfth title in 13 years? Worryingly, the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: ANSWER THIS, SFA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119117</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-answer-this-sfa/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-30T09:53:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE SFA are to common sense what Long John Silver was to tap-dancing. How else can you explain their absurd decision to award the silver whistle to Don Robertson to adjudicate in Celtic’s Premiership game at Livingston tomorrow? Somehow in the selection process – if there is such a thing in their Hampden hideaway – the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS’ ‘MAJOR BONUS’ AT IBROX]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119115</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-major-bonus-at-ibrox/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-30T07:57:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS will be patrolling the touchline at Ibrox a week tomorrow – and that is a “major bonus” for Celtic, according to former goal hero Chris Sutton. The Hoops boss will be in the stand at Livingston tomorrow for the noon kick-off as he serves an SFA one-game ban with another match suspended after [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘A GOOD PLACE,’ HART CONTINUES COUNTDOWN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119107</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/a-good-place-hart-continues-countdown/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-30T06:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART continues the countdown to the conclusion of his three-year Celtic career with a visit to Livingston tomorrow. The evergreen keeper, who will celebrate his 37th birthday next month, has eight Premiership games to play before nearing the end of a spectacular 20-year career. Hart, capped 75 times by England, hopes to have a [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms dodgy Livingston pitch has influenced Sunday Celtic squad call]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193634</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-confirms-dodgy-livingston-pitch-has-influenced-sunday-celtic-squad-call/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T20:38:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The days of plastic pitches in Scotland could soon be numbered but Celtic still have to deal with them in the here and now. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The hypocrisy Celtic pointed out to SFA at Hampden to avoid Brendan Rodgers derby ban]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193586</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-hypocrisy-celtic-pointed-out-to-sfa-at-hampden-to-avoid-brendan-rodgers-derby-ban/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T19:50:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The news on Thursday that Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers would receive a touchline ban from the Scottish FA was met with a mixed reaction. Some...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers addresses lack of Celtic consistency and calls out area of needed improvement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193621</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-addresses-lack-of-celtic-consistency-and-calls-out-area-of-needed-improvement/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T19:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has addressed Celtic’s lack of consistency this season and discussed what is now needed to go on a run that will make them...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart shares observation on Celtic training and dressing room ahead of title run-in]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193616</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/joe-hart-shares-observation-on-celtic-training-and-dressing-room-ahead-of-title-run-in/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T18:27:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With so many potential twists and turns ahead, nobody at Celtic or Rangers is very keen on hyping up the coming title race beyond recognition...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rodgers sets record straight on Rangers row and makes it clear what Celtic will push for next]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193611</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-sets-the-record-straight-on-rangers-row-and-makes-it-clear-what-celtic-will-push-for-next/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T17:37:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although it’s convenient for some to forget, Celtic were not at all instigators in the row with Rangers over ticket allocations. It was a decision...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic confirm Hampden Scottish Cup ticket details: Criteria, prices and deadline]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193608</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-confirm-hampden-scottish-cup-ticket-details-criteria-prices-and-deadline/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T17:07:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have confirmed the ticketing details for the upcoming Scottish Cup semi-final against Aberdeen at Hampden on Saturday, 20th April. The Bhoys are on the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic team news vs Livingston: 3 out but Reo Hatate returns]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193601</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-news-vs-livingston-3-out-but-reo-hatate-returns/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T16:36:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic return to Scottish Premiership action this weekend and it’s a welcome comeback after a dull international break. We’re in the juicy part of the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NO REGRETS: RODGERS STANDS FIRM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119112</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/no-regrets-rodgers-stands-firm/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T15:07:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS goes into the unknown when Celtic play Livingston in West Lothian on Sunday. The 51-year-old Irishman will be forced to sit in the stand after receiving a touchline ban from the SFA after his comments relating to referee Don Robertson and VAR official John Beaton following the controversial 2-0 loss to Hearts at [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic goalkeeper Joe Hart reacts to SFA's Brendan Rodgers ban]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193594</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-goalkeeper-joe-hart-reacts-to-sfas-brendan-rodgers-ban/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T14:21:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic goalkeeper Joe Hart has given his thoughts on being without manager Brendan Rodgers in the dugout for this weekend’s trip to Livingston. Rodgers has...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More details emerge on Celtic allocation at Ibrox after club agreement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193590</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/more-details-emerge-on-celtic-allocation-at-ibrox-after-club-agreement/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T13:56:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The news on Friday that more Celtic supporters will be in attendance at future derbies against Rangers at Ibrox is welcome. The SPFL confirmed in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SPFL release statement as Celtic stance pays off on Rangers derby row]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193580</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/spfl-release-statement-as-celtic-stance-pays-off-on-rangers-derby-row/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T12:02:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Away allocations will return to the derby between Celtic and Rangers but not until the 2024/25 season. For several years, both clubs have significantly reduced...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LWYRUP.  Youth recruitment. Newco cave]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119096</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/lwyrup-youth-recruitment-newco-cave/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T12:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Beaton was the man who put pressure on referee Don Robertson earlier this month, not Brendan Rodgers.  Robertson had already awarded Celtic a penalty in the game against Hearts when VAR Beaton recommended he rewatch a high boot by Yang, who had already been cautioned for the incident. Right then we knew the chances [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC FANS’ IBROX GO-AHEAD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119097</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-fans-ibrox-go-ahead/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T11:52:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC fans WILL be allowed into Ibrox next season after a solution to recent lock-outs for derby games. An agreement has been struck which will allow Hoops supporters the opportunity to see their team in action in Govan. There is a reciprocal arrangement which will see rival followers into Parkhead when the Glasgow giants clash. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WAY TO GO, JOE: HART’S IN WITH A SHOUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119094</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/way-to-go-joe-harts-in-with-a-shout/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T10:11:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART is in line for a personal accolade as he prepares to bring down the curtain on his three eventful years at Celtic. The 75 times-capped England international keeper answered an SOS from former boss Ange Postecoglou to quit Spurs in a £1million switch to join the Greek-Australian’s revolution at the fallen champions. Hart [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NO GREEN LIGHT FOR IN-DEMAND YANG]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119092</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/no-green-light-for-in-demand-yang/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T09:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC will block any moves from South Korea to call up Yang Hyun-jun for their Olympic qualification bid next month. The right-winger is likely to be in head coach Hwang Sun-hong’s plans for the tournament in Qatar as he prepares his squad for the finals in Paris which are due to run from July 24 to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RHYTHM AND BRUISE: RODGERS PLANS FOR LIVI BATTLE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119055</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rhythm-and-bruise-rodgers-plans-for-livi-battle/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T07:13:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS will take his seat in the stand when Celtic play Livingston in West Lothian on Sunday. It will be a first for the manager not to be patrolling the touchline when the Hoops are in action on matchday. Rodgers copped a one-game ban with another suspended after facing the SFA disciplinary committee yesterday [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic want to sign £4 million-rated player in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45945</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-4-million-player-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T23:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The defeat at the hands of Lazio was further proof of Celtic’s need to strengthen in the January transfer window. The club might have brought in nine new faces in the summer but a lot of people feel that the team has taken a step back since last season, when they breezed past the competition […]
Celtic want to sign £4 million-rated player in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers sends clear message Celtic board must not ignore]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45941</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/brendan-rodgers-message-celtic-board/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T21:35:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s fate in Europe for this season is sealed after their 2-0 defeat at the hands of Lazio. The result means that the Hoops are guaranteed to finish bottom of their group in the UEFA Champions League. That also means that they will not be dropping down to the Europa League, something that should have […]
Brendan Rodgers sends clear message Celtic board must not ignore - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton publicly criticises Celtic after loss to Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45938</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/chris-sutton-celtic-loss-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T20:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic lost 2-0 away in Rome to Lazio. The Hoops were in the match for a long time before Ciro Immobile came off the bench to score a brace and put the game to bed. The result means that not only are Brendan Rodgers’ side out of the Champions League following the group stages but […]
Chris Sutton publicly criticises Celtic after loss to Lazio - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed £7 million Jeremie Frimpong windfall news]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45933</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-jeremie-frimpong-windfall-news/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremie Frimpong’s rise at Bayer Leverkusen has been fascinating, to say the least. The Dutchman had shown a lot of quality going forward at Celtic as well but not many could have foreseen him becoming one of the most prolific wingbacks in Europe just a few years later. That is exactly what has happened under […]
Celtic handed £7 million Jeremie Frimpong windfall news - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic told 29-goal striker is good enough amid links]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45930</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-told-29-goal-striker-good-enough/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T13:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to add to their options up top this January. Kyogo has done well once again but he is not scoring as frequently as he was last season. On the other hand, Oh Hyeon-gyu has been inconsistent as well and is not at the level required to start for the Hoops right now. There […]
Celtic told 29-goal striker is good enough amid links - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anderlecht consider making offer for Celtic standout in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45927</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/anderlecht-offer-celtic-standout-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T11:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have not had the greatest campaign till now. They were eliminated early from the Scottish League Cup and while they do lead the Premiership, their performances and results have been somewhat inconsistent. Almost half a season on, it feels like the Hoops are still finding their feet under the management of Brendan Rodgers and […]
Anderlecht consider making offer for Celtic standout in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serie A club want to sign Celtic player amid contract worry]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45907</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/serie-club-want-celtic-player-contract/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T22:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic fans hope for more quality players arriving there could be a problem with others heading for the exit door. It seems pretty clear that Brendan Rodgers wants to make the size of the squad more manageable over the next couple of transfer windows and departures are expected. But there is a risk of […]
Serie A club want to sign Celtic player amid contract worry - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur step up bid to sign Celtic-linked player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45918</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/tottenham-hotspur-bid-sign-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur made a fantastic start to the season under the management of Ange Postecoglou. With Harry Kane leaving the club in the summer for Bayern Munich, most expected them to struggle. Instead, they appeared to be putting up an unlikely title challenge and were sitting atop the Premier League table not too long ago. […]
Tottenham Hotspur step up bid to sign Celtic-linked player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boost in race to sign £11 million Real Madrid player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45914</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/celtic-boost-real-madrid-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to sign a goalkeeper in the near future. It is quite clear that Joe Hart is not the long-term solution between the posts. The Englishman’s performances have been criticised lately. Also, he is set to turn 37 years of age before this season comes to an end. So, while he has done a […]
Celtic boost in race to sign £11 million Real Madrid player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio boss Maurizio Sarri makes fantastic Celtic claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45910</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/lazio-boss-maurizio-sarri-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T18:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By now, Celtic fans have accepted that Brendan Rodgers’ side are most probably not going through or even finishing third in their group in the UEFA Champions League. It would be a positive step to get a win in the competition though. It has been quite some time since the Hoops won at this level. […]
Lazio boss Maurizio Sarri makes fantastic Celtic claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic tipped to go for 28-year-old Premiership striker]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45904</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/celtic-tipped-go-premiership-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T12:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans breathed a sigh of relief as the Rangers dropped points at the weekend against Aberdeen. In fact, it took a late penalty for them to even come out with a draw from the game. That means that the Hoops will maintain their strong position at the top of the Scottish Premiership table. That […]
Celtic tipped to go for 28-year-old Premiership striker - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£7.5 million Mathias Kvistgaarden to Celtic transfer update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45900</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/mathias-kvistgaarden-celtic-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T10:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to sign a striker in January. On one hand, we have seen the club struggle for goals in some games this season. When the opposition puts up a resolute defence, the Hoops do not appear to have a lot of answers other than Kyogo, Matt O’Riley or Luis Palma. On the other hand, […]
£7.5 million Mathias Kvistgaarden to Celtic transfer update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur have been eyeing Celtic superstar]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45896</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/tottenham-hotspur-eyeing-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T23:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou made the move to Tottenham Hotspur in the summer and it was only a matter of time before the Australian was linked with a reunion with some Celtic players. The manager enjoyed a lot of success at Parkhead, even though he was at the club for just two seasons, and won five trophies […]
Tottenham Hotspur have been eyeing Celtic superstar - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John McGinn claims he spoke to Celtic players about manager]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45890</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/john-mcginn-spoke-celtic-players/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T21:35:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most Celtic fans will remember how the club missed out on the opportunity to sign John McGinn some years back. The Scot grew up supporting the Hoops but a move to Parkhead failed to materialise even though it had looked close and he ended up moving down south to join Aston Villa. McGinn has risen […]
John McGinn claims he spoke to Celtic players about manager - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic must consider signing striker from Premiership rivals]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45886</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-signing-striker-premiership-rivals/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T20:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there is one position where Celtic need to strengthen during the upcoming January transfer window, it is striker. The Hoops have been pretty inconsistent in front of goal this season so far. Of course, there are games when they can go out and score six times. But then, on days they are having a […]
Celtic must consider signing striker from Premiership rivals - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend takes dig at Rangers player for diving]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45884</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-legend-rangers-player-diving/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T18:35:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Celtic drew 1-1 against Motherwell, the Rangers were handed a major chance to get back into the title race. All they needed to do was win their games in hand and they would be just three points behind the Hoops in the league table. We have seen the Ibrox side not perform at their […]
Celtic legend takes dig at Rangers player for diving - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player criticised after draw against Motherwell]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45881</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-player-criticised-draw-motherwell/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T12:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Titles are not decided this early in the season. That has been proven once again. Not too long ago, Celtic were sitting seven points clear at the top of the Premiership table and most fans felt that the league was pretty much in the bag with the Rangers struggling for any kind of form.  It […]
Celtic player criticised after draw against Motherwell - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgio Chiellini makes superb claim about Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45874</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/giorgio-chiellini-claim-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T10:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Giorgio Chiellini is one of the best defenders of all time and he had some pretty positive comments about Celtic Park recently. The 39-year-old spent the majority of his career playing for Juventus and won more silverware there than one should try to count. Overall, he made more […]
Giorgio Chiellini makes superb claim about Celtic Park - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s problem is very clear and needs solving quick]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45870</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/celtic-problem-needs-solving-quick/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T19:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two more dropped points mean that Celtic have well and truly allowed the Rangers to get back into the title race. A lead which once stood at seven points, could be reduced to three if Philippe Clement’s side are able to win their games in hand. And the sad thing is that the Hoops have […]
Celtic’s problem is very clear and needs solving quick - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic problem after draw]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45866</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/brendan-rodgers-celtic-problem-draw/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T18:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was not the result Celtic were looking for, as they dropped two valuable points against Motherwell. David Turnbull’s goal appeared to have won it for the Hoops but the visitors equalised in the 90th minute and it ended 1-1. That means that if the Rangers win their games in hand, the gap will be […]
Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic problem after draw - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hollywood superstar pictured wearing Celtic jersey]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45861</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/hollywood-pictured-wearing-celtic-jersey/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T12:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Celtic have their fair share of famous fans. Rod Stewart is the first name that comes to most people’s minds, one of the best-selling music artists in history. Lewis Capaldi is another popular musician known to support the Hoops. And several A-list celebrities like Gerard Butler, Snoop Dogg, […]
Hollywood superstar pictured wearing Celtic jersey - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic pushing for priority signing in January window]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45859</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/celtic-priority-signing-january-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T09:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s January transfer window is expected to be a busy one. The club might have made nine signings in the summer, seven arriving on a permanent basis and two on loan, but there are still holes in Brendan Rodgers’ squad that need to be filled. On the other hand, there are way too many players […]
Celtic pushing for priority signing in January window - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable source offers Sydney van Hooijdonk to Celtic update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45854</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/reliable-sydney-van-hooijdonk-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T22:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are believed to be on the lookout for a striker in the January transfer window. There might be a few reasons behind that. Firstly, both Kyogo and Oh Hyeon-gyu might be unavailable for a considerable length of time early next year due to the AFC Asian Cup. They are the club’s two options to […]
Reliable source offers Sydney van Hooijdonk to Celtic update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou claims Celtic success gets dismissed]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45852</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/ange-postecoglou-claims-celtic-success/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T21:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has proven to be a major success in the Premier League since swapping Celtic for Tottenham Hotspur. Of course, a lot of fans were not happy to see him depart after just two years at Parkhead. But he has been very respectful about the club even after leaving. And it is hard not […]
Ange Postecoglou claims Celtic success gets dismissed - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>