<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-09-22T08:13:13.138Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Got to thank Eddie Howe"; Postecoglou talks Celtic with Gary Lineker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175109</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/got-to-thank-eddie-howe-ange-postecoglou-talks-celtic-with-gary-lineker/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has been speaking about Celtic in an interview with Gary Lineker. The Australian departed the Hoops in the summer after a glorious couple...
The post "Got to thank Eddie Howe"; Postecoglou talks Celtic with Gary Lineker appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I HAVE NO DOUBTS,’ BOSS BACKS HART]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112253</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-have-no-doubts-boss-backs-hart/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T07:36:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has re-emphasised his faith in Joe Hart despite his keeper taking flak for the opening goal in Rotterdam that opened the way for Feyenoord’s 2-0 win. The Dutch netted from a long-range direct free-kick in the second minute of first-half stoppage time as the ball curled and whipped past the diving Celtic netminder. Calvin [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I LIKE TO DREAM, BUT I DON’T LIVE IN FANTASY LAND,’ INSISTS RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112249</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-like-to-dream-but-i-dont-live-in-fantasy-land-insists-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T06:47:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS insists he doesn’t “live in fantasy land”. The Celtic manager witnessed his team being reduced to nine men as they got their Champions League campaign off to the worst possible start with a 2-0 loss against Feyenoord at a hostile De Kuip on Tuesday. Two summer purchases from Swedish clubs – centre-back Gustaf Lagerbiekle, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers saw one big positive from midweek Celtic defeat; will be vital going forward]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175073</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-saw-one-big-positive-from-midweek-celtic-defeat-will-be-vital-going-forward/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers saw one big positive during Celtic’s 2-0 loss to Feyenoord on Tuesday. It was a deflating start to our UEFA Champions League campaign...
The post Brendan Rodgers saw one big positive from midweek Celtic defeat; will be vital going forward appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's Luis Palma reality as early talking point is raised]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175084</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-luis-palma-reality-as-early-talking-point-is-raised/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Luis Palma made his first start for Celtic in Tuesday night’s defeat to Feyenoord. The Honduras international had featured as a second-half substitute during our...
The post Celtic's Luis Palma reality as early talking point is raised appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plenty of merit as Brendan Rodgers cites Red Bull example Celtic must strive for]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175066</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/plenty-of-merit-as-brendan-rodgers-cites-red-bull-example-celtic-must-strive-for/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers spent a fair amount of time on Thursday talking about Celtic transfer issues. Recruitment was certainly the main topic of his broadcast press...
The post Plenty of merit as Brendan Rodgers cites Red Bull example Celtic must strive for appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic star is absolutely flying in Saudi Arabia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175099</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-star-moussa-dembele-is-absolutely-flying-in-saudi-arabia/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T05:15:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic star Moussa Dembele is absolutely flying in Saudi Arabia. The French forward is playing for Al Ettifaq — the team managed by Steven...
The post Former Celtic star is absolutely flying in Saudi Arabia appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE JOCK STEIN YEARS (Part Twelve)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=82806</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-jock-stein-years-part-twelve/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-22T04:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Jock Stein made an extraordinary immediate impact on the Parkhead club when he returned as manager in March 1965. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE,  Alex Gordon, author of fifteen publications on Celtic, has opened his book files on the Parkhead great for an absorbing twenty-one part series. Today, in Part Twelve of our fascinating look back [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic decision to let Ange Postecoglou signing go questioned]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44308</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/21/celtic-ange-postecoglou-signing-go/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T22:34:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic experienced a disappointing night in Rotterdam losing 2-0 to Feyenoord in the opening round of the Champions League group stage. It was a game in which Brendan Rodgers’ side saw two red cards and conceded a bad goal. And the Hoops have come under the microscope for their recent transfer decisions, not for the […]
Celtic decision to let Ange Postecoglou signing go questioned - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Wyatt-Hupton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic summer signing tipped to struggle for chances]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44360</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/21/celtic-summer-signing-tipped-struggle/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T21:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The summer additions that Celtic made did raise the eyebrows of a lot of fans. Many had been hoping and expecting for some established and experienced players to be brought in in order to take a step forward in the Champions League and make the second Brendan Rodgers reign just as successful as the last […]
Celtic summer signing tipped to struggle for chances - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss makes brutally honest admission about summer signings]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44358</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/21/celtic-boss-honest-admission-signings/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T19:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many Celtic fans were left with the club’s transfer business over the summer. When Brendan Rodgers was appointed for a second run as the manager of the club, there were rumours floating in the media about a blockbuster budget and record-breaking bids. None of that came true. Instead, the Hoops stuck to bringing in highly-rated […]
Celtic boss makes brutally honest admission about summer signings - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss confirms when Cameron Carter-Vickers will return]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44354</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/21/celtic-cameron-carter-vickers-return/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T18:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a number of defensive issues at this point in time. Cameron Carter-Vickers, Stephen Welsh and Maik Nawrocki are all out due to injury. Nat Phillips rolled his ankle last weekend as well and is not available for selection, even though his issue is believed to be more short-term. And Gustaf Lagerbielke picked up […]
Celtic boss confirms when Cameron Carter-Vickers will return - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Hartson's ten-word reaction on whether Celtic would beat West Ham amid financial gulf]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175044</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/john-hartsons-ten-word-reaction-on-whether-celtic-would-beat-west-ham-amid-financial-gulf/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Hartson says Brendan Rodgers’ Celtic would beat David Moyes’ West Ham United amid the talk of the financial gulf between the two clubs. It’s...
The post John Hartson's ten-word reaction on whether Celtic would beat West Ham amid financial gulf appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Composed’: Barry Ferguson says Celtic star continues to shine despite Feyenoord loss]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175025</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/really-good-barry-ferguson-says-celtic-star-continues-to-shine-despite-feyenoord-loss/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the start of the season, Liam Scales wouldn’t have seen himself as a starter for Celtic. It could have been argued that Celtic probably...
The post ‘Composed’: Barry Ferguson says Celtic star continues to shine despite Feyenoord loss appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REVEALED: RODGERS’ TRANSFER PLANS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112244</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/revealed-rodgers-transfer-plans/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T14:35:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has revealed he is already preparing to strengthen Celtic in the January transfer window. The Hoops boss oversaw £18.25 million worth of incoming deals in the summer with players such as Maik Nawrocki, Gustaf Lagerbiekle, Luis Palma and Odin Holm being introduced to the champions. However, there are some critics who insist the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More than 90 Minutes 22 years on]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58422</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/more-than-90-minutes-22-years-on/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T12:59:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to Us Its been 22 years today since More than 90 Minutes first went on sale outside Celtic Park. It’s been some buzz travelling up and down Scotland, Europe and beyond covering the Celtic Fans journey  following the famous Celtic FC. There have been ups and downs along the way but we thank […]
The post More than 90 Minutes 22 years on appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero Ange Postecoglou shares Rangers fan story]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44345</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/21/celtic-hero-ange-postecoglou-rangers-fan/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T12:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Ange Postecoglou was appointed as the manager of Celtic, it was not a popular decision. For months, the club had been linked with a move for Eddie Howe. That failed to materialise and the Hoops quickly got a deal done for the relatively unknown Australian instead. Naturally, there were doubts about whether he could […]
Celtic hero Ange Postecoglou shares Rangers fan story - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feyenoord the Past the Present]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58418</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/feyenoord-the-past-the-present/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T12:13:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Tuesday night we faced Feyenoord for the first time competitively since that night in Milan in 1970. It’s a different world especially in football since those halcyon days of the early ‘70’s. We were European giants whereas the Dutch were an unknown quality probably the reverse of 3 years previously when we were the […]
The post Feyenoord the Past the Present appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston blown away by Celtic team-mate he's only just come in to contact with]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175010</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alistair-johnston-blown-away-by-celtic-team-mate-who-hes-only-just-come-in-to-contact-with/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston has become the latest Celtic figure to praise Liam Scales. The Irish defender has been rejuvenated in recent weeks. Scales was named man...
The post Alistair Johnston blown away by Celtic team-mate he's only just come in to contact with appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[National outlets line up to take a pop at Celtic but none of it truly matters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174959</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/national-outlets-line-up-to-take-a-pop-at-celtic-but-none-of-it-truly-matters/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been on the end of some harsh treatment ever since our loss to Feyenoord on Tuesday evening. It wasn’t the start to our...
The post National outlets line up to take a pop at Celtic but none of it truly matters appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Re-orientating our expectations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112242</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/re-orientating-our-expectations/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T11:05:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The disappointment online and among supporters in general since Tuesday’s defeat in Rotterdam has been tangible.  That’s an indication of just how hopeful we had become, despite extenuating circumstances and an away track record that should have prepared us for much worse. Frustrations were shared by the squad, who know they let an opportunity slip.  [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lagerbielke and Holm suspension situation; another Celtic player already looking over shoulder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174953</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/lagerbielke-and-holm-suspension-situation-another-celtic-player-already-looking-over-his-shoulder/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gustaf Lagerbielke and Odin Thiago Holm will both be unavailable for Celtic’s clash against Lazio after being sent off on Tuesday. The Scandinavian pair, both...
The post Lagerbielke and Holm suspension situation; another Celtic player already looking over shoulder appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers confirm another problem as Celtic build lead]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44342</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/21/rangers-confirm-problem-celtic-lead/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T10:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The mood around Celtic Park is not expected to be great after the Hoops suffered a 2-0 defeat at the hands of Feyenoord in their Champions League group opener. But overall, things have been positive for Brendan Rodgers’ side in recent weeks. The same cannot be said about the Rangers, who find themselves in a […]
Rangers confirm another problem as Celtic build lead - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Brendan Rodgers said about plastic pitches before his last Celtic trip to Livingston]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175018</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/what-brendan-rodgers-said-about-plastic-pitches-before-his-last-celtic-trip-to-livingston/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers isn’t a fan of plastic pitches and made that clear before his last Celtic visit to Livingston. The Hoops are back in action...
The post What Brendan Rodgers said about plastic pitches before his last Celtic trip to Livingston appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THREE AND QUEASY? RIVAL BOSS’ WISH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112239</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/three-and-queasy-rival-boss-wish/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T08:53:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIVINGSTON boss David Martindale has named three Celtic players who could find difficulty in coming to terms with conditions in West Lothian on Saturday. New Bhoys Gustaf Lagerbiekle, Odin Holm and Luis Palma all arrived at the Hoops in the summer and the trio faced the traumas of Champions League football in a toxic atmosphere [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liam Scales, Greg Taylor and an important Celtic consideration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174983</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/liam-scales-greg-taylor-and-an-important-celtic-consideration/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The resurgence of Liam Scales for Celtic in recent weeks has been great to see. After being thrown into the limelight following a spate of...
The post Liam Scales, Greg Taylor and an important Celtic consideration appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘UNBELIEVABLE,’ JOHNSTON HAILS TEAM-MATE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112232</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/unbelievable-johnston-hails-team-mate/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T07:51:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIAM SCALES could have been preparing to play for Aberdeen against Eintracht Frankfurt in their Euro Conference League match in Germany this evening. It looked as though the Republic of Ireland defender was on his way to Pittodrie in a permanent move in the summer after impressing in his season-long loan at the Dons in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘A LEARNING CURVE,’ ADMITS CELTIC’S LOST BHOY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112228</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/a-learning-curve-admits-celtics-lost-bhoy/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T07:22:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ALISTAIR JOHNSTON went into the unknown in Rotterdam on Tuesday night. The Canadian World Cup defender sampled defeat for the first time as a Celtic player since joining from CF Montreal in a £3.5million deal in January. Johnston had gone 23 games unbeaten in his Hoops career until the 2-0 loss against Feyenoord in the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bartley can't believe moment from Feyenoord vs Celtic; surprised Rodgers didn't call it out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174999</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/marvin-bartley-cant-believe-decision-from-feyenoord-vs-celtic-surprised-rodgers-didnt-call-it-out/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marvin Bartley reckons that Celtic were on the end of a “diabolical” refereeing decision in Tuesday night’s defeat to Feyenoord. The Hoops fell to a...
The post Bartley can't believe moment from Feyenoord vs Celtic; surprised Rodgers didn't call it out appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic star nets in Champions League, Tierney impresses, more Madrid pain for Juranovic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174966</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-star-nets-in-champions-league-as-tierney-impresses-and-juranovic-suffers-more-madrid-pain/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic may have played their UEFA Champions League opener on Tuesday but there was still plenty of Hoops interest in Wednesday’s action. The first matchday...
The post Former Celtic star nets in Champions League, Tierney impresses, more Madrid pain for Juranovic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[David Martindale strangely names three Celtic players who could be spooked in Livingston]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174975</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/david-martindale-strangely-names-three-celtic-players-who-could-be-spooked-in-livingston/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Livingston manager David Martindale has strangely named three Celtic players who could be spooked by the Tony Macaroni Arena. The Hoops continue their Premiership campaign...
The post David Martindale strangely names three Celtic players who could be spooked in Livingston appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic pair have great things to say about team-mate following Feyenoord criticism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174992</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-pair-have-great-things-to-say-about-joe-hart-following-feyenoord-free-kick-criticism/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart came in for some criticism following Feyenoord’s opening goal in their win over Celtic on Tuesday. The Hoops had taken part in an...
The post Celtic pair have great things to say about team-mate following Feyenoord criticism appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE JOCK STEIN YEARS (Part Eleven)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=82754</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-jock-stein-years-part-eleven/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-21T04:15:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Jock Stein made an extraordinary immediate impact on the Parkhead club when he returned as manager in March 1965. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE,  Alex Gordon, author of fifteen publications on Celtic, has opened his book files on the Parkhead great for an absorbing twenty-one part series. Today, in Part Eleven of our fascinating look back [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player accepts responsibility for Feyenoord opener]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44303</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/20/celtic-player-accepts-feyenoord-opener/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T22:32:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It wasn’t the best of nights for Celtic in Europe. One player has acknowledged that and has taken responsibility for his part in the 2-0 defeat. It wasn’t the worst of nights either to be fair. In amongst the disappointments and errors in the opening Champions League group match against Feyenoord, there were some promising […]
Celtic player accepts responsibility for Feyenoord opener - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou explains how Tottenham convinced him to leave Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44322</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/20/ange-postecoglou-tottenham-leave-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T21:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou is not just another manager. He proved that at Celtic Park. When the Australian arrived, there was no lack of doubters. He was a relative unknown to the majority of Scottish football fans and media. And many felt that he was destined to fail, as the Parkhead would prove too big for him. […]
Ange Postecoglou explains how Tottenham convinced him to leave Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thierry Henry completely rules out Celtic in blunt claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44316</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/20/thierry-henry-completely-rules-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T19:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Celtic were drawn into the same group as Atletico Madrid, Lazio and Feyenoord in the Champions League, a lot of fans felt that the Hoops had an outsider’s chance of getting into second or dropping down to the Europa League by finishing third. Their performance on the first matchday of Europe’s elite competition did […]
Thierry Henry completely rules out Celtic in blunt claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['That's for sure': Thierry Henry states if Celtic will progress from UCL group stages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174930</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/thierry-henry-states-if-celtic-will-progress-from-champions-league-group-stages/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thierry Henry doesn’t think Brendan Rodgers’ Celtic will progress from the Champions League group stages this season. It’s not what Celtic fans want to hear...
The post 'That's for sure': Thierry Henry states if Celtic will progress from UCL group stages appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic want to sign international winger on free transfer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44312</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/20/celtic-want-international-free-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T18:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic signed three wingers in the summer in the form of Yang Hyun-jun, Luis Palma and Marco Tilio. On the other hand, Jota left the club in order to join Al-Ittihad. The Hoops might be in need of further strengthening on the flanks though, with Liel Abada picking up an injury while away on international […]
Celtic want to sign international winger on free transfer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘He has done well’: What Neil Lennon said after FT following Celtic's defeat to Feyenoord]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174910</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/he-has-done-well-what-neil-lennon-said-after-ft-following-celtics-defeat-to-feyenoord/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon offered differing views on the two red cards dishes out to Gustaf Lagerbielke and Odin Holm during Celtic’s 2-0 defeat to Feyenoord in...
The post ‘He has done well’: What Neil Lennon said after FT following Celtic's defeat to Feyenoord appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aiden McGeady is already looking forward to "massive" Celtic game; sees midweek positives]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174876</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/aiden-mcgeady-is-already-looking-forward-to-massive-celtic-game-sees-midweek-positives/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aiden McGeady is already looking forward to Lazio’s visit to Celtic Park on matchday two of the UEFA Champions League. It was a disappointing evening...
The post Aiden McGeady is already looking forward to "massive" Celtic game; sees midweek positives appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Championship club make approach for Celtic coach]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44309</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/20/championship-club-approach-celtic-coach/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T12:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is an air of disappointment around Celtic after they made a losing start to their Champions League campaign. A decent first-half performance was undone at the stroke of half-time with Feyenoord scoring from direct free kick. Until that point, they had failed to create much in front of goal. The Dutch champions would score […]
Championship club make approach for Celtic coach - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘WE DIDN’T GIVE UP,’ INSISTS McGREGOR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112223</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/we-didnt-give-up-insists-mcgregor/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T12:07:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CALLUM McGREGOR insists Celtic can overcome their false start in the Champions League after last night’s 2-0 setback against Feyenoord in Rotterdam. The Hoops more than held their own for the first 45 minutes, but were undone when Calvin Steng’s curling free-kick foxed Joe Hart low down at his left-hand post in stoppage-time. The roof fell [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Points left on the table in Rotterdam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112174</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/points-left-on-the-table-in-rotterdam/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T11:31:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s get the negatives out of the way.  Lou Macari is one of the greatest human beings to pull on a football jersey, but for a while he carried a heavy load.  He was left on the end of a wall for a free kick in Argentina 1978.  Cubillas struck, ex-Celt Luigi winced, and future-Celt [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers was asked about Celtic transfer spending in wake of Feyenoord defeat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174862</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/journalist-asks-rodgers-about-celtic-transfer-spending-after-terrific-financial-results/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers was quizzed about the club’s recently announced financial figures on Tuesday. On Monday, Celtic released their annual financial results and there...
The post Brendan Rodgers was asked about Celtic transfer spending in wake of Feyenoord defeat appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arsenal hero Thierry Henry criticises Celtic player live on air]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44302</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/20/arsenal-hero-thierry-henry-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T10:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is safe to say that Celtic would have been bitterly disappointed with how the game against Feyenoord turned out for them. For a long time, they were very much in the contest and arguably had the better chances to score in the first-half. But things went south at the stroke of half-time when the […]
Arsenal hero Thierry Henry criticises Celtic player live on air - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers hails one Celtic star who was "outstanding" in Feyenoord defeat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174846</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-says-one-celtic-star-was-outstanding-in-feyenoord-loss-lagerbielke-holm-reaction/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has praised Liam Scales for his “outstanding” performance in Celtic’s loss to Feyenoord. The Irish defender was making his first UEFA Champions League...
The post Brendan Rodgers hails one Celtic star who was "outstanding" in Feyenoord defeat appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I’VE GOT HIGH STANDARDS,’ HART EXPLAINS FREE-KICK GOAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112217</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ive-got-high-standards-hart-explains-free-kick-goal/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T10:06:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART explained his stance on his goal-line at Feyenoord’s free-kick opener in Rotterdam last night. The veteran keeper was criticised in some quarters for allowing too much space to his left as Calvin Stengs shaped to take the deadball award 25 yards out. The Dutch ace hit the ball round the badly-erected Hoops defensive wall [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘You can’t’: Thierry Henry & Micah Richards argue over Celtic player's display v Feyenoord]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174883</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/you-cant-thierry-henry-micah-richards-argue-about-joe-hart-as-celtic-lose-to-feyenoord/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thierry Henry and Micah Richards disagreed about Joe Hart’s role in Celtic conceding the opening goal during their 2-0 Champions League defeat to Feyenoord on...
The post ‘You can’t’: Thierry Henry & Micah Richards argue over Celtic player's display v Feyenoord appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[X-CERTIFICATE CELTIC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112171</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/x-certificate-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T07:47:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WHEN Joe Hart picked the ball out of his net following Feyenoord’s second goal last night the experienced keeper must have had that old familiar sinking feeling. Celtic have conceded a massive FORTY-FOUR goals in their last 21 Euro ties with the 36-year-old 75 times-capped England keeper involved in 39 of the losses. Hart, of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["We didn't expect"; one part of Celtic's play made an impression on Feyenoord star]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174870</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/we-didnt-expect-one-part-of-celtics-play-made-an-impression-on-feyenoord-star/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feyenoord attacker Alireza Jahanbakhsh says he was surprised by one part of Celtic’s play on Tuesday night. The Iran international netted the Eredivisie winners’ second...
The post "We didn't expect"; one part of Celtic's play made an impression on Feyenoord star appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I’ll look at myself"; Celtic star takes responsibility after costly Champions League error]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174843</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/joe-hart-makes-honest-admission-about-feyenoord-free-kick-post-match-celtic-discussions-took-place/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic goalkeeper Joe Hart has accepted responsibility for Feyenoord’s opening goal on Tuesday night. Brendan Rodgers‘ Hoops had competed well in the first half at...
The post "I’ll look at myself"; Celtic star takes responsibility after costly Champions League error appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘HARSH,’ AS RODGERS DELIVERS VERDICT ON INEXPERIENCED CELTS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112162</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/harsh-as-rodgers-delivers-verdict-on-inexperienced-celts/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T06:40:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS searched for positives after the latest Champions League setback in Rotterdam last night. The Hoops did well to keep the contest even for 45 minutes, but the loss of a sloppy free-kick goal in stoppage-time to Calvin Stengs put the visitors on the back-foot. The second-half descended into chaos with central defender Gustaf [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch: The remarkable Tuesday scenes that could benefit Celtic in the Champions League]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174833</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/watch-the-remarkable-tuesday-scenes-that-could-benefit-celtic-in-the-champions-league/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There were some remarkable Tuesday night scenes in the other game in Celtic’s UEFA Champions League group. As the Hoops were drifting to a disappointing...
The post Watch: The remarkable Tuesday scenes that could benefit Celtic in the Champions League appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Shot themselves in the foot"; What the Dutch media are saying about Feyenoord vs Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174818</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/shot-themselves-in-the-foot-what-the-dutch-media-are-saying-about-feyenoord-vs-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Dutch media have been reacting to the UEFA Champions League meeting between Feyenoord and Celtic. It was a bruising start for the Hoops in...
The post "Shot themselves in the foot"; What the Dutch media are saying about Feyenoord vs Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor picks out one big positive from the closing stages of Celtic's loss to Feyenoord]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174825</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/callum-mcgregor-picks-out-one-big-positive-from-the-closing-stages-of-celtics-loss-to-feyenoord/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T04:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor was keen for some positivity after Celtic lost their Champions League opener against Feyenoord on Tuesday night. The Dutch side were 2-0 winners...
The post Callum McGregor picks out one big positive from the closing stages of Celtic's loss to Feyenoord appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HENRIK AT 52: ‘I DIDN’T WANT TO LEAVE AS A LOSER’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=78607</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/henrik-at-52-i-didnt-want-to-leave-as-a-loser/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T04:33:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HENRIK LARSSON, who celebrates his 52nd birthday today, said farewell to his adoring legions of Celtic fans with his usual flourish just over NINETEEN years ago. The Swede chose a bright afternoon at Hampden to bring down the curtain on his glittering career at the Hoops with a double salvo against Dunfermline in a 3-1 triumph [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HENRIK AT 52: BIRTHDAY BHOY’S FIFTIETH GOAL – AND IT’S PARTY TIME IN GOVAN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=76426</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/henrik-at-52-birthday-bhoys-fiftieth-goal-and-its-party-time-in-govan/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T04:32:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HENRIK LARSSON celebrates his 52nd birthday today and will deserve every good wish that comes his way. The talismanic Swede, one of Celtic’s greatest-ever purchases at a bargain £650,000 from Feyenoord in 1997, has left Hoops followers everywhere with a host of wonderful and endearing memories. One such heartwarming recollection was delivered in Govan on [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HENRIK AT 52: ‘I LOVE IT…I LOVE IT,’ LARSSON BEAMS AFTER 1998 TITLE TRIUMPH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=80274</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/henrik-at-52-i-love-it-i-love-it-larsson-beams-after-1998-title-triumph/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T04:31:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WIM JANSEN was named as successor to the popular Tommy Burns in July 1997 – and was tasked with preventing Walter Smith’s Ibrox outfit from claiming a historic tenth successive title. The Dutchman was more concerned with guiding Celtic to THEIR first championship in a decade. Author Alex Gordon investigates the glorious season of 1997/98 [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HENRIK AT 52: HOW CELTIC ALMOST LOST LEGEND FOR £140,000]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=54558</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/henrik-at-52-how-celtic-almost-lost-legend-for-140000/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T04:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Henrik Larsson celebrates his 52nd birthday today and Hoops followers everywhere will join CQN in wishing the Swedish superstar many happy returns on the occasion. However, there was a time when Celtic came so close to losing out in bringing in the fans’ favourite from Feyenoord. Hoops icon Davie Hay revealed all in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE JOCK STEIN YEARS (Part Ten)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=55203</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-jock-stein-years-part-ten/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-20T04:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Jock Stein made an extraordinary immediate impact on the Parkhead club when he returned as manager in March 1965. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE,  Alex Gordon, author of fifteen publications on Celtic, has opened his book files on the Parkhead great for an absorbing twenty-one part series. Today, in Part Ten of our fascinating look [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic want to sign Chelsea target with £8m release clause]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44298</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/19/celtic-want-sign-chelsea-release-clause/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T22:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The summer transfer window might be long over, but Celtic continue to be linked with one player after another. Left-back is one area of the pitch where the Hoops might be in need of strengthening. And it looks like they have a youngster in their sights who is wanted by the likes of Chelsea, Manchester […]
Celtic want to sign Chelsea target with £8m release clause - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has his say on two Celtic red cards; opinion changed from initial viewing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174811</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-has-his-say-on-two-celtic-red-cards-opinion-changed-from-initial-viewing/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T22:15:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has shared his thoughts on the two red cards Celtic suffered against Feyenoord. It was a disappointing start to our UEFA Champions League...
The post Brendan Rodgers has his say on two Celtic red cards; opinion changed from initial viewing appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FEYENOORD 2 CELTIC 0: SEEING RED AS NINE-MAN CELTS CRASH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112158</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/feyenoord-2-celtic-0-seeing-red-as-nine-man-celts-crash/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T21:21:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FEYENOORD 2 CELTIC 0 GUSTAF LAGERBIEKLE and Odin Holm were both dismissed in a night of red card mayhem in Rotterdam. Celtic plunged to defeat in the opening game of the Champions League Group E campaign which erupted in controversy with the second-half sendings-off of the centre-back and the midfielder. Ropey Bosnian referee Irfan Peljto [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 things we learned as Celtic collapse vs Feyenoord]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44293</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/19/3-things-learned-celtic-feyenoord/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T21:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a new season but the same old story for Celtic. The Hoops have struggled badly in Europe for quite some time now and that continued in their Champions League opener away in the Netherlands against Dutch champions, Feyenoord. It was an evening that promised so much and provided so little. But the Hoops […]
3 things we learned as Celtic collapse vs Feyenoord - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Same old mistakes, Palma verdict; 3 things we learned as Celtic lose to Feyenoord]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174803</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/same-old-mistakes-palma-verdict-3-things-we-learned-as-celtic-lose-to-feyenoord/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T20:59:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fell to a 2-0 defeat in their UEFA Champions League opener to Feyenoord on Tuesday evening. It was an action-packed encounter that saw the...
The post Same old mistakes, Palma verdict; 3 things we learned as Celtic lose to Feyenoord appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic player chasing Erling Haaland for Golden Boot]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44289</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/19/former-celtic-player-erling-haaland/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T18:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A number of Celtic players have left for the Premier League over the years. Unfortunately, the Hoops have become a bit of a stepping stone to the English top flight for many. But then, if they do end up getting the move, it generally means that they have done exceptionally well during their time at […]
Former Celtic player chasing Erling Haaland for Golden Boot - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feyenoord v Celtic, GG Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112155</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/feyenoord-v-celtic-gg-live-updates/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T18:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 20:00.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: HATATE, PALMA START]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112152</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-hatate-palma-start/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T17:50:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE makes his first start of the season for Celtic in their Champions League opener against Feyenoord in Rotterdam tonight. There is also a place in Brendan Rodgers’ line-up for Honduran winger Luis Palma who made his Hoops debut in the 3-0 win over Dundee at Parkhead at the weekend. Gustaf Lagerbielke will partner [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More than 90 Minutes Feyenoord v CELTIC Matchday Minizine]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58414</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/more-than-90-minutes-feyenoord-v-celtic-matchday-minizine/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T15:46:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post More than 90 Minutes Feyenoord v CELTIC Matchday Minizine appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I am sure': Barry Ferguson hails Celtic star who has got 'everything', makes contract claim]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174784</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-am-sure-barry-ferguson-hails-celtic-star-who-has-got-everything-makes-contract-claim/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Barry Ferguson has lauded the qualities of Celtic midfielder Reo Hatate and how he has got ‘everything’ in his locker. With the 2023 summer transfer...
The post 'I am sure': Barry Ferguson hails Celtic star who has got 'everything', makes contract claim appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First start under Rodgers, attacker unleashed; Celtic team news and Predicted XI vs Feyenoord]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174748</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/first-start-under-rodgers-attacker-unleashed-celtic-team-news-and-predicted-xi-vs-feyenoord/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are back in amongst it in the UEFA Champions League on Tuesday evening as we take on Feyenoord. A trip to the Eredivisie champions...
The post First start under Rodgers, attacker unleashed; Celtic team news and Predicted XI vs Feyenoord appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feyenoord boss Arne Slot makes superb Celtic vs Rangers claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44285</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/19/feyenoord-boss-arne-slot-celtic-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T15:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are getting ready to take on a tough test as they face Feyenoord in the Champions League group stage opener away at Feyenoord. Brendan Rodgers’ team might be coming into the game on the back of a couple of wings but the Dutch champions will have to be considered the favourites on the day […]
Feyenoord boss Arne Slot makes superb Celtic vs Rangers claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Last season of the Champions League in its current format]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58411</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/last-season-of-the-champions-league-in-its-current-format/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T14:44:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic start their Champions League campaign tonight against Feyenoord in Rotherham. This will be the last season of the current CL format.  UEFA will replace it with a new format from next season. The group stages as we know them will be replaced with a 36 team league structure. Is the new format to counter anymore […]
The post Last season of the Champions League in its current format appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic star on fire in Premier League; only Haaland has scored more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174755</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/odsonne-edouards-time-has-arrived-down-south-and-its-reflecting-really-well-on-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic forward Odsonne Edouard is having a terrific start to the season down south. The Frenchman has netted five goals in six matches for...
The post Former Celtic star on fire in Premier League; only Haaland has scored more appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Injured Celtic player pictured in training before Feyenoord game]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44283</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/19/celtic-player-training-feyenoord-game/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T12:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are set to begin their Champions League group stage journey with the away trip to De Kuip to take on Dutch champions, Feyenoord. It is not going to be an easy task for Brendan Rodgers’ side for sure. Arne Slot’s team showed their quality at the weekend with a 6-1 win over Heerenveen in […]
Injured Celtic player pictured in training before Feyenoord game - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic hero continues bright start to managerial career; wins treble in homeland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174704</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-hero-continues-bright-start-to-managerial-career-wins-treble-in-homeland/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic hero Scott McDonald has continued his bright start to life in management. McDonald is the manager of National Premier Leagues Queensland side Gold...
The post Former Celtic hero continues bright start to managerial career; wins treble in homeland appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feyenoord vs Celtic referee managed to get a big reaction out of Ally McCoist last season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174710</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/feyenoord-vs-celtic-referee-managed-to-get-a-big-reaction-out-of-ally-mccoist-last-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The referee for Tuesday night’s Feyenoord vs Celtic clash managed to get a big reaction out of Ally McCoist last season. It’s a big evening...
The post Feyenoord vs Celtic referee managed to get a big reaction out of Ally McCoist last season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On form Feyenoord, spectacular financials]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112147</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/on-form-feyenoord-spectacular-financials/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T11:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feyenoord beat Heerenveen 6-1 on Saturday, won 1-5 at Utrecht in their previous game and recorded another 6-1, home to Almere before that.  That is lightening form.  Draws in their opening two games of the season are the only chink in the armour.  The Dutch champions are a weaker Pot 1 side, but they won [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Tuesday September 19: Here We Go Again]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18492</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18492"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T10:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ladies and gentlemen, lads and lassies, take your seats for tonight’s show.   Alright, some of you may elect to view the proceedings from behind…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Malph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New keeper involved, Palma's friend, Phillips status; Watch Celtic train ahead of Feyenoord]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174740</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/new-keeper-involved-palmas-friend-phillips-status-watch-celtic-stars-train-ahead-of-feyenoord/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic trained on home soil on Monday before heading off to Rotterdam. The Hoops are preparing for their first Champions League group stage fixture. It’s...
The post New keeper involved, Palma's friend, Phillips status; Watch Celtic train ahead of Feyenoord appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FEYENOORD v CELTIC: 5-MINUTE QUIZ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112149</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/feyenoord-v-celtic-5-minute-quiz/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T10:04:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have the opportunity in Rotterdam tonight to avenge their European Cup Final extra-time loss to Feyenoord in the San Siro Stadium in Milan on May 6 1970. Jock Stein’s side had conquered Europe in Lisbon in 1967 with their unforgettable triumph over Inter Milan and were looking at achieving a historic silverware double. Alas, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero tipped to be next Manchester United manager]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44280</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/19/celtic-next-manchester-united-manager/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T10:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manchester United have never been the same since Sir Alex Ferguson retired. They have brought in many reputed managers since then like David Moyes, Louis van Gaal, Jose Mourinho and more, but nobody has been able to guide them back to the top. Erik ten Hag showed a lot of promise last season but things […]
Celtic hero tipped to be next Manchester United manager - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE DEBT RODGERS OWES ARNE SLOT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112143</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-debt-rodgers-owes-arne-slot/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T09:43:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS might just have tonight’s rival manager Arne Slot to thank for the Irishman being given the opportunity to return to Celtic. It was well publicised in May that the Feyenoord boss was high on the list of Spurs’ wanted men as they searched for a long-term successor to Antonio Conte. At that time, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIRTHDAY BHOY’S DUTCH TREAT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112136</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/birthday-bhoys-dutch-treat/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T08:47:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic striker George McCluskey celebrates his 66th birthday today – and is hoping his old club stage an action replay of his heroics in Holland back on September 29 1982. The gifted frontman scored one of his most memorable goals in Billy McNeill’s side’s 2-1 victory over Ajax, Johan Cruyff et al, in Amsterdam for [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LARSSON v KYOGO: BRENDAN’S VERDICT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112132</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/larsson-v-kyogo-brendans-verdict/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T07:51:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has stepped into the Henrik Larsson v Kyogo Furuhashi debate. Celtic fans have been discussing the penalty-box prowess and all-round skills of the Swede and the Japanese personalities. Larsson, who was bought for a bargain £650,000 from tonight’s Champions League opponents in the summer of 1997, and Kyogo, who was brought to the Hoops [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dutch Assignment after Dundee Victory]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58406</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/dutch-assignment-after-dundee-victory/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T07:42:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I did not take my usual seat at Celtic Park in the Main Stand on Saturday. There were no buses, planes or airport pints. Instead my pre-match was a swim in the Spanish sea and a cup of coffee in the sun before getting a taxi to Paddy’s Point home of the Paddy’s Point CSC. […]
The post Dutch Assignment after Dundee Victory appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon's 11-word response on if Celtic star Kyogo is the best since Henrik Larsson]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174761</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/neil-lennons-11-word-response-on-if-celtic-star-kyogo-is-the-best-since-henrik-larsson/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The King of Kings. No one will ever probably touch what the Celtic hero did at Parkhead. Instead, one of football’s generational talents and deadly...
The post Neil Lennon's 11-word response on if Celtic star Kyogo is the best since Henrik Larsson appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘TRULY A JOY,’ INSISTS EVERGREEN HART]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112128</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/truly-a-joy-insists-evergreen-hart/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T06:58:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART has conceded 37 goals in 17 European games since making his Celtic debut in the 4-2 win over FK Jablonec in the Czech Republic two days after signing in August 2021. The 36-year-old 75 times-capped England international keeper has been in direct line of firing squads from teams such as Real Madrid, Real [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Kyogo Furuhashi question lingers ahead of Celtic Champions League campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174733</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/big-kyogo-furuhashi-question-lingers-ahead-of-celtic-champions-league-campaign/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last season’s Champions League group stage was a fairly punishing one for Celtic and Kyogo Furuhashi. The Japanese forward has been a complete revelation ever...
The post Big Kyogo Furuhashi question lingers ahead of Celtic Champions League campaign appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star comes out fighting before Feyenoord; contract, critics and more tackled]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174717</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/joe-hart-comes-out-fighting-before-feyenoord-celtic-contract-critics-and-more-tackled/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic goalkeeper Joe Hart has had plenty of good stuff to say in the lead-up to our clash against Feyenoord. Hart is busy preparing with...
The post Celtic star comes out fighting before Feyenoord; contract, critics and more tackled appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIGHTING TALK: ‘THAT’S ALL I CAN PROMISE,’ CELTIC BOSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112100</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/fighting-talk-thats-all-i-can-promise-celtic-boss/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T06:08:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has issued a promise to Celtic fans as he prepares for the team’s Champions League kick off against Feyenoord in Rotterdam tonight. The Irishman, taking charge of the Hoops at this level for the first time since December 2017, vows his players will be willing to fight and scrap in every encounter in Group [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers suggests Celtic tactical change for Champions League campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174725</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-hints-at-celtic-tactical-change-for-champions-league-campaign/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has hinted at a tactical change for Celtic in the UEFA Champions League. The Hoops get their Group E campaign underway with a...
The post Brendan Rodgers suggests Celtic tactical change for Champions League campaign appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Darren O'Dea managerial story drops on eve of important Celtic B clash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174697</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/darren-odea-managerial-story-drops-on-eve-of-important-celtic-b-clash/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic coach Darren O’Dea is attracting interest from Inverness Caledonian Thistle about their vacant manager’s job, according to a report. The Highlanders, who we beat...
The post Report: Darren O'Dea managerial story drops on eve of important Celtic B clash appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN’S EURO GOALDEN BHOYS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112096</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/brendans-euro-goalden-bhoys/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T04:45:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have scored 57 goals in Brendan Rodgers’ 42 European games in his previous stint as Hoops boss. The Parkhead side have conceded 63 over the same period which has seen them win 16, lose 18 and draw eight of the encounters. Three players share top spot with eight goals – Moussa Dembele, Scott Sinclair [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS’ COMPLETE CELTIC EURO RECORD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112080</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-complete-celtic-euro-record/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T04:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS will take charge of Celtic for the 43rd time in European competition against Feyenoord in Rotterdam this evening. This season’s Champions League adventure will kick off with the Group E encounter in the De Kuip Stadium with games against Atletico Madrid and Lazio before the turn of the year. Results and performances in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE JOCK STEIN YEARS (Part Nine)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=55186</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-jock-stein-years-part-nine/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T04:15:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Jock Stein made an extraordinary immediate impact on the Parkhead club when he returned as manager in March 1965. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE,  Alex Gordon, author of fifteen publications on Celtic, has opened his book files on the Parkhead great for an absorbing twenty-one part series. Today, in Part Nine of our fascinating look [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JOE MILLER: GREAT UNCAPPED CELTS (Part Fifteen)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=73097</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/joe-miller-great-uncapped-celts-part-fifteen/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T04:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CQN is turning the spotlight once again on the Celtic players who never had the honour of playing for their country. Joe Miller was a fabulous addition to Billy McNeill’s centenary double-winning squad when he arrived from Aberdeen in November 1987. He became part of McNeill’s Three Musketeers along with Frank McAvennie and Andy Walker [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OFFICIAL: CELTIC’S £25.3m EURO WINDFALL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112097</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/official-celtics-25-3m-euro-windfall/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T23:10:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC received exactly £25.3million for their efforts in last season’s Champions League. The Hoops are already on course to beat that total with their share of the TV revenue this time around. Last term, they split the pot with Giovanni van Bronckhorst’s Ibrox side, but they are flying solo on this occasion after the Govan [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Championship club keen to open talks with Celtic coach]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44277</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/18/championship-open-talks-celtic-coach/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T22:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic coaches have certainly drawn quite a bit of interest in recent years. We saw Ange Postecoglou leave in the summer for Tottenham Hotspur. John Kennedy and Gavin Strachan have been linked with moves away from the club on numerous occasions as well, although they have remained stayed put. It is not just the first-team […]
Championship club keen to open talks with Celtic coach - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers explains Celtic’s target in Europe]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44273</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/18/brendan-rodgers-celtic-target-europe/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T21:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers is back in the Celtic managerial hot seat and set to guide the club into the Champions League once again. This is not the first time he has done so, although his past record in the competition can be considered shaky as best. The Northern Irishman has won only one of the twelve […]
Brendan Rodgers explains Celtic’s target in Europe - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed fresh injury doubt before Feyenoord game]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44271</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/18/celtic-fresh-injury-feyenoord-game/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T19:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been struggling with injuries this season, and we are just a few games into the campaign. Unfortunately, things do not seem to be getting any better for the Hoops. There is no position where they have had to face more issues than at centre-back. Cameron Carter-Vickers, Stephen Welsh and Maik Nawrocki are all […]
Celtic handed fresh injury doubt before Feyenoord game - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘He is a top player’: Neil McCann blown away by ‘cultured footballer’ at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174682</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/he-is-a-top-player-neil-mccann-blown-away-by-cultured-footballer-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T19:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neil McCann has spoken highly about the qualities of Celtic midfielder, Matt O’Riley. The 22-year-old has possibly been Celtic’s best player during these opening stages...
The post ‘He is a top player’: Neil McCann blown away by ‘cultured footballer’ at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou's exit to Spurs partly contributes to £13.5m windfall for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174679</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglous-exit-to-spurs-partly-contributes-to-13-5m-windfall-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T18:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou’s exit to Tottenham Hotspur and business interruption insurance recovery in relation to Covid-19 landed Celtic a one-off windfall of £13.5m in the last...
The post Ange Postecoglou's exit to Spurs partly contributes to £13.5m windfall for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s £40.7 million announcement should scare Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44267</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/18/celtic-announcement-scare-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T18:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been outright the most dominant team in Scottish football for over a decade now. That kind of success on the pitch has translated to success off it as well. At this point in time, they are in a very stable position right now and set up to continue their dominance for the foreseeable […]
Celtic’s £40.7 million announcement should scare Rangers - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Lawwell explains reasons behind £72m bank balance as Celtic announce massive profit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174674</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/peter-lawwell-explains-reasons-behind-72m-bank-balance-as-celtic-announce-massive-turnover-and-profit/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T17:12:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have released their annual financial results to the year ended 30th June 2023 and it shows the club have made big profits from a...
The post Peter Lawwell explains reasons behind £72m bank balance as Celtic announce massive profit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bonanza – the Celtic Accounts episode!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112095</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/bonanza-the-celtic-accounts-episode/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T16:51:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s financial results for the year to 20 June 2023 were released this evening and showed income grew to a new peak of £119.9m, up from £88.2m the previous season.  That 35% leap is largely (though not exclusively) a consequence of the club returning to Champions League football in September 2022. The bank balance was [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's annual financial results are due imminently and expect records to be broken]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174669</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-annual-financial-results-are-due-imminently-and-expect-records-to-be-broken/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T15:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s annual financial results for the year ending 30th June 2023 are expected to be released this week and they are likely to show that...
The post Celtic's annual financial results are due imminently and expect records to be broken appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers makes superb claim about returning Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44237</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/18/brendan-rodgers-claim-returning-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T15:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers was delighted with the Celtic win over Dundee FC at the weekend. The three goals would have come as a relief to the Northern Irishman as well, as the Hoops had struggled to score lately. He seemed even more pleased when talking about the performance of one of his players. The 3-0 victory […]
Brendan Rodgers makes superb claim about returning Celtic player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arne Slot rises above bizarre media question about using nefarious tactics vs Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174666</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/arne-slot-rises-above-bizarre-media-question-about-purposely-targeting-celtic-injury/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T14:54:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feyenoord manager Arne Slot was asked whether he would instruct his players to “test” the shoulder injury of Kyogo Furuhashi on Tuesday, but he was...
The post Arne Slot rises above bizarre media question about using nefarious tactics vs Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UCL opponent cuts through Celtic and Rangers myth; the players seen as clear dangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174660</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/feyenoord-boss-cuts-through-celtic-and-rangers-myth-the-players-seen-as-clear-dangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T14:25:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feyenoord boss Arne Slot says there is no use in comparing the upcoming matches against Celtic to the recent tie between PSV and Rangers. Slot...
The post UCL opponent cuts through Celtic and Rangers myth; the players seen as clear dangers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BBC pundit makes sensational claim about Celtic hero Kyogo]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44260</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/18/bbc-pundit-claim-celtic-kyogo/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T11:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Ange Postecoglou left Celtic for Tottenham Hotspur after the end of last season, many wondered what kind of an effect it would have on Kyogo. The Japanese forward had been absolutely brilliant under the management of the Australian. But could he replicate that with a new manager in place? Brendan Rodgers ended up replacing […]
BBC pundit makes sensational claim about Celtic hero Kyogo - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debuts aplenty but expectations tempered]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112061</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/debuts-aplenty-but-expectations-tempered/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T11:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The return of cherished players from injury is often anticlimactic as match sharpness takes time to achieve.  Not so with Reo Hatate on Saturday.  Apart from brief cameos against Ross County and Aberdeen, Reo had not seen competitive action since last season’s Scottish Cup Final. We have to temper expectations for tomorrow in Rotterdam, our [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Win Tickets for an evening with Martin O’Neill]]></title>
        <id>http://celticunderground.net/?p=6681</id>
        <link href="http://celticunderground.net/win-tickets-for-an-evening-with-martin-oneill/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T10:55:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This Wednesday, Graham Spiers is hosting an evening with Martin O’Neill. Listening to a chat with the great man is always fun and following our first UCL game the night before, it may be a great night for dismissing the sorrows or continuing the joy. Fans or all clubs are welcome but it’s likely to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harry Brady</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Monday September 18: The Eve of Construction?]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18490</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18490"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T08:49:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 3-0 win over Dundee on Saturday kept the hoops at the top of the table, a couple of points ahead of second place St…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Malph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘He is a master’: BBC pundit blown away by Celtic 28-year-old, compares him to Bhoys legend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174636</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/he-is-a-master-bbc-pundit-blown-away-by-celtic-28-year-old-compares-him-to-bhoys-legend/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen Craigan offered the highest of praises to Kyogo Furuhashi following Celtic’s 3-0 win over Dundee on Saturday. Celtic’s man up top was compared to,...
The post ‘He is a master’: BBC pundit blown away by Celtic 28-year-old, compares him to Bhoys legend appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO NAMES CELTIC’S ‘GAME-CHANGER’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112059</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kyogo-names-celtics-game-changer/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T07:48:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO FURUHASHI will be Celtic’s main goal threat as the Champions League excursion gets underway in Rotterdam tomorrow night. Brendan Rodgers’ men are preparing to take on Dutch title winners Feyenoord in the De Kuip stadium in the opening encounter in Group E which also includes Atletico Madrid and Lazio. Kyogo, who claimed a spectacular [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JOTA IN LIMBO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112055</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/jota-in-limbo/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T07:04:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic fans’ favourite Filipe Jota is in football limbo. As his ex-Hoops team-mates prepare to embark upon their Champions League quest with the opening Group E encounter against Feyenoord in Rotterdam due tomorrow night, the Portuguese maverick is wondering what the future holds in store. Jota ended his two-year stint at Parkhead in July [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE JOCK STEIN YEARS (Part Eight)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=55189</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-jock-stein-years-part-eight/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T04:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Jock Stein made an extraordinary immediate impact on the Parkhead club when he returned as team boss in March 1965. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE,  Alex Gordon, author of fifteen publications on Celtic, has opened his book files on the Parkhead great for an absorbing twenty-one part series. Today, in Part Eight of our [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BILLY STARK: GREAT UNCAPPED CELTS (Part Fourteen)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=73082</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/billy-stark-great-uncapped-celts-part-fourteen/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T04:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CQN is turning the spotlight again on the Celtic players who never had the honour of playing for their country. Billy Stark was Mr Reliable in the Hoops midfield during the club’s unforgettable centenary year after arriving in Billy McNeill’s summer rebuild of 1987. Although he was seen as the perfect foil to the likes [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALL-GO KYOGO PRAISED BY SKIPPER]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112050</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/all-go-kyogo-praised-by-skipper/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-17T23:10:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CALLUM McGREGOR has hailed the “selflessness” of Kyogo Furuhashi. The Japanese striker impressed everyone with his relentless spirit when he returned to the field in the first-half in the game against Dundee at Parkhead on Saturday. Kyogo was forced off with a shoulder injury in the 17th minute and it looked as though Brendan Rodgers would [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRING IT ON: MANY HAPPY RETURNS, BRENDAN?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112047</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/bring-it-on-many-happy-returns-brendan/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-17T23:05:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS will end a five-year spell in the Champions League wilderness against Feyenoord in Rotterdam tomorrow night. It will be the Celtic manager’s first involvement in the group stages of Europe’s elite competition since December 5 2017 when he saw the Hoops lose 1-0 to Anderlecht at Parkhead. The defeat dropped the Hoops into [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Furuhashi sends clear message to Celtic doubters]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44256</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/17/kyogo-furuhashi-message-celtic-doubters/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-17T22:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Furuhashi has been on a good run of form lately. He scored the winner for Celtic against the Rangers at Ibrox before the international break. And then he got himself another one against Dundee FC at the weekend. Thus, the Japanese forward should be ready to take on Feyenoord in the Champions League in […]
Kyogo Furuhashi sends clear message to Celtic doubters - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feyenoord legend makes superb claim about Celtic fans]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44253</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/17/feyenoord-legend-claim-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-17T21:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Feyenoord share a much longer history than a lot of fans might realise. The two teams had met in the European Cup final back in 1970. Jock Stein’s side had already won the competition back in 1967 and had the chance to lift it again a few years later. Unfortunately, they came up […]
Feyenoord legend makes superb claim about Celtic fans - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>