<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2022-10-23T12:51:33.598Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's missed penalty, the 'clear cut handball' and the IFAB rules which Nick Walsh would have considered]]></title>
        <id>3890575</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtics-missed-penalty-the-clear-cut-handball-and-the-ifab-rules-which-nick-walsh-would-have-considered-3890575"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T12:33:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just before half-time at Tynecastle Park, Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou had his hands on his head and turned away laughing in disbelief.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angus Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“I think it’s a penalty”, Bobby Madden weighs in on Celtic VAR debate]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/i-think-its-a-penalty-bobby-madden-weighs-in-on-celtic-var-debate/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/i-think-its-a-penalty-bobby-madden-weighs-in-on-celtic-var-debate/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T12:18:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former SFA Referee Bobby Madden has weighed in on the VAR debate that is rumbling on following Celtic’s win against Hearts at Tynecastle. Celitc were ahead after just 14 minutes through James Forrest. Minutes after Hearts went level with Lawrence Shankland from the spot – awarded by VAR, Forrest watched his cross hit Michael Smith’s Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Referee with recent Glasgow history confirmed for Celtic vs Shakhtar Donetsk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/referee-with-recent-glasgow-history-confirmed-for-celtic-vs-shakhtar-donetsk/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/referee-with-recent-glasgow-history-confirmed-for-celtic-vs-shakhtar-donetsk/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T11:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UEFA have confirmed the refereeing appointments for Celtic’s crucial Champions League clash with Shakhtar Donetsk on Tuesday. Serdar Gözübüyük is the main official, with the 36-year-old Dutchman returning to Glasgow for the third time in a year for his first Celtic assignment, after refereeing Rangers’ Europa League win at Ibrox over Red Star Belgrade last ...
The post Referee with recent Glasgow history confirmed for Celtic vs Shakhtar Donetsk appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marian Shved injury doubt for Celtic return as Shakhtar Donetsk suffer big blow]]></title>
        <id>8a15abbd94174760b1fd39ae0451f756</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23071666.marian-shved-injury-doubt-celtic-return-shakhtar-donetsk-suffer-big-blow/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T11:27:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic flop Marian Shved is a major doubt for a Champions League return to Parkhead tomorrow after suffering an injury setback.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic TV Commentary Sums Up Crazy Tynecastle Flashpoint]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-tv-commentary-sums-up-crazy-tynecastle-flashpoint/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-tv-commentary-sums-up-crazy-tynecastle-flashpoint/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T11:04:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC TV aired the Hearts vs Celtic game for supporters outside the UK and Ireland who subscribe to the service. The game finished 4-3 in the end, but the tie was not without controversy. Celtic looked to have made it 2-0 in the first half, but Nick Walsh blew early for a foul that looked […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend hails "top-quality" star who has excelled in Callum McGregor&#039;s absence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-legend-dalglish-hails-top-quality-star-who-has-excelled-in-callum-mcgregors-absence/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-legend-dalglish-hails-top-quality-star-who-has-excelled-in-callum-mcgregors-absence/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend Kenny Dalglish has sang the praises of Cameron Carter-Vickers and how the defender has handled the captain’s armband in the extended absence of Callum McGregor. The captain’s injury against RB Leipzig ruling him out until the World Cup initially seemed like a hammer blow to Celtic’s season across four competitions, but barring a ...
The post Celtic legend hails "top-quality" star who has excelled in Callum McGregor&#039;s absence appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['What? That's scandalous!' Celtic TV's furious VAR penalty refusal reaction in full]]></title>
        <id>6af45eb931c244c0c481a1be81d65e40</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23071527.what-scandalous--celtic-tvs-furious-var-penalty-refusal-reaction-full/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T10:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THIS is the moment that Celtic TV reacted to Nick Walsh and his VARs decision not to award their side a penalty against Hearts on Saturday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UNIQUE ANGLE: TAYLOR JOINS THE HIT PARADE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/unique-angle-taylor-joins-the-hit-parade/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/unique-angle-taylor-joins-the-hit-parade/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T10:07:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GREG TAYLOR joined the Celtic goal rush with his first Premiership strike since joining from Kilmarnock in September 2019. The unfussy and often understated left-back made certain of the points 10 minutes after being introduced to the action in the 66th minute against Hearts at Tynecastle yesterday. With the game deadlocked at 3-3, Taylor added [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton in VAR blast following Celtic 'stonewaller' penalty snub vs Hearts]]></title>
        <id>3cec8772ea2f4c3f75d294a10728758c</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23071506.chris-sutton-var-blast-following-celtic-stonewaller-penalty-snub-vs-hearts/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T10:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CHRIS SUTTON is adamant Celtic should have had a penalty against Hearts yesterday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Stewart in 'right decision' verdict over Hearts vs Celtic penalty call]]></title>
        <id>90d00c6436558cfb02e590dc7cdc9565</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23071487.michael-stewart-right-decision-verdict-hearts-vs-celtic-penalty-call/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T09:51:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT may only have been introduced this weekend, but VAR is already causing controversy in Scottish football.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laughable BBC Celtic Headline After Big Win at Tynecastle]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/laughable-bbc-celtic-headline-after-big-win-at-tynecastle/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/laughable-bbc-celtic-headline-after-big-win-at-tynecastle/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T09:50:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The BBC Scotland social media team have to be on the wind up as they continue to give baffling summaries of Celtic games. The Scottish Champions won 4-3 at Tynecastle, during a captivating game that had it all. The bhoys went ahead, then behind, then ahead, then were pegged back to 3-3 before finding the […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic stars lead tributes to retiring Paradise icon after incredible 26-year career]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-stars-lead-tributes-to-retiring-club-icon-nakamura-after-incredible-26-year-career/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-stars-lead-tributes-to-retiring-club-icon-nakamura-after-incredible-26-year-career/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T09:42:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s Japanese stars have paid tribute to Shunsuke Nakamura after the club icon announced his retirement from football at the age of 44. The former 98-cap Japan international was a revelation in Glasgow’s east end after signing for the Hoops in 2005, going on to win three successive titles and multiple individual awards in a ...
The post Celtic stars lead tributes to retiring Paradise icon after incredible 26-year career appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Stewart gives baffling verdict on Hearts - Celtic VAR chaos]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/michael-stewart-gives-baffling-verdict-on-hearts-celtic-var-chaos/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/michael-stewart-gives-baffling-verdict-on-hearts-celtic-var-chaos/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BBC pundit Michael Stewart has given his take on yesterday’s VAR carnage at Tynecastle, and it’s one that’s likely to baffle the Celtic support who watched their team beat Hearts in a whirlwind seven goal thriller. It was the first televised Premiership fixture to feature VAR following the introduction of the technology at Easter Road ...
The post Michael Stewart gives baffling verdict on Hearts - Celtic VAR chaos appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘EUPHORIA TAKES OVER YOUR BODY,’ GOAL HERO DISMISSES VAR INTERVENTION]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/euphoria-takes-over-your-body-goal-hero-dismisses-var-intervention/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/euphoria-takes-over-your-body-goal-hero-dismisses-var-intervention/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T09:07:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GREG TAYLOR waited for over three years for his first Premiership goal for Celtic and had no thoughts of interference from VAR as he took off on his wild and long-overdue celebrations. The Scotland international left-back, who had replaced a toiling Alexandro Bernabei in the 66th minute, netted his breakthrough goal 10 minutes later. The [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Icon Retires]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-icon-retires/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-icon-retires/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T08:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC Icon Shunsuke Nakamura has today hung up his boots after a glittering career that’s taken him all over the world. The Japanese hero bows out of the game at the age of 44, finishing up his playing days with Yokohama FC in Japan. お疲れ様Shunsuke! Pics for @CelticFC @HailHailMedia @CelticFCJPN @ACSOMPOD et al #CelticFC as […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Icon Retires - CeltsAreHere]]></title>
        <id>CBMiLWh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtaWNvbi1yZXRpcmVzL9IBMWh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtaWNvbi1yZXRpcmVzL2FtcC8</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiLWh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtaWNvbi1yZXRpcmVzL9IBMWh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtaWNvbi1yZXRpcmVzL2FtcC8?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T08:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Icon Retires  CeltsAreHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: “What a game, What a Unique Angle,” Celtic TV]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/video-what-a-game-what-a-unique-angle-celtic-tv/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-what-a-game-what-a-unique-angle-celtic-tv/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T08:46:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic TV’s Unique Angle is always a highlight after a Celtic victory and especially so after the Hoops repeatedly have to overcome the referee Nick Welsh who was aided and abetted by the VAR official Steven McLean in the most disgraceful series of dodgy decisions – all against one side – in any match in Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC AND THE PENALTY-KICK PUZZLER]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-and-the-penalty-kick-puzzler/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-and-the-penalty-kick-puzzler/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T08:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WITH the curious exception of referee Nick Walsh and Steven McLean in the VAR control room, just about everyone else who witnessed Michael Smith’s blatant handball believed it was a stonewall penalty-kick for Celtic. Only misguided souls, mischief-makers or even ex-Hearts players turned TV pundits thought the defender’s clear infringement was unworthy of a spot-kick [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘When key decisions went against us, we showed our mettle’]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/when-key-decisions-went-against-us-we-showed-our-mettle/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/when-key-decisions-went-against-us-we-showed-our-mettle/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T08:06:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecolgou reckoned that was some game of football yesterday afternoon as Celtic came away with all three points in a game that swung both ways and was marred by horrendous presumably biased refereeing and VAR decisions. Here’s what the Celtic manager was saying to Celtic TV afterwards with some supporter comments follwing that.“It was Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Celtic Penalty Claim Backed Up By Facts]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/ange-celtic-penalty-claim-backed-up-by-facts/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/ange-celtic-penalty-claim-backed-up-by-facts/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou rarely looks to make any headlines after a match. Even when decisions haven’t gone Celtic’s way, the manager tries to be as pragmatic as possible. On Saturday, we saw Ange’s fire at what he was witnessing from some of our officials. His reaction when VAR didn’t award Celtic a penalty against Hearts said […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE ‘PROBABLY HAD TO BEAT TWO TEAMS,’ INSISTS EX-CELT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ange-probably-had-to-beat-two-teams-insists-ex-celt/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ange-probably-had-to-beat-two-teams-insists-ex-celt/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T07:46:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOHN HARTSON insists Celtic had to beat TWO teams at Tynecastle yesterday – Hearts and VAR. The Hoops striking legend made the call after the champions had to overcome a number of obstacles concerning new technology before gaining a 4-3 victory over the hosts with goals from James Forrest, Giorgos Giakoumakis, Daizen Maeda and Greg [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Watching it again I think he moves his arm up to the ball,” Shelley Kerr]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/watching-it-again-i-think-he-moves-his-arm-up-to-the-ball-shelley-kerr/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/watching-it-again-i-think-he-moves-his-arm-up-to-the-ball-shelley-kerr/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T07:38:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celt Chris Sutton and the former Hearts player Michael Stewart adopted contrasting opinions on the biggest controverial incident to go against Celtic at Tynecastle yesterday in a match that Celtic still managed to win 4-3 despite the best efforts of Nick Welsh and his VAR colleague Steven McLean, both of whom have strong associations with Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘What a Guy’ – Giakoumakis Social Media Post is Spot On]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/what-a-guy-giakoumakis-social-media-post-is-spot-on/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/what-a-guy-giakoumakis-social-media-post-is-spot-on/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Giakoumakis helped Celtic to another important victory. The Greek striker staring the fight back after Hearts took a 2-1 lead in the second half. The frontman continues to score when he’s given game time and is giving Kyogo a run for his money. The game at Tynecastle has to be the most dramatic day of […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SO VAR SO BAD: SUTTON MYSTIFIED]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/so-var-so-bad-sutton-mystified/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/so-var-so-bad-sutton-mystified/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T07:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic striker Chris Sutton was baffled after VAR denied the champions a penalty-kick in the team’s rousing 4-3 victory over Hearts at Tynecastle yesterday. New technology was introduced to Scottish football for the first time this weekend and the Hoops were on the receiving end of a few bewildering decisions. The hosts were awarded [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Ange Postecoglou’s Celtic Tynecastle Celebration]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/video-ange-postecoglous-celtic-tynecastle-celebration/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/video-ange-postecoglous-celtic-tynecastle-celebration/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE always comes onto the pitch to celebrate a Celtic win, but it was on a different level at Tynecastle on Saturday afternoon. Celtic had a perfectly good goal chopped off to make it 2-0 and then had a stonewall penalty turned down for handball when the game was sitting at 1-1. It was a […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The other wrong call against Celtic that’s been overlooked]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/the-other-wrong-call-against-celtic-thats-been-overlooked/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/the-other-wrong-call-against-celtic-thats-been-overlooked/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T06:56:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the closing seconds of Celtic’s incident packed 4-3 win over Hearts at Tynecastle Liel Abada was flagged for offside – this is NOT the incident where the Israeli winger put the ball in the back of the Hearts net only for the flag to go up but no proof was ever provided that he Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC, VAR, THE STONEWALL PENALTY-KICK AND THE HISTORY-MAKING 28 SECONDS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-var-the-stonewall-penalty-kick-and-the-history-making-28-seconds/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-var-the-stonewall-penalty-kick-and-the-history-making-28-seconds/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T06:12:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT took exactly 28 SECONDS for VAR operator Steven McLean to review and dismiss Celtic’s valid penalty-kick claim at Tynecastle yesterday. Hearts defender Michael Smith clearly motioned his left hand to stop a pass from James Forrest in first-half stoppage-time with the game deadlocked at 1-1 following the hosts’ penalty-kick equaliser, courtesy of new technology. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hearts-Celtic reaction: 197 days - incredible Celtic penalty stat; 'Oooh, ahh up the VAR' and where's Willie Gibson?]]></title>
        <id>3890399</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/hearts/hearts-celtic-reaction-197-days-incredible-celtic-penalty-stat-oooh-ahh-up-the-var-and-wheres-willie-gibson-3890399"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hearts and Celtic put on a show at Tynecastle in the lunchtime kick-off on Saturday in the game of the season so far. The visitors earned the points in a seven-goal thriller that saw VAR play a pivotal part. Substitute Greg Taylor struck the winner to make it 4-3 with 14 minutes left in the epic Premiership contest. Lawrence Shankland, another sub, struck a hat-trick for the hosts – including two penalties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alan Pattullo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hearts-Celtic reaction: 197 days and counting - the incredible Celtic penalty stat; 'Oooh, ahh up the VAR' and where's Willie Gibson?]]></title>
        <id>3890399</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/hearts/hearts-celtic-reaction-197-days-and-counting-the-incredible-celtic-penalty-stat-oooh-ahh-up-the-var-and-wheres-willie-gibson-3890399"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hearts and Celtic put on a show at Tynecastle in the lunchtime kick-off on Saturday in the game of the season so far. The visitors earned the points in a seven-goal thriller that saw VAR play a pivotal part. Substitute Greg Taylor struck the winner to make it 4-3 with 14 minutes left in the epic Premiership contest. Lawrence Shankland, another sub, struck a hat-trick for the hosts – including two penalties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alan Pattullo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic On This Day – 23rd October  – David Potter’s Celtic Diary]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-on-this-day-23rd-october-david-potters-celtic-diary/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-on-this-day-23rd-october-david-potters-celtic-diary/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Month 3, Day 23 of Celtic Historian David Potter’s new diary on The Celtic Star which will run throughout the new season and will highlight key Celtic-related events relevant to each day, today covering 23 October…SATURDAY 23 OCTOBER 1915A combination of war time problems and injury mean that Celtic have to take the field to-day Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“The referee said the VAR said it was close to his body,” Greg Taylor]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/the-referee-said-the-var-said-it-was-close-to-his-body-greg-taylor/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/the-referee-said-the-var-said-it-was-close-to-his-body-greg-taylor/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T05:35:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Taylor summed up yesterday’s hugely significant 4-3 win over Hearts in the media room at Tynecastle yesterday afternoon, ahead of the day getting even better for Celtic with the news that theRangers could only draw at home to Livingston.Taylor was an unlikely goalscoring hero for the Hoops but who cares a jot about that? Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou shuts down Celtic style 'validation' as he stands by Champions League Plan A - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEA6Sa6SDwrq5WZ00aCCkDbEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiWGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2FuZ2UtcG9zdGVjb2dsb3Utc2h1dHMtZG93bi1jZWx0aWMtMjgzMDUzNTHSAQA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou shuts down Celtic style 'validation' as he stands by Champions League Plan A  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BOBBY MURDOCH: MIGHTY, MAGNIFICENT AND A CELTIC MAN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/bobby-murdoch-mighty-magnificent-and-a-celtic-man/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/bobby-murdoch-mighty-magnificent-and-a-celtic-man/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T04:30:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BOBBY MURDOCH was the epitome of a Celtic player; a skilled ball artiste blessed with breathtaking qualities. He brought flair and adventure to proceedings when he wore his beloved green and white hoops of his favourite team. Author Alex Gordon interviewed the player many times over the years and Murdoch’s inluence on Celtic features prominently [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matchwinner Greg Taylor hails Celtic character as champions dig deep and come up with the goods once more]]></title>
        <id>742f6681f4226684c4f762efa13762f6</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23070786.matchwinner-greg-taylor-hails-celtic-character-champions-dig-deep-come-goods/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GREG TAYLOR has praised the character of the Celtic team after they overcame a huge test against Hearts, and ignored the controversy over VAR’s involvement in the game to earn a crucial three points at Tynecastle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sandman’s Definitive Ratings – Celtic at Gargoyle Grove]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/sandmans-definitive-ratings-celtic-at-gargoyle-grove/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/sandmans-definitive-ratings-celtic-at-gargoyle-grove/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T21:29:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANDMAN’S DEFINITIVE RATINGS: CELTIC @ GARGOYLE GROVE“No penalty? Well I’ve been to a World Fair, a picnic, and a rodeo, and that’s the stupidest thing I ever heard come over a set of earphones.” – Slim Pickens as Major ‘King’ Kong, in ‘Dr.Strangelove’ROXIE – 7.5/10 – Big Joe steals the show… Almost. Tremendous ‘keeping to thwart Horribles Juniors, including a Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perfect Day for Celtic as Hoops Widen Gap]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/perfect-day-for-celtic-as-hoops-widen-gap/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/perfect-day-for-celtic-as-hoops-widen-gap/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T20:42:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well that was a quiet afternoon wasn’t it! I had a feeling in my gut that VAR was going to be the headline story today and so it transpired, although nothing should be taken away from what was an extremely exciting match at Tynecastle, one that proves Scottish football has a lot more to offer Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton in bemused Celtic VAR poser as operator called out over 'stonewaller' ref review - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEO4lSYtNFt2BdWhaE_vOHvAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiY2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvY2hyaXMtc3V0dG9uLWJlbXVzZWQtY2VsdGljLXZhci0yODMwNjUwNdIBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T20:28:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton in bemused Celtic VAR poser as operator called out over 'stonewaller' ref review  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Battle of Tynecastle: Hearts 3 – 4 Celtic: We NeVAR Stop]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/the-battle-of-tynecastle-hearts-3-4-celtic-we-nevar-stop/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/the-battle-of-tynecastle-hearts-3-4-celtic-we-nevar-stop/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T20:28:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That was action packed that one. Where to begin? After James Forrest grabbed his 101 goal for Celtic (yes that’s right, 101!), we never really took hold of the match and allowed Hearts a way into it, courtesy of an intervention by the much maligned VAR technology. Although in my opinion it was a stonewall Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Brilliant Post-match Greg Taylor Moment with Celtic Teammates]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/video-brilliant-post-match-greg-taylor-moment-with-celtic-teammates/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/video-brilliant-post-match-greg-taylor-moment-with-celtic-teammates/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T20:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GREG TAYLOR scored the goal that saw Celtic extend their lead at the top of the table. The left-back started on the bench before he replaced Alexandro Bernabei, who didn’t have his best game. He came on with the instruction to string a few passes together and settle down the game. Instead, he decided he’d […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arsenal, Manchester City &#039;among clubs interested in Celtic wonderkid&#039;]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sportsmole.co.uk/football/arsenal/transfer-talk/news/arsenal-man-city-among-clubs-interested-in-celtic-wonderkid_497643.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.sportsmole.co.uk/football/arsenal/transfer-talk/news/arsenal-man-city-among-clubs-interested-in-celtic-wonderkid_497643.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T20:10:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arsenal and Manchester City are keeping a close eye on 17-year-old Celtic wonderkid Rocco Vata, according to a report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scottish Cup R2 round-up: Sauchie stun Rose, Stranraer's long journey in vain, four-goal hero, R3 draw time]]></title>
        <id>3890363</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/scottish-cup-r2-round-up-sauchie-stun-rose-stranraers-long-journey-in-vain-four-goal-hero-r3-draw-time-3890363"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T20:05:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Highland League champions Fraserburgh took a league scalp on a busy day of action in the second round of the Scottish Cup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ross McLeish</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Penalty; BBC Pundit in Astonishing Celtic Take]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/no-penalty-bbc-pundit-in-astonishing-celtic-take/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/no-penalty-bbc-pundit-in-astonishing-celtic-take/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T19:52:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BBC Pundit Michael Stewart believes his old side did NOT get away with one when it came to the hand ball penalty claim against Celtic on Saturday. The game was sitting at 1-1 when Hearts player Michael Smith stops the momentum of the ball with his hand which was out with a natural position. Not […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["What a guy"; Giorgos Giakoumakis&#039; praise for Celtic teammate on Instagram]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-a-guy-giorgos-giakoumakis-praise-for-celtic-teammate-on-instagram/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-a-guy-giorgos-giakoumakis-praise-for-celtic-teammate-on-instagram/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T19:42:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgos Giakoumakis is a happy man tonight after scoring another goal for Celtic and helping his team to a 4-3 victory at Tynecastle. Giakoumakis scored a fine header from an Aaron Mooy corner, his seventh of the season in all competitions despite limited starts. After the match, he uploaded a post to Instagram, lauding the ...
The post "What a guy"; Giorgos Giakoumakis&#039; praise for Celtic teammate on Instagram appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robbie Neilson&#039;s bizarre claim after Celtic beat Hearts yet again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/robbie-neilsons-bizarre-claim-after-celtic-beat-hearts-yet-again/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/robbie-neilsons-bizarre-claim-after-celtic-beat-hearts-yet-again/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hearts manager Robbie Neilson has claimed that his team ‘absolutely rattled’ Celtic today, despite losing yet another match to the Bhoys. Neilson has faced Celtic on 16 occasions as a manager, losing 13 of them and winning just once – when Ange Postecoglou had been in the country for a matter of weeks. The Tynecastle ...
The post Robbie Neilson&#039;s bizarre claim after Celtic beat Hearts yet again appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kris Boyd fears Rangers end game for Gio as club hero pinpoints key reason for Ibrox fan backlash - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEPAWbGosGh3Op8gKWW4yx_sqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiX2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3Mva3Jpcy1ib3lkLWZlYXJzLXJhbmdlcnMtZW5kLTI4MzA0NTMz0gEA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T18:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kris Boyd fears Rangers end game for Gio as club hero pinpoints key reason for Ibrox fan backlash  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Talking Points As Celtic Overcome Hearts and VAR]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/3-talking-points-as-celtic-overcome-hearts-and-var/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/3-talking-points-as-celtic-overcome-hearts-and-var/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T18:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was an action-packed day in the capital as Celtic fought hard to overcome Hearts. VAR controversy and seven goals set up a thrilling game for the naturals, maybe not the fans! Sadly, the talking points coming away from the match will be about the VAR decision and Walsh’s decision, precisely what Ange was hoping […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou takes aim at what rival managers are saying about Celitc]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-takes-aim-at-what-rival-managers-are-saying-about-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-takes-aim-at-what-rival-managers-are-saying-about-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T18:03:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou gave a forthright opinion of today’s refereeing, VAR, and the perception of decisions Celtic get after the Bhoys beat Hearts 4-3 at Tynecastle. The 90 minutes were littered with strange refereeing calls, with officials’ use of VAR technology certainly attracting the ire of many supporters and pundits. Postecoglou has rarely discussed referees since ...
The post Ange Postecoglou takes aim at what rival managers are saying about Celitc appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James Tavernier swerves Celtic title question as gutted Rangers skippers admits 'we can't focus on them' - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEGbcVckCkysbEDrhIYaISuQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiaGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvamFtZXMtdGF2ZXJuaWVyLXN3ZXJ2ZXMtY2VsdGljLXRpdGxlLTI4MzA1NDY00gEA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Tavernier swerves Celtic title question as gutted Rangers skippers admits 'we can't focus on them'  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[”The euphoria took over my body,” Greg Taylor on his vital winner]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/the-euphoria-took-over-my-body-greg-taylor-on-his-vital-winner/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/the-euphoria-took-over-my-body-greg-taylor-on-his-vital-winner/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T17:59:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic overcame three dodgy VAR decisions earlier today which made the win at Tynecastle all the more enjoyable and the icing on the cake came later in the afternoon with Livingston being unlucky to leave Ibriox with just one point after their 1-1 draw against theRangers.However, Greg Taylor stepped up and secured all three points for the Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former EPL Ref Shocked at Celtic Tynecastle Call]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/former-epl-ref-shocked-at-celtic-tynecastle-call/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/former-epl-ref-shocked-at-celtic-tynecastle-call/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T17:38:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was an astonishing decision at the time and it doesn’t get any better for the VAR operatives at Tynescastle on Saturday. Celtic were denied a stonewall penalty at Tynecastle with the game very much in the balance. James Forrest tried to get the ball into the box when Smith stopped the balls progress with […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hartson and Sutton’s reaction to shocking VAR decisions going against Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/hartson-and-suttons-reaction-to-shocking-var-decisions-going-against-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/hartson-and-suttons-reaction-to-shocking-var-decisions-going-against-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T17:29:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton and John Hartson weren’t exactly impressed by some of the decisions made by the VAR team today in Celtic’s victory over Hearts.Led by gaffer, Ange Postecoglou, Celtic went on to defeat Hearts 4-3 at Tynecastle earlier today. Securing all three points extends Celtic’s lead at the top of the table, so may prove Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gio van Bronckhorst confesses to Rangers pressure as embattled boss sends message to growing dissenters - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEKFVib9Fk9Da_2ibliU06iYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiaWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvZ2lvLXZhbi1icm9uY2tob3JzdC1jb25mZXNzZXMtcmFuZ2Vycy0yODMwNDk0MdIBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T17:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gio van Bronckhorst confesses to Rangers pressure as embattled boss sends message to growing dissenters  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How VAR, Hearts and Celtic combined to create a chaotic yet compelling spectacle at Tynecastle]]></title>
        <id>3890252</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/how-var-hearts-and-celtic-combined-to-create-a-chaotic-yet-compelling-spectacle-at-tynecastle-3890252"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T16:28:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Forrest ushered in what he hopes will be a second century of goals for his beloved Celtic before even this significant moment was rendered a mere detail as a new VAR era in Scottish football erupted in organised chaos.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alan Pattullo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Extend Their Lead at the Top of the SPFL]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-extend-their-lead-at-the-top-of-the-spfl/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-extend-their-lead-at-the-top-of-the-spfl/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T16:12:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE RANGERS relied on a late John Lundstrum goal as they drew 1-1 to Livingston at home. The English midfielder had a chance to score with the last touch of the game, but the header was off-target. The referee’s whistle was met with boos from the remaining fans. FULL-TIME: Rangers 1-1 Livingston pic.twitter.com/T7jtXBMytX — Rangers […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hearts boss Robbie Neilson expresses concerns over VAR 'discrepancies' in 4-3 defeat to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>3890233</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/hearts/hearts-boss-robbie-neilson-expresses-concerns-over-var-discrepancies-in-4-3-defeat-to-celtic-3890233"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T16:09:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robbie Neilson fears VAR may become more of a "hindrance than a help" after experiencing it for the first time during his side's 4-3 defeat to Celtic at Tynecastle Park.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Elder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC GO FOUR AHEAD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-go-four-ahead/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-go-four-ahead/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T16:07:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC moved four points ahead at the top of the Premiership on a day of VAR controversy. The champions overcame Hearts 4-3 at Tynecastle in an encounter where they had to battle all obstacles to achieve the triumph. They managed to fight all the way in Edinburgh with goals from James Forrest, Giorgos Giakoumakis, Daizen [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers 1 Livingston 1 RECAP as Ibrox angst continues after dreary draw - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEGqW3k9c_s_rFct8pk7LMg8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiZGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvcmFuZ2Vycy12cy1saXZpbmdzdG9uLWxpdmUtc2NvcmUtMjgzMDI2NjjSAQA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T16:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers 1 Livingston 1 RECAP as Ibrox angst continues after dreary draw  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s multi-million pound windfall wait as Manchester United track youngster - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEN6N69nUSJ1Zqb1btHgg65EqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiaWh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vY2VsdGljcy1tdWx0aS1taWxsaW9uLXBvdW5kLXdpbmRmYWxsLXdhaXQtYXMtbWFuY2hlc3Rlci11bml0ZWQtdHJhY2steW91bmdzdGVyL9IBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T15:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s multi-million pound windfall wait as Manchester United track youngster  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou questions Celtic's lack of penalties as he hits out at VAR 'theatre' after win over Hearts]]></title>
        <id>3890192</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/ange-postecoglou-questions-celtics-lack-of-penalties-as-he-hits-out-at-var-theatre-after-win-over-hearts-3890192"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T15:21:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou hit out at the VAR "theatre" and pointed to Celtic's lack of penalty awards this season after a controversial decision went against his side in the 4-3 win over Hearts at Tynecastle Park.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Elder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robbie Neilson warns officials they need to iron out VAR problems before novelty wears off]]></title>
        <id>b9538ece379f946a5192c05383059bd1</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23070738.robbie-neilson-warns-officials-need-iron-var-problems-novelty-wears-off/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T14:53:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HEARTS manager Robbie Neilson doesn’t understand why VAR decisions took so long in his side’s loss to Celtic, saying he hopes that Scottish officials can quickly iron out the flaws in the system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou laughs off Celtic VAR 'circus' as he fires 'starring role' dig at video technology]]></title>
        <id>654bb261dafd4d391151caa7a2443ba4</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23070734.ange-postecoglou-laughs-off-celtic-var-circus-fires-starring-role-dig-video-technology/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T14:52:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU laughed off the role of VAR as his Celtic side grabbed three points against Hearts in the highly entertaining early Premiership kick-off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou blasts ‘theatre’ around VAR as he lays out concerns over impact delays will have on Celtic’s high tempo style]]></title>
        <id>9491479e0e5961ada99dc196dccfede9</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23070731.ange-postecoglou-blasts-theatre-around-var-lays-concerns-impact-delays-will-celtics-high-tempo-style/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T14:47:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU has criticised the ‘theatre’ surrounding VAR, as the involvement of the technology in Celtic’s enthralling win over Hearts veered from tragedy to farce.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player ratings: Mixed bag of marks - 8 for real deal midfielder but three players lands 5s]]></title>
        <id>3890160</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-player-ratings-mixed-bag-of-marks-8-for-real-deal-midfielder-but-three-players-lands-5s-3890160"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T14:22:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic edged Hearts in a seven-goal thriller at Tynecastle Park to cement their position at the top of the Scottish Premiership. Here is how the Celtic players rated ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Elder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player ratings: Only one defender with pass marks as two stand-outs score 8s in 4-3 win over Hearts]]></title>
        <id>3890160</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-player-ratings-only-one-defender-with-pass-marks-as-two-stand-outs-score-8s-in-4-3-win-over-hearts-3890160"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T14:22:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic edged Hearts in a seven-goal thriller at Tynecastle Park to cement their position at the top of the Scottish Premiership. Here is how the Celtic players rated ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Elder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton fumes over VAR claiming Celtic defeated Hearts and video technology at Tynecastle]]></title>
        <id>e8e3b07ea8b08038539f03cd5a6c1a90</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23070686.chris-sutton-fumes-var-claiming-celtic-defeated-hearts-video-technology-tynecastle/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T13:54:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CHRIS SUTTON has vented his VAR frustration on Twitter following Celtic's victory over Hearts at Tynecastle today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic edge enthralling contest with Hearts as VAR barges its way onto centre stage]]></title>
        <id>44a73fbb4c85c6039b58ef6d1f684e0e</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23070664.celtic-edge-enthralling-contest-hearts-var-barges-way-onto-centre-stage/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T13:32:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VAR, VAR, glorious VAR. Or notorious, depending on your point of view. What was certain is that down at Tynecastle, the newly introduced technology played a central role in an enthralling contest between Hearts and Celtic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player ratings v Hearts as Giakoumakis and Jenz have contrasting afternoon during VAR chaos - Glasgow Live]]></title>
        <id>1617132654</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiS2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmdsYXNnb3dsaXZlLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2NlbHRpYy1wbGF5ZXItcmF0aW5ncy12LWhlYXJ0cy0yNTMzMDMxONIBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T13:32:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player ratings v Hearts as Giakoumakis and Jenz have contrasting afternoon during VAR chaos  Glasgow Live
Hearts 3 Celtic 4 RECAP: Ange's entertainers edge thriller at Tynecastle  Daily Record
Hearts vs Celtic: Live stream, TV channel, PPV, ref and team news  Football Scotland
VAR controversy as Hearts benefit, two big calls against Celtic  The Celtic Star
Hearts 3-4 Celtic: Greg Taylor's first league goal for league leaders sees them edge breathless thriller  Sky Sports
View Full coverage on Google News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Celtic talkers as champions come out on top of ding-dong battle at Tynecastle]]></title>
        <id>d99449d8f654b48232baa9050076a92e</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23070659.three-celtic-talkers-champions-come-top-ding-dong-battle-tynecastle/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T13:29:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou was fairly dismissive of the impact that VAR’s introduction would have on the Premiership but this encounter at Tynecastle demonstrated that the technology will have knock-on effects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hearts 3 Celtic 4 RECAP: Ange's entertainers edge thriller at Tynecastle - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEJ_EUo8mq5pxZ6tuWjxI9qsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiX2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvaGVhcnRzLXZzLWNlbHRpYy1saXZlLXNjb3JlLTI4Mjk2MDE30gEA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T13:01:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hearts 3 Celtic 4 RECAP: Ange's entertainers edge thriller at Tynecastle  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VAR controversy as Hearts benefit, two big calls against Celtic - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CBMiWWh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vdmFyLWNvbnRyb3ZlcnN5LWFzLWhlYXJ0cy1iZW5lZml0LXR3by1iaWctY2FsbHMtYWdhaW5zdC1jZWx0aWMv0gFdaHR0cHM6Ly90aGVjZWx0aWNzdGFyLmNvbS92YXItY29udHJvdmVyc3ktYXMtaGVhcnRzLWJlbmVmaXQtdHdvLWJpZy1jYWxscy1hZ2FpbnN0LWNlbHRpYy9hbXAv</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiWWh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vdmFyLWNvbnRyb3ZlcnN5LWFzLWhlYXJ0cy1iZW5lZml0LXR3by1iaWctY2FsbHMtYWdhaW5zdC1jZWx0aWMv0gFdaHR0cHM6Ly90aGVjZWx0aWNzdGFyLmNvbS92YXItY29udHJvdmVyc3ktYXMtaGVhcnRzLWJlbmVmaXQtdHdvLWJpZy1jYWxscy1hZ2FpbnN0LWNlbHRpYy9hbXAv?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T12:35:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VAR controversy as Hearts benefit, two big calls against Celtic  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch the goals from Celtic FC Women’s 4-0 win over Dundee United - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEF3tJZWrfDrP8rbxcx98orYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiW2h0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vd2F0Y2gtdGhlLWdvYWxzLWZyb20tY2VsdGljLWZjLXdvbWVucy00LTAtd2luLW92ZXItZHVuZGVlLXVuaXRlZC_SAQA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T10:36:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Watch the goals from Celtic FC Women’s 4-0 win over Dundee United  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic teams news vs Hearts confirmed as Ange Postecoglou makes changes]]></title>
        <id>4b4218bc3e9106449e4c0e24b1ba30e3</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23070419.celtic-teams-news-vs-hearts-confirmed-ange-postecoglou-makes-changes/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T10:17:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU has named his Celtic team to take on Hearts in the Scottish Premiership.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton sends VAR 'calamity' warning to fans as Celtic hero hits out at 'amateurs' running technology]]></title>
        <id>d44adb1be04316847191176f513023f0</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23070377.chris-sutton-sends-var-calamity-warning-fans-celtic-hero-hits-amateurs-running-technology/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T09:47:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CHRIS SUTTON believes the introduction of VAR to Scottish football has "calamity written all over it".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hearts and Celtic squad news ahead of Scottish Premiership clash]]></title>
        <id>2afc0556f6028ff32acb8f94553bb267</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23070358.hearts-celtic-squad-news-ahead-scottish-premiership-clash/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T09:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andy Halliday, Josh Ginnelly and Michael Smith have all trained ahead of Hearts’ clash with Celtic and could be in contention to play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Caldwell to land Exeter job but not in time to face old Celtic mate Scott Brown - Scottish Daily Express]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEP6TAFHtacdtvV-TPsRBw70qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowi76vCzCYyccDMKvzuAc</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiXGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnNjb3R0aXNoZGFpbHlleHByZXNzLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2dhcnktY2FsZHdlbGwtbGFuZC1leGV0ZXItam9iLTI4MzAyNjg20gEA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T09:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Caldwell to land Exeter job but not in time to face old Celtic mate Scott Brown  Scottish Daily Express]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Caldwell to land Exeter job but not in time to face old Celtic mate Scott Brown - Scottish Daily Express]]></title>
        <id>CBMiXGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnNjb3R0aXNoZGFpbHlleHByZXNzLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2dhcnktY2FsZHdlbGwtbGFuZC1leGV0ZXItam9iLTI4MzAyNjg20gFgaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuc2NvdHRpc2hkYWlseWV4cHJlc3MuY28udWsvc3BvcnQvZm9vdGJhbGwvZ2FyeS1jYWxkd2VsbC1sYW5kLWV4ZXRlci1qb2ItMjgzMDI2ODYuYW1w</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiXGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnNjb3R0aXNoZGFpbHlleHByZXNzLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2dhcnktY2FsZHdlbGwtbGFuZC1leGV0ZXItam9iLTI4MzAyNjg20gFgaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuc2NvdHRpc2hkYWlseWV4cHJlc3MuY28udWsvc3BvcnQvZm9vdGJhbGwvZ2FyeS1jYWxkd2VsbC1sYW5kLWV4ZXRlci1qb2ItMjgzMDI2ODYuYW1w?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T09:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Caldwell to land Exeter job but not in time to face old Celtic mate Scott Brown  Scottish Daily Express]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hearts v Celtic late team news, probable line-ups, TV channel: More than ten players missing, Jota situation improving]]></title>
        <id>3890009</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/hearts/hearts-v-celtic-late-team-news-probable-line-ups-tv-channel-more-than-ten-players-missing-jota-situation-improving-3890009"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T08:24:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Both Hearts and Celtic are missing a number of players for this lunchtime’s cinch Premiership match at Tynecastle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angus Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rocco Vata Celtic exit talk addressed by Postecoglou with Callum McGregor example after 'valuation' - Glasgow Live]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEL_aNfWERxISR_WoXhrqVb4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow96D9CjDOy_QCMPvp0wU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiSGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmdsYXNnb3dsaXZlLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L3JvY2NvLXZhdGEtY2VsdGljLWV4aXQtdGFsay0yNTMyOTA4NdIBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T07:21:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rocco Vata Celtic exit talk addressed by Postecoglou with Callum McGregor example after 'valuation'  Glasgow Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou reflects on 500 days in charge of Celtic - 'we all have a ticking clock against us']]></title>
        <id>3889943</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/ange-postecoglou-reflects-on-500-days-in-charge-of-celtic-we-all-have-a-ticking-clock-against-us-3889943"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T06:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s difficult to credit the reaction to the news that Ange Postecoglou was the new manager of Celtic – certainly in view of the impact he has enjoyed since.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alan Pattullo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What channel is Hearts v Celtic on? Kick-off time, TV details, referee and VAR officials]]></title>
        <id>3889970</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/what-channel-is-hearts-v-celtic-on-kick-off-time-tv-details-referee-and-var-officials-3889970"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hearts and Celtic have the historic distinction of being the first clubs to feature in a live televised Scottish Premiership match involving VAR on Saturday lunchtime.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Elder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou's 500 days of Celtic have felt like 500 minutes as relentless boss reflects on journey - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEEC_IAeTrkl0PS-ZH1I5gfQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiZWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvYW5nZS1wb3N0ZWNvZ2xvdXMtNTAwLWRheXMtY2VsdGljLTI4Mjk5NzY50gEA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou's 500 days of Celtic have felt like 500 minutes as relentless boss reflects on journey  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Gio van Bronckhorst get Rangers fans back onside after they turned to the boos? Saturday Jury - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiED5XH9eFKdI3DIFr41tHakEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiY2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvY2FuLWdpby12YW4tYnJvbmNraG9yc3QtcmFuZ2Vycy0yODMwMTM5MdIBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will Gio van Bronckhorst get Rangers fans back onside after they turned to the boos? Saturday Jury  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Having lost Ben Doak to Liverpool how can Celtic keep Rocco Vata? - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiENPDxX2jpuP0_ADtDk-StiAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiW2h0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vaGF2aW5nLWxvc3QtYmVuLWRvYWstdG8tbGl2ZXJwb29sLWhvdy1jYW4tY2VsdGljLWtlZXAtcm9jY28tdmF0YS_SAQA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T04:26:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having lost Ben Doak to Liverpool how can Celtic keep Rocco Vata?  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star reacts after partner sends Karim Benzema cheeky message following Ballon d'Or win]]></title>
        <id>3889925</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-star-reacts-after-partner-sends-karim-benzema-cheeky-message-following-ballon-dor-win-3889925"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It might have escaped Karim Benzema’s notice amid the wave of congratulation messages following his Ballon d’Or accolade earlier this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alan Pattullo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou explains why Celtic's Reo Hatate may be overlooked for Japan World Cup squad]]></title>
        <id>3889907</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/ange-postecoglou-explains-why-celtics-reo-hatate-may-be-overlooked-for-japan-world-cup-squad-3889907"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou believes there is still more to come from Reo Hatate as the in-form midfielder prepares to learn his World Cup fate with Japan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alan Pattullo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou insists Reo Hatate is Celtic key man regardless of whether World Cup dream comes true - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiENyhSrPffRnbA7NFtpjBTkkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiZ2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvYW5nZS1wb3N0ZWNvZ2xvdS1pbnNpc3RzLXJlby1oYXRhdGUtMjgzMDA0MDLSAQA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou insists Reo Hatate is Celtic key man regardless of whether World Cup dream comes true  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou reflects on Celtic journey as he ticks off 500 days in the dugout - Celtic Way]]></title>
        <id>CAIiED2yYfLlXoSuqXX7FYUMlYIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowsJStCzC9n8UDMNiMswc</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMibWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmNlbHRpY3dheS5jby51ay9uZXdzLzIzMDY5NDYxLmFuZ2UtcG9zdGVjb2dsb3UtcmVmbGVjdHMtY2VsdGljLWpvdXJuZXktdGlja3Mtb2ZmLTUwMC1kYXlzLWR1Z291dC_SAQA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou reflects on Celtic journey as he ticks off 500 days in the dugout  Celtic Way]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou rates Reo Hatate’s World Cup chances, and explains why he will be impossible for Japan to ignore in future]]></title>
        <id>9eb7f8dae624ca782fe9dbab560d56f6</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23069120.ange-postecoglou-rates-reo-hatates-world-cup-chances-explains-will-impossible-japan-ignore-future/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU says that in-form Reo Hatate should be aiming for a place in Japan’s World Cup squad, and has backed the midfielder to prove he belongs at such a level in the long term by continuing his rapid improvement with Celtic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moritz Jenz targets long-term Celtic stay as he says partnership with Cameron Carter-Vickers can last for ‘many, many more seasons’]]></title>
        <id>32b8d070258861ec176e66fed00572d9</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23069332.moritz-jenz-targets-long-term-celtic-stay-says-partnership-cameron-carter-vickers-can-last-many-many-seasons/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TECHNICALLY, Moritz Jenz is only due to be at Celtic until the end of the season. If he has it his way though, the loan deal that brought him to the club from Lorient will soon be traded for something a little more permanent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou reflects on Celtic journey as he ticks off 500 days in the dugout]]></title>
        <id>aff5bbaeb751376c79e32dbc6a66b2a2</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23069461.ange-postecoglou-reflects-celtic-journey-ticks-off-500-days-dugout/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT has now been 500 days since Ange Postecoglou became manager of Celtic. At times, he feels it has flown by. At others, the Celtic manager has felt every minute of it. But the only thing that is certain is that he wouldn’t have swapped it for the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic team news: 2 confirmed missing vs Hearts but Postecoglou predicts &#039;strong&#039; XI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-team-news-2-confirmed-out-vs-hearts-but-ange-postecoglou-predicts-strong-eleven/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-team-news-2-confirmed-out-vs-hearts-but-ange-postecoglou-predicts-strong-eleven/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T20:51:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has confirmed that Celtic duo David Turnbull and Jota will again not be involved in tomorrow’s match against Hearts but is buoyant about the strength of his available squad regardless. Both Jota and Turnbull have been missing for a number of matches despite consistently hopeful updates about imminent returns. But Postecoglou is relaxed ...
The post Celtic team news: 2 confirmed missing vs Hearts but Postecoglou predicts &#039;strong&#039; XI appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Rangers bosses in starkly different responses to the arrival of VAR in Scottish football]]></title>
        <id>3889952</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-and-rangers-bosses-in-starkly-different-responses-to-the-arrival-of-var-in-scottish-football-3889952"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T20:41:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Rangers are no strangers to VAR but both will experience it for the first time in a domestic setting when the technology makes its Scottish football debut this weekend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Elder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pundit claims ex-Celtic manager Neil Lennon interested in N Ireland vacancy]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/pundit-claims-ex-celtic-manager-neil-lennon-interested-in-n-ireland-vacancy/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/pundit-claims-ex-celtic-manager-neil-lennon-interested-in-n-ireland-vacancy/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T20:20:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic manager Neil Lennon is reportedly interested in the N Ireland vacancy, according to a pundit. Ian Baraclough was sacked after a dismal period in charge and the IFA are already looking for his replacement. Ex-Celtic and Partick Thistle goalkeeper Alan Rough has said that he thinks that Lennon is a ready-made replacement and Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hearts comments suggest Celtic will be kicked all over the pitch tomorrow; could backfire again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/hearts-comments-suggest-celtic-will-be-kicked-all-over-the-pitch-tomorrow-could-backfire-again/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/hearts-comments-suggest-celtic-will-be-kicked-all-over-the-pitch-tomorrow-could-backfire-again/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T19:43:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s another weekend, it’s another Scottish Premiership player talking about picking up fouls and cards as a viable tactic to stop Celtic in their tracks. This time it’s Hearts defender Alex Cochrane making it clear that his team will be right in the faces of the Bhoys tomorrow, picking up fouls and potentially cautions from ...
The post Hearts comments suggest Celtic will be kicked all over the pitch tomorrow; could backfire again appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic manager Neil Lennon  a 'ready-made replacement' for Northern Ireland job]]></title>
        <id>8063b996c2b9106b5e854bf30ff68120</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23069787.former-celtic-manager-neil-lennon-ready-made-replacement-northern-ireland-job/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T19:19:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic manager Neil Lennon has been touted as a 'ready-made replacement' for sacked Northern Ireland manager Ian Baraclough.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou dismisses Celtic appointment rumour - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEPcqAcG9KX8LiOiuexCfrX0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4KKJCzCv9JoDMICkoAY</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiT2h0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljYmhveXMuY29tLzIwMjIvMTAvMjEvYW5nZS1kaXNtaXNzZXMtY2VsdGljLWFwcG9pbnRtZW50LXJ1bW91ci_SAQA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T19:11:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou dismisses Celtic appointment rumour  The Celtic Bhoys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic Rising – Realising I was a Jimmy McGrory Celtic baby]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/the-celtic-rising-realising-i-was-a-jimmy-mcgrory-celtic-baby/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/the-celtic-rising-realising-i-was-a-jimmy-mcgrory-celtic-baby/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T19:06:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ll sometimes see a Celtic account on social media asking you to name the Celtic manager on the day you were born. I’ve always answered Jock Stein, but reading an advance copy of David Potter’s new book The Celtic Rising ~ 1965: The Year Jock Stein Changed Everything on Kindle (available next week in hardback Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“I’d Much Rather Be Talking About Football” Ange Isn’t Buying the VAR Hype]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/id-much-rather-be-talking-about-football-ange-isnt-buying-the-var-hype/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/id-much-rather-be-talking-about-football-ange-isnt-buying-the-var-hype/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T19:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VAR is set to be introduced to the Scottish game on Friday night, with the clash at Easter Road between Hibs and St Johnstone the first match to use the technology. Celtic are up next, with a 12.30 kick-off in the capital. VAR has been a major talking point for a few weeks now, but […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou talks Celtic&#039;s strategy as cash-rich teams show interest in Rocco Vata]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/ange-postecoglou-talks-celtics-strategy-as-cash-rich-teams-show-interest-in-rocco-vata/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/ange-postecoglou-talks-celtics-strategy-as-cash-rich-teams-show-interest-in-rocco-vata/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T18:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou was asked about the pathway from Celtic’s youth team into the senior set-up today in the wake of reports that teams from bigger leagues are showing interest in Rocca Vata. Vata is considered to be one of the top prospects coming through the academy and B team right now, a fact that has ...
The post Ange Postecoglou talks Celtic&#039;s strategy as cash-rich teams show interest in Rocco Vata appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou talks Celtic’s strategy as cash-rich teams show interest in Rocco Vata - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CBMif2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL2NlbHRpYy15b3V0aC9hbmdlLXBvc3RlY29nbG91LXRhbGtzLWNlbHRpY3Mtc3RyYXRlZ3ktYXMtY2FzaC1yaWNoLXRlYW1zLXNob3ctaW50ZXJlc3QtaW4tcm9jY28tdmF0YS_SAYMBaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuNjdoYWlsaGFpbC5jb20vY2VsdGljLXlvdXRoL2FuZ2UtcG9zdGVjb2dsb3UtdGFsa3MtY2VsdGljcy1zdHJhdGVneS1hcy1jYXNoLXJpY2gtdGVhbXMtc2hvdy1pbnRlcmVzdC1pbi1yb2Njby12YXRhLz9hbXA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMif2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL2NlbHRpYy15b3V0aC9hbmdlLXBvc3RlY29nbG91LXRhbGtzLWNlbHRpY3Mtc3RyYXRlZ3ktYXMtY2FzaC1yaWNoLXRlYW1zLXNob3ctaW50ZXJlc3QtaW4tcm9jY28tdmF0YS_SAYMBaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuNjdoYWlsaGFpbC5jb20vY2VsdGljLXlvdXRoL2FuZ2UtcG9zdGVjb2dsb3UtdGFsa3MtY2VsdGljcy1zdHJhdGVneS1hcy1jYXNoLXJpY2gtdGVhbXMtc2hvdy1pbnRlcmVzdC1pbi1yb2Njby12YXRhLz9hbXA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T18:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou talks Celtic’s strategy as cash-rich teams show interest in Rocco Vata  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Soul with Billy McGuinness Aslan]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-soul-with-billy-mcguinness-aslan/</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-soul-with-billy-mcguinness-aslan/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T18:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billy McGuinness from Aslan joins More than 90 Minutes Editor, Andrew Milne on the Celtic Soul Podcast. Billy gives an update on Christy Dignam and Aslan’s plans. While looking back at the bands highs and lows over the past 40 years. https://celticfanzine.com/product/more-than-90-minutes-issue-123-print-edition-pre-order/ Back in 80’s Ireland was a great place for music as record companies […]
The post Celtic Soul with Billy McGuinness Aslan appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero Chris Sutton makes sarcastic VAR prediction ahead of technology's debut]]></title>
        <id>1b85c3b03a2844d875b9773ed0f0b1d9</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23069679.celtic-hero-chris-sutton-makes-sarcastic-var-prediction-ahead-technologys-debut/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T18:21:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TONIGHT'S match between Hibernian and St Johnstone will be a momentous one for Scottish football - as it is the first time that VAR will be in use in the cinch Premiership.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moritz Jenz beams as he learns about his new nickname from Celtic fans in class Friday moment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/moritz-jenz-beams-as-he-learns-about-his-new-nickname-from-celtic-supporters/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/moritz-jenz-beams-as-he-learns-about-his-new-nickname-from-celtic-supporters/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T17:40:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A beaming Moritz Jenz was delighted to hear he has been given a kind nickname from some Celtic supporters already after interacting with fan podcast Homebhoys at today’s media event. The HomeBhoys were one of the fan-led outlets in attendance to question Jenz and manager Ange Postecoglou, as usual, prompting interesting and entertaining answers. Asked ...
The post Moritz Jenz beams as he learns about his new nickname from Celtic fans in class Friday moment appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic in line for windfall as Manchester United eye swoop for Jeremie Frimpong]]></title>
        <id>13cd6455e33407733f2d66b0ce0525d1</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23069637.celtic-line-windfall-manchester-united-eye-swoop-jeremie-frimpong/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T17:31:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC could be in line for a windfall after Manchester United were linked with a move for Jeremie Frimpong.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic v Hearts; Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-v-hearts-everything-you-need-to-know-2/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-v-hearts-everything-you-need-to-know-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T17:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC travel to Tynecastle on Saturday for a 12:30 kick-off in the capital. It’ll be the second Scottish game to use VAR; the first Celtic will compete in. Obviously, Celtic have had some experience with the equipment before, using it in Europe over the past couple of years. Its highly anticipated introduction has come sooner […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremie Frimpong is Manchester United transfer 'target' as former Celtic star catches Erik Ten Hag's eye - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEHLNfQSPkeBmsuDErInzY9gqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMib2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvamVyZW1pZS1mcmltcG9uZy1tYW5jaGVzdGVyLXVuaXRlZC10cmFuc2Zlci0yODMwMDA0NdIBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T16:57:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremie Frimpong is Manchester United transfer 'target' as former Celtic star catches Erik Ten Hag's eye  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic team to wear special Adidas tops at Tynecastle in support of LGBTQ+ communities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-team-to-wear-special-adidas-tops-at-tynecastle-in-support-of-lgbtq-communities/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-team-to-wear-special-adidas-tops-at-tynecastle-in-support-of-lgbtq-communities/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T16:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are showing support and raising money for LGBTQ+ communities this weekend by taking part in the ‘LOVE UNITES’ and Rainbow Laces campaigns. Love Unites is an endeavour organised by club kit manufacturers Adidas and has involved the creation of a special ‘Tiro x Pride Collection’ of training gear, which was released online for purchase ...
The post Celtic team to wear special Adidas tops at Tynecastle in support of LGBTQ+ communities appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic team to wear special Adidas tops at Tynecastle in support of LGBTQ+ communities - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEJzZD-LlRJrT37D5OlwwaXoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMLbFpgY</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMidmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL25ld3MvY2VsdGljLXRlYW0tdG8td2Vhci1zcGVjaWFsLWFkaWRhcy10b3BzLWF0LXR5bmVjYXN0bGUtaW4tc3VwcG9ydC1vZi1sZ2J0cS1jb21tdW5pdGllcy_SAQA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T16:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic team to wear special Adidas tops at Tynecastle in support of LGBTQ+ communities  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Ange Postecoglou’s Hilarious Reaction to VAR Questions]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/video-ange-postecoglous-hilarious-reaction-to-var-questions/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/video-ange-postecoglous-hilarious-reaction-to-var-questions/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T16:13:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou couldn’t hide his amusement at the chat surrounding VAR in Scottish football and it’s introduction. With the cameras set to be turned on this weekend, Celtic will get their first taste of Scottish Football VAR and the media were pressing Ange for his take. The Australian let out and audible snigger at the […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hit with UEFA fine over pyro display as RB Leipzig also punished]]></title>
        <id>e37857ceba951a164d16cb631421ad6f</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23069347.celtic-hit-uefa-fine-pyro-display-rb-leipzig-also-punished/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T15:56:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have been hit with a UEFA fine after the fan pyro display ahead of the Champions League match against RB Leipzig.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic slapped with fine for UCL pyro show against RB Leipzig]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-slapped-with-fine-for-ucl-pyro-show-against-rb-leipzig/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-slapped-with-fine-for-ucl-pyro-show-against-rb-leipzig/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T15:55:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UEFA have slapped Celtic with a fine after pyrotechnics were set off in the away end during the Champions League defeat against RB Leipzig earlier this month. The governing body enjoy handing down punishment for infringements against teams, regardless of whether it enhances the atmosphere or not.The spectacular scenes in the away end were not Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic slapped with fine for UCL pyro show against RB Leipzig - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEJa525JS3soSZAo2HWbDo5oqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiWGh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vY2VsdGljLXNsYXBwZWQtd2l0aC1maW5lLWZvci11Y2wtcHlyby1zaG93LWFnYWluc3QtcmItbGVpcHppZy_SAQA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T15:55:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic slapped with fine for UCL pyro show against RB Leipzig  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC FINED £17,000 BY UEFA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-fined-17000-by-uefa/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-fined-17000-by-uefa/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T15:16:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have been hit with another fine by Europe’s ruling body following their fans’ conduct in the 3-1 Champions League Group F loss to RB Leipzig in Germany earlier this month. The Hoops copped a £17,120 penalty for their pyrotechnic display in the travelling supporters’ end at the Red Bull Arena. It’s the second fine [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers urged Kieran Tierney to reject Arsenal move]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/brendan-rodgers-urged-kieran-tierney-to-reject-arsenal-move/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/brendan-rodgers-urged-kieran-tierney-to-reject-arsenal-move/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T15:11:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic defender Kieran Tierney has revealed that Brendan Rodgers instructed him to reject the opportunity to join Arsenal. The Irishman believed that he could take Tierney to the next level of his game if he stayed in Glasgow.Rodgers arrived in May 2016, after Tierney had enjoyed a breakthrough season under Ronny Deila. The ex-Liverpool Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers urged Kieran Tierney to reject Arsenal move - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEKMsCcYAfULRILvdhGy7tPUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiVmh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vYnJlbmRhbi1yb2RnZXJzLXVyZ2VkLWtpZXJhbi10aWVybmV5LXRvLXJlamVjdC1hcnNlbmFsLW1vdmUv0gEA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T15:11:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers urged Kieran Tierney to reject Arsenal move  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JOTA ROLLERCOASTER]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/jota-rollercoaster/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/jota-rollercoaster/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T15:03:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE BAD NEWS is that fans’ favourite Filipe Jota has no chance of playing against Hearts at Tynecastle tomorrow. THE GOOD NEWS is that the flamboyant Portuguese winger could make his return in the Champions League Group F encounter against Shakhtar Donetsk at Parkhead on Tuesday night. Central defenders Carl Starfelt and Stephen Welsh remain [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Receive Another UEFA Fine - CeltsAreHere]]></title>
        <id>CBMiOmh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtcmVjZWl2ZS1hbm90aGVyLXVlZmEtZmluZS_SAT5odHRwczovL2NlbHRzYXJlaGVyZS5jb20vY2VsdGljLXJlY2VpdmUtYW5vdGhlci11ZWZhLWZpbmUvYW1wLw</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiOmh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtcmVjZWl2ZS1hbm90aGVyLXVlZmEtZmluZS_SAT5odHRwczovL2NlbHRzYXJlaGVyZS5jb20vY2VsdGljLXJlY2VpdmUtYW5vdGhlci11ZWZhLWZpbmUvYW1wLw?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T14:42:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Receive Another UEFA Fine  CeltsAreHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jota injury boost for Celtic as winger given 'a chance' of making big game return]]></title>
        <id>3889466</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/jota-injury-boost-for-celtic-as-winger-given-a-chance-of-making-big-game-return-3889466"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T14:02:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic winger Jota will miss the weekend trip to Hearts but could return for the Champions League showdown with Shakhtar Donetsk in midweek.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Elder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic injury update as Jota and David Turnbull given 'closest' assessment]]></title>
        <id>0bd6b4d67fe14fbcba46921c8e382b86</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23068262.ange-postecoglou-issues-jota-injury-update-celtic-winger-has-chance/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T12:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Australian has revealed the injury status of the two players]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's Cameron Carter-Vickers tipped for World Cup role by US legend]]></title>
        <id>95c5cfeaf03da13e52da86f754546179</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23068099.celtics-cameron-carter-vickers-tipped-international-role-us-legend/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T12:24:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The American centre-back will be hoping to be part of his country's World Cup squad, and a former international feels the Hoops defender could have a starring role at the tournament]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Confirm James Forrest FIFA Recognition - CeltsAreHere]]></title>
        <id>CBMiR2h0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtY29uZmlybS1qYW1lcy1mb3JyZXN0LWZpZmEtcmVjb2duaXRpb24v0gFLaHR0cHM6Ly9jZWx0c2FyZWhlcmUuY29tL2NlbHRpYy1jb25maXJtLWphbWVzLWZvcnJlc3QtZmlmYS1yZWNvZ25pdGlvbi9hbXAv</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiR2h0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtY29uZmlybS1qYW1lcy1mb3JyZXN0LWZpZmEtcmVjb2duaXRpb24v0gFLaHR0cHM6Ly9jZWx0c2FyZWhlcmUuY29tL2NlbHRpYy1jb25maXJtLWphbWVzLWZvcnJlc3QtZmlmYS1yZWNvZ25pdGlvbi9hbXAv?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T11:27:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Confirm James Forrest FIFA Recognition  CeltsAreHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['You never know in football' - Kieran Tierney opens up on possible emotional Celtic return]]></title>
        <id>ef3b2d7a124142e88cfdaf874c7083d2</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23067631.kieran-tierney-potential-celtic-return-you-never-know-football/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T10:51:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Scotland international was speaking on a variety of topics before the discussion turned to whether he would ever once again pull on the Hoops]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Si Ferry reveals he got 'chucked out' of Glasgow chippy Da Vinci's ran by James McFadden's parents]]></title>
        <id>e7206575c0eef2842b4db2ef69fa1caa</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23067543.si-ferry-reveals-got-chucked-out-glasgow-chippy-da-vincis-ran-james-mcfaddens-parents/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T10:31:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast star Si Ferry has revealed he got "chucked out" of a Glasgow chippy run by the parents of former footballer James McFadden.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premier Sports Cup semi-final fixture date and times confirmed]]></title>
        <id>4eb8f8a93858229946b13730cef020b6</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23067466.premier-sports-cup-semi-final-fixture-date-times-confirmed/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T10:16:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE Premier Sports Cup semi-final fixtures have been confirmed for mid-January.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic v Kilmarnock and Rangers v Aberdeen Premier Sports Cup semi-final dates, times and ticket information revealed]]></title>
        <id>3888860</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic-v-kilmarnock-and-rangers-v-aberdeen-premier-sports-cup-semi-final-dates-times-and-ticket-information-revealed-3888860"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T10:10:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Scottish Professional Football League has confirmed the dates and kick-off times of the Premier Sports Cup semi-finals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premier Sports Cup Semi-Final Date Confirmed - afc.co.uk]]></title>
        <id>CBMiTmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmFmYy5jby51ay8yMDIyLzEwLzIxL3ByZW1pZXItc3BvcnRzLWN1cC1zZW1pLWZpbmFsLWRhdGUtY29uZmlybWVkL9IBAA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiTmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmFmYy5jby51ay8yMDIyLzEwLzIxL3ByZW1pZXItc3BvcnRzLWN1cC1zZW1pLWZpbmFsLWRhdGUtY29uZmlybWVkL9IBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T09:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Premier Sports Cup Semi-Final Date Confirmed  afc.co.uk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kieran Tierney on Potential Celtic Return - CeltsAreHere]]></title>
        <id>CBMiQ2h0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9raWVyYW4tdGllcm5leS1vbi1wb3RlbnRpYWwtY2VsdGljLXJldHVybi_SAUdodHRwczovL2NlbHRzYXJlaGVyZS5jb20va2llcmFuLXRpZXJuZXktb24tcG90ZW50aWFsLWNlbHRpYy1yZXR1cm4vYW1wLw</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiQ2h0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9raWVyYW4tdGllcm5leS1vbi1wb3RlbnRpYWwtY2VsdGljLXJldHVybi_SAUdodHRwczovL2NlbHRzYXJlaGVyZS5jb20va2llcmFuLXRpZXJuZXktb24tcG90ZW50aWFsLWNlbHRpYy1yZXR1cm4vYW1wLw?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T09:47:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kieran Tierney on Potential Celtic Return  CeltsAreHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sir Rod Stewart poses with Celtic strip as he enjoys dinner at Glasgow restaurant - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEG0AiXt9cKe93VY5rzoOtCoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMMbNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiW2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL2VudGVydGFpbm1lbnQvY2VsZWJyaXR5L3Npci1yb2Qtc3Rld2FydC1wb3Nlcy1jZWx0aWMtMjgyOTQ5MzbSAQA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T09:08:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sir Rod Stewart poses with Celtic strip as he enjoys dinner at Glasgow restaurant  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Adidas in Outstanding ‘Pride’ Collaboration - CeltsAreHere]]></title>
        <id>CBMiTmh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtYW5kLWFkaWRhcy1pbi1vdXRzdGFuZGluZy1wcmlkZS1jb2xsYWJvcmF0aW9uL9IBUmh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtYW5kLWFkaWRhcy1pbi1vdXRzdGFuZGluZy1wcmlkZS1jb2xsYWJvcmF0aW9uL2FtcC8</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiTmh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtYW5kLWFkaWRhcy1pbi1vdXRzdGFuZGluZy1wcmlkZS1jb2xsYWJvcmF0aW9uL9IBUmh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtYW5kLWFkaWRhcy1pbi1vdXRzdGFuZGluZy1wcmlkZS1jb2xsYWJvcmF0aW9uL2FtcC8?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T08:58:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Adidas in Outstanding ‘Pride’ Collaboration  CeltsAreHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Killarney Celtic appoint Neilus Hayes as senior team manager - Independent.ie]]></title>
        <id>CBMihQFodHRwczovL3d3dy5pbmRlcGVuZGVudC5pZS9yZWdpb25hbHMva2VycnltYW4vc3BvcnQvc29jY2VyL2tpbGxhcm5leS1jZWx0aWMtYXBwb2ludC1uZWlsdXMtaGF5ZXMtYXMtc2VuaW9yLXRlYW0tbWFuYWdlci00MjA4NDQzMC5odG1s0gEA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMihQFodHRwczovL3d3dy5pbmRlcGVuZGVudC5pZS9yZWdpb25hbHMva2VycnltYW4vc3BvcnQvc29jY2VyL2tpbGxhcm5leS1jZWx0aWMtYXBwb2ludC1uZWlsdXMtaGF5ZXMtYXMtc2VuaW9yLXRlYW0tbWFuYWdlci00MjA4NDQzMC5odG1s0gEA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T08:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Killarney Celtic appoint Neilus Hayes as senior team manager  Independent.ie]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“He’s handling it well,” Postecoglou on O’Riley’s development - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEIw5PLtT3NF9PM0zGbpk260qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiUmh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vaGVzLWhhbmRsaW5nLWl0LXdlbGwtcG9zdGVjb2dsb3Utb24tb3JpbGV5cy1kZXZlbG9wbWVudC_SAQA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T06:42:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“He’s handling it well,” Postecoglou on O’Riley’s development  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joel Sked: VAR's introduction changes Scottish football forever tonight - but at what cost?]]></title>
        <id>3888010</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/joel-sked-vars-introduction-changes-scottish-football-forever-tonight-but-at-what-cost-3888010"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aberdeen v Hearts and Hibs v St Johnstone. Two October fixtures which wouldn’t usually be deemed as significant encounters so early on in the season. But this isn't any old season, this is one which will witness a seismic shift within the Scottish football landscape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Same old story as crazy kick-off times put armchair supporters above match-going punters]]></title>
        <id>0a9caeb1f6607ffaef41bca9fc14a9b4</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23065976.old-story-crazy-kick-off-times-puts-armchair-supporters-match-going-punters/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JUST to be clear at the outset, the prospect of an unusual 6.15pm kick-off for Celtic’s visit to Motherwell on Wednesday night was just fine and dandy by me. For journalists, midweek cup games – or more specifically, the threat of extra time and penalties – can be a fraught affair.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Callum McGregor’s Teenage Years and those Haircuts - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiENy7sFpnmqMUf8o2WKLB5zwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiUmh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vdmlkZW8tY2FsbHVtLW1jZ3JlZ29ycy10ZWVuYWdlLXllYXJzLWFuZC10aG9zZS1oYWlyY3V0cy_SAQA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T05:54:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Callum McGregor’s Teenage Years and those Haircuts  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kieran Tierney says Celtic plea from Brendan Rodgers kept Arsenal at bay - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEMw5YgXpffngs0jjcsWYp-kqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiZmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3Mva2llcmFuLXRpZXJuZXktcmV2ZWFscy1jZWx0aWMtcGxlYS0yODI5MjI2NNIBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kieran Tierney says Celtic plea from Brendan Rodgers kept Arsenal at bay  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robbie Neilson on Celtic and Rangers financial gap as Hearts chase top two - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEPWuT0RfM45qUkQWEvL-8YMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMia2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3Mvcm9iYmllLW5laWxzb24tY2VsdGljLXJhbmdlcnMtY2hhbXBpb25zLTI4MjkwNTQ40gEA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robbie Neilson on Celtic and Rangers financial gap as Hearts chase top two  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hearts players “need to take bookings” against Celtic says Cochrane]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/hearts-players-need-to-take-bookings-against-celtic-says-cochrane/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/hearts-players-need-to-take-bookings-against-celtic-says-cochrane/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T21:49:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hearts Manager Robbie Nelson earlier today previewed the match on Saturday when the high-flying Scottish Champions Celtic are the visitors to Tynecastle and the Hearts manager knows after watching the game at Fir Park last night that it is going to be no easy task trying to stop Glasgow Celtic from putting on a show.“It’s Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['We need our referees to go professional': Call for full-time official on eve of VAR's introduction to Scottish game]]></title>
        <id>3888303</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/hibs/we-need-our-referees-to-go-professional-call-for-full-time-official-on-eve-of-vars-introduction-to-scottish-game-3888303"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hibs manager Lee Johnson believes there is “a lot of improvement to be made” in the standard of Scottish officiating, saying the game would benefit if referees in the top flight go professional.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['We all want to play but we understand' - how Celtic players are reacting to Ange Postecoglou's squad rotation]]></title>
        <id>3888120</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/we-all-want-to-play-but-we-understand-how-celtic-players-are-reacting-to-ange-postecoglous-squad-rotation-3888120"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The old adage that you don't change a winning side does not apply to Celtic these days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Elder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Taylor says he didn’t need reminder to keep up his standards at Celtic as he praises left-back ‘rival’ Alexandro Bernabei]]></title>
        <id>8ef297b7b5c1cf278c2594e08b98d3d2</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23066166.greg-taylor-says-didnt-need-reminder-keep-standards-celtic-praises-left-back-rival-alexandro-bernabei/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FROM the first day he arrived at Celtic Park, Greg Taylor has been driven to prove he belongs there. As a relatively unheralded youngster signed from Kilmarnock, he went into every training session and every game knowing that he was fighting for his place at the club, let alone his place in the team.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My First Celtic Game: A Special Gift From Father To Son]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/my-first-celtic-game-a-special-gift-from-father-to-son/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/my-first-celtic-game-a-special-gift-from-father-to-son/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T21:06:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am told that my affinity with Celtic Football Club really began at the age of four. I was totally besotted with football and the time for selecting my supporting path had come. In truth, there was no decision to be made as I was heavily drawn towards Celtic and Ireland throughout my short life. Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My First Celtic Game: A Special Gift From Father To Son - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiECcxxw2NyFYKfhk6Y8-E5hYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiUWh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vbXktZmlyc3QtY2VsdGljLWdhbWUtYS1zcGVjaWFsLWdpZnQtZnJvbS1mYXRoZXItdG8tc29uL9IBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T21:06:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My First Celtic Game: A Special Gift From Father To Son  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Larkhall born Bobby Hogg, Celtic’s captain during WW2]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/larkhall-born-bobby-hogg-celtics-captain-during-ww2/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/larkhall-born-bobby-hogg-celtics-captain-during-ww2/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T20:34:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seldom have Celtic been better served than they way they were by Bobby Hogg who played something like 538 times for the club – a figure that puts him up there with Alec McNair and Billy McNeill for long service, but in Bobby’s case, so many of his appearances were in war-time football.He was born in Larkhall Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou goes into what "people on the outside" don&#039;t see when making Celtic decisions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-goes-into-what-people-on-the-outside-dont-see-when-making-celtic-decisions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-goes-into-what-people-on-the-outside-dont-see-when-making-celtic-decisions/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T20:11:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou was asked about his consistent rotation of the Celtic team last night and how much disciplines such as sports science help inform his decisions. Postecoglou has changed around half of his starting eleven in the last two matches, just a small part of a period that has seen a policy of using the ...
The post Ange Postecoglou goes into what "people on the outside" don&#039;t see when making Celtic decisions appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou goes into what “people on the outside” don’t see when making Celtic decisions - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEAWZDoIZ_Ad2wb09M2BnDwkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMLbFpgY</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMifGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL25ld3MvYW5nZS1wb3N0ZWNvZ2xvdS1nb2VzLWludG8td2hhdC1wZW9wbGUtb24tdGhlLW91dHNpZGUtZG9udC1zZWUtd2hlbi1tYWtpbmctY2VsdGljLWRlY2lzaW9ucy_SAQA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T20:11:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou goes into what “people on the outside” don’t see when making Celtic decisions  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oscar Gloukh to Celtic facing sliding doors moment as Maccabi Tel Aviv scramble to avoid cut price transfer - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEE-cxrUQi9QDCBxQjvQRcxMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiZmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3Mvb3NjYXItZ2xvdWtoLWNlbHRpYy1mYWNpbmctc2xpZGluZy0yODI5MjMxMdIBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T19:25:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oscar Gloukh to Celtic facing sliding doors moment as Maccabi Tel Aviv scramble to avoid cut price transfer  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scotland&#039;s cheaper version of VAR will be missing key technology as Celtic set for debut]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/scottish-footballs-cheaper-version-of-var-will-be-missing-key-technology-as-celtic-get-set-for-debut/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/scottish-footballs-cheaper-version-of-var-will-be-missing-key-technology-as-celtic-get-set-for-debut/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T18:41:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With VAR being introduced into Scottish football this week, it’s important to note what is and isn’t available to referees when determining big calls. Celtic’s match against Hearts this weekend will be the first time the Bhoys have experienced the system in a domestic match under the jurisdiction of the Scottish FA, although it was ...
The post Scotland&#039;s cheaper version of VAR will be missing key technology as Celtic set for debut appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou hints we&#039;re about to see more of Celtic signing with zero starts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/were-about-to-see-more-of-oliver-abildgaard-at-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/were-about-to-see-more-of-oliver-abildgaard-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou has addressed the subject of midfield balance in the absence of Callum McGregor, as well as his stance on slowly bedding in our clutch of summer signings. The Bhoys boss has been far more cautious exposing recent signings to first-team football than he was last year, with squad depth at the ...
The post Ange Postecoglou hints we&#039;re about to see more of Celtic signing with zero starts appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We’re about to see more of Oliver Abildgaard at Celtic - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEBWT1UeF_tgNY2NP6Tpwa40qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMLbFpgY</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiVmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL25ld3Mvd2VyZS1hYm91dC10by1zZWUtbW9yZS1vZi1vbGl2ZXItYWJpbGRnYWFyZC1hdC1jZWx0aWMv0gEA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re about to see more of Oliver Abildgaard at Celtic  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We’re about to see more of Oliver Abildgaard at Celtic - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CBMiVmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL25ld3Mvd2VyZS1hYm91dC10by1zZWUtbW9yZS1vZi1vbGl2ZXItYWJpbGRnYWFyZC1hdC1jZWx0aWMv0gFaaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuNjdoYWlsaGFpbC5jb20vbmV3cy93ZXJlLWFib3V0LXRvLXNlZS1tb3JlLW9mLW9saXZlci1hYmlsZGdhYXJkLWF0LWNlbHRpYy8_YW1w</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiVmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL25ld3Mvd2VyZS1hYm91dC10by1zZWUtbW9yZS1vZi1vbGl2ZXItYWJpbGRnYWFyZC1hdC1jZWx0aWMv0gFaaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuNjdoYWlsaGFpbC5jb20vbmV3cy93ZXJlLWFib3V0LXRvLXNlZS1tb3JlLW9mLW9saXZlci1hYmlsZGdhYXJkLWF0LWNlbHRpYy8_YW1w?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re about to see more of Oliver Abildgaard at Celtic  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Livingston boss David Martindale hopeful VAR can serve for fairer decisions against Celtic and Rangers]]></title>
        <id>95dfea58ccaa5852aa9aed500c37af6c</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23066272.livingston-boss-david-martindale-hopeful-var-can-serve-fairer-decisions-celtic-rangers/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T17:49:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Livingston manager David Martindale feels the introduction of VAR is perfect timing as his side prepare to travel to Ibrox.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["They were outstanding"; Robbie Neilson&#039;s Celtic verdict after scouting mission]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/they-were-outstanding-robbie-neilsons-celtic-verdict-ahead-of-tynecastle/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/they-were-outstanding-robbie-neilsons-celtic-verdict-ahead-of-tynecastle/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T17:40:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hearts boss Robbie Neilson is looking forward to facing the test of Celtic’s visit to Tynecastle on Saturday afternoon but has admitted being impressed by the Bhoys against Motherwell last night. Ange Postecoglou’s team were in rampant form, following up the 6-1 win over Hibernian on Saturday with a 4-0 cup thrashing at Fir Park. ...
The post "They were outstanding"; Robbie Neilson&#039;s Celtic verdict after scouting mission appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic On The Brink As Ange Is Shortlisted For Number 10: An Exclusive By Keith Jackass.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/10/articles-and-features/celtic-on-the-brink-as-ange-is-shortlisted-for-number-10-an-exclusive-by-keith-jackass/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/10/articles-and-features/celtic-on-the-brink-as-ange-is-shortlisted-for-number-10-an-exclusive-by-keith-jackass/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T17:36:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic On The Brink As Ange Is Shortlisted For Number 10: An Exclusive By Keith Jackass. Celtic is in turmoil tonight as sources in England confirm that Ange Postecoglou is being linked with a job in the most ruthless environment of all; he is “a serious contender” for the vacant post at Downing Street. If […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic On The Brink As Ange Is Shortlisted For Number 10: An Exclusive By Keith Jackass. - TheCelticBlog.com]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEKXKBwqATe_9nv7nayqOqFIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowne-jCzDg-bsDMLnLhQc</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMijwFodHRwczovL3RoZWNlbHRpY2Jsb2cuY29tLzIwMjIvMTAvYXJ0aWNsZXMtYW5kLWZlYXR1cmVzL2NlbHRpYy1vbi10aGUtYnJpbmstYXMtYW5nZS1pcy1zaG9ydGxpc3RlZC1mb3ItbnVtYmVyLTEwLWFuLWV4Y2x1c2l2ZS1ieS1rZWl0aC1qYWNrYXNzL9IBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T17:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic On The Brink As Ange Is Shortlisted For Number 10: An Exclusive By Keith Jackass.  TheCelticBlog.com]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange’s Latest One-Liner to the Media; ‘I Just Don’t Tell Them’]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/anges-latest-one-liner-to-the-media-i-just-dont-tell-them/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/anges-latest-one-liner-to-the-media-i-just-dont-tell-them/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T17:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU came out with another great one-liner after he was asked how he approached leaving certain players out of the starting XI. The question came after James Forrest was demoted to the bench after his hat-trick at the weekend. Asked how he approaches the subject of leaving players out Ange joked to The Scotsman: […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Written off Celtic striker finds form out on loan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/written-off-celtic-striker-finds-form-out-on-loan/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/written-off-celtic-striker-finds-form-out-on-loan/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-loan Celtic striker Albian Ajeti is finding form in Austria with Sturm Graz after scoring his third goal for his temporary side on Wednesday. The 25-year-old completed a move late in the summer transfer window, joining the Austrian Bundesliga club when his opportunities in Ange Postecoglou’s squad looked slim. Ajeti made a slow start to ...
The post Written off Celtic striker finds form out on loan appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic youngster Rocco Vata 'linked' with Manchester City,  Juventus and Arsenal]]></title>
        <id>b049db7670dfc7d9e55913def156a53f</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23066079.celtic-youngster-linked-host-top-european-clubs/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T16:29:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Hoops teenager has been making waves for the B team and has apparently caught the eye of several teams across the continent]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lafferty Finally Gets His Ten Match Ban And His Next Game Is Against Us.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/10/articles-and-features/lafferty-finally-gets-his-ten-match-ban-and-his-next-game-is-against-us/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/10/articles-and-features/lafferty-finally-gets-his-ten-match-ban-and-his-next-game-is-against-us/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T15:04:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SFA moves slowly, doesn’t it? But it does move, and it finally has. Kyle Lafferty has been given his ten match ban today, the one for abusing a Celtic fan with a sectarian slogan. It feels like we’ve been waiting for that longer than Liz Truss has been floundering in office; indeed, it happened […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lafferty Finally Gets His Ten Match Ban And His Next Game Is Against Us. - TheCelticBlog.com]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEMq5FbH7QgSqMa5--bi7lHwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowne-jCzDg-bsDMLnLhQc</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMigAFodHRwczovL3RoZWNlbHRpY2Jsb2cuY29tLzIwMjIvMTAvYXJ0aWNsZXMtYW5kLWZlYXR1cmVzL2xhZmZlcnR5LWZpbmFsbHktZ2V0cy1oaXMtdGVuLW1hdGNoLWJhbi1hbmQtaGlzLW5leHQtZ2FtZS1pcy1hZ2FpbnN0LXVzL9IBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T15:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lafferty Finally Gets His Ten Match Ban And His Next Game Is Against Us.  TheCelticBlog.com]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Longest Scottish football bans from Celtic's Bolingoli to Rangers' Covid 5 after Kyle Lafferty SFA hammering]]></title>
        <id>08138a9d4ea548dcf86e9dc272460237</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23063471.longest-scottish-football-bans-celtics-bolingoli-rangers-covid-5-kyle-lafferty-sfa-hammering/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T14:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYLE LAFFERTY has today been slapped with a ten-game ban by the Scottish FA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy Reacts to Getting More Celtic Minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/__trashed-89/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/__trashed-89/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T14:12:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy has been impressive over the past few weeks in a Celtic jersey and has admitted that the football the Hoops are playing is a joy. Ange Postecoglou knows the Australian international very well and was keen to bring someone of his expertise and talent to the club during the summer. With Callum McGregor […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The VAR “Information” Contains One Thing That Should Bother Celtic Fans.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/10/articles-and-features/the-var-information-contains-one-thing-that-should-bother-celtic-fans/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/10/articles-and-features/the-var-information-contains-one-thing-that-should-bother-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T14:11:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So the SPFL released a refresher on VAR today, to let people know what to expect from it. The news is pretty much as we expected it to be; it will cover four critical areas and no others. That’s the understanding most of us have had about the technology since discussions about it were introduced. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyle Lafferty's first Kilmarnock game after ban set to be vs Celtic in Premier Sports Cup semi-final]]></title>
        <id>85f037be17701ae956e6b8f2daaf24a3</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23063278.kyle-laffertys-first-kilmarnock-game-ban-set-vs-celtic-premier-sports-cup-semi-final/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T13:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYLE LAFFERTY looks set to face Celtic in his first game back after a ten-match ban.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arsenal legend claims ex-Celtic defender Kieran Tierney 'must fight for his place' at the club]]></title>
        <id>cb5d156a3bd8b2dcacf411b2ec2073fa</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23064884.arsenal-legend-claims-ex-celtic-defender-kieran-tierney-must-fight-place-club/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T13:32:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former Gunners player feels the Scotland international will have to work hard to remain in manager Mikel Arteta's plans]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are the VAR rules in Scotland? Where it can and cannot intervene]]></title>
        <id>3887674</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/what-are-the-var-rules-in-scotland-where-it-can-and-cannot-intervene-3887674"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T13:28:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VAR will be used in the Scottish Premiership for the first time this weekend, starting with Hibs v St Johnstone at Easter Road on Friday night.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Elder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Virgil Van Dijk Was Celtic’s Last Truly World Class Performer. Who Will Be Our Next One?]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/10/articles-and-features/virgil-van-dijk-was-celtics-last-truly-world-class-performer-who-will-be-our-next-one/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/10/articles-and-features/virgil-van-dijk-was-celtics-last-truly-world-class-performer-who-will-be-our-next-one/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T13:24:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I watched, as I’m sure most of us did, the game between Liverpool and Manchester City the other night with a great deal of admiration for the individual talents on display. Before the game, everyone who had an interest in the match was talking, it seemed to me, about just one player; the big City […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion: Ange Postecoglou’s Vision Coming to Life]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/opinion-ange-postecoglous-vision-coming-to-life/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/opinion-ange-postecoglous-vision-coming-to-life/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T12:57:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent weeks, Ange Postecoglou has been able to rotate the squad as he pleases, which is paying off for Celtic. Going back just over a month ago, there was criticism directed at the Celtic boss for the number of changes he made going into the league match against St Mirren before the international break. […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ineptitude of Scottish refereeing was on full display last night at Ibrox. Celtic should be worried on Saturday - Read Celtic]]></title>
        <id>CBMilQFodHRwczovL3JlYWRjZWx0aWMuY29tLzIwMjIvMTAvMjAvdGhlLWluZXB0aXR1ZGUtb2Ytc2NvdHRpc2gtcmVmZXJlZWluZy13YXMtb24tZnVsbC1kaXNwbGF5LWxhc3QtbmlnaHQtYXQtaWJyb3gtY2VsdGljLXNob3VsZC1iZS13b3JyaWVkLW9uLXNhdHVyZGF5L9IBAA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMilQFodHRwczovL3JlYWRjZWx0aWMuY29tLzIwMjIvMTAvMjAvdGhlLWluZXB0aXR1ZGUtb2Ytc2NvdHRpc2gtcmVmZXJlZWluZy13YXMtb24tZnVsbC1kaXNwbGF5LWxhc3QtbmlnaHQtYXQtaWJyb3gtY2VsdGljLXNob3VsZC1iZS13b3JyaWVkLW9uLXNhdHVyZGF5L9IBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T12:14:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ineptitude of Scottish refereeing was on full display last night at Ibrox. Celtic should be worried on Saturday  Read Celtic]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hearts vs Celtic on TV: Channel, kick-off time and live stream details for Premiership clash - Glasgow Live]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEMz_HhW6tZ6nM4bt97USnwkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow96D9CjDOy_QCMPvp0wU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiSGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmdsYXNnb3dsaXZlLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2hlYXJ0cy12cy1jZWx0aWMtdHYtY2hhbm5lbC0yNTMxMDU4N9IBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T11:57:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hearts vs Celtic on TV: Channel, kick-off time and live stream details for Premiership clash  Glasgow Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers rejects claim he 'stormed out' Leicester press conference]]></title>
        <id>c22ad5c837c5c33d95851a9edc42c470</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23064316.former-celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-rejects-claim-stormed-out-leicester-city-press-conference/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T11:39:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ex-Hoops manager has been having a tough season at the Premier League side]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sublime Hatate and O’Riley]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/sublime-hatate-and-oriley/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/sublime-hatate-and-oriley/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T11:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Again, half the goals came from the right wing, but the midfield engine was where the win came from at in Motherwell last night.  In this form, Reo Hatate is a sublime joy.  He was able to control play, take as much time as he wanted on the ball, and continually find angles for Celtic [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic loanee Albian Ajeti scores derby winning goal in Austria]]></title>
        <id>f0b77bf318454d94a558bb6ac169b560</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23064001.celtic-loanee-scores-derby-winning-goal-austria/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T10:57:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Swiss striker scored a crucial winner against Grazer AK in the Austrian Cup]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seamless Celtic transition showcases the beauty of Ange Postecoglou rotation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/seamless-celtic-transition-showcases-the-beauty-of-ange-postecoglou-rotation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/seamless-celtic-transition-showcases-the-beauty-of-ange-postecoglou-rotation/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent weeks, we have seen Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou rotate his starting 11 during an extremely busy period in the Hoops season. The 57-year-old has regularly turned to several different options in all areas of the pitch, and that was no different as the Bhoys travelled to face Motherwell on Wednesday. Coming off the ...
The post Seamless Celtic transition showcases the beauty of Ange Postecoglou rotation appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preview: Hearts vs. Celtic - prediction, team news, lineups]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sportsmole.co.uk/football/hearts/race-for-the-scottish-premiership-title/preview/preview-hearts-vs-celtic-prediction-team-news-lineups_497380.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.sportsmole.co.uk/football/hearts/race-for-the-scottish-premiership-title/preview/preview-hearts-vs-celtic-prediction-team-news-lineups_497380.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T10:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sports Mole previews Saturday's Scottish Premiership clash between Hearts and Celtic, including predictions, team news and possible lineups.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GIVE THE BHOY A BREAK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/give-the-bhoy-a-break/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/give-the-bhoy-a-break/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T10:12:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FOR some obscure reason which will no doubt be lost on Ange Postecoglou, midfielder James McCarthy appears to have been singled out for some mindless observations. There are some arch critics of the player who insist he should be nowhere near Celtic and his signing on a four-year contract last August is still unfathomable. Everyone [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton Praises ‘Marvellous’ Celtic Moment]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/chris-sutton-praises-marvellous-celtic-moment/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/chris-sutton-praises-marvellous-celtic-moment/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T09:53:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CHRIS SUTTON didn’t give his usual post-match comments on the Celtic game with so much football being played on Wednesday night. However, the former Hoops striker made sure to acknowledge Reo Hatate’s outstanding goal to make it 3-0 to Celtic on the night. Celtic fans were in awe of Reo’s quick feet when they were […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s New Bhoy Reacts to Cup Win; Hails Supporters]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtics-new-bhoy-reacts-to-cup-win-hails-supporters/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtics-new-bhoy-reacts-to-cup-win-hails-supporters/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T09:33:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Benjamin Siegrist played his second game for Celtic on Wednesday evening against Motherwell, keeping a clean sheet as the bhoys made it through to the semi-final of the League Cup. Ange has handed the Swiss stopper the gloves for the League Cup ties this season so far. The former Dundee Utd goalkeeper acquitting himself well […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Rangers legend manager swap touted amid Neil Lennon Cyprus departure]]></title>
        <id>29a45f7d4c9e24e65929c54cac3eabe2</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23063595.neil-lennon-set-replaced-former-rangers-star-omonia-nicosia/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T09:26:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ex-Ibrox player could be set to take over after the former Hoops boss was dismissed from the Cypriot club]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[&#039;Lawwell is in the building&#039; - Celtic already plotting winter business behind the scenes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-ange-postecoglou-january-transfer-window-plans-latest-news-rumours/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-ange-postecoglou-january-transfer-window-plans-latest-news-rumours/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T09:15:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou has now shared his side’s plans for when the transfer window opens in January. The Lowdown: January successes In the winter window last season, the Hoops welcomed the likes of Reo Hatate and Matt O’Riley to Parkhead, who were able to hit the ground running in the famous Green and White […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘WE NEED TO RECOVER AND GO AGAIN,’ MOOY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/we-need-to-recover-and-go-again-mooy/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/we-need-to-recover-and-go-again-mooy/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T09:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWAY from the glare of the spotlight, Aaron Mooy has quietly and effectively settled into life at Celtic. The Australian World Cup midfielder arrived at Parkhead in the summer on a free transfer to agree a two-year contract with his former international gaffer Ange Postecoglou. Mooy, who celebrated his 32nd birthday last month, eased his [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Albian Ajeti Scores Brilliant Cup Winner for Loan Club]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/video-albian-ajeti-scores-brilliant-cup-winner-for-loan-club/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/video-albian-ajeti-scores-brilliant-cup-winner-for-loan-club/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T08:51:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ALBIAN AJETI scored the winning goal for his loan club Sturm Graz as they booked their place in the quarter final of the Austrian Cup. The on-loan Celtic striker made it three goals in four games for Graz and appears to be finding his feet for the club. An injury slowed down Albian’s start earlier […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Abada, Taylor, Juranovic and more take to Instagram as Celtic secure Hampden Park trip]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/abada-taylor-juranovic-and-more-take-to-instagram-as-celtic-secure-hampden-park-trip/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/abada-taylor-juranovic-and-more-take-to-instagram-as-celtic-secure-hampden-park-trip/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T08:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic stars have been reacting on Instagram to the Hoops’ dominant 4-0 win over Motherwell in the Premier Sports Cup quarter-finals. The Bhoys headed to Fir Park, looking to secure another trip to Hampden Park in January, as they took on the Steelmen for the second time within a matter of weeks. Right from the ...
The post Abada, Taylor, Juranovic and more take to Instagram as Celtic secure Hampden Park trip appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s Most Memorable Champions League Moments]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtics-most-memorable-champions-league-moments/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtics-most-memorable-champions-league-moments/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T08:28:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to recent research on sports streaming trends, football still dominates the streaming arena, with the Champions League being one of the leagues with the highest viewership. However, the Champions League isn’t equally prosperous for all teams.Celtic’s Champions League frustrations this season have been well documented on The Celtic Star, and it really boils down Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TOUGH DROPPING PLAYERS? ‘I JUST AVOID THEM, MATE,’ REPLIES POSTECOGLOU]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/tough-dropping-players-i-just-avoid-them-mate-replies-postecoglou/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/tough-dropping-players-i-just-avoid-them-mate-replies-postecoglou/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T08:24:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU shuffled the Celtic pack again with his line-up for the 4-0 Premier Sports League Cup victory over Motherwell at Fir Park to set up a semi-final clash with Kilmarnock at Hampden in January. Three of the players who made way from the side that thrashed Hibs 6-1 at Parkhead four days were the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou hails Celtic stars pleasing contribution after goalscoring display]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-hails-celtic-stars-pleasing-contribution-after-goalscoring-display/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-hails-celtic-stars-pleasing-contribution-after-goalscoring-display/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T08:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou has insisted he has been happy with the contributions of Kyogo Furuhashi, as he put a frustrating run in front of goal to an end last night. After making an incredible goalscoring start to the season, producing six goals in the first five games, the Celtic forward then went on a ...
The post Ange Postecoglou hails Celtic stars pleasing contribution after goalscoring display appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We’re top of the league – Celtic’s other 4-0 away win last night]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/were-top-of-the-league-celtics-other-4-0-away-win-last-night/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/were-top-of-the-league-celtics-other-4-0-away-win-last-night/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T07:43:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Celtic enjoyed an impressive 4-0 away win at Fir Park in the earlier kick-off against Motherwell in the League Cup quarter final tie, setting up a January semi-final trip to Hampden to play Kilmarnock, Fran Alonso’s side were up on Gussie Park on Tannadice Street for Celtic FC Women’s first ever SWPL1 meeting with Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We’re top of the league – Celtic’s other 4-0 away win last night - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiELtkChc_3LvuxpNah50SNSYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiV2h0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vd2VyZS10b3Atb2YtdGhlLWxlYWd1ZS1jZWx0aWNzLW90aGVyLTQtMC1hd2F5LXdpbi1sYXN0LW5pZ2h0L9IBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T07:43:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re top of the league – Celtic’s other 4-0 away win last night  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Does not look fit’ – Pundit Takes Aim at Celtic Midfielder]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/does-not-look-fit-pundit-takes-aim-at-celtic-midfielder/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/does-not-look-fit-pundit-takes-aim-at-celtic-midfielder/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T07:36:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FRANK MCAVENNIE has questioned the wisdom of Celtic signing James McCarthy. The former Hoops striker believes the Irish international looks ‘lost’ at Parkhead and questioned the player’s fitness. We would caveat all Frank’s comments by saying he is paid to give his opinions to Football Insider, and if they suddenly became mundane or on the […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[McAvennie takes bizarre swipe at Celtic’s James McCarthy]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/mcavennie-takes-bizarre-swipe-at-celtics-james-mccarthy/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/mcavennie-takes-bizarre-swipe-at-celtics-james-mccarthy/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T07:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic player Frank McAvennie has taken a bizarre swipe at Celtic midfielder James McCarthy. McCarthy joined the Hoops last Summer on a free transfer, signing a 4-year contract. With 272 appearances in the Premier League under his belt, McCarthy brought valuable experience to Ange Posteciglou’s side, who were looking to replace the Scott Brown-shaped Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Little Bro’, ‘My Guy’ – Juranovic Posts Hilarious Post-Match Picture]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/little-bro-my-guy-juranovic-posts-hilarious-post-match-picture/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/little-bro-my-guy-juranovic-posts-hilarious-post-match-picture/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T06:54:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Josip Juranovic posted a hilarious picture from the 4-0 cup victory against Motherwell on Wednesday night. The bhoys thumped the Steelmen 4-0 at Fir Park thanks to goals from Liel Abada, Reo Hatate and Kyogo. Abada got a brace on the night and should’ve got a hat-trick, his shot coming off the post and landing […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic reaction: O'Riley's suitors keep growing, why Ange might need more players, cracking ratings]]></title>
        <id>3886682</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-reaction-orileys-suitors-keep-growing-why-ange-might-need-more-players-cracking-ratings-3886682"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T06:53:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We pick out three observations and give players a mark out of ten after Celtic’s 4-0 Premier Sports Cup triumph over Motherwell ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘THE WORLD COLLAPSES IN ON THEM,’ ANGE BACKS KYOGO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-world-collapses-in-on-them-ange-backs-kyogo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-world-collapses-in-on-them-ange-backs-kyogo/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T06:45:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO FURUHASHI scored just his second goal since his first-half hat-trick against Dundee United in August when he snapped up Celtic’s fourth strike in the 4-0 win over Motherwell at Fir Park. The Japanese international frontman was unlucky with a whizzbang 30-yarder that crashed off the underside of the crossbar and bounced on the line [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou Teases Presenter On-Air]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/ange-postecoglou-teases-presenter-on-air/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/ange-postecoglou-teases-presenter-on-air/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T06:39:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou showed the lighter side of his personality on Wednesday evening when the cameras went live for his post-match interview. Rory Hamilton was doing the honours for Premier Sports. When he began to ask Ange questions, the Celtic manager stopped ask Rory if he should tell Chris Sutton what Rory was saying about him […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic On This Day – 20th October – David Potter’s Celtic Diary]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-on-this-day-20th-october-david-potters-celtic-diary/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-on-this-day-20th-october-david-potters-celtic-diary/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T05:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Month 3, Day 20 of Celtic Historian David Potter’s new diary on The Celtic Star which will run throughout the new season and will highlight key Celtic-related events relevant to each day, today covering 20th October…SATURDAY 20 OCTOBER 1917The war continues in spite of the arrival of the Americans (as yet in small numbers) and Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic On This Day – 20th October – David Potter’s Celtic Diary - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEBEGGmEQFHHEpi5lXJDtVw0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiVWh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vY2VsdGljLW9uLXRoaXMtZGF5LTIwdGgtb2N0b2Jlci1kYXZpZC1wb3R0ZXJzLWNlbHRpYy1kaWFyeS_SAQA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T05:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic On This Day – 20th October – David Potter’s Celtic Diary  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Motherwell 0-4 Celtic – Next up, a nicer ground, but with nastier supporters]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/motherwell-0-4-celtic-next-up-a-nicer-ground-but-with-nastier-supporters/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/motherwell-0-4-celtic-next-up-a-nicer-ground-but-with-nastier-supporters/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T05:31:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not really an awful lot about this game that we didn’t know before, other than that our team played superbly, and that there wasn’t a poor player in the team.The goals were all superbly worked, and it was a pity that Liel Abada didn’t get his deserved hat-trick. Reo Hatate’s goal was a superb piece Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sandman’s Definitive Ratings – Celtic at Wells Fargo]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/sandmans-definitive-ratings-celtic-at-wells-fargo/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/sandmans-definitive-ratings-celtic-at-wells-fargo/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T05:15:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SANDMAN’S DEFINITIVE RATINGS: CELTIC @ WELLS FARGO…“I knew things were getting dire when Alfie tried to win a penalty by throwing himself at the ground. And missed.” – Giovanni van Bronkhorst. Undertaker.SIEGHEIL – 7/10 – That’s what we needed – fingertip defiance of a home resurgence right after the break as Seigy took on the entire Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defeat was sore, and Aberdeen clash will test our character, says Motherwell star - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEAsxW00_JNTTlk44xFdCpAkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiWmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2xvY2FsLXNwb3J0L2NlbHRpYy1kZWZlYXQtc29yZS1hYmVyZGVlbi1jbGFzaC0yODI4Mzc1OdIBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defeat was sore, and Aberdeen clash will test our character, says Motherwell star  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Postecoglou insists there is still room for improvment for Abada]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/postecoglou-insists-there-is-still-room-for-improvment-for-abada/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/postecoglou-insists-there-is-still-room-for-improvment-for-abada/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T04:35:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss, Ange Postecoglou was impressed by Liel Abada’s performance against Motherwell in their 4-0 mauling of the Steelmen. However, the Celtic gaffer believes there is still room for improvement for the young winger.Celtic put in another top-tier performance against Motherwell in the Premier Sports Cup, easily knocking them out of the competition by putting Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WAR GAMES: PART THREE: THE SECOND BATTLE OF THE RIVER PLATE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/war-games-part-three-the-second-battle-of-the-river-plate/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/war-games-part-three-the-second-battle-of-the-river-plate/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T04:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FIFTY-FIVE YEARS ago Celtic were involved in three of the most infamous games in the club’s proud history. The first encounter at Hampden on October 18 1967 had seen a header from Billy McNeill give Jock Stein’s men a 1-0 win over Racing Club of Buenos Aires in the Parkhead side’s historic quest to conquer [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premier Sports Cup semi-final draw - afc.co.uk]]></title>
        <id>CBMiRGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmFmYy5jby51ay8yMDIyLzEwLzE5L3ByZW1pZXItc3BvcnRzLWN1cC1zZW1pLWZpbmFsLWRyYXcv0gEA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiRGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmFmYy5jby51ay8yMDIyLzEwLzE5L3ByZW1pZXItc3BvcnRzLWN1cC1zZW1pLWZpbmFsLWRyYXcv0gEA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T21:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Premier Sports Cup semi-final draw  afc.co.uk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scottish League Cup: Celtic, Rangers discover semi-final opponents]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sportsmole.co.uk/football/celtic/scottish-league-cup/news/scottish-league-cup-celtic-rangers-discover-semi-final-opponents_497352.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.sportsmole.co.uk/football/celtic/scottish-league-cup/news/scottish-league-cup-celtic-rangers-discover-semi-final-opponents_497352.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T21:40:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Holders Celtic are drawn against Kilmarnock in the semi-finals of the Scottish League Cup, while Rangers will lock horns with Aberdeen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premier Sports Cup semi-final draw: Celtic and Rangers kept apart as Aberdeen and Kilmarnock learn fate]]></title>
        <id>3886597</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/premier-sports-cup-semi-final-draw-celtic-and-rangers-kept-apart-as-aberdeen-and-kilmarnock-learn-fate-3886597"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T21:37:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Rangers were kept apart in the draw for the Premier Sports Cup semi-finals after coming through their last eight ties in differing fashion on Wednesday night.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Elder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Motherwell boss Stevie Hammell bemoans Abada’s second goal]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/motherwell-boss-stevie-hammell-bemoans-abadas-second-goal/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/motherwell-boss-stevie-hammell-bemoans-abadas-second-goal/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T21:24:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stevie Hammell has revealed his belief that the second Celtic goal, scored by Liel Abada, was the turning point of the quarter-final. Hammell, who succeeded Graham Alexander in September, believes that this goal deflated his Motherwell side, who had created chances in the first half.Celtic soundly defeated Motherwell in the Premier Sports Cup quarter-final, putting Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CUP SEMI-FINAL DRAW: CELTIC v KILLIE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/cup-semi-final-draw-celtic-v-killie/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/cup-semi-final-draw-celtic-v-killie/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T21:20:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC will play Kilmarnock in the Premier Sports League Cup semi-final at Hampden in January. The Hoops booked their place in the last four with a 4-0 romp against Motherwell at Fir Park with a double from Liel Abada and singles from Reo Hatate and Kyogo Furuhashi. Goals from Kyle Lafferty (pen) and Danny Armstrong [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confirmed: Celtic draw Kilmarnock in League Cup Semi Final]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/confirmed-celtic-draw-kilmarnock-in-league-cup-semi-final/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/confirmed-celtic-draw-kilmarnock-in-league-cup-semi-final/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T21:15:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been drawn against Kilmarnock in the semi-final of the Premier Sports Cup. After the game at Ibrox tonight, Kenny Miller pulled the holders out of the draw to face Derek McInnes’ Killie.Celtic sealed their place in the draw with an impressive 4-0 win at Fir Park. Liel Abada hit a brace while Japanese Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confirmed: Celtic draw Kilmarnock in League Cup Semi Final - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEPfHJ7kaAk0mhJA49LxJeywqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiVGh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vY29uZmlybWVkLWNlbHRpYy1kcmF3LWtpbG1hcm5vY2staW4tbGVhZ3VlLWN1cC1zZW1pLWZpbmFsL9IBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T21:15:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Confirmed: Celtic draw Kilmarnock in League Cup Semi Final  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic to play Kilmarnock in Premier Sports Cup semi-final]]></title>
        <id>bba1533cf1d373cb8acdc01aaa10c72f</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23060293.celtic-play-premier-sports-cup-semi-finals/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T21:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have discovered their Premier Sports Cup semi-final opponents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic draw Kilmarnock in the cup as Ange Postecoglou reacts to another Hampden trip]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-draw-kilmarnock-in-the-cup-as-ange-postecoglou-reacts-to-another-hampden-trip/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-draw-kilmarnock-in-the-cup-as-ange-postecoglou-reacts-to-another-hampden-trip/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T21:14:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been confirmed Celtic will play Kilmarnock in the Premier Sports Cup semi-final at Hampden after a late-night draw on Wednesday. Rangers have been drawn against Aberdeen in the other half of the draw. Celtic are, of course, the reigning tournament winners after dispatching Hibernian in last season’s final. Strong wins against Ross County ...
The post Celtic draw Kilmarnock in the cup as Ange Postecoglou reacts to another Hampden trip appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premier Sports Cup draw LIVE as Rangers draw Aberdeen and Celtic face Kilmarnock in the last four - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEIeRFIf8-XybYsKCP4-C34AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiYGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvcHJlbWllci1zcG9ydHMtY3VwLWRyYXctbGl2ZS0yODI4MDA5MtIBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T21:11:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Premier Sports Cup draw LIVE as Rangers draw Aberdeen and Celtic face Kilmarnock in the last four  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premier Sports Cup draw as it happened as Celtic, Rangers, Aberdeen and Kilmarnock learn semi-final fate]]></title>
        <id>17a20541cf1c5904f7404b61189608b8</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23062905.premier-sports-cup-draw-happened-celtic-rangers-aberdeen-kilmarnock-learn-semi-final-fate/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T21:04:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIVE coverage of the Premier Sports Cup semi-final draw.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I just avoid them mate"; Ange Postecoglou has fun with media after Celtic victory]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-just-avoid-them-mate-ange-postecoglou-has-fun-with-media-after-celtic-victory/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-just-avoid-them-mate-ange-postecoglou-has-fun-with-media-after-celtic-victory/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T20:39:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou was in fine media form in the aftermath of Celtic’s win over Motherwell at Fir Park tonight, both on broadcasts and in his post-match press conference. From a Chris Sutton joke on Premier Sports, to playful responses in the Q+A, the Bhoys boss was certainly a good mood and intent on having a ...
The post "I just avoid them mate"; Ange Postecoglou has fun with media after Celtic victory appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Of Celtic’s Travelling Support Need To Sit The Hell Down.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/10/articles-and-features/some-of-celtics-travelling-support-need-to-sit-the-hell-down/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/10/articles-and-features/some-of-celtics-travelling-support-need-to-sit-the-hell-down/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T20:39:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing but good to take from the game tonight, on the park. But reports from friends who were at the game are less joyous than they might be, for one simple reason; there is a stone selfish element of our support who no matter where they are in a stadium insist on standing up and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Of Celtic’s Travelling Support Need To Sit The Hell Down. - TheCelticBlog.com]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEP2SGR3sHZUIbkeG830HzP8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowne-jCzDg-bsDMLnLhQc</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMidWh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljYmxvZy5jb20vMjAyMi8xMC9hcnRpY2xlcy1hbmQtZmVhdHVyZXMvc29tZS1vZi1jZWx0aWNzLXRyYXZlbGxpbmctc3VwcG9ydC1uZWVkLXRvLXNpdC10aGUtaGVsbC1kb3duL9IBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T20:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some Of Celtic’s Travelling Support Need To Sit The Hell Down.  TheCelticBlog.com]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Draw Kilmarnock in League Cup Semi-Final]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-draw-kilmarnock-in-league-cup-semi-final/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-draw-kilmarnock-in-league-cup-semi-final/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T20:33:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have drawn against Kilmarnock in the Semi Final of the Premier Sports Cup, with the fixture to be played at Hampden on the weekend of January 14/15th. The Final of the competition will take place at the national stadium in the following month. The dates are delayed this season due to the World Cup taking […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I just avoid them mate’: Ange Postecoglou explains reasoning behind Celtic team rotation, and how he breaks news to dropped players]]></title>
        <id>16b686d14e40c7d0d4af5ace990c9432</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23062880.i-just-avoid-mate-ange-postecoglou-explains-reasoning-behind-celtic-team-rotation-breaks-news-dropped-players/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T20:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU has revealed his tactic for avoiding awkward conversations with his players over his team selections, saying he simply puts the starting XI up on the board and walks away.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou backs Kyogo to rediscover ruthless edge after Celtic striker’s misses had him feeling ‘the world was collapsing’]]></title>
        <id>eb4cb7272169103961d7339b1b2223eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23062869.ange-postecoglou-backs-kyogo-rediscover-ruthless-edge-celtic-strikers-misses-feeling-the-world-collapsing/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T20:22:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU has backed striker Kyogo to get back on the goal trail after bringing his recent drought to an end with the final strike in Celtic’s 4-0 League Cup quarter-final stroll against Motherwell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can get even better: Ange Postecoglou lauds top Celtic performer vs Motherwell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/he-wants-to-improve-ange-postecoglou-lauds-top-celtic-performer-vs-motherwell/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/he-wants-to-improve-ange-postecoglou-lauds-top-celtic-performer-vs-motherwell/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T20:17:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou was delighted with the performance of Liel Abada this evening, as well as the other players who were rotated into the team. Postecoglou made five changes from the weekend demolition against Hibernian, but there was no drop off in the intensity of Celtic’s football, with Abada showing he can be as ...
The post Can get even better: Ange Postecoglou lauds top Celtic performer vs Motherwell appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Postecoglou Jokes About Team Selection]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/video-postecoglou-jokes-about-team-selection/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/video-postecoglou-jokes-about-team-selection/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T20:16:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU made five changes heading into Wednesday’s match after a rotated squad was fielded on Saturday. Guys like James Forrest and Giorgos Giakoumakis dropped to the bench, despite scoring five goals between themselves on Saturday. Maeda, who came on from off the bench at the weekend and scored, also started on the bench for […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou reveals how he tells Celtic players they are not in team]]></title>
        <id>3886572</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/ange-postecoglou-reveals-how-he-tells-celtic-players-they-are-not-in-team-3886572"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T20:14:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the hardest parts of the job for Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou right now is to rotate his team.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou in live TV tease as Celtic boss reveals Chris Sutton 'badmouthing']]></title>
        <id>e1729417528234eb1523f0d78c686520</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23062864.ange-postecoglou-live-tv-tease-celtic-boss-reveals-chris-sutton-badmouthing/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T20:12:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTCOGLOU almost dropped a Premier Sports commentator in the bad books with Chris Sutton as Celtic booked their spot in the semi-finals of the League Cup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['The world collapses in on them': Kyogo Furuhashi gets Ange Postecoglou Celtic assessment after win over Motherwell]]></title>
        <id>3886569</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/the-world-collapses-in-on-them-kyogo-furuhashi-gets-ange-postecoglou-celtic-assessment-after-win-over-motherwell-3886569"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T20:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou cut a contented figure after watching his Celtic team defeat Motherwell 4-0 to book their place in the semi-finals of the Premier Sports Cup, but took particular satisfaction in watching Kyogo Furuhashi get back on the scoresheet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Celtic goal was never in doubt as Ange Postecoglou's faith in star didn't waver - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEEHwZk9u8r2dSMZUyK5uQeAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiYWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3Mva3lvZ28tY2VsdGljLWdvYWwtbmV2ZXItZG91YnQtMjgyODE0NzHSAQA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T19:45:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Celtic goal was never in doubt as Ange Postecoglou's faith in star didn't waver  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘That’s the reality of it’ – Ange’s Candid Post-Match Appraisal]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/thats-the-reality-of-it-anges-candid-post-match-appraisal/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/thats-the-reality-of-it-anges-candid-post-match-appraisal/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T19:37:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIEL ABADA was great as Celtic booked themselves into the next round of the Premier Sports Cup, scoring two goals on the night. His brace came from some great movement in and around the box, which enabled him to create some space for himself before hitting the back of the net. As the winger looked […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Brilliant post-match scenes as Ange insists Kyogo faces Celtic fans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/match/video-brilliant-post-match-scenes-as-ange-insists-kyogo-faces-celtic-supporters/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/video-brilliant-post-match-scenes-as-ange-insists-kyogo-faces-celtic-supporters/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T19:36:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Furuhashi is back in amongst the goals at Celtic and couldn’t be more delighted if the post-match scenes at Fir Park are anything to go by. It threatened to be another frustrating night for the Japanese international, who missed two good chances and hit the bar with a stunning long-range shot in the first ...
The post Video: Brilliant post-match scenes as Ange insists Kyogo faces Celtic fans appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Brilliant post-match scenes as Ange insists Kyogo faces Celtic supporters - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEDH0l2ol-0biBpm-MGSUQwMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMI7NpgY</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMicWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL21hdGNoL3ZpZGVvLWJyaWxsaWFudC1wb3N0LW1hdGNoLXNjZW5lcy1hcy1hbmdlLWluc2lzdHMta3lvZ28tZmFjZXMtY2VsdGljLXN1cHBvcnRlcnMv0gEA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T19:36:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Brilliant post-match scenes as Ange insists Kyogo faces Celtic supporters  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Brilliant Post Match Ange and Kyogo Moment]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/video-brilliant-post-match-ange-and-kyogo-moment/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/video-brilliant-post-match-ange-and-kyogo-moment/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T19:27:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO has been lacking confidence over the past couple of games, and it showed on Wednesday night. The striker missed some sitter with the game level, and you could see it getting to him. Thankfully, he was able to get back onto the scoresheet, his first goal since Celtic’s last match against Motherwell, when the […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic show Rangers how it is done at Motherwell as cup holders show off their array of riches]]></title>
        <id>3886554</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-show-rangers-how-it-is-done-at-motherwell-as-cup-holders-show-off-their-array-of-riches-3886554"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T19:26:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hampden beckons once again for Celtic after this comfortable 4-0 victory over Motherwell at Fir Park in the Premier Sports Cup. Manager Ange Postecoglou will no doubt be grateful for such a serene night in South Lanarkshire, with their semi-final berth secured with an accomplished performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MOTHERWELL 0 CELTIC 4: FOUR-MIDABLE: TWO-GOAL ABADA LEADS CUP ROUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/motherwell-0-celtic-4-four-midable-two-goal-abada-leads-cup-rout/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/motherwell-0-celtic-4-four-midable-two-goal-abada-leads-cup-rout/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T19:23:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MOTHERWELL 0 CELTIC 4 LETHAL Liel Abada fired in a double salvo as Celtic overwhelmed Motherwell at Fir Park this evening to book their place in the Premier Sports League Cup semi-final draw. The holders were ruthless after the interval as they took control of the game and killed off their hosts with a two-goal [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Talking Points as Celtic Into Premier Sports Cup Semi Final]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/three-talking-points-as-celtic-into-premier-sports-cup-semi-final/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/three-talking-points-as-celtic-into-premier-sports-cup-semi-final/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T19:19:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC were brilliant as they overcame Motherwell 4-0 in Lanarkshire on Wednesday evening. The Hoops were brilliant and deserved a couple more goals. Kyogo missed a handful of chances and watched his shot from twenty-odd yards rattle the underneath of the crossbar before bouncing out. It was a great performance from Postecoglou’s side, who will […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic told they&#039;re a &#039;selling club&#039; and &#039;anyone will be gone&#039;, pundit not concerned]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-cameron-carter-vickers-transfer-news-latest-rumours-postecoglou/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-cameron-carter-vickers-transfer-news-latest-rumours-postecoglou/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T19:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic could choose to sell defender Cameron Carter-Vickers ‘if the price is right’, according to former Hoops striker Frank McAvennie. The Lowdown: CCV at Parkhead Having played a key role in the Hoops’ Premiership and Cup triumphs whilst on loan last season, the 24-year-old signed a four-year deal at Parkhead this summer after Tottenham agreed […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premier Sports Cup draw: Live semi-final stream, fixture dates, TV channel and start time]]></title>
        <id>546b4812ee7179352928e535d5800d78</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23055878.premier-sports-cup-draw-live-stream-semi-final-dates-tv-channel-start-time/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T19:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE Premier Sports Cup is heading into the semi-final stage with quarter-final ties set to take place this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Goal Rout Proves That The Bhoys Are Back! (At Hampden!)]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/10/articles-and-features/four-goal-rout-proves-that-the-bhoys-are-back-at-hampden/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/10/articles-and-features/four-goal-rout-proves-that-the-bhoys-are-back-at-hampden/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T19:09:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic revival continues. That, tonight, was what we’ve come to expect in the same way that the performance at the weekend was. As the next stop is Tynecastle this is a timely moment to re-find our scoring touch. It was a great overall display. There are players who, tomorrow, will hog the headlines; Abada […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s League Cup semi-final draw: when is it and where to watch it]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtics-league-cup-semi-final-draw-when-is-it-and-where-to-watch-it/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtics-league-cup-semi-final-draw-when-is-it-and-where-to-watch-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T19:08:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will enter the Premier Sports Cup semi-final after the result at Fir Park this evening. Ange Postecoglou’s side were comfortable as goals from Liel Abada, Reo Hatate and Kyogo sealed progression into the next round.Kilmarnock are already in the hat, having beaten Dundee United at Rugby Park last night. Celtic’s 4-0 win dumps Motherwell Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange squad calls, returning Bhoy sends reminder; 3 things we learned as Celtic thrash Motherwell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/match/ange-squad-calls-returning-bhoy-sends-reminder-3-things-we-learned-as-celtic-thrash-motherwell/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/ange-squad-calls-returning-bhoy-sends-reminder-3-things-we-learned-as-celtic-thrash-motherwell/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T19:06:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have moved into the semi-finals of the Premier Sports Cup after thrashing Motherwell 4-0 at Fir Park this evening. It felt unusual to have the Bhoys kick-off at such an early time, mid-week, but it was business as usual from the team, with a double from Liel Abada and a fine Reo Hatate finish ...
The post Ange squad calls, returning Bhoy sends reminder; 3 things we learned as Celtic thrash Motherwell appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nightmare under Fir Park lights for Motherwell as classy Celtic canter into semi-finals]]></title>
        <id>f3646ffb9e58ff72eee84bdb3fcbe734</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23062820.nightmare-fir-park-lights-motherwell-classy-celtic-canter-semi-finals/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T19:05:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THERE’S no better nights than under the Fir Park lights, said a banner unveiled by the Motherwell fans before this game. Unfortunately for them, it seems the Celtic players agree.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Kyogo makes it 4-0, Celtic putting on the style]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/video-kyogo-makes-it-4-0-celtic-putting-on-the-style/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-kyogo-makes-it-4-0-celtic-putting-on-the-style/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T19:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo made it 4-0 to Celtic as the Scottish Champions put on the style at Fir Park this evening. The Japanese striker benefited after Liel Abada struck the post in his hunt for a hat-trick with the ball falling favourably into his path. Motherwell 0 Celtic 4. Kyogo. pic.twitter.com/YGuFZqDxOj — Jungle Lover. (@kirkwallkid) October 19, Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Celtic talkers as Ange Postecoglou's side defeat Motherwell to book place at Hampden]]></title>
        <id>9ad63bcc14dbb8e1c293995f319a49cb</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23062728.3-celtic-talkers-ange-postecglous-defeat-motherwell-book-place-hampden/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T18:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Hoops put on a dominant display at Fir Park as they progressed to the semi-finals of the Premier Sports Cup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Brilliant skill from Reo Hatate makes it 3-0 to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/video-brilliant-skill-from-reo-hatate-makes-it-3-0-to-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-brilliant-skill-from-reo-hatate-makes-it-3-0-to-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T18:40:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate has put Celtic within touching distance of the League Cup Semi Finals after a clever bit of skill allowed him to make it 3-0. The midfielder has been bright this evening and he was rewarded with a goal. He took the ball on the turn, shielding it from the defender and then using Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Liel Abada opens the scoring for Celtic, tidy team goal]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/video-liel-abada-opens-the-scoring-for-celtic-tidy-team-goal/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-liel-abada-opens-the-scoring-for-celtic-tidy-team-goal/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T18:04:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liel Abada has opened the scoring for Celtic on the stroke of half-time. The Israeli winger has a great habit of being in the right place at the right time and he capitalised on a tidy interchange between Celtic’s left-flank to send Ange Postecoglou’s side into the lead at the break.Greg Taylor and Sead Haksabanovic Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First VAR match in SPFL to be shown live as Hibs confirm PPV for historic St Johnstone clash]]></title>
        <id>3886479</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/hibs/first-var-match-in-spfl-to-be-shown-live-as-hibs-confirm-ppv-for-historic-st-johnstone-clash-3886479"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T16:51:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first Scottish Premiership match to implement VAR is to be broadcast live online.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Elder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic team news vs Motherwell as Ange Postecoglou names side for Premier Sports Cup clash]]></title>
        <id>a318321bfd80f21b924815e39fe2916d</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/22295761.ange-postecoglou-shuts-question-celtic-fan-anti-monarchy-display-st-mirren-loss/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T16:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Australian has named a strong starting XI for the match at Fir Park]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Team’s Up – Siegrist has gloves, Hakšabanović plays]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/teams-up-siegrist-has-gloves-haksabanovic-plays/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/teams-up-siegrist-has-gloves-haksabanovic-plays/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T16:28:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sead Hakšabanović: starts for Celtic at Fir Park in the League Cup quarter final match this evening while Ange Postecoglou has opted to give Ben Siegrist the gloves.Josip Juranovic and Greg Taylor are back after sitting out the win over Hibs and play alongside Cameron Carter Vickers and Moritz Jenz in the Celtic defence.  In Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premier Sports Cup Draw; Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/premier-sports-cup-draw-everything-you-need-to-know/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/premier-sports-cup-draw-everything-you-need-to-know/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T16:27:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC are in action in the League Cup on Wednesday evening, with a trip to Motherwell lined up. If Celtic are to get passed Motherwell, they will have their name in the draw for the semi finals at Hampden, which will be played on the 14/15th of January, before the final a month later. The […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Motherwell vs Celtic in pictures - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEJOBLp8Qsb375K8qLQjVQRwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMibGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvZ2FsbGVyeS9tb3RoZXJ3ZWxsLXZzLWNlbHRpYy1pbi1waWN0dXJlcy0yODI4MDE0NdIBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T16:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Motherwell vs Celtic in pictures  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Motherwell v Celtic, Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/motherwell-v-celtic-live-updates-20/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/motherwell-v-celtic-live-updates-20/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T16:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 18:15.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: CELTIC SHAKE-UP, SIEGRIST IN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-celtic-shake-up-siegrist-in/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-celtic-shake-up-siegrist-in/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T16:14:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BENJI SIEGRIST will take over from Joe Hart for tonight’s Premier Sports League quarter-final against Motherwell at Fir Park. The Swiss keeper played in the 4-1 win over Ross County in Dingwall in the previous round and boss Ange Postecoglou has given him the nod to start again. Siegrist is one of five changes from [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange goes strong: Celtic XI confirmed, 5 changes, global TV details, instant reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-vs-motherwell-confirmed-ange-goes-strong-global-tv-details-instant-reaction/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-vs-motherwell-confirmed-ange-goes-strong-global-tv-details-instant-reaction/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T16:10:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has named his Celtic team vs Motherwell in the Premier Sports Cup tonight. The full match squad is as follows: Starting XI – Siegrist, Juranovic, Carter-Vickers, Jenz, Taylor, O’Riley, Mooy, Hatate, Abada, Haksabanovic, Kyogo. Substitutes – Hart, Giakoumakis, McCarthy, Ideguchi, Bernabei, Abildgaard, Maeda, Forrest, Ralston. The manager has named a very strong line-up ...
The post Ange goes strong: Celtic XI confirmed, 5 changes, global TV details, instant reaction appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premier Sports Cup semi-finals: How to watch the draw, TV channel, live stream, semi-final dates]]></title>
        <id>3886427</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/premier-sports-cup-semi-finals-how-to-watch-the-draw-tv-channel-live-stream-semi-final-dates-3886427"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T16:09:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Premier Sports Cup semi-final line-up will be completed on Wednesday night following the conclusion of the remaining quarter-final ties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Elder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confirmed Starting XI to Face Motherwell; Postecoglou Makes Big Goalkeeper Call]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/confirmed-starting-xi-to-face-motherwell-postecoglou-makes-big-goalkeeper-call/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/confirmed-starting-xi-to-face-motherwell-postecoglou-makes-big-goalkeeper-call/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T16:03:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU has named his side that will take on Motherwell in the Premier Sports Cup. With a few notable changes from the weekend, the side is looking to make the trip to Hampden as they continue their cup defence. It was the first piece of silverware that Ange Postecoglou, and many of the players, […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic team news: 2 missing tonight but they could make Tynecastle return]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-team-news-2-missing-tonight-but-they-could-make-tynecastle-return/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-team-news-2-missing-tonight-but-they-could-make-tynecastle-return/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T15:43:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re not far away from the official announcement of tonight’s Celtic team, but two who definitely won’t be involved are David Turnbull and Jota, as already confirmed by manager Ange Postecoglou. The Bhoys boss shared the news in a press conference yesterday, but the good news is that we could see their return against Hearts ...
The post Celtic team news: 2 missing tonight but they could make Tynecastle return appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon named shock outsider for managerial gig after Omonia Nicosia sacking]]></title>
        <id>2943dc87fb6f962bcd1a3695e9eebd0b</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23062183.neil-lennon-named-shock-outsider-managerial-gig-omonia-nicosia-sacking/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T15:35:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AFTER Neil Lennon's sacking as Omonia Nicosia boss yesterday, the former Celtic and Hibernian manager has been named as an outsider for the vacant Cardiff City job.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contingency Plan Set for Celtic Scenario]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/contingency-plan-set-for-celtic-scenario/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/contingency-plan-set-for-celtic-scenario/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T15:26:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC plays Motherwell in the Premier Sports Cup on Wednesday night, with the sides given a rather bizarre kick-off time of 6.15. Premier Sports are broadcasting the match before switching to Ibrox to show The Rangers’ tie against Dundee. The station will switch to Govan just five minutes before that match is to kick off, […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tonight&#039;s strange Celtic kick-off time vs Motherwell explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/tonights-strange-celtic-kick-off-time-vs-motherwell-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/tonights-strange-celtic-kick-off-time-vs-motherwell-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T15:13:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consider this a friendly reminder that this evening’s Celtic vs Motherwell match kicks off at 6:15pm, far earlier than the more traditional 7:45pm or 8pm timeslots. But why? Put simply, it’s because of Premier Sports’ live TV coverage, despite both clubs seeking to kick off at another hour to benefit their supporters. That situation was ...
The post Tonight&#039;s strange Celtic kick-off time vs Motherwell explained appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tonight’s strange Celtic kick-off time vs Motherwell explained - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEG0xNZAXUodSwZiJxzK7AYoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMLbFpgY</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiXmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL25ld3MvdG9uaWdodHMtc3RyYW5nZS1jZWx0aWMta2ljay1vZmYtdGltZS12cy1tb3RoZXJ3ZWxsLWV4cGxhaW5lZC_SAQA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T15:13:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tonight’s strange Celtic kick-off time vs Motherwell explained  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tonight’s strange Celtic kick-off time vs Motherwell explained - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CBMiXmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL25ld3MvdG9uaWdodHMtc3RyYW5nZS1jZWx0aWMta2ljay1vZmYtdGltZS12cy1tb3RoZXJ3ZWxsLWV4cGxhaW5lZC_SAWJodHRwczovL3d3dy42N2hhaWxoYWlsLmNvbS9uZXdzL3RvbmlnaHRzLXN0cmFuZ2UtY2VsdGljLWtpY2stb2ZmLXRpbWUtdnMtbW90aGVyd2VsbC1leHBsYWluZWQvP2FtcA</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiXmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL25ld3MvdG9uaWdodHMtc3RyYW5nZS1jZWx0aWMta2ljay1vZmYtdGltZS12cy1tb3RoZXJ3ZWxsLWV4cGxhaW5lZC_SAWJodHRwczovL3d3dy42N2hhaWxoYWlsLmNvbS9uZXdzL3RvbmlnaHRzLXN0cmFuZ2UtY2VsdGljLWtpY2stb2ZmLXRpbWUtdnMtbW90aGVyd2VsbC1leHBsYWluZWQvP2FtcA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T15:13:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tonight’s strange Celtic kick-off time vs Motherwell explained  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Rangers could 'give anyone a game' in Premier League except Manchester City, insists Si Ferry]]></title>
        <id>aa0282d05e3987ec4d8fba87c5734bf3</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23061846.former-celtic-midfielder-feels-hoops-can-give-anyone-game-premier-league-except-manchester-city/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T14:49:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ex-Hoops youth academy prospect and current Open Goal Broomhill boss feels Ange Postecoglou's men can compete at the highest level]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero set for ideal opportunity as he looks to achieve another century landmark]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/celtic-hero-set-for-ideal-opportunity-as-he-looks-achieve-another-century-landmark/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/celtic-hero-set-for-ideal-opportunity-as-he-looks-achieve-another-century-landmark/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic winger James Forrest looks set for the opportunity to build upon his hat trick performance at the weekend against Motherwell this evening. The 31-year-old has found opportunities under Ange Postecoglou hard to come by, having suffered from his fair share of injury issues and with several quality options ahead of him. However, after some ...
The post Celtic hero set for ideal opportunity as he looks to achieve another century landmark appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Legend And Ex-Ibrox Player Come Together To Accuse The Record Of Lying.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/10/articles-and-features/celtic-legend-and-ex-ibrox-player-come-together-to-accuse-the-record-of-lying/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/10/articles-and-features/celtic-legend-and-ex-ibrox-player-come-together-to-accuse-the-record-of-lying/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T14:18:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday, The Daily Record “quoted” Craig Moore where he appeared to suggest that Leon King, Ibrox’s new “wonderkid”, had an agent who was up to no good and basically indulging in the sort of naughty behaviour that some of these guys do. The implication was that he was trying to drum up transfer interest in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Motherwell boss outlines his plan of what is needed ahead &#039;high-quality&#039; Celtic test]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/motherwell-boss-outlines-his-plan-of-what-is-needed-ahead-high-quality-celtic-test/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/motherwell-boss-outlines-his-plan-of-what-is-needed-ahead-high-quality-celtic-test/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Motherwell boss Steven Hammell has challenged his squad to take the next step in their development under his management when they face Celtic in the Premier Sports Cup tonight. Ange Postecoglou’s side travel to Fir Park having only faced the Well over two weeks ago, where the Bhoys came out 2-1 winners at Parkhead. The ...
The post Motherwell boss outlines his plan of what is needed ahead &#039;high-quality&#039; Celtic test appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First start, four changes; Celtic Predicted XI vs Motherwell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/first-start-four-changes-celtic-predicted-xi-vs-motherwell/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/first-start-four-changes-celtic-predicted-xi-vs-motherwell/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T13:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic continue the defence of their status as Premier Sports Cup winners tonight with a visit to Motherwell and Fir Park for the chance to reach the semi-finals of the tournament. A win away to Ross County in the last round has set up this evening’s kick-off, which has the unusual kick-off time of 6:15pm. ...
The post First start, four changes; Celtic Predicted XI vs Motherwell appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sead Hakšabanović: “The best is yet to come from him. Absolutely,” Ange Postecoglou]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/sead-haksabanovic-the-best-is-yet-to-come-from-him-absolutely-ange-postecoglou/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/sead-haksabanovic-the-best-is-yet-to-come-from-him-absolutely-ange-postecoglou/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T13:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sead Hakšabanović’s transfer to Celtic from Rubin Kazan was unusually complex given the situation that Russian football finds itself in due to the aggressive nature of the country’s rulers, but perseverance paid off when the deal was eentually concluded and the player is now showing strong signs of becoming a top quality performer for the Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Si Ferry claims Celtic and Rangers can match any English side minus Man City - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEDBurb35Ia47acCZksLeZS8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiVWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL3NpLWZlcnJ5LWluc2lzdHMtY2VsdGljLXJhbmdlcnMtMjgyNzg1MznSAQA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T13:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Si Ferry claims Celtic and Rangers can match any English side minus Man City  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Record Publishes Another Ridiculous “Celtic On Red Alert” Story On Europe.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/10/articles-and-features/the-record-publishes-another-ridiculous-celtic-on-red-alert-story-on-europe/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/10/articles-and-features/the-record-publishes-another-ridiculous-celtic-on-red-alert-story-on-europe/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T12:56:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday I wrote about how The Daily Record’s lazy hacks are increasingly obsessed with writing stories about European football and broadcasting how Celtic are “on red alert” over various developments. I wrote that because they were banging on about the co-efficient. Today they are banging on about the European Super League. I want to scream […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 3 Celtic fringe players that could receive surprise cup opportunity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-3-celtic-fringe-players-that-could-receive-surprise-cup-opportunity/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-3-celtic-fringe-players-that-could-receive-surprise-cup-opportunity/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will take a break from Scottish Premiership action this evening when they face Motherwell in the Premier Sports Cup. Having defeated Ross County on the road earlier in the competition, the Bhoys face another away trip to Fir Park, taking on the Well for the second time within a matter of weeks. And with ...
The post The 3 Celtic fringe players that could receive surprise cup opportunity appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 3 Celtic fringe players that could receive surprise cup opportunity - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEG9vDr1nhxS90NYO83xSgMAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMOHTpgY</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMia2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL29waW5pb24vdGhlLTMtY2VsdGljLWZyaW5nZS1wbGF5ZXJzLXRoYXQtY291bGQtcmVjZWl2ZS1zdXJwcmlzZS1jdXAtb3Bwb3J0dW5pdHkv0gEA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 3 Celtic fringe players that could receive surprise cup opportunity  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 3 Celtic fringe players that could receive surprise cup opportunity - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>1611665634</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMia2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL29waW5pb24vdGhlLTMtY2VsdGljLWZyaW5nZS1wbGF5ZXJzLXRoYXQtY291bGQtcmVjZWl2ZS1zdXJwcmlzZS1jdXAtb3Bwb3J0dW5pdHkv0gFvaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuNjdoYWlsaGFpbC5jb20vb3Bpbmlvbi90aGUtMy1jZWx0aWMtZnJpbmdlLXBsYXllcnMtdGhhdC1jb3VsZC1yZWNlaXZlLXN1cnByaXNlLWN1cC1vcHBvcnR1bml0eS8_YW1w?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 3 Celtic fringe players that could receive surprise cup opportunity  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News
Jota Celtic return timeline provided as McGregor, Starfelt and Turnbull injury updates land  Glasgow Live
Motherwell v Celtic: team news, KO time and where to watch  The Celtic Star
Jota out for Celtic Cup clash as Ange future proofs ahead of World Cup  Daily Record
Jota Injury Update; Four Missing for Motherwell Tie  CeltsAreHere
View Full coverage on Google News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic Teammates Train With SPFL Premiership Club]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/former-celtic-teammates-train-with-spfl-premiership-club/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/former-celtic-teammates-train-with-spfl-premiership-club/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T12:24:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic midfielder Dylan McGeouch has been training with Livingston as he looks to get into shape in order to find a new club. It had been revealed last week that his old Hoops teammate Leigh Griffiths was also training under David Martindale at the West Lothian club. The 29-year old spent two years at […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange and his painstaking Celtic planning laid bare as Barrie McKay comes under the spotlight - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEEV6SrOU7fgObzW74PO7HZwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiW2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2FuZ2UtcGFpbnN0YWtpbmctY2VsdGljLXBsYW5uaW5nLWxhaWQtMjgyNzcwMTLSAQA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T12:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange and his painstaking Celtic planning laid bare as Barrie McKay comes under the spotlight  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Mark Lawwell is in the building now,” Postecoglou’s exciting Plan]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/mark-lawwell-is-in-the-building-now-postecoglous-exciting-plan/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/mark-lawwell-is-in-the-building-now-postecoglous-exciting-plan/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T11:57:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou yesterday outlined the plans that are being currently worked on to repeat the trick in the first few days of the winter transfer window by adding to the Celtic squad ahead of the second half of the season and hopefully to prepare for Champions League next time around.The Celtic manager added Mark Lawwell Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou to Bring Back Brendan Rodgers Cup Tactic – Opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/ange-postecoglou-to-bring-back-brendan-rodgers-cup-tactic-opinion/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/ange-postecoglou-to-bring-back-brendan-rodgers-cup-tactic-opinion/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T11:49:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has remained tight lipped on who he’ll start against Motherwell on Wednesday evening. However, we have a sneaky suspicion he’s about to give one Celtic player his second start of the season. Benjamin Siegrist has made his one and only appearance for Celtic in the League Cup when the bhoys took on Ross […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On-loan Celtic star reflects on the early positives of European spell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/going-really-well-on-loan-celtic-star-reflects-on-the-early-positives-of-temporary-exit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/going-really-well-on-loan-celtic-star-reflects-on-the-early-positives-of-temporary-exit/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T11:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-loan Celtic winger Mikey Johnston has opened up on the early stages of his temporary spell in Portugal with Vitoria de Guimaraes. The 23-year-old made the surprise loan move towards the end of the summer transfer window, choosing to go test himself within another European league. Nine games into the Portuguese season, the majority of ...
The post On-loan Celtic star reflects on the early positives of European spell appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ONE-TIME WONDER BHOY ON WAY BACK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/one-time-wonder-bhoy-on-way-back/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/one-time-wonder-bhoy-on-way-back/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T11:34:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DYLAN McGEOUCH, tipped as a potential wonder Bhoy when he made his Celtic first team debut in November 2011, is getting ready to return to football. The 29-year-old midfielder has been without a club since being released by Aberdeen in the summer. McGeouch is now training at Livingston alongside ex-Hoops goal hero Leigh Griffiths, 32, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major Publication Backs Ange’s Celtic Rise]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/major-publication-backs-anges-celtic-rise/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/major-publication-backs-anges-celtic-rise/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T11:20:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has been named as the 30th best manager in world football by FourFourTwo.  Before arriving in Glasgow last summer, Ange Postecoglou was not too familiar a name to the Celtic support but he very quickly captured the minds and hearts of the Hoops faithful. The list is of course arbitrary, but it shows […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harry Kewell discloses his initial Ange Postecoglou &#039;wow&#039; factor upon Celtic arrival]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/harry-kewell-discloses-his-initial-ange-postecoglou-wow-factor-upon-celtic-arrival/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/harry-kewell-discloses-his-initial-ange-postecoglou-wow-factor-upon-celtic-arrival/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic coach Harry Kewell has stated that his role at Parkhead working under Ange Postecoglou is exactly what he needed at this stage of his coaching career. The former Liverpool and Leeds player already has several managerial roles on his CV from between 2015-2021 at clubs such as Crawley Town and Barnet. However, during the ...
The post Harry Kewell discloses his initial Ange Postecoglou &#039;wow&#039; factor upon Celtic arrival appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[League Cup games importance on the result]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/league-cup-games-importance-on-the-result/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/league-cup-games-importance-on-the-result/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T11:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a quirk of scheduling that between now and the World Cup break, that we have three games at Celtic Park and two at Fir Park Motherwell, the first coming during rush hour this evening.  After a straightforward win over Hibs on Saturday, we embark on what looks like a challenging run of fixtures. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lawwell’s Greatest Mistake Haunts Neil Lennon More Than Celtic.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/10/articles-and-features/lawwells-greatest-mistake-haunts-neil-lennon-more-than-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/10/articles-and-features/lawwells-greatest-mistake-haunts-neil-lennon-more-than-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T10:49:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon’s sacking by Omonia Nicosia, which was announced to the amazement of almost everyone who heard it last night, is not something any Celtic fan will take the least pleasure or satisfaction from. But for many of us, it had a grim inevitability about it from the moment he was announced in the role. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Rangers on alert amid claims European Super League 'could be running by 2024']]></title>
        <id>3885511</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-and-rangers-on-alert-amid-claims-european-super-league-could-be-running-by-2024-3885511"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T10:21:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Rangers will be watching on with interest following claims that a new European Super League with no permanent membership could be up and running by the 2024-25 season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angus Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic youngsters suffer opening defeat in prestigious international tournament]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-youngsters-suffer-opening-defeat-in-prestigious-international-tournament/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-youngsters-suffer-opening-defeat-in-prestigious-international-tournament/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T10:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A young Celtic team lost out to the academy of English Premier League side Fulham in their opening game of the Premier League International Cup last night. The Bhoys travelled to London on Tuesday to take on Fulham in their first of four games after being invited to participate in the prestigious tournament. Alongside the ...
The post Celtic youngsters suffer opening defeat in prestigious international tournament appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘IT DOESN’T MATTER,’ ANGE WELCOMES LATEST CHALLENGE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/it-doesnt-matter-ange-welcomes-latest-challenge/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/it-doesnt-matter-ange-welcomes-latest-challenge/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T10:04:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU admits “it doesn’t matter” that Celtic won the Premier Sports League Cup in December last year. It was the manager’s first piece of silverware after arriving six months earlier as Neil Lennon’s long-term successor. The Greek-Australian gaffer had witnessed his team successfully negotiate their way through two huge obstacles at Hampden to claim [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Brown hugs Fleetwood superfan ahead of Man Utd clash in heartwarming clip - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEPZGRbyIMJ76dZ2txRJY4ccqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPPfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiaGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZvb3RiYWxsc2NvdGxhbmQuY28udWsvc2NvdHMtYWJyb2FkL2VuZ2xpc2gtZm9vdGJhbGwvd2F0Y2gtY2VsdGljLWhlcm8tc2NvdHQtYnJvd25zLTI1Mjk5MTAx0gEA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T09:51:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Brown hugs Fleetwood superfan ahead of Man Utd clash in heartwarming clip  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dylan McGeouch training with Livingston as ex-Celtic and Aberdeen ace looks to maintain fitness]]></title>
        <id>b2adba9edd197b15af79d926e71bb037</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23060540.dylan-mcgeouch-training-livingston-ex-celtic-aberdeen-ace-looks-maintain-fitness/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T09:49:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic, Hibs and Aberdeen star Dylan McGeouch is training with with Livingston.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Josip Juranovic reveals his new important behind-the-scenes role at Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/josip-juranovic-reveals-his-new-important-behind-the-scenes-role-at-celtic-park/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/josip-juranovic-reveals-his-new-important-behind-the-scenes-role-at-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Josip Juranovic has revealed that as a full-back, he has played a role in helping summer addition Alexandro Bernabei settle into life at Parkhead. The Croatian arrived at Parkhead last summer as part of Ange Postecoglou’s recruitment overhaul and rebuild at the club. Juranovic was quickly thrown into the starting line-up as the ...
The post Josip Juranovic reveals his new important behind-the-scenes role at Celtic Park appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Motherwell v Celtic: Predicted Starting XI]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/motherwell-v-celtic-predicted-starting-xi/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/motherwell-v-celtic-predicted-starting-xi/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T09:25:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With no Champions League football this week, the Hoops return to League Cup action with a visit to Fir Park. Both sides have already met once this season with it being a tight encounter that finished with a 2-1 victory for Celtic with captain Callum McGregor being shown a red card. The difference between that […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Omonia Nicosia to thrash out Neil Lennon compensation as sacking reasons come to light]]></title>
        <id>7cae191f75011f614d0a82923f2e9ac7</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23060440.omonia-nicosia-thrash-neil-lennon-compensation-sacking-reasons-come-light/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T09:23:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OMONIA NICOSIA have revealed they will thrash out a compensation deal with Neil Lennon in the next few days after going into more details about why they sacked him after just seven months in charge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 16 looming transfer free agents ready for Scottish Premiership chance - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEOzQUy0NimSpVqUt_HdACIgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiY2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvMTYtbG9vbWluZy10cmFuc2Zlci1mcmVlLWFnZW50cy0yODI2ODgwM9IBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T09:11:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 16 looming transfer free agents ready for Scottish Premiership chance  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harry Kewell’s First Day at Celtic Surprise]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/harry-kewells-first-day-at-celtic-surprise/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/harry-kewells-first-day-at-celtic-surprise/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HARRY KEWELL’s job before Celtic was in the fifth tier of English football. The Celtic coach was sacked from his position at Barnet in September 2021 and was out of a job until joining Celtic in the summer. He’s never been at a top club in a coaching capacity and has admitted he wasn’t sure […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Motherwell v Celtic: team news, KO time and where to watch]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/motherwell-v-celtic-team-news-ko-time-and-where-to-watch-2/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/motherwell-v-celtic-team-news-ko-time-and-where-to-watch-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T08:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou’s Celtic continue their defence of the League Cup this evening as they travel to face Motherwell at Fir Park. A place in the Semi-Finals at Hampden awaits the winner and the holders will be hoping to book their place at the National Stadium. Celtic won 4-1 against Ross County back in August in Dingwall, Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MOOY: ‘A BIG CONTRIBUTOR FOR US’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/mooy-a-big-contributor-for-us/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/mooy-a-big-contributor-for-us/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T08:58:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU is convinced Australia international midfielder Aaron Mooy “will be a big contributor” for Celtic. The Hoops face nine games in 24 hectic days before the break for the World Cup Finals in Qatar next month. The champions go into a crucial sequence of matches – starting tonight in the Premier Sports League Cup [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou delivers &#039;more to come&#039; vow for improving Celtic summer additions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-delivers-more-to-come-vow-for-improving-celtic-summer-additions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-delivers-more-to-come-vow-for-improving-celtic-summer-additions/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou has praised Hoops duo Sead Haksabanovic and Alexandro Bernabei following their first league start at Parkhead. Both players arrived at Celtic in the summer transfer window, and supporters were excited to see what the duo could offer to the squad. However, Haksabanovic and Bernabei have had to bide their time for ...
The post Ange Postecoglou delivers &#039;more to come&#039; vow for improving Celtic summer additions appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HAKSABANOVIC: ‘THE BEST IS YET TO COME’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/haksabanovic-the-best-is-yet-to-come/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/haksabanovic-the-best-is-yet-to-come/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T08:38:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU is convinced “the best is yet to come” from Sead Haksabanovic. The Celtic boss has unleashed the Sweden-born Montenegro international winger after eventually getting the cut-price £1.7million deal from Rubin Kazan over the line before the August transfer deadline. The hard-working and tricky wide Bhoy has already impressed and he sizzled through an [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend Scott Brown in wholesome moment as he meets Fleetwood Town superfan - Glasgow Live]]></title>
        <id>CAIiENtgGnAd2FOB0pkW54kAXq4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow96D9CjDOy_QCMKzp0wU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiUGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmdsYXNnb3dsaXZlLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2NlbHRpYy1sZWdlbmQtc2NvdHQtYnJvd24td2hvbGVzb21lLTI1Mjk4NDMx0gEA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T08:32:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend Scott Brown in wholesome moment as he meets Fleetwood Town superfan  Glasgow Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Star Talks Winning Mentality; League Cup Tie]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-star-talks-winning-mentality-league-cup-tie/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-star-talks-winning-mentality-league-cup-tie/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T08:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOSIP JURANOVIC has a busy few weeks ahead, with four potential competitions to compete in. His call-up to his national squad for the World Cup hasn’t been confirmed, but it’s expected he’ll jet to Qatar and compete in the competition. It’s a favourable group for the country, who’ll fancy their chances to progress into the […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“We see a really bright future for him,” Bernabei praised by Postecoglou]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/we-see-a-really-bright-future-for-him-bernabei-praised-by-postecoglou/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/we-see-a-really-bright-future-for-him-bernabei-praised-by-postecoglou/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T08:22:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has opened up on the plan to gradually intergate his summer signings into the Celtic set-up before exposing them to too much first team football as had to happen last season out of necessity. Having now completed that arrival stage, Argentinian left-back Alexandro Bernabei looks like becoming a top quality performer wearing the Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BERNABEI: ‘HE IS ONE WE ARE REALLY EXCITED ABOUT’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/bernabei-he-is-one-we-are-really-excited-about/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/bernabei-he-is-one-we-are-really-excited-about/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T08:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU has admitted he is “really excited” about the prospects of Argentinian left-back Alexandro Bernabei. The young defender, who celebrated his 22nd birthday last month, joined the champions in the summer in a £3.75million deal from top-flight club Lanus. Postecoglou has refused to rush the player into the first team as he was forced [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou talks up recruitment chiefs influence in exciting Celtic transfer update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-talks-up-mark-lawwell-influence-in-exciting-celtic-transfer-update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-talks-up-mark-lawwell-influence-in-exciting-celtic-transfer-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou has insisted that the Hoops’ preparation for the January transfer window is well underway as they eye new recruits. The 57-year-old has enjoyed success in the transfer market, rebuilding this squad and stamping his own identity over the past 18 months. The January window proved to be a fantastic one for ...
The post Ange Postecoglou talks up recruitment chiefs influence in exciting Celtic transfer update appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Rangers on alert over 'rebel three' as Super League plot causes major Champions League headache - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiELqwzUafJwtNZ3h8nwH6hwwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiY2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvY2VsdGljLXJhbmdlcnMtYWxlcnQtb3Zlci1yZWJlbC0yODI3NDczNtIBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T07:59:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Rangers on alert over 'rebel three' as Super League plot causes major Champions League headache  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hibs boss Lee Johnson in 'brainwashed' Celtic and Rangers defeatist attitude claim]]></title>
        <id>96906ba43dc4b6f9785c83d710bebab5</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23060159.hibs-boss-lee-johnson-brainwashed-celtic-rangers-defeatist-attitude-claim/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T07:54:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HIBS boss Lee Johnson insists that players in Scotland are brainwashed into thinking they cannot beat Celtic or Rangers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GREEN LIGHT FOR HAKSABANOVIC, JOTA STILL OUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/green-light-for-haksabanovic-jota-still-out/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/green-light-for-haksabanovic-jota-still-out/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T07:37:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FILIPE JOTA will not be rushed back into first-team action by boss Ange Postecoglou. The Portuguese winger was replaced at the interval in the dramatic late, late win over St Johnstone in Perth and missed the 2-0 loss to RB Leipzig and the 6-1 success over Hibs. There is no chance of Jota making his [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Postecoglou on Celtic’s Goalkeeper Situation]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/postecoglou-on-celtics-goalkeeper-situation/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/postecoglou-on-celtics-goalkeeper-situation/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T07:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU still has complete faith in Joe Hart as number one. The Englishman has had a few high profile errors but Ange knows Joe is the best goalkeeper at the club. The Aussie manager also praised Ben Seigrist, who started Celtic’s last cup game when the side beat Ross County. Scott Bain and B team […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Wednesday October 19: Paranoid ?]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=17998</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=17998"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T07:19:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will be without four key players tonight when they face Motherwell, Jota, Turnbull, Startfelt and MacGregor. It’s also not certain that they will have…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[POSTECOGLOU POSER]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/postecoglou-poser/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/postecoglou-poser/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T07:17:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU is swithering on a goalkeeper poser to see who plays against Motherwell at Fir Park tonight. Benji Siegrist, who arrived on a four-year deal in the summer after quitting Dundee United at the end of the season, played in the previous Premier Sports League Cup-tie against Ross County in Dingwall. The Swiss shotstopper [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable journalist: ‘Outstanding’ Celtic star may be getting frustrated with Ange]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-james-forrest-news-latest-rumours-gossip-postecoglou/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-james-forrest-news-latest-rumours-gossip-postecoglou/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T07:10:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star James Forrest may be frustrated by the lack of game time he has received under manager Ange Postecoglou this season, according to Sky Sports reporter Anthony Joseph. The Lowdown: Lack of minutes Despite signing a three-year contract extension with the Hoops this summer, the 31-year-old has thus far only featured once in the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Juranovic on Celtic Squad Dynamic]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/juranovic-on-celtic-squad-dynamic/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/juranovic-on-celtic-squad-dynamic/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T07:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOSIP JURANOVIC started on the bench at the weekend, with Anthony Ralston coming in for a rare league start. The Croatian full-back has come under some criticism lately, with some supporters believing his performances have dipped after such a great first season with the club. Like clockwork, fans have demanded Tony Ralston be handed a […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“At the moment it is absolutely irrelevant,” Fran’s focus on Dundee United]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/at-the-moment-it-is-absolutely-irrelevant-frans-focus-on-dundee-united/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/at-the-moment-it-is-absolutely-irrelevant-frans-focus-on-dundee-united/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T06:54:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a big cup tie on the horizon this weekend, Fran Alonso has told his players to forget all about that and concentrate instread on collecting three points this evening when Celtic FC Women visit Dundee United on Talladice Street for the very first time in SWPL1 action.It’s been a perfect start to the season Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“At the moment it is absolutely irrelevant,” Fran’s focus on Dundee United - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEAQibhHKhXWkxldD_2iPltkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiYWh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vYXQtdGhlLW1vbWVudC1pdC1pcy1hYnNvbHV0ZWx5LWlycmVsZXZhbnQtZnJhbnMtZm9jdXMtb24tZHVuZGVlLXVuaXRlZC_SAQA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T06:54:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“At the moment it is absolutely irrelevant,” Fran’s focus on Dundee United  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon sees former Celtic team-mate's punch line come true amid multiple Omonia warning signs - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEGHS7VCFqT8i_hWLgAEDIegqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiamh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvbmVpbC1sZW5ub24tbWFueS1vbW9uaWEtZm9yZXNoYWRvd2luZ3MtMjgyNzQzNjXSAQA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T06:43:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon sees former Celtic team-mate's punch line come true amid multiple Omonia warning signs  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lee Johnson’s Poorly Worded Celtic Claim]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/lee-johnsons-poorly-worded-celtic-claim/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/lee-johnsons-poorly-worded-celtic-claim/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T06:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LEE JOHNSON has claimed that players are “brainwashed” into believing they are defeated before playing Celtic or The Rangers. Celtic ran rampant at the weekend, thrashing Hibs 6-1, and, in all honesty, it could’ve and probably should’ve been more. The former Sunderland manager has expressed his amazement that The Rangers hadn’t been beaten by Motherwell […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘SCOUR THE WORLD,’ ANGE’S TRANSFER ACTION REPLAY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/scour-the-world-anges-transfer-action-replay/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/scour-the-world-anges-transfer-action-replay/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T06:34:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU is plotting a transfer action replay at the turn of the year. The Celtic boss is convinced the club’s swoop in the January window set them up for their charge towards their tenth title in 11 years. Postecoglou moved to bring in the J-League trio Reo Hatate, Daizen Maeda and Yosuke Ideguchi, Matt [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero Neil Lennon sacked just hours after Omonia Nicosia post-match media address - Glasgow Live]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEGqGlfPePJB8EAMUDbooIrcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow96D9CjDOy_QCMPvp0wU</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiS2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmdsYXNnb3dsaXZlLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2NlbHRpYy1oZXJvLW5laWwtbGVubm9uLXNhY2tlZC0yNTI5NzY2NNIBAA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T06:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero Neil Lennon sacked just hours after Omonia Nicosia post-match media address  Glasgow Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Best is yet to come': Celtic feel sky is limit for player who is clearly 'all in' for club]]></title>
        <id>3884983</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/best-is-yet-to-come-celtic-feel-sky-is-limit-for-player-who-is-clearly-all-in-for-club-3884983"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T06:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou believes Celtic are yet to see the best of new signing Sead Haksabanovic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic still swithering over goalkeeper selection for Motherwell cup clash]]></title>
        <id>3884965</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-still-swithering-over-goalkeeper-selection-for-motherwell-cup-clash-3884965"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T06:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou is deliberating whether to change his goalkeeper for this evening’s Premier Sports Cup quarter-final against Motherwell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Motherwell vs Celtic: TV channel, live stream & kick-off time]]></title>
        <id>7118349df271869f0b029de7030c5fac</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/23054548.motherwell-vs-celtic-tv-channel-live-stream-kick-off-time/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T06:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ALL of a sudden the latter stages of the League Cup are upon us.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou’s January Transfer Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/ange-postecoglous-exciting-january-transfer-plans/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/ange-postecoglous-exciting-january-transfer-plans/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T06:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LAST JANUARY, Celtic were brilliant in the transfer market, bringing in some top-quality players. REUTERS/Russell Cheyne O’Riley, Hatate and Maeda were all brought into the club, as were Kenny and Ideguchi. The Celtic manager has promised fans that the club is covering the globe as they prepare for the January transfer market to open, a […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic On This Day – 19th October – David Potter’s Celtic Diary]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-on-this-day-19th-october-david-potters-celtic-diary/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-on-this-day-19th-october-david-potters-celtic-diary/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Month 3, Day 19 of Celtic Historian David Potter’s new diary on The Celtic Star which will run throughout the new season and will highlight key Celtic-related events relevant to each day, today covering 19th October…SATURDAY 19 OCTOBER 190755,000 fans are somewhat disappointed when the Glasgow Cup final replay between Celtic and Rangers ends yet Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LENNY ON LOOK-OUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/lenny-on-look-out/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/lenny-on-look-out/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T05:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER two-time Celtic boss Neil Lennon is on the look-out for the new managerial post after being sacked by Omonia Nicosia. The Northern Irishman was dismissed by the Cypriot club just eight months after taking over from ex-Manchester United and Ibrox defender Henning Berg who was also axed by the club’s hierarchy. Bizarrely, Lennon was [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former SFA Performance Director Makes Celtic Star Claim]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/former-sfa-performance-director-makes-celtic-star-claim/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/former-sfa-performance-director-makes-celtic-star-claim/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T05:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic winger James Forrest has been grabbing a lot of headlines since his hat-trick for the club at the weekend which saw him become the thirtieth man in the clubs history reach 100 goals. Over the past 14 seasons, the Celtic academy graduate has scored in each season for the club and is currently the […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘OH HAMPDEN IN THE SUN: CELTIC 7 RANGERS 1’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/oh-hampden-in-the-sun-celtic-7-rangers-1/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/oh-hampden-in-the-sun-celtic-7-rangers-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T05:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT was 65 years ago today when Celtic enjoyed their biggest victory over old foes Rangers. With a certain display of elan and commendable timing, they chose a showpiece event, the League Cup Final, at the national stadium to mark the achievement. CQN rolls back the years to look at the famous encounter. Enjoy a [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Celtic’s Magnificent Seven as Perfect Start Continues]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/video-celtics-magnificent-seven-as-perfect-start-continues/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-celtics-magnificent-seven-as-perfect-start-continues/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T04:48:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic FC Women extended their unbeaten run in the SWPL as a day full of positives was rounded off with a convincing 7-0 win over Glasgow Women.The seven goals and the eighth successive clean sheet complimented an afternoon to remember, in which Jacynta and Clarissa Larisey hit their 10th goals of the season so far Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Celtic’s Magnificent Seven as Perfect Start Continues - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEBDr3T9Ufnu9WtKMNX5-er4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiVWh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vdmlkZW8tY2VsdGljcy1tYWduaWZpY2VudC1zZXZlbi1hcy1wZXJmZWN0LXN0YXJ0LWNvbnRpbnVlcy_SAQA?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T04:48:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Celtic’s Magnificent Seven as Perfect Start Continues  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Celtic’s Magnificent Seven as Perfect Start Continues - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CBMiVWh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vdmlkZW8tY2VsdGljcy1tYWduaWZpY2VudC1zZXZlbi1hcy1wZXJmZWN0LXN0YXJ0LWNvbnRpbnVlcy_SAVlodHRwczovL3RoZWNlbHRpY3N0YXIuY29tL3ZpZGVvLWNlbHRpY3MtbWFnbmlmaWNlbnQtc2V2ZW4tYXMtcGVyZmVjdC1zdGFydC1jb250aW51ZXMvYW1wLw</id>
        <link href="https://news.google.com/__i/rss/rd/articles/CBMiVWh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vdmlkZW8tY2VsdGljcy1tYWduaWZpY2VudC1zZXZlbi1hcy1wZXJmZWN0LXN0YXJ0LWNvbnRpbnVlcy_SAVlodHRwczovL3RoZWNlbHRpY3N0YXIuY29tL3ZpZGVvLWNlbHRpY3MtbWFnbmlmaWNlbnQtc2V2ZW4tYXMtcGVyZmVjdC1zdGFydC1jb250aW51ZXMvYW1wLw?oc=5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T04:48:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Celtic’s Magnificent Seven as Perfect Start Continues  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WAR GAMES: PART TWO: THE BRAWL IN BUENOS AIRES: ‘THE RIOT POLICE WERE OUT IN FORCE’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/war-games-part-two-the-brawl-in-buenos-aires-the-riot-police-were-out-in-force/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/war-games-part-two-the-brawl-in-buenos-aires-the-riot-police-were-out-in-force/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T04:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FIFTY-FIVE YEARS ago, Celtic were involved in three of the most infamous games in the club’s proud history. Yesterday was the anniversary of the first vicious encounter in the Parkhead club’s quest to conquer the world and win the first leg of the Intercontinental Cup Final against Argentina’s Racing Club of Buenos Aires. The confrontation at [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon offers Champions League support to Ange Postecoglou]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/neil-lennon-offers-champions-league-support-to-ange-postecoglou/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/neil-lennon-offers-champions-league-support-to-ange-postecoglou/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T04:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic manager Neil Lennon has offered his successor Ange Postecoglou support after Celtic failed to qualify for the Round of 16 in the Champions League. Lennon, who took his Celtic team to the Last 16 in the 2012/13 season, was full of support for the Australian and his team, who have impressed despite only Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: James Forrest on his reaching one hundred goals for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/video-james-forrest-on-his-reaching-one-hundred-goals-for-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-james-forrest-on-his-reaching-one-hundred-goals-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T04:06:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following Celtic’s 6-1 demolition of Hibernian on Saturday, James Forrest made it crystal clear to everyone that he is still a formidable force in the Celtic squad by scoring three of the six goals put past David Marshall.These three goals mean that Forrest has now scored 100 goals for Celtic, an achievement only accomplished by Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>