<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-07-25T01:02:24.328Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss makes Liel Abada claim amid exit rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42873</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/24/celtic-boss-makes-liel-abada-claim-amid-exit-rumours/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T23:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has plenty on his to do list at Celtic right now. Preparation for the new season is well underway and there seems to be a heavy focus on strengthening the squad. But it also very important to work closely with, carefully manage and improve the players who are already at Parkhead. Rodgers will […]
Celtic boss makes Liel Abada claim amid exit rumours - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic linked with move for Manchester City midfielder]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42886</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/24/celtic-linked-move-manchester-city/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T22:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already signed a couple of midfielders this summer. They brought in Odin Thiago Holm early on in the window from Valerenga. He is one of the biggest talents in Norwegian football right now and has even earned comparisons with Martin Odegaard. And recently, the Hoops also announced the signing of Kwon Hyeok-kyu from […]
Celtic linked with move for Manchester City midfielder - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic target agrees personal terms with Serie A club]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42883</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/24/celtic-target-agrees-terms-serie/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T20:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with a number of players in recent times. It will be interesting to see how many of the rumours are accurate and how many are not. One area where they clearly need to improve though is centre-back. The Hoops have struggled at the back ever since Cameron Carter-Vickers has been absent, […]
Celtic target agrees personal terms with Serie A club - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New signing already showing great Celtic confidence as first interview hits the spot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168433</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kwon-already-showing-great-celtic-confidence-as-first-interview-hits-the-spot/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T19:32:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyeokkyu Kwon is already proving to be popular with Celtic supporters after a confident first interview following the signing a five-year deal at the club....
The post New signing already showing great Celtic confidence as first interview hits the spot appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fields of Athenry – Christy Dignam Tribute]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58153</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/the-fields-of-athenry-christy-dignam-tribute/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T19:05:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are in Dublin this weekend to take on Wolves in a pre-season friendly at the Aviva Stadium. One of Dublin’s finest bands Aslan have just released their version of the “The Fields of Athenry” The last recording made by the band with their lead singer, Christy Dignam who sadly passed away recently. Christy will […]
The post The Fields of Athenry – Christy Dignam Tribute appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic make superb triple announcement ahead of new season]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42879</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/24/celtic-make-superb-triple-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T18:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic certainly appear to be moving in the right direction right now. They will have three trophies to defend next season, having won the domestic treble last time around under the management of Ange Postecoglou. On top of that, Brendan Rodgers’ side are guaranteed a place in the UEFA Champions League group stage as well. […]
Celtic make superb triple announcement ahead of new season - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Hartson's monster record fee condition for Celtic selling star to Spurs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168397</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/john-hartsons-monster-record-fee-condition-for-celtic-parting-with-reo-hatate/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Hartson says it’s a ’no-brainer’ for Reo Hatate to reunite with Ange Postecoglou at Tottenham Hotspur if a bid of ‘£45 million’ is put...
The post John Hartson's monster record fee condition for Celtic selling star to Spurs appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Women depart for pre-season camp; fixture details and schedule]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168416</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/celtic-women-depart-for-pre-season-camp-fixture-details-and-schedule/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Women are heading off to their preseason training camp in Gran Canaria as Fran Alonso prepares his side for the new season ahead. The...
The post Celtic Women depart for pre-season camp; fixture details and schedule appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic take in final training session in Japan before returning to Glasgow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168393</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-take-in-final-training-session-in-japan-before-returning-to-glasgow/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think it is fair to say that Celtic’s tour of Japan has certainly been a successful one. On the pitch, Brendan Rodgers got to...
The post Celtic take in final training session in Japan before returning to Glasgow appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers reacts as Celtic announce second signing of the day; more to come]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168408</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-reacts-as-celtic-announce-second-signing-of-the-day-more-to-come/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T14:08:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have announced the signing of South Korean midfielder Hyeoukkyu Kwon from Busan in his homeland. It’s the second signing that the Bhoys have announced...
The post Brendan Rodgers reacts as Celtic announce second signing of the day; more to come appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“He’s not as crazy as I thought he would be": SPFL newcomer on being managed by Celtic legend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168355</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/spfl-newcomer-shares-what-he-saw-from-former-celtic-hero-scott-brown-at-fleetwood-town/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Corrie Ndaba has recently joined Kilmarnock in the summer transfer window. The on-loan Ipswich defender has joined the Ayrshire club on loan until the end...
The post “He’s not as crazy as I thought he would be": SPFL newcomer on being managed by Celtic legend appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic announce new contract for long serving Women's first team star]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168379</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/celtic-announce-new-contract-for-chloe-craig/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have announced a new contract for Women’s defender Chloe Craig. The 29-year-old put pen to paper on a new three-year deal this afternoon as...
The post Celtic announce new contract for long serving Women's first team star appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic hero says he's urged Dermot Desmond to make ambitious Celtic move in Ireland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168358</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/pat-bonner-says-hes-urged-dermot-desmond-to-make-ambitious-celtic-move-in-ireland/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are a club that is known over the globe as a worldwide brand with huge commercial reach. The club is also renowned for its...
The post Former Celtic hero says he's urged Dermot Desmond to make ambitious Celtic move in Ireland appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic finally make long-awaited morning announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42876</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/24/celtic-make-long-awaited-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T12:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to strengthen their squad this summer, if they are to challenge for all three domestic titles this upcoming season and also make their presence felt in the UEFA Champions League group stages. That is easier said than done though, as they have lost a key player in the form of Jota, who has […]
Celtic finally make long-awaited morning announcement - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘GREAT ADDITION,’ RODGERS WELCOMES NEW BHOY YANG]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110220</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/great-addition-rodgers-welcomes-new-bhoy-yang/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T11:13:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS believes Yang Hyun-jun will add to Celtic’s firepower in the new season. The Hoops manager welcomed the South Korean to the champions after it was confirmed the K-League Young Player of the Year had signed a five-year contract. Yang, 21, agreed the switch – with the fee reported to be £2.1million – from [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Volume and variety from Hyunjun and Liel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110219</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/volume-and-variety-from-hyunjun-and-liel/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T11:11:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Still 21-years-old, Liel Abada is the same age Jota was when Benfica sent him out on a season long loan to Valladolid.  The insanely valuable talents of Jota were not evident at his mother club and remained hidden for his duration in Spain. Kyogo was 23 before he played top-flight football in Japan, also as [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic announce signing of Hyunjun Yang; Brendan Rodgers and player reaction, contract details]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168365</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-announce-signing-of-yang-hyun-jun-brendan-rodgers-and-player-reaction-contract-details/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have announced the signing of South Korean attacker Hyunjun Yang in an official statement on the club’s website. The club have been on the...
The post Celtic announce signing of Hyunjun Yang; Brendan Rodgers and player reaction, contract details appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INVINCIBLE OUT IN THE COLD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110215</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/invincible-out-in-the-cold/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T10:04:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOM ROGIC, one of Brendan Rodgers’ Invincibles during Celtic’s glorious undefeated treble-winning 2016/17 season, is still on the look-out for a new club. The stylish 30-year-old Australian midfielder was released by West Brom at the end of the season after the Midlands club failed to gain promotion to the English top flight. Rogic was signed [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spartak Moscow ready to make bid for key Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42868</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/24/spartak-moscow-key-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T09:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already lost one important player this summer in the form of Jota. The Portuguese winger departed Parkhead after two incredibly successful seasons in order to make a move to Al-Ittihad. He was instrumental to the Hoops’ successes under the management of Ange Postecoglou and thus, they will need to find a suitable replacement […]
Spartak Moscow ready to make bid for key Celtic player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On-loan Celtic striker backed by manager as open-goal miss compounds winless run]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168346</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/johnny-kenny-backed-by-manager-as-on-loan-celtic-strikers-open-goal-miss-compounds-winless-run/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T08:44:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-loan Celtic striker, Johnny Kenny was backed by Shamrock Rovers manager, Stephen Bradley, despite the 20-year-old’s open goal miss that contributed to his side’s 1-0...
The post On-loan Celtic striker backed by manager as open-goal miss compounds winless run appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic set to be made an offer for important first-team player]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168335</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/carl-starfelt-emerges-as-summer-transfer-target-as-club-prepare-offer-for-celtic-defender/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender, Carl Sarfelt, is reportedly a transfer target for Russian Premier League side, Spartak Moscow. Football Scotland claims that an offer is being prepared...
The post Report: Celtic set to be made an offer for important first-team player appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE IN A RAGE AFTER KANE STUNT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110210</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ange-in-a-rage-after-kane-stunt/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T07:44:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou was furious as he reacted to a Harry Kane stunt from a reporter. The Greek-Australian, who quit the treble winners after two years for Spurs last month, blew his top at a press conference before the friendly against Leicester City due in Bangkok which was subsequently washed out. Postecoglou has [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano: Steven Gerrard set to sign second ex-Celtic star; medical set]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168329</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/fabrizio-romano-steven-gerrard-set-to-sign-second-ex-celtic-star-medical-set/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T07:18:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano has confirmed that Steven Gerrard is set to add former Celtic defender, Jack Hendry, as his next summer signing at his new club...
The post Fabrizio Romano: Steven Gerrard set to sign second ex-Celtic star; medical set appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC £1.2m MISFIT IS EX-IBROX BOSS TARGET]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110207</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-1-2m-misfit-is-ex-ibrox-boss-target/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T07:06:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC misfit Jack Hendry has emerged as a shock target for Steven Gerrard at Saudi Arabia outfit Al-Ettifaq. The Scotland international centre-back, who cost Brendan Rodgers £1.2million when he arrived from Dundee in January 2018, is wanted by the former Ibrox boss who joined former Hoops fans’ favourite Filipe Jota in the Middle East earlier [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers delivers "exciting" pre-season Celtic squad assessment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168324</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-delivers-exciting-pre-season-celtic-squad-assessment/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T06:10:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers is seeing progress in his squad through this tough pre-season period and is heartened by the honesty flowing through the group,...
The post Brendan Rodgers delivers "exciting" pre-season Celtic squad assessment appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘HE WILL IMPROVE,’ BRENDAN’S GREEN LIGHT FOR ABADA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110198</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/he-will-improve-brendans-green-light-for-abada/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T06:05:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIEL ABADA has been given the green light to continue his career at Celtic after a face-to-face meeting with Brendan Rodgers. The Israeli international winger has been linked with a move away from the champions since he knocked back a contract extension at the same time as Giorgos Giakoumakis on November 1 last year. The [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premier League star addresses exit rumours after links to Celtic and Rodgers comments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168319</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/kieran-tierney-addresses-arsenal-future-after-links-to-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T05:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arsenal defender Kieran Tierney has admitted ‘it’s not up to him’ whether he stays at the club or heads elsewhere this summer, stating that he’ll...
The post Premier League star addresses exit rumours after links to Celtic and Rodgers comments appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost for Celtic: Private Brendan Rodgers chat convinces star of Bhoys future after exit rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168314</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/private-chat-with-brendan-rodgers-convinces-killer-instinct-celtic-star-to-stay/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T05:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has shared that Liel Abada wants a Celtic future, after having a private one-to-one chat with the winger in pre-season. There have been...
The post Boost for Celtic: Private Brendan Rodgers chat convinces star of Bhoys future after exit rumours appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COLLINS EXIT – AND TARGET THAT GOT AWAY: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Thirteen)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=94266</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/collins-exit-and-target-that-got-away-the-tommy-burns-story-part-thirteen/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T04:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS was preparing for his third year in charge of Celtic since returning as manager on July 12 1994. A Scottish Cup had been won in his first campaign in the dug-out, but the following term had seen the team fail on the domestic and European fronts. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE series, we chart [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Invincible hero set to join Steven Gerrard’s team]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42865</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/23/celtic-invincible-steven-gerrard-team/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T22:30:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans are not fond of Steven Gerrard and it is pretty simple to understand why. The Liverpool legend spent several years managing the Rangers. And while he did only manage to win one trophy during that period of time, it was a big one, as his team were able to stop the Hoops from […]
Celtic Invincible hero set to join Steven Gerrard’s team - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer insider delivers brilliant Tete to Celtic claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42861</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/23/transfer-insider-tete-celtic-claim/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T21:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Celtic brought back Brendan Rodgers for a second stint in the Parkhead hot seat, there were also rumours that the club were ready to sign some marquee players this summer in order to make sure that they could make an impact in the Champions League group stage next season. It remains to be seen […]
Transfer insider delivers brilliant Tete to Celtic claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Some people can’t wait to have a pop at him"; Kenny Dalglish defends Celtic star]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168309</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/some-people-cant-wait-to-have-a-pop-at-him-kenny-dalglish-defends-celtic-star/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T20:49:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend Kenny Dalglish has urged critics to take a “balanced view” of what Joe Hart has offered the Bhoys since signing for the club...
The post "Some people can’t wait to have a pop at him"; Kenny Dalglish defends Celtic star appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano confirms Celtic boss appreciates €20m winger]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42856</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/23/fabrizio-romano-celtic-20m-winger/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T19:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Jota leaving the club in order to join Al-Ittihad this summer in a £25 million transfer move, Celtic will need to bring in a top quality winger this summer in order to replace the Portuguese ace. He was a nailed on starter for the club for the past two seasons and had proven himself […]
Fabrizio Romano confirms Celtic boss appreciates €20m winger - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polish FA chief scout tips big things for incoming Celtic signing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168303</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/polish-fa-chief-scout-tips-big-things-for-incoming-celtic-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T19:29:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Incoming Celtic signing Maik Nawrocki has been tipped to be a mainstay of the Polish national team for many years by the Polish FA’s chief...
The post Polish FA chief scout tips big things for incoming Celtic signing appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed superb Cameron Carter-Vickers news]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42852</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/23/celtic-superb-carter-vickers-news/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T18:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic might have won the treble last season, but it is quite clear that they were not the same team after Cameron Carter-Vickers’ campaign came to an end in order to undergo surgery. The Hoops leaked goals in the last few Premiership matches and have not looked great defensively in pre-season either, conceding six against […]
Celtic handed superb Cameron Carter-Vickers news - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers dishes out praise to Celtic fringe players who impressed him in Japan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168199</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-dishes-out-praise-to-celtic-fringe-players-who-impressed-him-in-japan/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers named checked Celtic fringe players Liam Scales and Bosun Lawal when summing up the attitude and application he witnessed from his team in...
The post Brendan Rodgers dishes out praise to Celtic fringe players who impressed him in Japan appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[English club’s manager rules out move for Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42846</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/23/english-club-manager-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T16:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plenty of Celtic players have been linked with a move away from Parkhead this summer, whether that be on loan for the season or on a permanent basis. Pre-season training and friendly games will give Brendan Rodgers a chance to have a look at the squad available to him and make decisions about the futures […]
English club’s manager rules out move for Celtic player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andy Walker says it's 'surprising' some want 'dominant' Celtic player to leave]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168249</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/andy-walker-backs-criticised-celtic-star-surprised-at-recent-exit-debate/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andy Walker has expressed his ‘surprise’ at calls for Joe Hart to be replaced and leave Celtic despite his ‘dominant’ performances. Back in 2021, Celtic...
The post Andy Walker says it's 'surprising' some want 'dominant' Celtic player to leave appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EFL boss addresses transfer links with Celtic defender]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168286</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/bosun-lawal-admired-as-efl-boss-comments-on-transfer-links-with-celtic-defender/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Portsmouth boss, John Mousinho has denied that he is interested in young Celtic defender Bosun Lawal. The League One boss was asked about the links...
The post EFL boss addresses transfer links with Celtic defender appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The two Celtic players that impressed Gamba Osaka's Jiro Nakamura]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168228</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/how-callum-mcgregor-and-reo-hatate-impressed-gamba-osakas-jiro-nakamura/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Japan Tour has given the Celtic fans their first glimpse of their heroes and Brendan Rodgers tactics no less than three weeks until the...
The post The two Celtic players that impressed Gamba Osaka's Jiro Nakamura appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Brendan Rodgers decision that could save Celtic millions in the transfer market]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168279</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-brendan-rodgers-decision-that-could-save-celtic-millions-in-the-transfer-market/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic look set to continue their activity in the transfer market with the imminent announcements of Yang Hyun-jun and Kwon Hyeok-kyu and Legia Warsaw’s Polish...
The post The Brendan Rodgers decision that could save Celtic millions in the transfer market appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Totally dedicated": Alan Thompson on Celtic's Japanese Bhoys; shares insight on incoming Korean]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168251</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alan-thompsons-insight-on-kwon-hyeok-kyu-and-what-hes-been-told-about-celtics-japanese-bhoys/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s fair to say that when reports started breaking about Celtic looking at signing Kwon Hyeok-kyu and Yang Hyun-jun, the majority of the Celtic fans...
The post "Totally dedicated": Alan Thompson on Celtic's Japanese Bhoys; shares insight on incoming Korean appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gamba Osaka boss makes humorous Kyogo quip as Celtic duo impress in Japan Tour]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168246</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/gamba-osaka-boss-makes-humorous-kyogo-quip-as-celtic-duo-impress-in-japan-tour/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic signed off their Japan Tour with a 1-0 win over Gamba Osaka in Suita yesterday morning. Despite the 6-4 loss to Yokohama F Marinos,...
The post Gamba Osaka boss makes humorous Kyogo quip as Celtic duo impress in Japan Tour appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano: Former Celtic Invincible close to joining new club]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168238</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/fabrizio-romanos-moussa-dembele-update-ex-celtic-hero-close-to-joining-new-club/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T09:45:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker, Moussa Dembele is close to joining Saudi Arabian Pro League outfit, Al Ettifaq. 67 Hail Hail discussed ten days ago how the...
The post Fabrizio Romano: Former Celtic Invincible close to joining new club appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC CLEAR-OUT: TWO DOWN – EIGHT TO GO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110194</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-clear-out-two-down-eight-to-go/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T09:25:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIAM SHAW has signed a 12-month contract with Wigan – the former Sheffield Wednesday midfielder’s THIRD loan deal since joining Celtic in June 2021. The 22-year-old playmaker spent last season at Morecambe following a six-month stint at Motherwell the previous term. Shaw made 39 appearances for the English third-tier side lasty season, but has made only [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star on transfer rumours; identifies pre-season improvement the fans will love]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168231</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/reo-hatate-on-transfer-rumours-identifies-pre-season-improvement-the-celtic-fans-will-love/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder, Reo Hatate has been the subject of much transfer speculation over the last few months. The Japanese midfielder was in superb form for...
The post Celtic star on transfer rumours; identifies pre-season improvement the fans will love appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic triple announcement close as trio reach Glasgow]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42843</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/23/celtic-triple-announcement-close-trio/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T09:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic got two deals done early this summer, bringing in Odin Thiago Holm from Valerenga and Marco Tilio from Melbourne City FC. Since then, there have been plenty of rumours surrounding potential signings but no deal has been announced. That could end up changing very soon, as they get closer to a trio of players. […]
Celtic triple announcement close as trio reach Glasgow - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo's pre-season verdict of Brendan Rodgers and what his Celtic goal celebration really means]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168220</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kyogos-pre-season-verdict-of-brendan-rodgers-and-what-his-celtic-goal-celebration-really-means/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that the Japan Tour is over, the Celtic fans are digesting what they have witnessed in the first two fixtures under Brendan Rodgers. The...
The post Kyogo's pre-season verdict of Brendan Rodgers and what his Celtic goal celebration really means appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘MASSIVE CREDIT,’ BRENDAN HAILS BERNABEI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110167</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/massive-credit-brendan-hails-bernabei/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T07:11:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS was all smiles as he praised the stamina and determination of Alexandro Bernabei after the defender’s extraordinary goal as Celtic overcame Gamba Osaka in their final game of the Japan tour. The Argentinian full-back combined the woeful with the wonderful to unlock the hosts’ rearguard with only five minutes to go and the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HATATE AND THE HONEST ADMISSION]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110165</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hatate-and-the-honest-admission/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T06:49:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE has a crucial role to play for Celtic in the new season even though it looks unlikely he will join his countrymen Kyogo Furuhashi and Daizen Maeda in signing an enhanced contract with the champions. The 25-year-old Japanese international midfielder has terms with the Hoops until June 2026 following his January 2022 arrival [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three new Celtic signings arrive in Glasgow as club prepare for big announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168216</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/three-new-celtic-signings-arrive-in-glasgow-as-club-prepare-for-big-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T06:13:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic could make a triple transfer announcement over the next 48 hours after three new signings arrived in Glasgow to put the finishing touches to...
The post Three new Celtic signings arrive in Glasgow as club prepare for big announcement appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed big Cameron Carter-Vickers boost as Lennoxtown report emerges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168211</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-handed-big-cameron-carter-vickers-boost-as-lennoxtown-report-emerges/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T05:41:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Cameron Carter-Vickers is set to step up his return from injury over the next week after it was reported he resumed “full training”...
The post Celtic handed big Cameron Carter-Vickers boost as Lennoxtown report emerges appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo shoulder injury explained; overblown Celtic headlines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168201</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kyogo-shoulder-injury-explained-overblown-celtic-headlines/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T05:13:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Furuhashi continues to manage an ongoing shoulder issue but suggestions that Celtic have been struck with a ‘major injury blow’ seem inaccurate. It’s long...
The post Kyogo shoulder injury explained; overblown Celtic headlines appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…EYAL BERKOVIC?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110136</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-eyal-berkovic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T05:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EYAL BERKOVIC was Celtic’s record signing when he arrived in July 1999 in a £5.75million deal from West Ham. Rookie boss John Barnes and Director of Football Kenny Dalglish, the so-called ‘dream team’ who had replaced Jozef Venglos the previous month, reckoned the 27-year-old Israeli midfielder would become a pivotal figure in their plans to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CADETE ‘BAN’ BLOW-UP, SFA SUPREMO FARRY SACKED, TITLE FADE: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Twelve)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=94217</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/cadete-ban-blow-up-sfa-supremo-farry-sacked-title-fade-the-tommy-burns-story-part-twelve/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T04:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AFTER winning the Scottish Cup in his first season as Celtic manager following his appointment on July 12 1994, Tommy Burns’ driving ambition was to lift the championship. The Hoops had lost their way in challenges for the title that had last been won in such memorable fashion by Lisbon Lion Billy McNeill in the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player rejects chance to leave the club this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42822</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/22/celtic-player-rejects-chance-leave/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T22:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There appears to be so much transfer activity going on for Celtic right now that it is hard to keep up with all the potential moves. A number of fresh faces are expected to arrive over the coming days. But in amongst all the news, it looks like one player has turned down the chance […]
Celtic player rejects chance to leave the club this summer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ramon Vega believes £5m Celtic signing is not a good player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42835</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/22/ramon-vega-5m-celtic-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T21:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been pretty good when it comes to identifying the right talents over the past couple of years, bringing in players such as Kyogo, Reo Hatate, Cameron Carter-Vickers, Alistair Johnston, Matt O’Riley, Daizen Maeda and several others. That was not always the case though. In fact, their recruitment in the summer transfer window of […]
Ramon Vega believes £5m Celtic signing is not a good player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou appears to take dig at Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42830</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/22/ange-postecoglou-dig-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T19:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou was a massive success as Celtic manager. When the appointment was made, not many people gave him a chance. After all, he was pretty much an unknown in European football despite of his successes in Japan and Australia. It did not take him too long to prove himself at Parkhead though. Ultimately, he […]
Ange Postecoglou appears to take dig at Celtic player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic history made at Women's World Cup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168187</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/celtic-history-made-at-womens-world-cup/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T17:44:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic FC Women star Shen Mengyu has become the first ever Celtic player to represent their country at the Women’s World Cup, making history with...
The post Celtic history made at Women's World Cup appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports man delivers £4 million Celtic transfer update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42825</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/22/sky-sports-man-4-million-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T17:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already completed a few signings this summer. Odin Thiago Holm and Marco Tilio were brought in early on in the window. On the other hand, it is believed that they have gotten deals over the line for Kwon Hyeok-kyu and Yang Hyun-jun, even though they have not been officially announced yet. And now, […]
Sky Sports man delivers £4 million Celtic transfer update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expert Tim Vickery delivers verdict on Celtic's "exciting" South American transfer target]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168104</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/expert-tim-vickery-delivers-verdict-on-celtics-exciting-south-american-transfer-target/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T17:12:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Journalist Tim Vickery is one of the most respected English-language authorities on South American football, so when he talks about one of Celtic’s transfer targets...
The post Expert Tim Vickery delivers verdict on Celtic's "exciting" South American transfer target appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘VERY ENJOYABLE,’ ADMITS O’RILEY AFTER JAPAN ‘CHALLENGE’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110147</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/very-enjoyable-admits-oriley-after-japan-challenge/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T13:29:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY admitted it had been a challenge, but ultimately “very enjoyable” as Celtic finished their two-game tour of Japan with a 1-0 win over Gamba Osaka. The stylish midfielder came on as a second-half substitute as returning manager Brendan Rodgers rang the changes to make sure the players got crucial game time ahead of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GAMBA OSAKA 0 CELTIC 1: BERNABEI BREAKS OSAKA BARRIER]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110138</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/gamba-osaka-0-celtic-1-bernabei-breaks-osaka-barrier/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T12:13:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GAMBA OSAKA 0 CELTIC 1 ALEXANDRO BERNABEI proved to be the unlikely matchwinner as Celtic brought down the curtain on their week-long tour of Japan in Osaka. The Argentinian defender, a second-half substitute, is hardly a noted goalscorer, but you can’t fault the player’s timing. The game was heading for a scoreless stalemate with just [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic morning announcement goes under the radar]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42820</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/22/celtic-morning-announcement-goes-radar/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T12:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are in the middle of a very important summer transfer window. With Ange Postecoglou leaving the club for Tottenham Hotspur, Brendan Rodgers has been brought back for a second stint in the Parkhead hot seat. The Hoops might have enjoyed a lot of success over the past two seasons, but they will need to […]
Celtic morning announcement goes under the radar - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two XIs, first glimpse of Holm; The talking points after Celtic beat Gamba Osaka]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168159</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/two-xis-first-glimpse-of-holm-the-talking-points-after-celtic-beat-gamba-osaka/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T11:59:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have finished their Japan tour on a high with a 1-0 win over J-League outfit Gamba Osaka. Alexandro Bernabei was the goal hero, netting...
The post Two XIs, first glimpse of Holm; The talking points after Celtic beat Gamba Osaka appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: CELTIC FANS ‘AN IRREPLACEABLE TREASURE’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110134</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-celtic-fans-an-irreplaceable-treasure/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T09:58:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TWO blokes from farflung corners of the globe have been eulogising about Celtic over the past week or so. A chap from Yokohama in Japan and another from Athens, the capital of Greece, were clearly singing from the same hymn sheet. Reflecting fondly on his four years in the east end of Glasgow following his [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Josip Juranovic advises £4 million player to join Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42817</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/22/josip-juranovic-4-million-player-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T09:35:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are expected to complete several more signings before the summer transfer window closes. There have been rumours about marquee additions but we have seen nothing in that regard till now. The Hoops do seem to be closing in on a move for a very highly-rated and promising centre-back in order to strengthen their backline. […]
Josip Juranovic advises £4 million player to join Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic confirm season-long loan exit; EFL manager thanks Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168151</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/liam-shaw-speaks-as-celtic-confirm-loan-exit-shaun-maloney-thanks-bhoys/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T09:18:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wigan Athletic have signed midfielder Liam Shaw on a season-long loan from Celtic, it was confirmed by both clubs this morning. Shaw joined Celtic in...
The post Celtic confirm season-long loan exit; EFL manager thanks Bhoys appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic XI vs Gamba Osaka confirmed: 3 changes, new Bhoy on bench, TV details, instant reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168144</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-vs-gamba-osaka-confirmed-3-changes-tv-details-instant-reaction/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T08:54:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manager Brendan Rodgers has confirmed the Celtic team vs Gamba Osaka in this morning’s pre-season friendly from Japan. The full match squad is as follows:...
The post Celtic XI vs Gamba Osaka confirmed: 3 changes, new Bhoy on bench, TV details, instant reaction appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HART FAILURE? ‘I DON’T THINK RODGERS WILL BE LOSING TOO MUCH SLEEP,’ SUTTON]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110131</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hart-failure-i-dont-think-rodgers-will-be-losing-too-much-sleep-sutton/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T08:25:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CHRIS SUTTON insists Brendan Rodgers will not be too worried about Celtic’s goalkeeping position as he prepares the squad for the new season. There have been reports the returning boss has been examining the No.1 position – speculation that was heightened during the week when the Irishman was linked with Croatia World Cup hero Dominik Livakovic. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Josip Juranovic convinces £4m man to sign for Celtic; medical set]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168137</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/josip-juranovic-convinces-4m-man-to-sign-for-celtic-medical-set/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T06:49:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic right-back Josip Juranovic has helped convince Maik Nawrocki to sign for the Bhoys. Journalist Stephen McGowan of The Scottish Daily Mail [22/07 print...
The post Report: Josip Juranovic convinces £4m man to sign for Celtic; medical set appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RACE HOTS UP FOR CELTIC KID]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110109</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/race-hots-up-for-celtic-kid/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T06:32:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S kid stopper Bosun Lawal is a wanted man as the race for a loan deal hots up. English clubs are lining up a season-long temporary deal for the Hoops’ 20-year-old central defender. The impressive four times-capped Republic of Ireland Under-21 star has already been linked with English League One sides Portsmouth and Bristol Rovers, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rodgers confirms his next Celtic transfer priority position; first-team-ready signings coming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168131</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-confirms-his-next-celtic-transfer-priority-position-first-team-ready-signings-coming/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T06:19:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers has confirmed he is looking to bolster the central defensive area after being linked with a number of targets over the...
The post Rodgers confirms his next Celtic transfer priority position; first-team-ready signings coming appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton has Celtic worries but is heartened by recent transfer rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168128</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-has-celtic-concerns-but-is-heartened-by-recent-transfer-rumours/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton has urged Celtic supporters to shake off the mid-week defeat to Yokohama F.Marinos but has urged the Bhoys to get a move on...
The post Chris Sutton has Celtic worries but is heartened by recent transfer rumours appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers delivers firm message on Celtic transfers and available budget]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168119</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-delivers-firm-message-on-celtic-transfers-and-available-budget/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has insisted he hasn’t returned to the club to rip up the transfer model in place and work out with the...
The post Brendan Rodgers delivers firm message on Celtic transfers and available budget appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO AIMS FOR PERSONAL TOUCH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110105</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kyogo-aims-for-personal-touch/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T05:07:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO FURUHASHI is hoping to get the nod from Brendan Rodgers to play in some part of today’s game against Gamba Osaka for “personal reasons”. The Celtic talisman wasn’t risked to start the midweek 6-4 loss against Yokohama F Marinos and only made an appearance in the 67th minute as a substitute for hat-trick star [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…EDSON BRAAFHEID?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110081</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-edson-braafheid/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T05:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EDSON BRAAFHEID featured in the 2010 World Cup Final – just six weeks after getting the boot from Celtic. The 27-year-old Dutch left-back was brought in by Tony Mowbray on a short-term loan from Bayern Munich on February 1. Braafheid made only 12 appearances before the Hoops rejected the option of making his move permanent [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MONEY TALKS: RODGERS RAMPS UP RECRUITMENT DRIVE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110103</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/money-talks-rodgers-ramps-up-recruitment-drive/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T04:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is ready to ramp up his recruitment drive to strengthen Celtic for the new season with the Premiership due to kick off a fortnight today. The returning Hoops boss has been assessing the squad he inherited from Ange Postecoglou and is now set to put the jigsaw together. Rodgers has already brought in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CUP CRACKER AND DERBY DEADLOCKS: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Eleven)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=94176</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/cup-cracker-and-derby-deadlocks-the-tommy-burns-story-part-eleven/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T04:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS had won the Scottish Cup in his first season as Celtic manager after his appointment on July 12 1994. The league title, though, was his priority target and the legendary Celt came so tantalisingly and frustratingly close to achieving his aim during his second campaign. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE series, we chart Tommy Burns’ career as [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NAWROCKI ON THE BRINK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110101</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/nawrocki-on-the-brink/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-22T03:57:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[POLISH centre-back Maik Nawrocki is poised to become Celtic’s latest signing within the next 48 hours. The 22-year-old Legia Warsaw defender, who will cost a total of £5.2million, is said to be in Glasgow for a medical before signing a five-year deal with the champions, as reported in local media Super Express Sport. There was [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Managers Ranked! – Part Three]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18423</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18423"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T23:27:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve had the bad and the ugly, the good and the nearly good, so now it’s time to get to the business end of our…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kiwi Mick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero sends Kris Boyd message after Sky Sports move]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42779</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/21/celtic-hero-kris-boyd-message-sky-sports/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T22:30:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Viaplay are set to drop their UK football coverage. That will have an impact on the sponsorship of Scottish football trophies, of the national team and of course on the coverage of cup matches. That isn’t helpful news for football in the country at all. Celtic fans have been given something to be positive about […]
Celtic hero sends Kris Boyd message after Sky Sports move - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[€6 million player in Glasgow to undergo Celtic medical]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42811</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/21/6-million-player-glasgow-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T20:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already signed quite a few players this summer and are expected to add several more, as they reshape their squad in order to fit Brendan Rodgers’ vision and plans. One position that has been a bit of a worry for them is centre-back. They leaked goals at the end of last season and […]
€6 million player in Glasgow to undergo Celtic medical - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wolves complete popular Irish signing a week before Celtic Dublin clash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168112</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/wolves-complete-popular-irish-signing-a-week-before-celtic-dublin-clash/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wolves have made a signing that will go down well in Dublin, just a week before they face Celtic there. Brendan Rodgers‘ Hoops are currently...
The post Wolves complete popular Irish signing a week before Celtic Dublin clash appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The group of kids that got a special Celtic first-team experience on Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168106</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-group-of-kids-that-got-a-special-celtic-first-team-experience-on-friday/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic trained in Gamba Osaka’s Panasonic Stadium on Friday as their Japan tour continued. It’s been a busy few weeks for members of the Celtic...
The post The group of kids that got a special Celtic first-team experience on Friday appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable journalist offers £16m Fabian Rieder to Celtic update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42807</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/21/reliable-journalist-fabian-rieder-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T19:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Brendan Rodgers returning for a second stint in the Celtic hot seat, there have been plenty of rumours that the club want to make a few marquee additions to their squad this summer. Such news has excited the fans without doubt and one name that has been heavily linked with the Hoops is that […]
Reliable journalist offers £16m Fabian Rieder to Celtic update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic getting closer to next Rodgers signing; fee and clause details]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168081</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-getting-closer-to-defensive-signing-fee-and-clause-details/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T18:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are ‘closing in’ on the signing of Legia Warsaw defender Maik Nawrocki, it has been reported on Friday. Football Scotland journalist Mark Hendry states...
The post Report: Celtic getting closer to next Rodgers signing; fee and clause details appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing spotted in Japan training; closing in on first appearance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168092</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/new-celtic-signing-spotted-in-japan-training-closing-in-on-first-appearance/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Odin Thiago Holm is closing in on making his first-ever Celtic appearance this summer after being spotted training with the first team in Osaka on...
The post New Celtic signing spotted in Japan training; closing in on first appearance appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic superstar dealing with shoulder injury once again]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42804</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/21/celtic-superstar-dealing-shoulder-injury/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T17:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a big season coming up. Not only do they have three trophies to defend, having won the domestic treble in the previous campaign, but they also will be in the UEFA Champions League group stage. With Ange Postecoglou gone and Brendan Rodgers back in the Parkhead hot seat, it will be very interesting […]
Celtic superstar dealing with shoulder injury once again - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five new teams Celtic could face in the Champions League this season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168083</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/five-new-teams-celtic-could-face-in-the-champions-league-this-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic supporters around the world are waiting patiently for the UEFA Champions League group stage draw. Okay, we’ve still got the best part of six...
The post Five new teams Celtic could face in the Champions League this season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star seems impressed as journalist asks a question about his younger days]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168065</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-star-kyogo-furuhashi-seems-impressed-as-journalist-brings-up-his-younger-days/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic forward Kyogo Furuhashi is back in Osaka — and it’s a city that seems to mean a lot to him. His Celtic side have...
The post Celtic star seems impressed as journalist asks a question about his younger days appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks another Sold Out Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58122</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/thanks-another-sold-out-issue/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T15:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to everyone who bought a copy of the print edition of More than 90 Minutes Issue 127 which is now SOLD OUT. Good to see someone enjoying a pint while reading the latest issue in @darraghsbar in Belfast You can still read the fanzine by downloading the digital edition https://celticfanzine.com/…/more-than-90-minutes-issue…/ Never Miss A Copy […]
The post Thanks another Sold Out Issue appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic hero Aiden McGeady finds next playing role but that only tells half of the story]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168068</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-hero-aiden-mcgeady-finds-his-next-playing-role-but-that-only-tells-half-of-the-story/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T14:56:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic hero Aiden McGeady has found his next Scottish club and taken a new career step. The 37-year-old has signed a two-year deal with...
The post Former Celtic hero Aiden McGeady finds next playing role but that only tells half of the story appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why reported Celtic transfer target won't play for his club this weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168059</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/the-innocent-explanation-for-maik-nawrockis-legia-absence-amid-celtic-links/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T14:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reported Celtic transfer target Maik Nawrocki won’t play for Legia Warsaw this weekend. Legia begin their new Ekstraklasa campaign with a home clash against LKS...
The post Why reported Celtic transfer target won't play for his club this weekend appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic footage highlights the full extent of Brendan Rodgers hands-on approach]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168051</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-training-footage-highlights-the-full-extent-of-brendan-rodgers-hands-on-approach/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers likes to get his hands dirty during Celtic training. It’s something we’ve covered already this summer. Hoops training will be different under Rodgers,...
The post Celtic footage highlights the full extent of Brendan Rodgers hands-on approach appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two English clubs make moves to sign Celtic defender]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42802</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/21/two-english-clubs-celtic-defender/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T13:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are expected to bring in a lot of fresh faces in the ongoing summer transfer window in order to reshape the squad to fit Brendan Rodgers’ vision and plans. At the same time though, there are quite a few at the club, who do not seem to have a place in the first-team right […]
Two English clubs make moves to sign Celtic defender - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo comes in to his own after being asked about Celtic by Japanese reporter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168045</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kyogo-furuhashi-comes-in-to-his-own-after-being-asked-about-celtic-by-japanese-reporter/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T11:56:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic forward Kyogo Furuhashi was in front of the media in Japan on Friday. The Hoops first-team have travelled west from Yokohama and are now...
The post Kyogo comes in to his own after being asked about Celtic by Japanese reporter appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ambitious technology move FIFA are testing right now; could be seen at Celtic Park one day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168039</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-ambitious-var-move-fifa-are-testing-right-now-could-be-seen-at-celtic-park-one-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T11:23:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FIFA are currently testing an ambitious VAR move that could be seen at Celtic Park one day. The governing body’s Women’s World Cup got underway...
The post The ambitious technology move FIFA are testing right now; could be seen at Celtic Park one day appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If not on the wing, where does Maeda find space?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110086</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/if-not-on-the-wing-where-does-maeda-find-space/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T11:01:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers post-match press conference in Yokohama was interesting on two fronts.  Almost a year after sustaining a shoulder injury, the manager revealed Kyogo did not start the game as the same issue left him short of the fitness levels even his team-mates were at.  If the medics have not resolved the issue by now, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ideguchi link, upward curve, ex Premiership attacker; What to expect from Gamba Osaka vs Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168032</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/ideguchi-link-upward-curve-ex-premiership-attacker-what-to-expect-from-gamba-osaka-vs-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T10:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic play their second and final game of the Japan tour against Gamba Osaka on Saturday. The Hoops took part in a manic 6-4 defeat...
The post Ideguchi link, upward curve, ex Premiership attacker; What to expect from Gamba Osaka vs Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic close to signing €6 million player this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42798</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/21/celtic-close-signing-6-million-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T10:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already made quite a few signings this summer, bringing in Odin Thiago Holm and Marco Tilio, while they are believed to be on the verge of announcing the arrivals of Yang Hyun-jun and Kwon Hyeok-kyu as well. All of them are very talented young players and might have bright futures ahead of them, […]
Celtic close to signing €6 million player this summer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOOPS KID IN DEMAND]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110077</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hoops-kid-in-demand-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T07:54:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BOSUN LAWAL is on the brink of a loan move from Celtic to gain some valuable game-time in the new season. The 20-year-old centre-back impressed former boss Ange Postecoglou after arriving from Watford two years ago. However, Lawal is still awaiting his Hoops first-team debut and new gaffer Brendan Rodgers may be willing to allow [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO ‘ISSUE’ AS RODGERS HAILS DAIZAN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110071</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kyogo-issue-as-rodgers-hails-daizan/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T07:12:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has revealed the reason last season’s 34-goal top scorer Kyogo Furuhashi didn’t start the midweek friendly against Yokohama F Marinos. The prolific hitman remained on the substitutes’ bench until the 67th minute before replacing hat-trick ace Daizen Maeda in the side’s 6-4 loss. Rodgers explained: “Kyogo has obviously been brilliant for Celtic. But he’s [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Celtic star left "buzzing" with what he's heard from Brendan Rodgers so far; squad morale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168026</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/greg-taylor-left-buzzing-with-what-hes-heard-from-brendan-rodgers-so-far-celtic-squad-morale/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T06:50:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Taylor can’t hide his excitement about what’s ahead under Brendan Rodgers at Celtic, admitting his been left “buzzing” with some of the comments made...
The post One Celtic star left "buzzing" with what he's heard from Brendan Rodgers so far; squad morale appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£5.2m NAWROCKI: CELTIC v GALATASARAY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110066</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/5-2m-nawrocki-celtic-v-galatasaray/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T05:45:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC are locked in a £5.2million transfer tug-of-war with Turkish giants Galatasaray for Polish centre-back Maik Nawrocki. The Hoops have made their move for the 22-year-old Legia Warsaw star in a bid to strengthen their central defence, as CQN reported yesterday. Original fees of around the £4million mark have been dwarfed as the figure has climbed [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rodgers signals one Celtic star will be used very differently under his watch; tactical change]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168021</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-signals-celtic-tactical-change-one-will-be-used-very-differently/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T05:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has stated he prefers Daizen Maeda used as a central attacking option, rather than placing him out on the wing. Under...
The post Rodgers signals one Celtic star will be used very differently under his watch; tactical change appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers confirms Kyogo fitness issue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168016</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-confirms-kyogo-fitness-issue/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T05:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic striker Kyogo Furuhashi has been struggling with a shoulder problem during this pre-season period, which is why he didn’t feature from the start against...
The post Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers confirms Kyogo fitness issue appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…FREDDIE LJUNBERG?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110059</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-freddie-ljunberg/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T05:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FREDDIE LJUNGBERG, one of Arsenal’s Invincibles in season 2003/04, was 33 by the time he arrived at Celtic. It is fair to say he was past his best by the time he signed terms on December 30 2010 and made a quickfire debut in a 2-0 Scottish Cup win over Berwick Rangers at Shielfield 10 [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE PERFECT FAILURE: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Ten)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=94068</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-perfect-failure-the-tommy-burns-story-part-ten/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T04:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS had won the Scottish Cup in his first season as Celtic manager after his appointment on July 12 1994. The league title, though, was his priority target and the legendary Celt came so tantalisingly and frustratingly close to achieving his aim during his second campaign. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE series, we chart Tommy [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers addresses Anthony Ralston’s Celtic future]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42708</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/20/brendan-rodgers-anthony-ralston-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T22:38:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the departure of Ange Postecoglou and the subsequent arrival of Brendan Rodgers, the Celtic fans have witnessed a paradigm shift. In the aftermath of a decision that saw the Australian parting ways with the Scottish champions and moving to Tottenham Hotspur, the Hoops turned to the Northern Irishman, a familiar face, for the most […]
Brendan Rodgers addresses Anthony Ralston’s Celtic future - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jyotirmoy Halder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player linked with £10 million-plus summer exit]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42789</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/20/celtic-player-10-million-plus-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T21:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There have been rumours that Celtic could try to make a few marquee signings this summer. Of course, those kind of suggestions have been very successful in getting the fans excited but till now, they have not led to anything of substance. Let’s see if that changes as we head into the later weeks of […]
Celtic player linked with £10 million-plus summer exit - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers singles out 'exceptional' Celtic performer vs Yokohama FM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168010</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-singles-out-exceptional-celtic-performer-vs-yokohama-fm/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T20:47:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers isn’t reading too much into Wednesday’s 6-4 Celtic defeat at the hands of Yokohama F.Marinos, setting out the variety of factors that always...
The post Brendan Rodgers singles out 'exceptional' Celtic performer vs Yokohama FM appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's total summer spend so far as Bhoys enter new phase of transfer window]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=168004</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-total-summer-spend-so-far-as-bhoys-enter-new-phase-of-transfer-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T20:01:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has always maintained his first few weeks at Celtic would be one of assessment. He’s had a good look at the squad available...
The post Celtic's total summer spend so far as Bhoys enter new phase of transfer window appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic submit €6 million transfer bid for centre-back]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42786</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/20/celtic-submit-6-million-bid-centre-back/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T19:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already made quite a few additions to their ranks this summer as they aim to retain three trophies and make their presence felt in the Champions League group stage, now that Brendan Rodgers is back in the Parkhead hot seat. Marco Tilio and Odin Thiago Holm have already arrived, while the belief is […]
Celtic submit €6 million transfer bid for centre-back - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How much Viaplay are worth to Celtic and Scottish football; immediate concerns addressed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167996</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/how-much-viaplay-are-worth-to-celtic-and-scottish-football-immediate-concerns-addressed/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The news about Viaplay pulling out of the UK market over time has certainly generated a fair amount of headlines today. Suggestions of chaos and...
The post How much Viaplay are worth to Celtic and Scottish football; immediate concerns addressed appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's next transfer priority is clear after first wave of signings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167990</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-next-transfer-priority-is-clear-after-first-wave-of-signings/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T18:19:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer rumours have actually been few and far between this summer, so when a number of articles appear addressing a specific department of the...
The post Celtic's next transfer priority is clear after first wave of signings appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic join transfer race to sign €5 million-rated player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42783</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/20/celtic-transfer-race-5-million-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T18:05:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a lot of positions across the pitch where Celtic could do with reinforcements, following the arrival of Brendan Rodgers for a second stint in the Parkhead hot seat. One of them is centre-back. Cameron Carter-Vickers is recovering after undergoing surgery, which has left Carl Starfelt, Yuki Kobayashi and Stephen Welsh as options while […]
Celtic join transfer race to sign €5 million-rated player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic confirm upcoming plans after change of scenery in Japan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167939</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-confirm-upcoming-plans-after-change-of-scenery-in-japan/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have announced the finer details for the rest of the team’s stay in Japan. The squad flew in to the country on Monday and...
The post Celtic confirm upcoming plans after change of scenery in Japan appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premiership club have no plans to increase Celtic away allocation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167977</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/premiership-club-have-no-plans-to-increase-celtic-away-allocation/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kilmarnock have referenced the decision to halve the Celtic allocation for games at Rugby Park in a fresh report. On Thursday the Ayrshire side released...
The post Premiership club have no plans to increase Celtic away allocation appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["What shocked me the most" - Brendan Rodgers left stunned by Japanese reception for Celtic duo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167943</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-overwhelmed-by-japanese-crowds-love-for-celtics-daizen-maeda-and-tomoki-iwata/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic kicked off their Japan Tour with a 6-4 defeat to Yokohama F Marinos yesterday, there was still positives to take away from the...
The post "What shocked me the most" - Brendan Rodgers left stunned by Japanese reception for Celtic duo appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Maik Nawrocki said recently about his future; how much he would likely cost Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167969</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-maik-nawrocki-said-recently-about-his-future-how-much-he-would-be-likely-to-cost-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reported Celtic transfer target Maik Nawrocki has been asked about his future already this summer. The Legia Warsaw central-defender is the latest player to be...
The post What Maik Nawrocki said recently about his future; how much he would likely cost Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda drops two intriguing tactical tweaks that Brendan Rodgers is applying at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167938</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/daizen-maeda-drops-two-intriguing-tactical-tweaks-that-brendan-rodgers-is-applying-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new Brendan Rodgers era has kicked off as the Celtic fans got their first real glimpse of what kind of football they are likely...
The post Daizen Maeda drops two intriguing tactical tweaks that Brendan Rodgers is applying at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Fans Continue Japanese Adventure]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58110</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-fans-continue-japanese-adventure/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T14:37:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans continue their Japanese adventure after yesterdays 6-4 defeat to Yokahoma. They will now start make the 500k journey to Osaka on the famous bullet train for the Gamba Game. Yokohama F. Marinos and Celtic fans had plenty to cheer with the ball hitting the back of the net 10 times. The J. League […]
The post Celtic Fans Continue Japanese Adventure appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kieran Tierney and Giorgos Giakoumakis want Celtic fans to know all about their meeting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167942</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kieran-tierney-and-giorgos-giakoumakis-want-celtic-fans-to-know-all-about-their-meeting/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T14:29:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic pair Kieran Tierney and Giorgos Giakoumakis met in Washington on Wednesday night. They were playing for opposing sides in the annual MLS All-Star...
The post Kieran Tierney and Giorgos Giakoumakis want Celtic fans to know all about their meeting appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some pleasing Allan McGregor comments as he finishes firmly second best to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167931</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/some-pleasing-allan-mcgregor-comments-as-he-finishes-firmly-second-best-to-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Rangers goalkeeper Allan McGregor has been speaking about the Ibrox side’s performance during a period of utter Celtic dominance. It’s been a glorious spell to support Celtic over past seven seasons. Since Brendan Rodgers first arrived at the club in 2016, we’ve won five trebles and a total of 17 domestic trophies from 21. ...
The post Some pleasing Allan McGregor comments as he finishes firmly second best to Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>