<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-08-03T10:10:27.605Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two referees step back from on-field duties as VAR changes come in for Celtic opener]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169796</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/two-referees-step-back-from-on-field-duties-as-var-changes-come-in-for-celtic-opener/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T09:40:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SFA have made changes to their VAR operations ahead of Celtic’s league opener this weekend. The Hoops get the new Premiership season underway on...
The post Two referees step back from on-field duties as VAR changes come in for Celtic opener appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic interested in move for 29-year-old free agent]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43119</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/03/celtic-interested-move-free-agent/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T08:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have signed five highly-rated youngsters this summer till now. All of them have the potential to be key players for the Hoops in the future. At the same time though, they will need to bring in some experience as well, if they are to defend the three domestic titles and make a mark in […]
Celtic interested in move for 29-year-old free agent - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["He is different"; The Celtic squad sound buzzing to be working with Brendan Rodgers right now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169790</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/he-is-different-the-celtic-squad-sound-buzzing-to-be-working-with-brendan-rodgers-right-now/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Forrest is the latest Celtic player to laud the methods of manager Brendan Rodgers this summer as the feel-good factor continues heading into the...
The post "He is different"; The Celtic squad sound buzzing to be working with Brendan Rodgers right now appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHY JOE HART WILL BE No.1 ON FLAG DAY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110587</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/why-joe-hart-will-be-no-1-on-flag-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T06:59:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART will be in goal when Celtic kick off the Premiership campaign on Flag Day against Ross County at Parkhead on Saturday. There has been recent conjecture over the future of the 36-year-old 75 times-capped England international who is going into the final 12 months of his Hoops contract. Hart answered an SOS from [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The latest on Celtic transfer rumours surrounding exciting South American attacker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169784</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/the-latest-on-celtic-transfer-rumours-surrounding-brazilian-winger-tete/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T06:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summer transfer window rumours have been few and far between in a Celtic context recently but one name that has consistently appeared as a discussion...
The post The latest on Celtic transfer rumours surrounding exciting South American attacker appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MAKE-OR-BREAK FOR ‘EXCELLENT’ TURNBULL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110574</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/make-or-break-for-excellent-turnbull/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T05:57:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAVID TURNBULL has been branded “excellent” by Brendan Rodgers in acknowledgement of the midfielder’s form during the pre-season games. The Scotland international has impressed the returning Hoops boss and he caught the eye again with a composed finish for the winning goal against Athletic Bilbao in James Forrest’s testimonial match at Parkhead. The 24-year-old playmaker [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 3 Celtic players heading for exit this month; unlikely to play in Hoops again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169780</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/the-3-celtic-players-heading-for-exit-this-month-unlikely-to-play-in-hoops-again/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T05:45:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Brendan Rodgers has been keen to stress it’s a ‘clean slate’ for the majority of the Celtic squad heading into the new season, three...
The post The 3 Celtic players heading for exit this month; unlikely to play in Hoops again appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rodgers hands hope to Celtic player with just 9 starts last season; manager left impressed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169777</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-hands-hope-to-david-turnbull-celtic-boss-left-impressed/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T05:16:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has handed hope to David Turnbull that he can play a significant role at the Hoops this season. Turnbull came off...
The post Rodgers hands hope to Celtic player with just 9 starts last season; manager left impressed appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIG YOGI: PUTTING THE RECORD STRAIGHT (Part Two)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=94905</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/big-yogi-putting-the-record-straight-part-two/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T04:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC great John ‘Yogi’ Hughes passed away on August 1 2022 at the age of 79 following a short illness. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE, Alex Gordon, who co-authored the fans’ favourite’s autobiography, ‘Yogi Bare: The Life and Times of a Celtic Legend’, presents Part Two of ‘Putting The Record Straight’, selected from his friend’s 2014 [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GERS ‘TROUBLEMAKERS’ BLASTED, SAD END FOR McSTAY: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Twenty-three)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=94758</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/gers-troublemakers-blasted-sad-end-for-mcstay-the-tommy-burns-story-part-twenty-three/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-03T04:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS was witnessing Celtic’s title bid disintegrating during the defining month of March during the turbulent 1996/97 crusade. The fans’ favourite had returned to the club on July 12 1994 and had won the Scottish Cup in his debut campaign. That was followed by a barren term and all eyes were on the boss [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two clubs enquire about signing forgotten Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43094</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/02/two-clubs-forgotten-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T23:04:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is likely that we will see an increased focus on exits from the Celtic squad in what remains of the summer transfer window. There are too many players in the squad currently. Some of them are nowhere near the first-team picture at this point in time and thus, parting ways would make sense for […]
Two clubs enquire about signing forgotten Celtic player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic not interested in €20m player despite rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43110</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/02/celtic-20m-player-despite-rumours/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T21:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Brendan Rodgers was appointed as the Celtic manager for the second time in his career, rumours broke out that the club were looking to make some marquee signings this summer in order to back the Northern Irishman. Till now, that has not happened but with a month left in the transfer window, there is […]
Celtic not interested in €20m player despite rumours - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans must be delighted with journalist’s Brendan Rodgers claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43105</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/02/celtic-journalist-brendan-rodgers-claim/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T20:02:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a promising pre-season campaign that saw them lose only one game, Celtic will begin their Premiership title defence this weekend against Ross County. Brendan Rodgers has a point to prove as well, as he is back in the Parkhead hot seat for a second stint, having been shown the exit door by Leicester City […]
Celtic fans must be delighted with journalist’s Brendan Rodgers claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Explained: UEFA's homegrown quota rules and what they mean for Celtic this season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169699</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/explained-uefas-homegrown-quota-rules-and-what-they-mean-for-celtic-this-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will have to name their squad for this season’s UEFA competition in the not too distant future. Brendan Rodgers‘ side will begin their Champions...
The post Explained: UEFA's homegrown quota rules and what they mean for Celtic this season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic-linked player set to join Ajax in £17 million deal]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43101</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/02/celtic-linked-player-ajax-17-million/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:31:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with some very highly-rated young players in the ongoing summer transfer window. They have brought in five already in the form of Odin Thiago Holm, Yang Hyun-jun, Kwon Hyeok-kyu, Marco Tilio and Maik Nawrocki. Fans would be hoping for a few more signings over the coming month. Another player who was […]
Celtic-linked player set to join Ajax in £17 million deal - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Celtic fans helped the SPFL hit record attendances in season 2022/23]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169739</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/how-celtic-fans-helped-the-spfl-hit-record-attendances-in-season-2022-23/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Football in Scotland is followed by one of the most passionate supporter bases in the game. We might not have the glamour of the English...
The post How Celtic fans helped the SPFL hit record attendances in season 2022/23 appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Under the radar; Odin Thiago Holm reacts online to Celtic Park debut]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169770</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/under-the-radar-odin-thiago-holm-reacts-online-to-celtic-park-debut/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Odin Thiago Holm has had his say online after making his Celtic Park debut. The Norwegian was part of the second-half side who turned around...
The post Under the radar; Odin Thiago Holm reacts online to Celtic Park debut appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s attacking options could make this a season to remember]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169751</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/celtics-attacking-options-could-make-this-a-season-to-remember/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Celtic fans can take anything away from what we have witnessed this preseason, it’s that we have seen two sides to this Celtic team...
The post Celtic’s attacking options could make this a season to remember appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The last Celtic allocation at Pittodrie as away fans prepare to be squeezed further this season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169756</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-last-celtic-allocation-at-pittodrie-as-away-fans-prepare-to-be-squeezed-further-this-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T16:10:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans will soon hear about arrangements for our upcoming trip to Pittodrie. The Hoops visit Aberdeen on Sunday 13 August in our first domestic...
The post The last Celtic allocation at Pittodrie as away fans prepare to be squeezed further this season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The eight players representing Celtic as Masters Football returns for 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169743</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-eight-players-representing-celtic-as-masters-football-makes-a-return-for-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Masters Football will make a return in 2023 with Celtic once against fielding a team. The blue pitch six-a-side game was made popular by Sky...
The post The eight players representing Celtic as Masters Football returns for 2023 appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star Joe Hart and world football react as Italy legend announces retirement on Instagram]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169708</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-star-joe-hart-and-world-football-react-as-italy-legend-announces-retirement-on-instagram/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T14:42:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The word ‘legend’ is so overused in the world of football these days. Last night, Celtic paid tribute to their very one legend in James...
The post Celtic star Joe Hart and world football react as Italy legend announces retirement on Instagram appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Master at work"; Journalist with excellent recent Celtic access shares his findings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169711</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/master-at-work-journalist-with-excellent-recent-celtic-access-shares-his-findings/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A journalist who had exceptional access to Celtic during the team’s trip to Japan has shared some thoughts. The Daily Record’s Michael Gannon was sent...
The post "Master at work"; Journalist with excellent recent Celtic access shares his findings appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘HE DESERVES IT,’ CELTIC HERO GRANT BACKS FORREST TO BREAK HIS RECORD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110569</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/he-deserves-it-celtic-hero-grant-backs-forrest-to-break-his-record/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T14:04:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JAMES FORREST is zeroing in on Peter Grant’s Celtic appearance record. The evergreen Hoops winger, who was honoured with a testimonial match which was won 3-2 against Athletic Bilbao, has played 467 games for the first team since his goalscoring debut in a 4-0 home league win over Motherwell on May 1 2010. Former fans’ [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic 3 Bilbao 2. All in all a good day and night out following the Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58212</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-3-bilbao-2-all-in-all-a-good-day-and-night-out-following-the-bhoys/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T13:13:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Forest has never been a chest pumping, badge kissing type of Celtic player and he deserved his night out in Celtic Park last night. Tens of thousands of Celtic fans turned up to thank him for his contribution to our club. From he broke into the first team from the youth set up he’s […]
The post Celtic 3 Bilbao 2. All in all a good day and night out following the Bhoys appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Early television selections will see Celtic play after rivals more often than not]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169702</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/early-television-selections-will-see-celtic-play-after-rivals-more-often-than-not/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T12:40:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The early Premiership television selections will see Celtic play after our rivals more often than not. We’re now a matter of days away from the...
The post Early television selections will see Celtic play after rivals more often than not  appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers impressed by Celtic summer signing]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43095</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/02/brendan-rodgers-impressed-celtic-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T12:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers had a lot to be happy about going into the new campaign. His team ended pre-season on a positive note, with a 3-2 win over Athletic Bilbao in James Forrest’s testimonial match. At the same time, he got a warm reception from the Celtic Park crowd, as it looks like the fears of […]
Brendan Rodgers impressed by Celtic summer signing - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More to come as the Celtic support are treated to some new culinary delights]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169692</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/more-to-come-as-the-celtic-support-are-treated-to-some-new-culinary-delights/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic support were treated to some new culinary delights on Tuesday evening. The first-team were returning to Celtic Park for the first-time in nine...
The post More to come as the Celtic support are treated to some new culinary delights appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Decision beckons for Celtic as clubs enquire about out of favour midfielder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169687</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/decision-beckons-for-celtic-as-clubs-enquire-about-ismaila-soro/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has added five new faces to the Celtic squad this summer. And with that, there comes a balancing act as we all know...
The post Report: Decision beckons for Celtic as clubs enquire about out of favour midfielder appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ignore the delightful and the dreadful]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110568</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ignore-the-delightful-and-the-dreadful/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T11:01:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best news of the week is the return to action of three injured central defenders.  Cameron Carter-Vickers, out since April recuperating after an operation, started last night’s game.  He was partnered by new-signing Maik Nawrocki.  Both were swapped out at halftime but should be ready for a fuller challenge against Ross County on Saturday. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Celtic stars with big question marks have come flying out of pre-season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169678</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/three-celtic-stars-with-big-question-marks-have-come-flying-out-of-pre-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pre-season is now over for Celtic and there’s a fair chance you’re pretty happy about that. Sure, after six weeks or so of no Hoops...
The post Three Celtic stars with big question marks have come flying out of pre-season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton believes Celtic winger has 'an opportunity' after Jota exit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169669</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-believes-celtic-winger-has-an-opportunity-after-jota-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The loss of Jota this summer is one that took every Celtic supporter by surprise. The Portuguese star was a huge fan favourite and his...
The post Chris Sutton believes Celtic winger has 'an opportunity' after Jota exit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rodgers plays it cool over Celtic man but fans have already witnessed something exciting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169667</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/rodgers-plays-it-cool-over-carter-vickers-but-celtic-fans-have-already-witnessed-something-exciting/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers was playing it cool over the fitness of Cameron Carter-Vickers after Tuesday’s win over Athletic Club. The American defender made his long-awaited return...
The post Rodgers plays it cool over Celtic man but fans have already witnessed something exciting appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IDEAL HOLM’S EXHIBITION]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110562</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ideal-holms-exhibition/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T09:25:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NORWEGIAN new Bhoy Odin Thiago Holm made a distinct first impression on Brendan Rodgers when he made his Parkhead debut last night. The 20-year-old midfielder, a £2.5million buy from Valerenga in June, came on after the interval with the Hoops trailing 2-1 to Athletic Bilbao in James Forrest’s Testimonial Match. The first-half focus of the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers looks forward to Flag Day with rousing title message]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169662</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-looks-forward-to-flag-day-with-rousing-title-message/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Forrest’s testimonial brings pre-season to an end for Celtic. Now the fans can look forward to Saturday afternoon when the Hoops legend will have...
The post Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers looks forward to Flag Day with rousing title message appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Athletic Bilbao beautiful message to Celtic after friendly]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43089</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/02/athletic-bilbao-message-celtic-friendly/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T09:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s pre-season campaign came to an end with a 3-2 win over Athletic Bilbao. The Spanish giants went ahead twice, but ultimately, the Hoops came out on top. Reo Hatate, Alexandro Bernabei and David Turnbull were the three players to find the back of the net for the Scottish champions on the day. It was […]
Athletic Bilbao beautiful message to Celtic after friendly - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["He's a terrific footballer"; Peter Grant impressed with Celtic fringe player's preseason form]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169590</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/hes-a-terrific-footballer-peter-grant-impressed-with-celtic-fringe-players-preseason-form/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has to be said, one of the most impressive parts of this preseason is how some players seem to have instantly improved under the...
The post "He's a terrific footballer"; Peter Grant impressed with Celtic fringe player's preseason form appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Athletic Club send classy message to Celtic after defeat at Paradise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169619</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/athletic-club-send-classy-message-to-celtic-after-defeat-at-paradise/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Forrest’s testimonial was certainly a game that showed us two faces to this Celtic side. The side that has concentration lapses and the side...
The post Athletic Club send classy message to Celtic after defeat at Paradise appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘IT’S EVERYONE’S NIGHT,’ FORREST SHARES THE PRAISE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110505</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/its-everyones-night-forrest-shares-the-praise/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T07:17:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JAMES FORREST shared the spotlight on his special evening in the east end of Glasgow with fans, family, friends and team-mates. The evergreen Celt was honoured with a testimonial match against Athletic Bilbao at Parkhead last night which saw Brendan Rodgers’ side fight back twice to win 3-2 with excellent strikes from Reo Hatate, Alexandro [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton's transfer advice as ex-Celtic hero backs first-team star]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169613</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-suttons-transfer-advice-as-ex-celtic-hero-backs-first-team-star/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T06:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been tipped to bring in more new faces this summer as Brendan Rodgers looks to strengthen the squad ahead of the new season....
The post Chris Sutton's transfer advice as ex-Celtic hero backs first-team star appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Some better than others"; The Brendan Rodgers verdict on four Celtic Park debuts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169624</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/some-better-than-others-the-brendan-rodgers-verdict-on-four-celtic-park-debuts/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T06:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers had good things to say about some of his summer arrival’s Celtic Park debuts. The Hoops manager gave first home run-outs to four...
The post "Some better than others"; The Brendan Rodgers verdict on four Celtic Park debuts appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I NEED TO PROVE MYSELF AGAIN,’ ADMITS RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110503</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-need-to-prove-myself-again-admits-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T06:08:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS picked up where he left off with a victory at Parkhead in a game in which five goals were scored. Four and a half years ago, the Irishman bowed out with a 4-1 league triumph over Motherwell in the east end of Glasgow on February 24 2019. Two days later, his seven successive [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The thoughtful Athletic Club tribute that didn't go unnoticed at Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169583</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-thoughtful-athletic-club-tribute-that-didnt-go-unnoticed-at-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T05:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before Tuesday night’s game, Athletic Club paid a thoughtful tribute to Celtic legend Billy McNeill. The Hoops have a great relationship with the Basque side...
The post The thoughtful Athletic Club tribute that didn't go unnoticed at Celtic Park appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers reacts to Celtic's win over Athletic Club; addresses fan reaction to his return]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169580</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-reacts-to-celtics-win-over-athletic-club-addresses-fan-reaction-to-his-return/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T05:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a night for Celtic and the supporters to pay tribute to James Forrest for the Celtic winger’s incredible career at Paradise. The last...
The post Brendan Rodgers reacts to Celtic's win over Athletic Club; addresses fan reaction to his return appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIG YOGI: PUTTING THE RECORD STRAIGHT (Part One)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=94889</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/big-yogi-putting-the-record-straight-part-one/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T04:45:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC great John ‘Yogi’ Hughes passed away on August 1 2022 at the age of 79 after a short illness. In a CQN EXCLUSIVE, Alex Gordon, who co-authored the fans’ favourite’s autobiography, ‘Yogi Bare: The Life and Times of a Celtic Legend’, which was published in 2014, has selected a few chapters from his friend’s [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RED CARD OLD FIRM UPROAR: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Twenty-two)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=94740</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/red-card-old-firm-uproar-the-tommy-burns-story-part-twenty-two/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T04:30:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS was riding a rollercoaster of emotions during the turbulent 1996/97 crusade. The fans’ favourite had returned to the club on July 12 1994 and had won the Scottish Cup in his debut campaign. That was followed by a barren term and all eyes were on the boss during a third challenging season. In [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou recruit confirms Celtic departure]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43071</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/01/ange-postecoglou-recruit-confirms-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T22:35:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Brendan Rodgers rejoined Celtic as manager, it was a relief to see the backroom team of coaches and advisers remained in place as well. A few of them had been linked with a reunion with Ange Postecoglou at Tottenham Hotspur. Inevitably though, there will be changes and one of the Australian’s recruits has confirmed […]
Ange Postecoglou recruit confirms Celtic departure - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lustig, Edouard, Rogic and more react on James Forrest's big Celtic Park night]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169612</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/lustig-edouard-rogic-and-more-react-on-james-forrests-big-celtic-park-night/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T21:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic stars past and present have been reacting to James Forrest’s big night. It was a great night for the Hoops as they came from...
The post Lustig, Edouard, Rogic and more react on James Forrest's big Celtic Park night appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James Forrest delighted with special Celtic Park night; targets new season ahead]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169604</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/james-forrest-delighted-with-special-celtic-park-night-targets-new-season-ahead/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T21:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s win over Atheltic Club really was a fitting tribute to James Forrest. The Celtic winger endured a game of two halves as the Hoops...
The post James Forrest delighted with special Celtic Park night; targets new season ahead appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forgotten Celtic player might have a role in Brendan Rodgers’ team]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43084</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/01/forgotten-celtic-player-brendan-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T21:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pre-season has come and gone for Celtic, and this weekend, they will begin their league title defence with a game against Ross County on Flag Day. The Hoops gave the fans a lot to cheer about in midweek as well though, staging a comeback win against Athletic Bilbao. They managed to win 3-2 against the […]
Forgotten Celtic player might have a role in Brendan Rodgers’ team - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC 3 ATHLETIC BILBAO 2: THREE CHEERS ON FORREST’S BIG NIGHT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110499</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-3-athletic-bilbao-2-three-cheers-on-forrests-big-night/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T20:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC 3 ATHLETIC BILBAO 2 THE heavens opened over the east end of Glasgow as James Forrest was honoured in Paradise last night. The evergreen Celtic winger played for 49 minutes in his own testimonial match against Spanish cracks Athletic Bilbao in front of a healthy crowd. It may have started slowly with most of the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rodgers roar, Nawrocki impression; 3 things we learned as Celtic beat Athletic Club]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169588</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/rodgers-roar-nawrocki-impression-3-things-we-learned-as-celtic-beat-athletic-club/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T20:23:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic came from behind to beat Athletic Club 3-2 and end pre-season on a high on Tuesday evening. It was a positive night for the...
The post Rodgers roar, Nawrocki impression; 3 things we learned as Celtic beat Athletic Club appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player tipped to join Premiership rivals this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43080</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/01/celtic-player-premiership-rivals-summer/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T19:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic might have a lack of options at the back right now due to injury problems, but when everybody is fit and available, the Hoops are stacked in that area of the pitch as well. At centre-back, they have the established duo of Cameron Carter-Vickers and Carl Starfelt. Maik Nawrocki will surely be looking to […]
Celtic player tipped to join Premiership rivals this summer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player makes first-team return out of nowhere]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43074</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/01/celtic-player-makes-first-team-return/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T18:07:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will start their campaign this weekend. The Hoops will take on Ross County on Flag Day at Parkhead. But before that, they have one more pre-season friendly game to go. It is the most high-profile match that they have been a part of for a while, as Athletic Bilbao will face them at Parkhead […]
Celtic player makes first-team return out of nowhere - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: CCV COMEBACK, NAWROCKI DEBUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110491</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-ccv-comeback-nawrocki-debut/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T17:33:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CAMERON CARTER-VICKERS is back in the Celtic line-up while Maik Nawrocki makes his debut in James Forrest’s testimonial match against Athletic Bilbao at Parkhead this evening. The USA World Cup central defender has been sidelined since the end of April after undergoing knee surgery. Polish new Bhoy Nawrocki, signed for £4.3million from Legia Warsaw, missed out [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic v Athletic Bilbao, GG Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110497</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-athletic-bilbao-gg-live-updates/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T17:29:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 19:30.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic team vs Athletic Club confirmed: double defender boost, TV details, instant reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169548</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-vs-athletic-club-confirmed-double-defender-boost-tv-details-instant-reaction/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T17:26:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has named his Celtic team vs Atheltic Club for tonight’s James Forrest testimonial at Celtic Park. The full match squad is as follows:...
The post Celtic team vs Athletic Club confirmed: double defender boost, TV details, instant reaction appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Successful staff member departed Celtic this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169561</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/successful-staff-member-departed-celtic-at-the-start-of-brendan-rodgers-era/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T16:40:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anton McElhone departed Celtic this summer. The Scotsman had been Head of Sports Science at the club from September 2021. Former Greenock Morton manager McElhone...
The post Successful staff member departed Celtic this summer appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans watch on with interest as the English crackdown on time-wasting begins]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169554</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/celtic-fans-watch-on-with-interest-as-the-english-crackdown-on-time-wasting-begins/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T15:10:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[English football will have a crackdown on time-wasting this season, as Celtic and Scottish football watch-on. Details have been emerging over the past few days...
The post Celtic fans watch on with interest as the English crackdown on time-wasting begins appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['He's one of us', 'He's always representing'; three Celtic heroes lead James Forrest tributes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169551</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/hes-one-of-us-hes-always-representing-three-celtic-heroes-lead-james-forrest-tributes/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today should just be named ‘James Forrest Day’ shouldn’t it? And why not. The Celtic winger has been at the club since he joined the...
The post 'He's one of us', 'He's always representing'; three Celtic heroes lead James Forrest tributes appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Levi Garcia decides on his future as reported Celtic target ends summer speculation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169534</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/levi-garcia-update-reported-celtic-target-decides-on-his-future/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s reported interest in Levi Garcia looks to be ending after reports in Greece have claimed he has agreed a new contract with AEK Athens....
The post Report: Levi Garcia decides on his future as reported Celtic target ends summer speculation appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Popular debut and an uncontroversial choice; Celtic Predicted XI vs Athletic Club]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169533</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/popular-debut-and-an-uncontroversial-choice-celtic-predicted-xi-vs-athletic-club/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T12:42:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic return home for the first time in nine weeks on Tuesday evening. La Liga outfit Athletic Club are the visitors on a big night...
The post Popular debut and an uncontroversial choice; Celtic Predicted XI vs Athletic Club appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOW WELL DO YOU KNOW JAMES FORREST? TRY OUR FIVE-MINUTE QUIZ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110482</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/how-well-do-you-know-james-forrest-try-our-five-minute-quiz/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T12:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JAMES FORREST is honoured by Celtic with his well-mertited testimonial match against Athletic Bilbao at Parkhead this evening. The 32-year-old winger has been performing consistently in the hoops for 13 years after making his first-team debut on May 1 2010 when Neil Lennon introduced him as a late substitute for Aiden McGeady. So, how well do [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Athletic Club name 23 man squad for James Forrest’s Celtic testimonial; two notable absentees]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169522</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/athletic-club-name-23-man-squad-for-james-forrests-celtic-testimonial-two-notable-absentees/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Celtic getting set to face Athletic Club in Glasgow for James Forrest’s testimonial tonight, the supporters will be looking forward to seeing their heroes...
The post Athletic Club name 23 man squad for James Forrest’s Celtic testimonial; two notable absentees appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic release next batch of Adidas gear and there's some crackers; prices, impressions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169517</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-release-next-batch-of-adidas-gear-and-theres-some-crackers-prices-impressions/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T11:42:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August seems to have been the cue for Celtic to release the next batch of their Adidas 2023/24 training gear. We’ve been covering clothing developments...
The post Celtic release next batch of Adidas gear and there's some crackers; prices, impressions appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arsenal decision hands Celtic chance to sign Kieran Tierney]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43068</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/01/arsenal-decision-celtic-kieran-tierney/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T11:30:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with an unexpected move for Kieran Tierney this summer. The Scottish international left the club in the summer of 2019 in order to join Arsenal for a transfer fee believed to be around £25 million. His time in London has been up and down though, and an exit is a real […]
Arsenal decision hands Celtic chance to sign Kieran Tierney - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The three biggest goals of James Forrest's career and the impact on Celtic's history]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169409</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-three-biggest-goals-of-james-forrests-career-and-the-impact-on-celtics-history/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over his 13-year career at Celtic, James Forrest has had a phenomenal impact on the club’s success over that period. With over 100 goals and...
The post The three biggest goals of James Forrest's career and the impact on Celtic's history appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Club Man’s historic haul]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110480</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/one-club-mans-historic-haul/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T11:01:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aiden McGeady broke the Scottish transfer sale record when he left for Spartak Moscow in 2010.  Neil Lennon had just taken over as permanent manager after the departure of Tony Mowbray and Celtic put the McGeady money to good use. Over the next two years, they embarked on a purple patch of signing players.  Kris [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James Forest – The One Club Man]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58205</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/james-forest-the-one-club-man/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T10:45:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the opening fixture of our league campaign almost here,  the match against Wolves at the Aviva stadium served as a good exercise in building momentum towards our challenge of retaining the Scottish title.  There was more than enough action in defence and in attack for us to over analyse, yeah we could be more […]
The post James Forest – The One Club Man appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upgraded turnstiles and a pre-match speech; club confirm plans for Celtic Park return]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169498</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/upgraded-turnstiles-and-a-pre-match-speech-club-confirm-plans-for-celtic-park-return/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T10:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Park hosts its first match since May this evening as the Hoops return home. A lot has changed since Celtic beat Aberdeen 5-0 on...
The post Upgraded turnstiles and a pre-match speech; club confirm plans for Celtic Park return appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Athletic Club continue their Celtic education ahead of James Forrest testimonial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169482</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/athletic-club-continue-their-celtic-education-ahead-of-james-forrests-testimonial/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of their preparations to come to Glasgow and take part in the James Forrest testimonial, Athletic Club seem to have gone on a...
The post Athletic Club continue their Celtic education ahead of James Forrest testimonial appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘STILL GOT A BIT TO GO,’ KENNEDY HAILS EVERGREEN CELT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110479</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/still-got-a-bit-to-go-kennedy-hails-evergreen-celt/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T09:03:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC No.2 John Kennedy has some bad news for the opposition: James Forrest isn’t quite ready to call it quits after 13 trophy-laden years at the top. The 32-year-old winger, who has claimed 22 honours and scored over 100 goals since his debut in May 2010, still has two seasons to run on his current [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Athletic captain makes superb claim about Bilbao’s love for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43063</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/01/athletic-captain-bilbao-love-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T09:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have had a good pre-season and the start of the Premiership campaign is now less than a week away. The Hoops will take on Ross County at Parkhead this weekend on Flag Day. But before that, they have one more friendly game to play. It will be against the historic Spanish club, Athletic Bilbao, […]
Athletic captain makes superb claim about Bilbao’s love for Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ibrox figure fails to learn from last season as he suggests Celtic dominance is about to end]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169475</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ibrox-figure-fails-to-learn-last-seasons-lesson-as-he-suggests-celtic-dominance-is-about-to-end/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers attacker Todd Cantwell doesn’t seem to have learned his lesson from last season despite Celtic winning a treble. The former Norwich City player arrived...
The post Ibrox figure fails to learn from last season as he suggests Celtic dominance is about to end appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former fan favourite's perfect one-word reply to Celtic’s James Forrest Instagram post]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169470</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/josip-juranovics-perfect-one-word-reply-to-celtics-james-forrest-instagram-post/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic prepare to face Atheltic Club in tonight’s testimonial for club legend, James Forrest, the fans will be looking forward to being given the...
The post Former fan favourite's perfect one-word reply to Celtic’s James Forrest Instagram post appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KILLIE v CELTIC LIVE ON VIAPLAY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110469</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/killie-v-celtic-live-on-viaplay/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T07:59:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HOLDERS Celtic’s Viaplay League Cup last-16 match against Kilmarnock at Rugby Park will be televised live. Brendan Rodgers will take his squad to Ayrshire for the tie on Sunday August 20 with a 3pm kick-off and the tournament sponsors and stallite broadcasters will beam the match live. It’s an action replay of last season’s semi-final [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James Forrest is given a special role by Celtic on Flag Day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169453</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/james-forrest-is-given-a-special-role-by-celtic-on-flag-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tonight marks the start of the celebrations for James Forrest‘s long-term service at Celtic. The 32-year-old winger is set to be honoured in a testimonial...
The post James Forrest is given a special role by Celtic on Flag Day appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FORREST FLIES THE FLAG]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110466</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/forrest-flies-the-flag/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T07:29:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JAMES FORREST will be flying the flag for Celtic at the weekend – literally. The evergreen Hoops winger, who has been granted a well-deserved testimonial game against Athletic Bilbao at Parkhead this evening, will be doing the honours on Saturday before the Premiership kick-off against Ross County. Forrest, who has won 22 medals in his glittering [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Celtic take part in Sky Sports crossbar challenge at Lennoxtown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169437</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/video-celtic-star-takes-part-in-sky-sports-crossbar-challenge-at-lennoxtown/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports were continuing their tour of Scottish Premiership training grounds on Monday with Lennoxtown and Celtic the venue for interviews and features. The broadcaster...
The post Video: Celtic take part in Sky Sports crossbar challenge at Lennoxtown appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers shares first impressions of new signings after Celtic cameos vs Wolves]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169442</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-shares-first-impressions-of-kwon-and-yang-after-celtic-cameos-vs-wolves/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T06:34:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers was pleased with the initial contributions of new South Korean signings Hyeokkyu Kwon and Hyunjun Yang on Saturday against Wolves. The...
The post Brendan Rodgers shares first impressions of new signings after Celtic cameos vs Wolves appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JAMES FORREST: A BHOYS’ OWN STORY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110463</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/james-forrest-a-bhoys-own-story/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T06:04:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JAMES FORREST could take his privileged place alongside Lisbon Lion Bobby Lennox as Celtic’s joint most decorated player by the end of the forthcoming season. The 32-year-old product from the club’s academy picked up his 22nd winner’s medal following his cameo appearance in the 3-1 Scottish Cup Final triumph over Inverness Caley Thistle at Hampden [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Athletic Club star can't wait to play at Celtic Park tonight; say Bhoys are loved in Bilbao]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169444</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/athletic-club-star-cant-wait-to-play-at-celtic-park-tonight-say-bhoys-are-loved-in-bilbao/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T05:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Athletic Club captain Iker Muniain is relishing the opportunity to play at Celtic Park in front of Celtic supporters tonight for James Forrest’s testimonial match....
The post Athletic Club star can't wait to play at Celtic Park tonight; say Bhoys are loved in Bilbao appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YOGI REMEMBERED: A PERSONAL THOUGHT BY GERDA GORDON]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110450</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/yogi-remembered-a-personal-thought-by-gerda-gordon/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T05:32:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE day I met Yogi is stored forever in my memory bank. Gruff doesn’t do him justice. Not even close. It was around Christmastime in 2013 and he had made an arrangement to meet my husband Alex to discuss the possibility of an autobiography. (It hit the bookshelves the following year, entitled: Yogi Bare: The [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YOGI REMEMBERED: OFFER THE CELTIC GREAT COULD REFUSE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=94846</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/yogi-remembered-offer-the-celtic-great-could-refuse/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T05:31:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC great John ‘Yogi’ Hughes passed away on August 1 2022 at the age of 79 after a short illness. In a CQN EXCLUSIVE, Alex Gordon, who co-authored the fans’ favourite’s autobiography, ‘Yogi Bare: The Life and Times of a Celtic Legend’, which was published in 2014, has selected another chapter from his friend’s best-seller. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YOGI REMEMBERED: MY BIG PAL, RANGERS FANS AND THE ‘FAIR FIGHT’, DAVIE HAY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=94773</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/yogi-remembered-my-big-pal-rangers-fans-and-the-fair-fight-davie-hay/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T05:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAVIE HAY paid a heartfelt tribute to his former Celtic team-mate John ‘Yogi’ Hughes when he passed away on August 1 2022 at the age of 79 following a short illness. The ex-Hoops player and manager played alongside the fans’ favourite after making his first-team breakthrough in 1968. Hay, speaking to Celtic book author Alex Gordon, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star addresses his future after making just 5 starts last season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169439</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/james-forrest-addresses-his-celtic-future-after-just-5-starts-last-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T05:27:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic winger James Forrest is eager to remain part of the Bhoys squad and fight hard for a place in the team under Brendan Rodgers...
The post Celtic star addresses his future after making just 5 starts last season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIG YOGI: JOCK AND I (Part Five)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=94733</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/big-yogi-jock-and-i-part-five/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T05:04:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOHN ‘YOGI’ HUGHES was one of the most colourful and charismatic characters in Celtic history. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE series, author Alex Gordon pays tribute to his long-time friend who passed away on August 1 2022. Alex, who co-authored Hughes’ autobiography, ‘Yogi Bare: The Life and Times of a Celtic Legend’, concludes extracts from the legend’s [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIG YOGI: JOCK AND I (Part Four)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=94732</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/big-yogi-jock-and-i-part-four/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T05:03:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOHN ‘YOGI’ HUGHES was one of the most colourful and charismatic characters in Celtic history. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE series, author Alex Gordon pays tribute to his long-time friend who passed away on August 1 2022. Alex, who co-authored Hughes’ autobiography, ‘Yogi Bare: The Life and Times of a Celtic Legend’, continues the life story of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIG YOGI: JOCK AND I (Part Three)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=94729</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/big-yogi-jock-and-i-part-three/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T05:02:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOHN ‘YOGI’ HUGHES was one of the most remarkable and charismatic characters in Celtic history. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE series, author Alex Gordon pays tribute to his long-time friend who passed away on August 1 2022. Alex, who co-authored Hughes’ autobiography, ‘Yogi Bare: The Life and Times of a Celtic Legend’, continues the life story of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIG YOGI: JOCK AND I (Part Two)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=94728</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/big-yogi-jock-and-i-part-two/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T05:01:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend John Hughes – known as Big Yogi to his adoring multitude of fans – was aware his remarkable career at Parkhead was coming to an end in the summer of 1971. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE series, author Alex Gordon pays tribute to his long-time friend who passed away on August 1 2022. Alex, who [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIG YOGI: JOCK AND I (Part One)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=94724</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/big-yogi-jock-and-i-part-one/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T05:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC great John ‘Yogi’ Hughes passed away a year ago at the age of 79. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE series, author Alex Gordon pays tribute to his long-time friend. Alex, who co-authored Hughes’ autobiography, ‘Yogi Bare: The Life and Times of a Celtic Legend’, has selected a few extracts from the life story of the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FEED THE BEAR: ALEX GORDON’S TRIBUTE TO JOHN ‘YOGI’ HUGHES ON THE ANNIVERSARY OF THE PASSING OF A LEGEND]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=94717</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/feed-the-bear-alex-gordons-tribute-to-john-yogi-hughes-on-the-anniversary-of-the-passing-of-a-legend/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T04:45:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LEGIONS of Celtic supporters lost a hero a year ago today with the passing of John ‘Yogi’ Hughes at the age of 79. Alas, at the same time, I said farewell to a truly wonderful friend and one of life’s exceptional characters. It was impossible not to warm to Big John while I co-authored his [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOODOO DEMOLISHED AND THE CUP THAT CHEERS: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Twenty-one)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=94682</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hoodoo-demolished-and-the-cup-that-cheers-the-tommy-burns-story-part-twenty-one/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-01T04:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS had a massive moment to celebrate as he attempted to guide Celtic to success in the turbulent 1996/97 crusade. The fans’ favourite had returned to the club on July 12 1994 and had won the Scottish Cup in his debut campaign. That was followed by a barren term and all eyes were on [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic captain makes fantastic Brendan Rodgers claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43038</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/31/celtic-captain-brendan-rodgers-claim-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T22:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unsurprisingly, there are still Celtic fans with doubts over the return of Brendan Rodgers as manager. The manner of his exit the last time around has still left a bitter taste for some supporters. Others have moved on and perhaps the latest comments about the Northern Irishman from Callum McGregor will help convince more to […]
Celtic captain makes fantastic Brendan Rodgers claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player confirms he has recovered from injury]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43055</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/31/celtic-player-confirms-recovered-injury/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T21:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are less than a week away from the start of the new Premiership campaign. They have had a decent pre-season and should be confident of their chances against Ross County on Flag Day. Before that they have a friendly to play against Athletic Bilbao as well, in what would be James Forrest’s Testimonial. The […]
Celtic player confirms he has recovered from injury - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed superb boost by Keylor Navas news]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43050</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/31/celtic-handed-keylor-navas-news/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T19:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are coming off winning a treble. Thus, there is no doubt that that is a brilliant group of players. There were fears that the departure of Ange Postecoglou would have a major impact on the team but the club have done very well to replace the Australian with Brendan Rodgers, a superb manager in […]
Celtic handed superb boost by Keylor Navas news - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Late ticket sale surge promises special Celtic Park night for James Forrest Testimonial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169432</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/late-ticket-sale-surge-promises-special-celtic-park-night-for-james-forrest-testimonial/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T19:11:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After strong ticket sales on Friday and over the weekend, Celtic made more seats available for Tuesday night’s James Forrest Testimonial at Celtic Park. A...
The post Late ticket sale surge promises special Celtic Park night for James Forrest Testimonial appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Soul Podcast View from South Korea]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58203</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-soul-podcast-view-from-south-korea/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T18:28:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steve Han is a South Korean football journalist, and he joins More than 90 Minutes Editor Andrew Milne on the Celtic Soul Podcast to chat about Kwon and Yang signing for Celtic and the cultural and football changes they will face settling into life in Glasgow. The Celtic v Wolves game was moved from South […]
The post Celtic Soul Podcast View from South Korea appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports man confirms multiple clubs want Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43044</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/31/sky-sports-clubs-want-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T18:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have some very highly-rated young talents in their squad at this point in time. Thus, it is only natural that other teams would be interested in such youngsters as well. Yet, that is not what the fans want to hear. Now, it remains to be seen what the future holds for such players, who […]
Sky Sports man confirms multiple clubs want Celtic player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RIP David Potter  1948 – 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58196</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/rip-david-potter-1948-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T16:48:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Sunday evening we found out that our friend and contributor, David Potter had sadly passed away. David’s contribution to Celtic FC and it’s history is immense and leaves behind a legacy of Celtic writing, in books, blogs, programmes and fanzines. I can’t even remember when David started to write for the fanzine but […]
The post RIP David Potter  1948 – 2023 appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Kennedy fully focused on Celtic but harbours a long-term career ambition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169427</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/john-kennedy-fully-focused-on-celtic-but-harbours-a-long-term-career-ambition/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Kennedy has revealed that although he remains happy at Celtic under Brendan Rodgers, he still has a long-term career ambition to become his own...
The post John Kennedy fully focused on Celtic but harbours a long-term career ambition appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic coach speaks about summer exit rumours; why he decided to stay at Paradise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169412</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/john-kennedy-speaks-about-summer-exit-rumours-why-he-decided-to-stay-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Kennedy has addressed the summer speculation linking the Celtic assistant manager with a move away from the club. At one point during the summer,...
The post Celtic coach speaks about summer exit rumours; why he decided to stay at Paradise appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing pictured in training as club release Lennoxtown images]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169415</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/maik-nawrocki-pictured-in-training-as-club-release-lennoxtown-images/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T14:51:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic prepare to face Athletic Club in James Forrest’s testimonial tomorrow night, the club have released pictures that show new summer signing, Maik Nawrocki...
The post New Celtic signing pictured in training as club release Lennoxtown images appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘THAT WON’T BE THE CASE,’ RODGERS TRANSFER UPDATE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110458</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/that-wont-be-the-case-rodgers-transfer-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T13:31:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS insists he will not be splashing out £15million or £20million signings as he prepares for life as Celtic manager second time-around. The Irishman still holds the record as bringing in the Hoops’ most expensive purchase – the £9million for Odsonne Edouard from Paris Saint-Germain in June 2018 – but he won’t be breaking [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports transfer update as young Celtic prospect makes agent switch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169399</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/sky-sports-worrying-rocco-vata-claim-as-young-celtic-prospect-makes-agent-switch/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports have provided an update on the Rocco Vata situation at Celtic. Considering how many youth prospects we have lost over the years, fans...
The post Sky Sports transfer update as young Celtic prospect makes agent switch appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['That's my only concern'; Brendan Rodgers comments on Rangers' challenge to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169391</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/thats-my-only-concern-brendan-rodgers-comments-on-rangers-challenge-to-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been very active in the summer transfer window as Brendan Rodgers looks to bolster his squad to defend the treble and make a...
The post 'That's my only concern'; Brendan Rodgers comments on Rangers' challenge to Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everton transfer update hands fresh problem to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43041</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/31/everton-transfer-update-problem-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T12:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already signed five players this summer and are not expected to make further additions before the first league game of the season, against Ross County. All the fresh faces who have arrived at Parkhead are highly-rated youngsters with a ton of potential. At the same time, the club must add some experienced and […]
Everton transfer update hands fresh problem to Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers explains the process of Celtic's summer recruitment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169386</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-explains-the-process-of-celtics-summer-recruitment/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s pursuit of talent in the Asian markets and beyond has been very successful over the last two seasons. With the arrival of Brendan Rodgers,...
The post Brendan Rodgers explains the process of Celtic's summer recruitment appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Material gap in preparedness for new season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110449</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/material-gap-in-preparedness-for-new-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T11:03:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was pleased when the league fixtures were announced, and we learned Newco would start their season on Kilmarnock’s plastic pitch.  Already four competitive fixtures into their season, Killie present a randomness of a challenge at home.  For Newco’s sake the pitch is unlikely to be dry on Saturday. Killie will have completed six competitive [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic are still active in the transfer market but with a caveat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169379</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-confirms-celtic-are-still-active-in-the-transfer-market-but-with-a-caveat/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T10:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has already added five new names to his squad this summer and the Celtic boss has confirmed that he plans to add more...
The post Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic are still active in the transfer market but with a caveat appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor explains how Celtic will improve on last season's style of football]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169371</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/callum-mcgregor-explains-how-celtic-will-improve-on-last-seasons-style-of-football/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been absolutely relentless in their pursuit of silverware over the last ten years. A Quadruple Treble and another nine-in-a-row show just how good...
The post Callum McGregor explains how Celtic will improve on last season's style of football appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harald Brattbakk discusses why he struggled at Celtic; the ex-boss he considers a ‘good friend’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169365</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/harald-brattbakk-discusses-why-he-struggled-at-celtic-the-ex-boss-he-considers-a-good-friend/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker, Harald Brattbakk will always be regarded as a legend of the club. His goal in the 2-0 win over St Johnstone back...
The post Harald Brattbakk discusses why he struggled at Celtic; the ex-boss he considers a ‘good friend’ appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed boost in Dominik Livakovic transfer race]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43035</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/31/celtic-boost-dominik-livakovic-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T08:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans were delighted when the club were linked with a move for Dominik Livakovic earlier in the summer transfer window. The Croatian goalkeeper was arguably his national team’s best performer at the 2022 World Cup, as they finished third in the competition. And at this point in time, he could be the perfect signing […]
Celtic handed boost in Dominik Livakovic transfer race - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BBC pundit reckons Derek McInnes won't be happy with Celtic challenge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169357</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/bbc-pundit-reckons-derek-mcinnes-wont-be-happy-with-celtic-challenge/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Viaplay League Cup draw yesterday paired Celtic with Kilmarnock as Brendan Rodgers faces the task of defending the trophy at Rugby Park next month....
The post BBC pundit reckons Derek McInnes won't be happy with Celtic challenge appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MAKE MINE A DOUBLE: BRENDAN REVEALS GAME PLAN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110441</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/make-mine-a-double-brendan-reveals-game-plan/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T07:47:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is planning to field TWO Celtic teams in James Forrest’s testimonial game against Athletic Bilbao at Parkhead tomorrow night. The second time-around manager is determined to make sure his first-team squad get as many game-time minutes into their legs as possible before the competitive action kicks off on Flag Day when Ross County [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Ross County star has loads of Celtic pals and sounds buzzing to play at Paradise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169353</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/new-ross-county-star-has-loads-of-celtic-pals-and-sounds-buzzing-to-play-at-paradise/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T07:40:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Ross County arrival James Brown can’t wait to turn out at Celtic Park this weekend, even if it means his friends aren’t cheering him...
The post New Ross County star has loads of Celtic pals and sounds buzzing to play at Paradise appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘A POINT TO PROVE,’ McGREGOR’S VERDICT ON RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110438</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/a-point-to-prove-mcgregors-verdict-on-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T07:14:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CALLUM McGREGOR insists Brendan Rodgers is a man on a mission in his second coming as Celtic manager. The inspirational captain and midfielder chatted with the Irishman before his return as Ange Postecoglou’s successor was signed, sealed and delivered last month. McGregor was part of the first encounter with Rodgers as they both embarked on [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS RESPONDS TO ‘GREATER PRESSURE’ CHALLENGE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110428</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-responds-to-greater-pressure-challenge/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T06:23:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has only ever known success in Scottish football. In his first stint as Celtic manager, the Irishman won seven successive domestic trophies – including historic back-to-back trebles – before his abrupt exit to Leicester City. From the May 2016 day Rodgers was paraded in front of thousands of joyous Hoops fans in the east [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star lifts lid on Lennoxtown meeting that showed "one of the best things" about Rodgers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169348</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-star-lifts-lid-on-lennoxtown-meeting-that-showed-squad-one-of-the-best-things-about-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T06:11:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic captain Callum McGregor has hailed manager Brendan Rodgers as a ‘master tactician’ ahead of the new season, stating that he sees the same qualities...
The post Celtic star lifts lid on Lennoxtown meeting that showed "one of the best things" about Rodgers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers clues fans in on new mindset ahead of Tuesday Celtic Park return]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169345</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-clues-fans-in-on-new-mindset-ahead-of-tuesday-celtic-park-return/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T05:15:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers is relishing the prospect of taking Celtic into the new season, telling supporters he is hungrier than ever to achieve at the Bhoys...
The post Brendan Rodgers clues fans in on new mindset ahead of Tuesday Celtic Park return appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BOX-OFFICE ATTRACTION: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Twenty)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=94646</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/box-office-attraction-the-tommy-burns-story-part-twenty/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T04:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WITH commendable gritty determination, Tommy Burns soldiered on as the obstacles piled up during his third year as Celtic manager during the intriguing 1996/97 crusade. The fans’ favourite had returned to the club on July 12 1994 and had won the Scottish Cup in his debut campaign. That was followed by a barren term and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic suffer blow in race to sign €20 million Tete for free]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43031</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/30/celtic-race-sign-tete-free/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T22:32:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with a lot of highly-rated players in recent times, as rumours have suggested that the club are prepared to make some marquee signings this summer. One player who would fall under that category is Tete. The Brazilian winger has recently become a free agent after bringing an end to his time […]
Celtic suffer blow in race to sign €20 million Tete for free - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic urged to sign €10 million player this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43029</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/30/celtic-urged-sign-10-million-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T21:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Considering Celtic are coming off of a treble-winning campaign, there are not a lot of holes in this squad. They have depth in almost all areas across the pitch at this time. Still, there are a few positions that the Hoops should perhaps consider strengthening. One of them is certainly goalkeeper. Joe Hart has done […]
Celtic urged to sign €10 million player this summer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers' mid-week Celtic plan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169341</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-mid-week-celtic-plan/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T20:47:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers is intending to give as many Celtic players minutes as possible on Tuesday night against Athletic Club, believing some in the squad still...
The post Brendan Rodgers' mid-week Celtic plan appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic coach explains how Brendan Rodgers inspired "massive jump" in Bhoys star's development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169336</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/darren-odea-explains-how-brendan-rodgers-inspired-massive-jump-in-celtic-stars-development/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T19:47:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers is a manager known for improving players and that coaching trait will be crucially important to Celtic over the next couple of years....
The post Celtic coach explains how Brendan Rodgers inspired "massive jump" in Bhoys star's development appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano drops fantastic Celtic transfer update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43025</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/30/fabrizio-drops-celtic-transfer-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T19:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have made five signings this summer, bringing in the likes of Marco Tilio, Odin Thiago Holm, Yang Hyun-jun, Kwon Hyeok-kyu and Maik Nawrocki to the club. All of them are highly-rated youngsters with the potential of becoming first-team regulars for the Hoops. But they are not the headline-grabbing additions that the fans would have […]
Fabrizio Romano drops fantastic Celtic transfer update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Athletic Bilbao pay superb tribute to Celtic ahead of friendly]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43021</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/30/athletic-bilbao-pay-superb-tribute-celtic-ahead-friendly/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T18:04:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are set to take on Athletic Bilbao in the final friendly game ahead of the start of the 2023/24 campaign. It will not just be another pre-season match though. Instead, it is also going to be the testimonial of James Forrest, who has given so much to the Hoops over the years and he […]
Athletic Bilbao pay superb tribute to Celtic ahead of friendly - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic draw Kilmarnock in League Cup; dates, details]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169324</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-draw-kilmarnock-in-league-cup-dates-details/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will begin the second part of their Treble defence after they were drawn with Kilmarnock in the last 16 of the Viaplay League Cup...
The post Celtic draw Kilmarnock in League Cup; dates, details appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC AT KILLIE IN VIAPLAY DRAW]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110422</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-at-killie-in-viaplay-draw/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T16:05:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC will kick off the defence of their Viaplay League Cup when they face Kilmarnock at Rugby Park. Brendan Rodgers’ side were paired with the Ayrshire club in the last-16 draw which followed Dundee’s 1-0 win over Inverness Caley Thistle at Dens Park this afternoon. Neither the Tayside outfit nor the Highlanders progressed to the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's Unique Angle shows Kyogo Furuhashi's off-the-ball work that led to goal vs Wolves]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169307</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-unique-angle-shows-kyogo-furuhashis-off-the-ball-work-that-led-to-goal-vs-wolves/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans all know that Kyogo Furuhashi is one of the hardest-working members of the Celtic first team. The Japanese striker has been a pivotal...
The post Celtic's Unique Angle shows Kyogo Furuhashi's off-the-ball work that led to goal vs Wolves appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Athletic Club's brilliant Celtic tribute ahead of James Forrest testimonial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169303</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/athletic-clubs-brilliant-celtic-tribute-ahead-of-james-forrest-testimonial/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Forrest’s upcoming testimonial is one that every Celtic fan will agree is well deserved. The Celtic winger has had an astonishing career in which...
The post Athletic Club's brilliant Celtic tribute ahead of James Forrest testimonial appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton believes new summer signing could give Celtic tactical options for Europe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169296</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-believes-new-summer-signing-could-give-celtic-tactical-options-for-europe/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The addition of Maik Nawrocki to the Celtic defence has done two things for Brendan Rodgers. It has given us extra strength in depth in...
The post Chris Sutton believes new summer signing could give Celtic tactical options for Europe appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Egyptian player confirms Celtic interest in signing him]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43018</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/30/egyptian-player-confirms-celtic-interest/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T11:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already made quite a few additions this summer. There were rumours about potential marquee signings but till now, the club have stuck to bringing in highly-rated youngsters from around the globe. The five players who the Hoops have signed in the ongoing transfer window are Odin Thiago Holm, Marco Tilio, Yang Hyun-jun, Kwon […]
Egyptian player confirms Celtic interest in signing him - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Celtic were very interested" - Reported target addresses Parkhead summer transfer rumour]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169290</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/mohamed-reda-addresses-celtic-summer-transfer-rumour/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has already been hard at work adding fresh faces to the Celtic squad this summer. However, the Hoops boss is tipped to add...
The post "Celtic were very interested" - Reported target addresses Parkhead summer transfer rumour appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WAIT FOR IT: CELTIC IN VIAPLAY LEAGUE CUP DRAW TODAY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110419</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/wait-for-it-celtic-in-viaplay-league-cup-draw-today/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T10:35:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HOLDERS Celtic will discover their Viaplay League Cup opponents today when the draw is made after the Dundee v Inverness Caley Thistle at Dens Park with a 3pm kick-off. Brendan Rodgers’ side, who have won the competition in SIX of the last SEVEN seasons, enter the tourney at the knock-out stage along with the other [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REVEALED: RODGERS’ SALES TALK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110416</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/revealed-rodgers-sales-talk/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T10:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has delivered a message to Celtic fans after his five-player signing spree: There’s more to come! The returning Hoops boss has overseen somethig in the region of £11.5million deals with Norwegian midfielder Odin Thiago Holm the first to arrive from Valerenga. Next up was Australian international winger Marco Tilio from Melbourne City and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor's early verdict of new Celtic signings after Dublin draw with Wolves]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169285</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/callum-mcgregors-early-verdict-of-new-celtic-signings-after-dublin-draw-with-wolves/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic move into the last fixture of the preseason preparations, Callum McGregor has reflected on the draw with Wolves in Dublin. Whilst the performance...
The post Callum McGregor's early verdict of new Celtic signings after Dublin draw with Wolves appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SCALES IN FRANK CELTIC ADMISSION]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110412</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/scales-in-frank-celtic-admission/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T09:10:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIAM SCALES admits he is in the dark as far as his Celtic career is concerned. The 24-year-old Republic of Ireland international defender turned in an impressive performance in the Hoops’ 1-1 draw with Wolves at the Aviva Stadium yesterday. Brendan Rodgers pitched the player in from the start with Carl Starfelt, Cameron Carter-Vickers, Yuki [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers tipped to make summer transfer move that will excite the Celtic fans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169278</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/alan-stubbs-makes-a-summer-transfer-prediction-that-will-excite-the-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been extremely busy in this summer’s transfer window. With five new faces added to the squad already, Brendan Rodgers has been tipped to...
The post Brendan Rodgers tipped to make summer transfer move that will excite the Celtic fans appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I REALLY LIKE HIM,’ BOSS PRAISES SCALES]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110411</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-really-like-him-boss-praises-scales/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T08:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is still pondering the future of comeback Bhoy Liam Scales after his performance in the 1-1 draw with Wolves at the Aviva Stadium in Dublin yesterday. The versatile 24-year-old defender formed a new-look partnership alongside Stephen Welsh in the middle of the rearguard with Carl Starfelt and Maik Nawrocki ruled out with ankle [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEW BHOYS: ‘IT’S UP TO US GUYS TO TEACH THEM,’ INSISTS McGREGOR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110408</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/new-bhoys-its-up-to-us-guys-to-teach-them-insists-mcgregor/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T08:39:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC captain Callum McGregor eased himself through the 90-plus minutes of the 1-1 draw with Wolves at the Aviva Stadium in Dublin yesterday. Once again, the masterful midfielder led by example as he delivered another effective shift from the engine room of the champions. McGregor shared a pitch for the first time with South Korean [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss provides timeline for next summer signings]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43015</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/30/celtic-boss-timeline-next-signings/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T08:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already completed five signings this summer. The club have brought in highly-rated youngsters like Odin Thiago Holm, Marco Tilio, Yang Hyun-jun, Kwon Hyeok-kyu and Maik Nawrocki. All of them have a lot of potential and it will be interesting to see their developments at Parkhead over the coming months. Celtic fans cannot be […]
Celtic boss provides timeline for next summer signings - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Arsenal's £20m defender has inspired new Celtic summer signing's next career goal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169253</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/how-arsenals-20m-defender-has-inspired-new-celtic-man-maik-nawrockis-next-career-goal/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T08:14:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing, Maik Nawrocki, has told how Arsenal defender, Jakub Kiwior has inspired him to realise his burning international ambition. The new Hoops defender...
The post How Arsenal's £20m defender has inspired new Celtic summer signing's next career goal appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SPFL club explain away ticket allocation stance that Celtic fans may find baffling]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169256</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kilmarnock-explain-away-ticket-allocation-stance-that-celtic-fans-may-find-baffling/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The away ticket controversy that is currently surrounding Scottish football has become a bit of a circus over the last two seasons. First initiated by...
The post SPFL club explain away ticket allocation stance that Celtic fans may find baffling appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN’S DOUBLE DILEMMA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110376</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/brendans-double-dilemma/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T07:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is facing a double dilemma as he prepares for Celtic’s return to action against Ross County at Parkhead on Saturday. The Hoops boss is sweating over the fitness of central defenders Carl Starfelt and new Bhoy Maik Nawrocki ahead of the big day in the east end of Glasgow when the champions will [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["People hated you"; New signing already perfectly understands the Celtic dynamic in Scotland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169249</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/people-hated-you-maik-nawrocki-already-perfectly-understands-the-celtic-dynamic-in-scotland/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T06:40:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing Maik Nawrocki is ready to play his football in Scotland with a target on his back, understanding the dynamic of teams treating...
The post "People hated you"; New signing already perfectly understands the Celtic dynamic in Scotland appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Dalglish delivers early verdict on upcoming Celtic and Rangers title race]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169245</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kenny-dalglish-delivers-early-verdict-on-upcoming-celtic-and-rangers-title-race/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T06:10:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend Kenny Dalglish can’t see past the Bhoys as favourites for the Scottish Premiership this coming season, just six days out from the opening...
The post Kenny Dalglish delivers early verdict on upcoming Celtic and Rangers title race appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers provides timeline for next wave of Celtic transfer business]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=169240</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-provides-timeline-for-next-wave-of-celtic-transfer-business/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T05:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers expects to club to add more players to his squad before the end of the transfer window, but not until after...
The post Brendan Rodgers provides timeline for next wave of Celtic transfer business appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CADETE CONTROVERSY, ANNONI ARRIVES, PIERRE EXITS: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Nineteen)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=94595</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/cadete-controversy-annoni-arrives-pierre-exits-the-tommy-burns-story-part-nineteen/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-30T04:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS continued to concentrate on the title as the pressure grew in his third year as Celtic manager during the absorbing 1996/97 crusade. The fans’ favourite had returned to the club on July 12 1994 and had won the Scottish Cup in his debut campaign. That was followed by a barren term and all [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing makes Champions League claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42973</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/29/new-celtic-signing-champions-league/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-29T22:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interviews with new players tend to follow a fairly typical format but there seems to be a very encouraging and confident air about one of the Celtic summer signings. And he appeared to impress the club’s supporters with his performance in the pre-season friendly against Wolves in Dublin. It is inevitable that in early interviews, […]
New Celtic signing makes Champions League claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>