<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-12-16T22:09:05.001Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Stewart shares account of Main Stand events as Bhoys fans challenge Celtic board]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183713</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/michael-stewart-shares-account-of-main-stand-events-as-bhoys-fans-challenge-celtic-board/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T18:34:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic board didn’t leave Celtic Park without criticism of their stewardship being aired loud and clear during the 2-0 Scottish Premiership defeat to Hearts....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers reacts to dreadful Saturday for Celtic as Hearts beat Bhoys, apologises to fans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183704</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-reacts-to-dreadful-saturday-for-celtic-as-hearts-beat-bhoys-apologises-to-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T17:42:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been defeated for the second successive Scottish Premiership match after Hearts were victorious with a 2-0 scoreline at Celtic Park on Saturday. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton criticises Brendan Rodgers with damning verdict after Celtic defeat to Hearts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183706</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/chris-sutton-criticises-brendan-rodgers-with-damning-verdict-after-celtic-defeat-to-hearts/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T17:06:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker Chris Sutton thinks the Bhoys have been “bang average” all season and shared criticism of Brendan Rodgers in the wake of today’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC 0 HEARTS 2: SHAMBOLIC CELTS’ TWO IN A WOE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115418</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-0-hearts-2-shambolic-celts-two-in-a-woe/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T16:54:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC 0 HEARTS 2 SHAMBOLIC Celtic stumbled to a second successive defeat in another Premiership shocker at Parkhead this afternoon. The champions have now carelessly thrown away six points in back-to-back league games following the loss to Kilmarnock at Rugby Park last weekend. The reaction from the stands at the end of a frustrating encounter [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic v Hearts, GG Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115416</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-hearts-gg-live-updates/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T14:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 15.00.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: CCV RETURNS, EURO HERO MISSING]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115309</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-ccv-returns-euro-hero-missing/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T13:53:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CAMERON CARTER-VICKERS takes his place in Celtic’s central defence against Hearts at Parkhead this afternoon after missing the last two games. A tight hamstring ruled the USA World Cup star out of the line-up for the matches against Kilmarnock and Feyenoord, but he returns alongside Liam Scales for the visit of the Tynecastle outfit. Stephen [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic XI confirmed: Big return, 2 changes, broadcast details, instant reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183700</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-vs-hearts-confirmed-2-changes-maeda-call-broadcast-details-instant-reaction/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T13:50:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manager Brendan Rodgers has named his Celtic team vs Hearts for today’s Scottish Premiership clash at Celtic Park. The full match squad is as follows:...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["My word"; BBC Sportsound panel rave about Celtic teenager coming through Lennoxtown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183694</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/james-mcfadden-raves-about-celtic-teenager-coming-through-lennoxtown/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T13:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the major positives coming out of the mid-week clash with Feyenoord was the impact of Mitchel Frame coming off the bench. The 17-year-old...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: £4m Celtic deal now expected to go through; could hasten exit of Ange-signed talent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183689</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/4m-celtic-deal-now-likely-and-it-could-hasten-exit-of-fringe-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T12:56:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have lots of work to do on the pitch before the winter break but January’s work off of it will be just as pivotal...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Brendan Rodgers set to show ruthless edge in Celtic January transfer window]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183686</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/report-indicates-brendan-rodgers-will-show-ruthless-edge-in-celtic-january-transfer-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T11:29:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are busy preparing for a pivotal January transfer window and it seems the month could throw up some surprising transfer business. Just six months...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 changes, boost for Rodgers; Celtic Predicted XI vs Hearts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183681</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/3-changes-boost-for-rodgers-celtic-predicted-xi-vs-hearts/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T10:56:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic can extend their Scottish Premiership points lead with a win over Hearts at Celtic Park on Saturday. With second-placed Rangers not featuring in league...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: KYOGO’S MISFIRING 387 MINUTES]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115413</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-kyogos-misfiring-387-minutes/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T09:55:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SHOCK! Horror! Kyogo Furuhashi has fired blanks in six consecutive games. If you wish to place the Japanese striker under even more intense scrutiny, he has delivered just one goal in the past nine outings. The last time we witnessed a pyramid celebration from the fans’ favourite came when he knocked one over the line from [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘NOT A SITUATION I FEEL RODGERS WOULD HAVE SIGNED UP FOR,’ EX-CELT FIRES WARNING]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115411</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/not-a-situation-i-feel-rodgers-would-have-signed-up-for-ex-celt-fires-warning/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T09:01:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS urgently requires quality additions to his squad – or Celtic will NOT be prepared for the challenges of Europe next season. Former Hoops goal hero Chris Sutton insists his old club were not ready for the Champions League this time out as they won only one, drew one and lost four of their [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GUSTAF OFF? EURO HERO TIPPED FOR EXIT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115394</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/gustaf-off-euro-hero-tipped-for-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T07:23:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CHAMPIONS League goal hero Gustaf Lagerbielke could be heading for the Celtic exit. The Swedish centre-back was the unlikely matchwinner when he headed in the clinching effort in the 2-1 midweek victory over Feyenoord at Parkhead. However, Lagerbielke, who arrived in the summer in a £3million deal from Elfsborg, is reported to be one of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC v HEARTS: 5-MINUTE QUIZ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115308</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-hearts-5-minute-quiz-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T06:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC were are at their swashbuckling best when they overwhelmed Hearts 4-1 at Tynecastlle earlier in the season. Brendan Rodgers will be hoping for an action replay against the Edinburgh team at Parkhead this afternoon, espeically after last weekend’s stumble at Rugby Park. How much can you remember about past associations with the club from [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS AND PRACTISING FREE-KICKS WITH THE KIDS AT 10PM: McGREGOR’S MEMORIES]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=39922</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/tommy-burns-and-practising-free-kicks-with-the-kids-at-10pm-mcgregors-memories/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T05:45:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC captain Callum McGregor has always insisted Tommy Burns was “a massive influence” in his career. The Hoops legend was born on this day in 1956 and would have celebrated his 67th birthday today. Burns served the Parkhead club as a gifted left-sided midfielder and he also as manager when he took over from Lou [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE BERTIE AULD: PART THIRTY-TWO: THE LONG GOODBYE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=87162</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-unforgettable-bertie-auld-part-thirty-two-the-long-goodbye/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T05:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bertie Auld always referred to Celtic fans “as the best in the world” and the irrepressible midfield mastermind liked nothing more than to put a smile of their faces. CQN have been celebrating the life and incredible times of the club legend in an EXCLUSIVE series with extracts from his best-selling autobiography, ‘A Bhoy [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic team news and potential starters for Hearts clash with big returns confirmed, one doubt]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183677</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-news-and-potential-starters-ahead-of-hearts-clash-with-big-returns-confirmed/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T19:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic take on Hearts in the Scottish Premiership on Saturday looking to pick up three points and move further ahead of second-placed Rangers in the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our Coefficient Monkeys, Insurrections, Daizen and CCV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115391</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/our-coefficient-monkeys-insurrections-daizen-and-ccv/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T12:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consecutive defeats saw Hearts slip from a promising third to a Gorgie Insurrectionist sixth over the last nine days.  Both reversals were by a single goal and came against our Coefficient Monkeys, Aberdeen and Newco, the latter of whom continue to do sterling work in Europe on behalf of the Scottish champions.  It really does [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NAT’S ALL, FOLKS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115389</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/nats-all-folks/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T08:48:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NAT PHILLIPS has almost certainly kicked his last ball for Celtic and will be on his way back to Liverpool when his short-term loan deal expires next month. The 26-year-old central defender was overlooked by Brendan Rodgers for the 2-1 Champions League midweek win over Feyenoord at Parkhead with Stephen Welsh making his comeback after [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I HAVEN’T ACHIEVED MUCH,’ INSISTS HOOPS HERO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115380</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-havent-achieved-much-insists-hoops-hero/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T07:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIAM SCALES played in all six of Celtic’s six Champions League games this season and won the Man of the Match accolade after the Hoops’ 2-1 midweek win over Feyenoord. However, the 25-year-old Republic of Ireland international acknowledged he has a lot to prove at his boyhood idols as he admits: “I haven’t achieved much [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE BERTIE AULD: PART THIRTY-ONE: ‘THE HUMBLING OF LEEDS’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=71489</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-unforgettable-bertie-auld-part-thirty-one-the-humbling-of-leeds/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T05:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bertie Auld and his good friend Bobby Murdoch were a formidable midfield double-act in Jock Stein’s all-conquering Celtic side. CQN are celebrating the life and incredible times of the club legend in an EXCLUSIVE series with extracts from his best-selling autobiography, ‘A Bhoy Called Bertie‘, co-authored by his friend and writer Alex Gordon. The [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘He wouldn’t’: James McFadden says Brendan Rodgers won’t answer one question at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183652</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/james-mcfadden-says-brendan-rodgers-wont-answer-one-question-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T21:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many were left surprised when Brendan Rodgers decided to re-join Celtic in the summer following Ange Postecoglou’s exit. Let’s be honest, how Brendan Rodgers left...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic 2-1 Feyenoord: Celtic get their first Champions League home win in 10 years]]></title>
        <id>https://celticunderground.net/?p=6705</id>
        <link href="http://celticunderground.net/celtic-2-1-feyenoord-celtic-get-their-first-champions-league-home-win-in-10-years/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T21:25:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MOTM, Liam Scales said: “I feel like today was sort of like the peak of it today, and I’m just glad that I could help the team to get the win and it’s a nice personal achievement as well to have that in the locker.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ethan Barlow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[’Not a happy man’: BBC reporter noticed what Arne Slot did moments before Celtic-Feyenoord incident]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183634</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/bbc-reporter-noticed-what-unhappy-arne-slot-did-moments-before-celtic-feyenoord-incident/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Diego Simeone to Arne Slot. There have been a few unhappy campers in Celtic’s opposition dugout in the Champions League this season. Celtic deservedly...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['He isn't going anywhere': John Hartson names Celtic player who will never leave]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183618</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/john-hartson-states-whether-celtic-captain-callum-mcgregor-will-finish-his-career-at-the-club/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T19:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor has been Mr Reliable and Mr Consistent in Celtic colours for a number of years now. That fresh-faced teenager, who went on-loan to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The UEFA Champions League will now never been the same again for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183616</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-uefa-champions-league-will-now-never-be-the-same-again-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T18:47:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic win over Feyenoord not only represented the end of this season’s UEFA Champions League group stage but the end of a European era...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘You don’t see on the telly’: James McFadden says Celtic star is 'frightening' to watch live]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183597</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/james-mcfadden-states-what-he-noticed-watching-celtics-kyogo-furuhashi-live-compared-to-on-the-telly/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans have had the privilege of watching two years of Kyogo Furuhashi’s magic.  That unknown figure who thrived at the club under Celtic’s Treble-winning...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's precarious UEFA coefficient position after Champions League group stage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183592</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-precarious-uefa-coefficient-position-after-champions-league-group-stage/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T17:32:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic earned more coefficient points this term than in the last three European campaigns but need a big performance next season to avoid slipping further...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James McFadden reckons fringe Celtic player just proved a point up against £44m-rated talent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183586</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/james-mcfadden-reckons-celtic-defence-just-proved-a-point-up-against-44m-rated-talent/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T16:58:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James McFadden was impressed with the way a makeshift Celtic defence competed against Feyenoord on Wednesday night, noting that they kept red-hot forward Santiago Gimenez...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Yaaaas: Trevor Sinclair delivers verdict on Mitchel Frame's Celtic debut, hails 'superb' teammate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183566</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/trevor-sinclair-delivers-verdict-on-mitchel-frames-celtic-debut-makes-joe-hart-claim-after-win-v-feyenoord/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic rounded off the 2023/24 Champions League campaign very positively after leaving it late to beat Feyenoord 2-1.  Brendan Rodgers sprung a few surprises from...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So much achieved in landmark Celtic win]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115376</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/so-much-achieved-in-landmark-celtic-win/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T12:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scouts who watch Celtic will know they can go months without facing a high press.  As a consequence, when we are forced to hold the ball in our final third without a safe option, you, me, and 11 Celtic players get a bit anxious. Greg Taylor was the most senior Celtic defender and took on [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘EVERYTHING SHOULD BE EASY FOR HIM NOW,’ McGREGOR’S TAKE ON TEEN NEW BHOY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115371</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/everything-should-be-easy-for-him-now-mcgregors-take-on-teen-new-bhoy/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T11:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CALLUM McGREGOR reckons teenage debutant Mitchel Frame will coast through the rest of his career! The 17-year-old left-sided defender took his Celtic bow as a 75th-minute substitute for the limping Luis Palma, scorer of the Hoops’ first goal via the penalty spot in long-overdue 2-1 Champions League victory over Feyenoord at Parkhead last night. Frame, who [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘ANIMALS,’ WELSH’S TRIBUTE TO TEAM-MATES]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115367</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/animals-welshs-tribute-to-team-mates/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T09:35:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[STEPHEN WELSH has given Brendan Rodgers a problem after answering the call to make his comeback in the 2-1 Champions League triumph over feyenoord at a rocking Parkhead last night. The centre-back admitted he was surprised to get the nod to play against the Dutch cracks after being sidelined with an ankle injury since his last [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[’That’s a surprise’: James McFadden shocked by what Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers did v Feyenoord]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183546</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/james-mcfadden-shocked-by-what-brendan-rodgers-did-before-celtics-win-over-feyenoord/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On paper, nothing was on the line for Celtic in their Group E Champions League clash against Feyenoord. But that doesn’t mean that pressure wasn’t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘NEED TO ADD QUALITY,’ RODGERS REMAINS FOCUSED]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115333</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/need-to-add-quality-rodgers-remains-focused/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T07:48:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS turned his thoughts to next month’s transfer window in the immediate aftermath of the courageous 2-1 victory over Feyenoord at Parkhead last night. The goals from Luis Palma, from the penalty spot, and Gustaf Lagerbielke, a late, late header at the back post, sealed the Hoops’ first home win in the Champions League [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Up there': Paul Merson sends Celtic Champions League message after dig at Manchester United]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183524</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/paul-merson-sends-celtic-champions-league-message-after-dig-at-manchester-united/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Merson spoke highly about the atmosphere at Celtic Park on Champions League nights, whilst digging at Manchester United. There were a number of big...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['He's unbelievable': Neil Lennon blown away by Celtic star with 'genuine quality' v Feyenoord]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183500</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/neil-lennon-delivers-verdict-on-matt-oriley-after-celtics-win-over-feyenoord-in-the-uefa-champions-league/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T06:30:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is anyone surprised? Probably not. But Matt O’Riley was at it again for Celtic on Wednesday. Whether it’s the Champions League or in the Scottish...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE BERTIE AULD: PART THIRTY: ‘THE BIG JOCK MYSTERY I NEVER SOLVED’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=61115</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-unforgettable-bertie-auld-part-thirty-the-big-jock-mystery-i-never-solved/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T05:30:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bertie Auld was an irresistible force in the engine room of Jock Stein’s all-conqering Celts in the sixties. CQN are celebrating the life and incredible times of the club legend in an EXCLUSIVE series with extracts from his best-selling autobiography, ‘A Bhoy Called Bertie‘, co-authored by his friend and writer Alex Gordon. The remarkable [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC 2 FEYENOORD 1: GUSTAF GLORY ENDS 10-YEAR WAIT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115328</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-2-feyenoord-1-gustaf-glory-ends-10-year-wait/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T22:15:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC 2 FEYENOORD 1 THE agonising decade-long wait for a Champions League group stage win ended in dramatic fashion at Parkhead tonight. Brendan Rodgers’ side had seen a first-half penalty-kick opener from Luis Palma wiped out by Feyenoord substitute Yankuba Minteh in the 82nd minute and the heads could have gone down. Instead, with Callum [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic banish unwelcome Champions League streak with dramatic win over Feyenoord]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183490</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-banish-unwelcome-champions-league-streak-with-dramatic-win-over-feyenoord/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T22:02:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s winless streak in the UEFA Champions League is finally over after a 2-1 victory at home to Feyenoord. Luis Palma put the Bhoys 1-0...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star set to return after 7-game absence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183483</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-latest-on-cameron-carter-vickers-and-daizen-maeda-celtic-injuries-after-missing-feyenoord/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T19:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have noticed Cameron Carter-Vickers and Daizen Maeda returned to full Celtic team training in videos and pictures on Tuesday, but it was always...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic v Feyenoord, GG Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115327</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-feyenoord-gg-live-updates/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T19:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 20:00.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surprise selection: Celtic XI confirmed, 2 changes, global TV details, instant reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183481</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-vs-feyenoord-confirmed-defensive-surprise-2-changes-global-tv-details-instant-reaction/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T18:51:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manager Brendan Rodgers has named his Celtic team vs Feyenoord for tonight’s UEFA Champions League match at Celtic Park. The full squad is as follows:...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: WELSH IN AS PHILLIPS DROPS OUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115251</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-welsh-in-as-phillips-drops-out/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T18:51:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[STEPHEN WELSH gets a start against Feyenoord in the final Champions League Group E encounter against Feyenoord at Parkhead tonight. The former Scotland Under-21 skipper returns to central defence in place of on-loan Nat Phillips who drops to the substitutes’ bench from the line-up that lost to Kilmarnock at Rugby Park on Sunday. Welsh has [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['They suffer': Neil Lennon expresses concern for current Celtic side with Victor Wanyama message]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183449</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/neil-lennon-expresses-concern-for-current-celtic-side-drops-scott-brown-and-victor-wanyamas-names/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon has highlighted a real concern he is seeing in this Celtic side under Brendan Rodgers and how it lacks that bite. From Kyogo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["The most fanatical"; Brendan Rodgers responds to Celtic fan backlash after defeat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183453</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-responds-to-celtic-fan-backlash-after-defeat/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T17:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers wants his staff and players to remain calm in the wake of defeat to Kilmarnock on Sunday. The Bhoys slipped to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers just gave us another glimpse into how he feels about regressive Celtic summer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183444</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-just-gave-us-another-glimpse-into-how-he-feels-about-regressive-celtic-summer/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has said he was initially “excited” to return to Celtic and take charge of the squad that was in place at the time....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I have never': Chris Sutton shocked by what’s happening with 'dynamic' star Celtic sold in 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183420</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-shocked-at-what-is-happening-with-ryan-christie-now-after-celtic-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Years and years after strong services for Celtic, Ryan Christie has now worked his way up to be an established Premier League player in England. ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feyenoord boss Arne Slot makes it clear what he thinks of Celtic after Champions League group]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183418</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/feyenoord-boss-arne-slot-makes-it-clear-what-he-thinks-of-celtic-after-champions-league-group/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T16:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feyenoord boss Arne Slot reckons that Celtic have been desperately unlucky in their UEFA Champions League group stage campaign. Slot’s side are in Glasgow for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic dramatically beaten by Feyenoord in UEFA Youth League after second-half collapse]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183410</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/celtic-dramatically-beaten-by-feyenoord-in-uefa-youth-league-after-second-half-collapse/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T16:01:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic U19s have been beaten by their Feyenoord counterparts in Glasgow today, ending their participation in this season’s UEFA Youth League. Goals from Lewis Dobbie...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers fronts up and explains why struggling Celtic star was benched]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183405</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-shares-why-kyogo-was-benched-for-celtic-lennoxtown-analysis-addresses-big-issue/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T15:26:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers benched Celtic striker Kyogo Furuhashi primarily to help him get speed and intensity back into his game after a heavy run of matches....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defensive absences, midfield call; Celtic team news and Predicted XI for Feyenoord test]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183399</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/defensive-absences-midfield-call-celtic-team-news-and-predicted-xi-for-feyenoord-test/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic end their 2023/24 UEFA Champions League campaign with a home match against Feyenoord tonight. It’s fair to say Group E hasn’t gone well for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I'm not going to’: Neil Lennon issues classy response to comment about Celtic's Brendan Rodgers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183380</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/neil-lennon-issues-classy-response-to-comment-about-celtic-and-brendan-rodgers-in-europe/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T14:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s European performances haven’t gone as well as many would have liked, with only one point registered from this season’s Champions League campaign. Both Celtic...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘They were a disgrace’: John Hartson expresses annoyance at four Celtic players]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183364</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/john-hartson-expresses-annoyance-at-four-celtic-players-labels-them-a-disgrace/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T12:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not only was it headlines that Celtic suffered a defeat at Kilmarnock over the weekend, it was also the manner of defeat which frustrated everyone....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘You get comfortable’: John Hartson says Celtic star only starting so Brendan Rodgers can sell him]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183350</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/john-hartson-says-celtic-24-year-old-only-starting-so-brendan-rodgers-can-sell-him/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T12:10:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a lot of opinions and thoughts flying around about Mikey Johnston at Celtic, even from Brendan Rodgers. After Celtic’s thumping win over Hibernian...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running out of road against the Rotters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115310</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/running-out-of-road-against-the-rotters/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T12:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has no relevance for tonight, but the best news from Brendan Rodgers media appearance yesterday was that Cameron Carter-Vickers and Daizen Maeda will return to action for Saturday’s game against Hearts.  Both are huge players, especially so on Champions League nights, but the urgency of that matter has passed. The defence will inevitably line-up [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘BLAME ME,’ INSISTS RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115312</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/blame-me-insists-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T10:27:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has rallied round Nat Phillips as he prepares his squad for the Champions League encounter against Feyenoord at Parkhead tonight. The Celtic manager has a massive decision to make in his team selection for the final European outing of the season. Cameron Carter-Vickers will be sidelined for the second consecutive game with a hamstring [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘HE’S NOT A BABY,’ BRENDAN’S WAKE-UP CALL TO KYOGO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115304</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hes-not-a-baby-brendans-wake-up-call-to-kyogo/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T08:41:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO FURUHASHI will lead the Celtic attack against Feyenoord at Parkhead tonight, despite firing blanks in the past five games. The Japanese international striker has failed to start the previous two Premiership encounters with Oh Hyeon-gyu getting the nod to face Hibs and Kilmarnock. However, Brendan Rodgers will show faith in Kyogo, who has claimed [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘WE HAVE A LOT TO PROVE,’ McGREGOR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115298</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/we-have-a-lot-to-prove-mcgregor/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T07:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CALLUM McGREGOR insists the pain from the calamitous collapse against Kilmarnock will add to Celtic’s motivation to overcome Feyenoord at Parkhead tonight. Unfortunately, the final Champions League Group E encounter is meaningless in regard to remaining in European competition after Christmas, but the Hoops captain is convinced pride and true grit will carry them through on [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC v FEYENOORD: 5-MINUTE QUIZ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115246</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-feyenoord-5-minute-quiz/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T06:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS and Celtic are aiming for a grand finale in their last European encounter of the campaign when Feyenoord provide the opposition at Parkhead this evening. As far as qualification is concerned, the game is meaningless, but pride is at stake and the Hoops will want to go out in a blaze of glory [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['There are 18 days to go': John Hartson thinks Celtic star could make surprising return v Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183333</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/john-hartson-thinks-a-surprise-could-be-on-the-cards-with-reo-hatate-ahead-of-celtic-v-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T06:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have hugely missed Reo Hatate’s personality in the middle of the park and it’s great to hear that he is edging closer to returning...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS IN EURO MISSION: No.48]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113932</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-in-euro-mission-no-48/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T06:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS will take charge of Celtic for the 48th time in European competition against Feyenoord at Parkhead this evening. The Hoops boss hopes to bring down the curtain on a luckless qualifying campaign in Group E with a win over the Dutch outfit who kick-started the club’s misery with a 2-0 victory over nine-man [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELT’S ZERO AMBITION]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115243</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celts-zero-ambition/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T06:15:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AT THE age of 36 and with 75 international appearances for England on his impressive CV, Joe Hart is searching for a football first this evening – a Champions League clean sheet for Celtic. The experienced keeper goes into the final match in Group E of Europe’s elite competition after shipping TWENTY-NINE goals in 11 [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE LAST HURRAH: TEN YEARS AGO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113412</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-last-hurrah-ten-years-ago/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T06:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE last time the Celtic fans streamed out of Parkhead after witnessing a Champions League group triumph was just over a decade ago. James Forrest, who opened the scoring with a penalty-kick in the first-half of the 2-1 win over Ajax, is the only survivor from the EIGHTEEN players who were stripped in Neil Lennon’s matchday [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE BERTIE AULD: PART TWENTY-NINE: ‘BIG BILLY, A BORN WINNER’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=63461</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-unforgettable-bertie-auld-part-twenty-nine-big-billy-a-born-winner/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T05:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bertie Auld was the strutting maestro of Jock Stein’s team of all-stars in the sixties. CQN are celebrating the life and incredible times of the Celtic legend in an EXCLUSIVE series with extracts from his best-selling autobiography, ‘A Bhoy Called Bertie‘, co-authored by his friend and writer Alex Gordon. The remarkable life story continues [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xmas Podcast with Hail Hail History]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18545</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18545"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T22:38:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Desi and Hector get together with a very special Xmas Podcast guest, Matthew from Hail Hail History to discuss the past, present and future like…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Desi Mond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['You have to do more': James McFadden reacts to Brendan Rodgers' public actions towards Celtic star]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183313</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/james-mcfadden-weighs-in-on-brendan-rodgers-comments-on-celtic-winger-mikey-johnston/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T20:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James McFadden has weighed in on the situation involving Celtic winger, Mikey Johnston. Brendan Rodgers took an interesting step in deciding to publicly critique the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['The man is on form': Scott Brown impressed by 24-year-old on Celtic's transfer radar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183297</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-scott-brown-said-about-celtic-transfer-target-and-aberdeen-striker-bojan-miovski/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T19:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite Aberdeen’s struggles in the Scottish Premiership this season, Bojan Miovski is having a campaign to remember. That’s why the 24-year-old is attracting interest elsewhere,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘We are talking as if’: Neil Lennon fires Celtic and Rangers warning ahead of December 30 meeting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183283</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/neil-lennon-fires-celtic-and-rangers-warning-ahead-of-december-30-meeting/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T17:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon was in a pretty blunt mood when discussing Celtic’s showdown against Rangers on December 30. Celtic dropped points for the first time on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FINAL SAY: ‘WE WANT TO DO EVERYTHING WE CAN,’ INSISTS RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115286</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/final-say-we-want-to-do-everything-we-can-insists-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T17:27:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is looking for Celtic to return to their expected form when they bring down the curtain on the Champions League quest against Feyenoord at Parkhead tomorrow. Alas, only pride is at stake in the final Group E encounter that sees the Hoops rock-bottom of the section with only one point following four defeats and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['He's unbelievable': Scott Brown says Celtic star with only 2 starts under Rodgers has 'everything']]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=183263</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/scott-brown-reacts-to-brendan-rodgers-publicly-challenging-celtic-winger-mikey-johnston/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are now preparing for the final Group E game of the UEFA Champions League on Wednesday and changes are expected for Feyenoord’s visit. In...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC DOUBLE TV SWITCH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115282</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-double-tv-switch/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T16:43:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S Premiership trips to Aberdeen and Hibs will be shown live by Sky Sports early in the new year. The satellite will beam the game against the Dons at Pittodrie on Saturday February 3 with a 12.30pm kick-off. And the cameras will follow the champions to Edinburgh four days later for the meeting with Hibs [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A team with a hunted look to them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115267</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/a-team-with-a-hunted-look-to-them/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T12:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a bad defeat, would you rather a difficult game against a Champions League team at Celtic Park, or an awkward visit to a Premiership side playing 10 men behind the ball?  Neither seems a great prospect, but in a tight league race, the latter is definitely not a desired option. A big performance and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic want to sign £4 million-rated player in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45945</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-4-million-player-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T23:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The defeat at the hands of Lazio was further proof of Celtic’s need to strengthen in the January transfer window. The club might have brought in nine new faces in the summer but a lot of people feel that the team has taken a step back since last season, when they breezed past the competition […]
Celtic want to sign £4 million-rated player in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers sends clear message Celtic board must not ignore]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45941</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/brendan-rodgers-message-celtic-board/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T21:35:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s fate in Europe for this season is sealed after their 2-0 defeat at the hands of Lazio. The result means that the Hoops are guaranteed to finish bottom of their group in the UEFA Champions League. That also means that they will not be dropping down to the Europa League, something that should have […]
Brendan Rodgers sends clear message Celtic board must not ignore - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton publicly criticises Celtic after loss to Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45938</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/chris-sutton-celtic-loss-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T20:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic lost 2-0 away in Rome to Lazio. The Hoops were in the match for a long time before Ciro Immobile came off the bench to score a brace and put the game to bed. The result means that not only are Brendan Rodgers’ side out of the Champions League following the group stages but […]
Chris Sutton publicly criticises Celtic after loss to Lazio - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed £7 million Jeremie Frimpong windfall news]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45933</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-jeremie-frimpong-windfall-news/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremie Frimpong’s rise at Bayer Leverkusen has been fascinating, to say the least. The Dutchman had shown a lot of quality going forward at Celtic as well but not many could have foreseen him becoming one of the most prolific wingbacks in Europe just a few years later. That is exactly what has happened under […]
Celtic handed £7 million Jeremie Frimpong windfall news - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic told 29-goal striker is good enough amid links]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45930</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-told-29-goal-striker-good-enough/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T13:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to add to their options up top this January. Kyogo has done well once again but he is not scoring as frequently as he was last season. On the other hand, Oh Hyeon-gyu has been inconsistent as well and is not at the level required to start for the Hoops right now. There […]
Celtic told 29-goal striker is good enough amid links - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anderlecht consider making offer for Celtic standout in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45927</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/anderlecht-offer-celtic-standout-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T11:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have not had the greatest campaign till now. They were eliminated early from the Scottish League Cup and while they do lead the Premiership, their performances and results have been somewhat inconsistent. Almost half a season on, it feels like the Hoops are still finding their feet under the management of Brendan Rodgers and […]
Anderlecht consider making offer for Celtic standout in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serie A club want to sign Celtic player amid contract worry]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45907</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/serie-club-want-celtic-player-contract/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T22:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic fans hope for more quality players arriving there could be a problem with others heading for the exit door. It seems pretty clear that Brendan Rodgers wants to make the size of the squad more manageable over the next couple of transfer windows and departures are expected. But there is a risk of […]
Serie A club want to sign Celtic player amid contract worry - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur step up bid to sign Celtic-linked player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45918</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/tottenham-hotspur-bid-sign-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur made a fantastic start to the season under the management of Ange Postecoglou. With Harry Kane leaving the club in the summer for Bayern Munich, most expected them to struggle. Instead, they appeared to be putting up an unlikely title challenge and were sitting atop the Premier League table not too long ago. […]
Tottenham Hotspur step up bid to sign Celtic-linked player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boost in race to sign £11 million Real Madrid player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45914</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/celtic-boost-real-madrid-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to sign a goalkeeper in the near future. It is quite clear that Joe Hart is not the long-term solution between the posts. The Englishman’s performances have been criticised lately. Also, he is set to turn 37 years of age before this season comes to an end. So, while he has done a […]
Celtic boost in race to sign £11 million Real Madrid player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio boss Maurizio Sarri makes fantastic Celtic claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45910</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/lazio-boss-maurizio-sarri-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T18:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By now, Celtic fans have accepted that Brendan Rodgers’ side are most probably not going through or even finishing third in their group in the UEFA Champions League. It would be a positive step to get a win in the competition though. It has been quite some time since the Hoops won at this level. […]
Lazio boss Maurizio Sarri makes fantastic Celtic claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic tipped to go for 28-year-old Premiership striker]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45904</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/celtic-tipped-go-premiership-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T12:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans breathed a sigh of relief as the Rangers dropped points at the weekend against Aberdeen. In fact, it took a late penalty for them to even come out with a draw from the game. That means that the Hoops will maintain their strong position at the top of the Scottish Premiership table. That […]
Celtic tipped to go for 28-year-old Premiership striker - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£7.5 million Mathias Kvistgaarden to Celtic transfer update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45900</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/mathias-kvistgaarden-celtic-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T10:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to sign a striker in January. On one hand, we have seen the club struggle for goals in some games this season. When the opposition puts up a resolute defence, the Hoops do not appear to have a lot of answers other than Kyogo, Matt O’Riley or Luis Palma. On the other hand, […]
£7.5 million Mathias Kvistgaarden to Celtic transfer update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur have been eyeing Celtic superstar]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45896</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/tottenham-hotspur-eyeing-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T23:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou made the move to Tottenham Hotspur in the summer and it was only a matter of time before the Australian was linked with a reunion with some Celtic players. The manager enjoyed a lot of success at Parkhead, even though he was at the club for just two seasons, and won five trophies […]
Tottenham Hotspur have been eyeing Celtic superstar - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John McGinn claims he spoke to Celtic players about manager]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45890</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/john-mcginn-spoke-celtic-players/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T21:35:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most Celtic fans will remember how the club missed out on the opportunity to sign John McGinn some years back. The Scot grew up supporting the Hoops but a move to Parkhead failed to materialise even though it had looked close and he ended up moving down south to join Aston Villa. McGinn has risen […]
John McGinn claims he spoke to Celtic players about manager - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic must consider signing striker from Premiership rivals]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45886</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-signing-striker-premiership-rivals/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T20:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there is one position where Celtic need to strengthen during the upcoming January transfer window, it is striker. The Hoops have been pretty inconsistent in front of goal this season so far. Of course, there are games when they can go out and score six times. But then, on days they are having a […]
Celtic must consider signing striker from Premiership rivals - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend takes dig at Rangers player for diving]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45884</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-legend-rangers-player-diving/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T18:35:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Celtic drew 1-1 against Motherwell, the Rangers were handed a major chance to get back into the title race. All they needed to do was win their games in hand and they would be just three points behind the Hoops in the league table. We have seen the Ibrox side not perform at their […]
Celtic legend takes dig at Rangers player for diving - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player criticised after draw against Motherwell]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45881</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-player-criticised-draw-motherwell/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T12:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Titles are not decided this early in the season. That has been proven once again. Not too long ago, Celtic were sitting seven points clear at the top of the Premiership table and most fans felt that the league was pretty much in the bag with the Rangers struggling for any kind of form.  It […]
Celtic player criticised after draw against Motherwell - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgio Chiellini makes superb claim about Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45874</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/giorgio-chiellini-claim-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T10:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Giorgio Chiellini is one of the best defenders of all time and he had some pretty positive comments about Celtic Park recently. The 39-year-old spent the majority of his career playing for Juventus and won more silverware there than one should try to count. Overall, he made more […]
Giorgio Chiellini makes superb claim about Celtic Park - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s problem is very clear and needs solving quick]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45870</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/celtic-problem-needs-solving-quick/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T19:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two more dropped points mean that Celtic have well and truly allowed the Rangers to get back into the title race. A lead which once stood at seven points, could be reduced to three if Philippe Clement’s side are able to win their games in hand. And the sad thing is that the Hoops have […]
Celtic’s problem is very clear and needs solving quick - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic problem after draw]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45866</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/brendan-rodgers-celtic-problem-draw/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T18:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was not the result Celtic were looking for, as they dropped two valuable points against Motherwell. David Turnbull’s goal appeared to have won it for the Hoops but the visitors equalised in the 90th minute and it ended 1-1. That means that if the Rangers win their games in hand, the gap will be […]
Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic problem after draw - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hollywood superstar pictured wearing Celtic jersey]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45861</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/hollywood-pictured-wearing-celtic-jersey/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T12:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Celtic have their fair share of famous fans. Rod Stewart is the first name that comes to most people’s minds, one of the best-selling music artists in history. Lewis Capaldi is another popular musician known to support the Hoops. And several A-list celebrities like Gerard Butler, Snoop Dogg, […]
Hollywood superstar pictured wearing Celtic jersey - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic pushing for priority signing in January window]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45859</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/celtic-priority-signing-january-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T09:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s January transfer window is expected to be a busy one. The club might have made nine signings in the summer, seven arriving on a permanent basis and two on loan, but there are still holes in Brendan Rodgers’ squad that need to be filled. On the other hand, there are way too many players […]
Celtic pushing for priority signing in January window - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable source offers Sydney van Hooijdonk to Celtic update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45854</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/reliable-sydney-van-hooijdonk-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T22:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are believed to be on the lookout for a striker in the January transfer window. There might be a few reasons behind that. Firstly, both Kyogo and Oh Hyeon-gyu might be unavailable for a considerable length of time early next year due to the AFC Asian Cup. They are the club’s two options to […]
Reliable source offers Sydney van Hooijdonk to Celtic update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou claims Celtic success gets dismissed]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45852</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/ange-postecoglou-claims-celtic-success/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T21:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has proven to be a major success in the Premier League since swapping Celtic for Tottenham Hotspur. Of course, a lot of fans were not happy to see him depart after just two years at Parkhead. But he has been very respectful about the club even after leaving. And it is hard not […]
Ange Postecoglou claims Celtic success gets dismissed - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>