<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-07-19T18:12:33.709Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic new signing admits to Premier League dream already]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42750</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/19/celtic-admits-premier-league-dream/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T18:05:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Ange Postecoglou left Celtic, days after leading them to a domestic treble, it was viewed as a major problem for the club. They went out and brought in the best possible replacement though in the form of Brendan Rodgers. The Northern Irishman is already proven in the Scottish game, having won seven trophies during […]
Celtic new signing admits to Premier League dream already - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next Celtic signing looks imminent as club decide against Japan route]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167844</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/hyun-jun-yang-announcement-looks-imminent-as-celtic-decide-against-japan-option/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The signing of Hyun-jun Yang now looks imminent for Celtic after the player flew in to the UK. The Gangwon winger has been widely known to be moving to Glasgow for several days. The K League 1 club even confirmed that he had departed for Celtic four days ago. But to date there has been ...
The post Next Celtic signing looks imminent as club decide against Japan route appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's former POTY has shown his time at the club may not be up yet - Opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167825</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/david-turnbull-has-shown-he-could-still-have-a-role-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Turnbull is a player that arrived at Celtic with a lot of promise back in August 2020. After his initial move to the club fell through the previous summer due to a medical issue, Neil Lennon waited it out and finally got his man once he resolved his fitness concerns. He made an immediate ...
The post Celtic's former POTY has shown his time at the club may not be up yet - Opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic stars show off more cracking Adidas gear but there's a catch for supporters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167824</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-stars-show-off-more-cracking-adidas-gear-but-theres-a-catch-for-supporters/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic first-team squad showed off some cracking new Adidas gear on Wednesday. The players were at the Nissan Stadium in Yokohama, where they went down 6-4 to Kevin Muscat’s Yokohama F. Marinos. It was an exciting match in what was our first high-profile fixture since the Scottish Cup final at the start of June. ...
The post Celtic stars show off more cracking Adidas gear but there's a catch for supporters appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers praises Celtic star for performance in unfamiliar role]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167808</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-praises-tomoki-iwata-for-performance-in-unfamiliar-celtic-role/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The result in Celtic’s first fixture of the Japan Tour didn’t really go the way the fans would have wanted but for Celtic manager, Brendan Rodgers, today’s game was not about the result. It was all about getting minutes into the legs and casting his eye over the squad for the coming season. From today’s ...
The post Brendan Rodgers praises Celtic star for performance in unfamiliar role appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers explains how he will use the Celtic squad differently in Gamba Osaka clash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167801</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-explains-how-he-will-use-the-celtic-squad-differently-in-gamba-osaka-clash/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has explained how he will use his Celtic squad for the upcoming Gamba Osaka clash. The Hoops are in Japan where they went down 6-4 to Yokohama F. Marinos on Wednesday. They will now travel west to Osaka ahead of Saturday’s match. Rodgers has been speaking to Celtic TV in the aftermath of ...
The post Brendan Rodgers explains how he will use the Celtic squad differently in Gamba Osaka clash appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Odin Thiago Holm situation after he misses Celtic vs Yokohama F. Marinos clash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167784</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-odin-thiago-holm-situation-after-he-misses-celtic-vs-yokohama-f-marinos-clash/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New summer signing Odin Thiago Holm didn’t feature for Celtic in Wednesday’s game against Yokohama F. Marinos. Brendan Rodgers‘ side went down 6-4 to the slick hosts in a frantic match that saw a number of new players given opportunities. Potential stars of the future like Ben McPherson, Ben Summers and Daniel Kelly all got ...
The post The Odin Thiago Holm situation after he misses Celtic vs Yokohama F. Marinos clash appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: AEK Athens reject huge offer from French club for reported Celtic target Levi Garcia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167770</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/aek-athens-rejects-e22m-offer-from-french-club-for-reported-celtic-target-levi-garcia/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been fairly active in the transfer window over the last few weeks. The acquisition of Odin Thiago Holm and Marco Tilio has whetted the appetite of the Celtic support as they wait to see what other additions Brendan Rodgers will make to the first-team squad. There is, of course, the imminent arrivals of ...
The post Report: AEK Athens reject huge offer from French club for reported Celtic target Levi Garcia appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic footage shows class Yokohama airing of adored 2023 chant]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167776</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-footage-shows-class-yokohama-airing-of-adored-2023-chant/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic support in Yokohama made plenty of noise despite defeat on Wednesday. The Hoops went down 6-4 to Yokohama F. Marinos in an engrossing friendly match at the vast Nissan Stadium. Daizen Maeda netted a first-half hat-trick on his return to the stadium while David Turnbull struck a sweet consolation with the final kick ...
The post Celtic footage shows class Yokohama airing of adored 2023 chant appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers reacts as Celtic lose Japan Tour opener to Yokohama F Marinos]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167761</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-reacts-as-celtic-lose-japan-tour-opener-to-yokohama-f-marinos/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T13:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marked the first real test for Brendan Rodgers as Celtic took on Yokohama F Marinos in the first fixture of the Japan Tour. An outstanding first-half hattrick from Daizen Maeda wasn’t enough to prevent Celtic losing 6-4 to the J League side but, despite the scoreline, there was still a lot of positives to ...
The post Brendan Rodgers reacts as Celtic lose Japan Tour opener to Yokohama F Marinos appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YOKOHAMA F MARINOS 6 CELTIC 4: MAEDA HAT-TRICK AS HOOPS HIT FOR SIX]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110009</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/yokohama-f-marinos-6-celtic-4-maeda-hat-trick-as-hoops-hit-for-six/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T13:05:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YOKOHAMA F MARINOS 6 CELTIC 4 CELTIC lost out in 10-goal blitz as they were hit for six by their Japanese hosts in the Nissan Stadium. The Hoops were leading 3-2 at the interval following a superb hat-trick from Daizen Maeda before Brendan Rodgers’ men were caught up in an extraordinary second-half whirlwind. The defence [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano confirms Celtic interest in €20m player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42746</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/19/fabrizio-romano-celtic-20m-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T12:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a very important summer transfer window for Celtic. With Ange Postecoglou leaving the club and Brendan Rodgers replacing him in the Parkhead hot seat, the Hoops need to make sure that they back the Northern Irishman to reshape and rebuild the squad according to his vision and plans. Till now, they have completed […]
Fabrizio Romano confirms Celtic interest in €20m player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Important commercial day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110008</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/important-commercial-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T11:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[5,800 miles is a long way to go for two football games but that’s the distance from Celtic Park to the Nissan Stadium, where Celtic are currently playing Yokohama F. Marinos.  It has been a great trip so far for our sizeable Japanese contingent, while the commercial department have been able to put down some [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic team vs Yokohama confirmed; interesting right back options, youth options on the bench]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167742</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-team-vs-yokohama-confirmed-interesting-right-back-options-youth-options-on-the-bench/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T09:09:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hype of the Japan Tour has been building up since the announcement was made that Celtic was going to visit the country back in May. With Celtic’s first-team squad brimming with Japanese players, the opportunity to tour the country was a no-brainer by the club. And now, after months of preparation, Celtic are set ...
The post Celtic team vs Yokohama confirmed; interesting right back options, youth options on the bench appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports man confirms Celtic contact for Egyptian player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42742</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/19/sky-sports-celtic-contact-egyptian/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T09:05:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are rumoured to be considering marquee signings this summer but till now, they have only brought in highly-rated young talents. The signings of Marco Tilio and Odin Thiago Holm were completed early on in the window and it is believed that official announcements for the arrivals of Yang Hyun-jun and Kwon Hyeok-kyu will be […]
Sky Sports man confirms Celtic contact for Egyptian player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic make contact for international midfielder; Brendan Rodgers discusses Korean duo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167735</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-make-contact-for-mohamed-reda-brendan-rodgers-discusses-korean-duo/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s transfer business has been somewhat unpredictable this summer. Even though the club had added three new signings, with another two on the way, in a strange way it does seem like a quiet window. Maybe it’s because we all know Brendan Rodgers has a sizeable transfer fund that he hasn’t really dipped into as ...
The post Celtic make contact for international midfielder; Brendan Rodgers discusses Korean duo appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘A WONDERFUL JOB,’ RODGERS HAILS JAPANESE BHOYS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109990</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/a-wonderful-job-rodgers-hails-japanese-bhoys/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T08:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS praised Celtic’s Japanese Bhoys when he talked to the local media before the match against Yokohama F Marinos in the Nissan stadium today. Naturally, the Far East Press contingent were eager for informationtion on the progress of Kyogo Furuhashi, Reo Hatate, Daizen Maeda, Tomoki Iwata and Yuki Kobayashi at the treble winners. The [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No fear on show as Celtic's Japanese stars target Europe's big guns in Champions League]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167725</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/no-fear-on-show-as-celtics-japanese-stars-target-europes-big-guns-in-champions-league/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic prepare to face Yokohama F Marinos in the first leg of the Japanese Tour, all eyes will be on the Nissan Stadium as the fans get to see their heroes in action for the first time this season. The Hoops support will be fully focused on looking at the team’s set-up, style of ...
The post No fear on show as Celtic's Japanese stars target Europe's big guns in Champions League appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEW BHOYS DELAY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109987</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/new-bhoys-delay/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T07:34:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HOPES for South Korean duo Yang Hyun-jun and Kwon Hyeok-kyu to team up with Celtic in Japan have been dashed. The deals for the players have yet to be rubber-stamped, but the champions do not anticipate any problems with red tape before getting the transfers over the line. It is now more likely winger Yang [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic make intriguing digital and commercial-based announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167726</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-make-intriguing-digital-and-commercial-based-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T07:11:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have announced the appointment of lifelong supporter Brian Rose as a new Non-Executive Director. Just after 7:30am on Wednesday morning, the club released a statement confirming the arrival of digital and commercial expert Rose with immediate effect. They say that he is currently a Director of Apple Services based in London and has worked ...
The post Celtic make intriguing digital and commercial-based announcement appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers evaluates Reo Hatate; Celtic boss addresses transfer rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167720</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-evaluates-reo-hatate-the-champions-league-game-that-impressed-the-celtic-boss/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T06:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate has been a player that every Celtic fan has raved about over the last season and a half. The Japanese midfielder joined Celtic in the 2021 January window and right from the get-go, made an immediate impact on the first-team. A crucial goal against Hearts in the 2-1 win at Tynecastle was quickly ...
The post Brendan Rodgers evaluates Reo Hatate; Celtic boss addresses transfer rumours appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REVEALED: RODGERS’ REO HOPE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109983</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/revealed-rodgers-reo-hope/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T06:39:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is planning on unleashing a new, improved Reo Hatate in the forthcoming season. The returning Celtic manager is already aware of the qualities of the in-demand Japanese midfielder who was an immediate hit with the Hoops fans after a double salvo in a crucial 3-0 victory over Ibrox visitors on February 2 2022. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wolves player expecting to see a big Celtic support in Dublin; ticket latest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167628</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/wolves-player-expecting-to-see-a-big-celtic-support-in-dublin-ticket-latest/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T06:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wolves midfielder Joe Hodge sounds like he’s expecting a large Celtic support in Dublin later this month. The Hoops are due to face Wolves at the Aviva Stadium on Saturday 29 July in what will be our penultimate fixture before the start of the competitive action. The game was only announced last week, and there ...
The post Wolves player expecting to see a big Celtic support in Dublin; ticket latest appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic make approach for 25-year-old winger; estimated fee, EPL interest, player stance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167716</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-make-approach-for-ferreira-estimated-fee-epl-interest-player-stance/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T05:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have reportedly made an approach for Brazilian winger, Ferreira according to Football Scotland. The report says that the club has put out ‘early feelers’ to his club, Gremio, to get an idea of what the Brazilian Serie A side would be looking for for him. It is also claimed that Ferreira is also keen ...
The post Report: Celtic make approach for 25-year-old winger; estimated fee, EPL interest, player stance appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC MISFIT’S FOUR CLUBS IN A YEAR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109963</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-misfits-four-clubs-in-a-year/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T05:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OLIVER ABILDGAARD experienced a ‘now-you-see-me-now-you-don’t’ whistle-stop career at Celtic. The towering Danish midfielder agreed a season-long loan at the Hoops last summer from Ruben Kazan, the third player, along with Carl Starfelt and Sead Haksabanovic, to join from the cash-strapped Russian side since Ange Postecoglou’s arrival in June 2021. Abildgaard failed to impress in his [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…EFRAIN JUAREZ?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109965</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-efrain-juarez/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T05:15:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MEXICAN World Cup midfielder Efrain Juarez arrived at Celtic in a £2million four-year deal in July 2010. Expectation levels were high, but once again the 21-year-old playmaker, signed from homeland club UNAM Pumas, turned out to be an expensive flop. Juarez made a total of 13 league appearances for Neil Lennon’s side after his debut [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Managers Ranked! – Part One]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18402</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18402"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T05:10:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managers … they arrive, they talk the talk, they kiss the badge, and then they leave. Most, but not all, win a trophy or two…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kiwi Mick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Right-back chance, large Japanese influence; Celtic Predicted XI vs Yokohama F. Marinos]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167645</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/right-back-chance-large-japanese-influence-celtic-predicted-xi-vs-yokohama-f-marinos/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T05:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are back in action on Wednesday as we face Yokohama F. Marinos. It’s the first of two games we’ll face in Japan and the opposition could hardly be tougher. F. Marinos are the reigning champions of the J1 League and joint-top halfway through the current season. They will be fit, sharp and ready to ...
The post Right-back chance, large Japanese influence; Celtic Predicted XI vs Yokohama F. Marinos appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: ‘THE DAY I GOT TO PLAY WITH THE LIONS’: EVAN WILLIAMS REVEALS ALL (Part Five)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=93957</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-the-day-i-got-to-play-with-the-lions-evan-williams-reveals-all-part-five/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T05:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EVAN WILLIAMS made history on May 1 1971 when he played in the final appearance of the Lisbon Lions. Jock Stein decided to look to the future as the European Cup-winning team of four years earlier was now breaking up. Ronnie Simpson, at the age of 41, would say farewell to the Celtic support in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEW £17m STAND, NEW ERA, NEW HOPE: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Eight)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=93936</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/new-17m-stand-new-era-new-hope-the-tommy-burns-story-part-eight/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T04:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS had won the Scottish Cup in his first season as Celtic manager after his appointment on July 12 1994. The league title, though, was the legendary Celt’s priority target as his second campaign prepared to kick off. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE series, we chart Tommy Burns’ career as the Hoops gaffer during turbulent [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player encouraged Conor Hazard’s Plymouth Argyle move]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42663</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/18/celtic-player-conor-hazard-plymouth/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T22:05:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have emerged as one of the most notable clubs for youngsters to display their quality to the world. Things do not work out for everybody at the club though. One such example is that of Conor Hazard, who joined their youth set up in 2014 and quickly established himself as one of the most […]
Celtic player encouraged Conor Hazard’s Plymouth Argyle move - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jyotirmoy Halder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£6 million winger wants to join Celtic amid rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42734</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/18/6-million-winger-wants-join-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T20:30:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been active in the summer transfer window for sure but most of their focus has been on bringing in highly-rated young talents from around the globe. Odin Thiago Holm has been signed from Valerenga and Marco Tilio from Melbourne City FC, while a double announcement for Kwon Hyeok-kyu and Yang Hyun-jun is believed […]
£6 million winger wants to join Celtic amid rumours - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I like the kid" - Peter Grant backs 'unfortunate' Celtic man to thrive under Rodgers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167631</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/peter-grant-backs-unfortunate-celtic-24-year-old-to-thrive-under-brendan-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant has backed David Turnbull to showcase his worth under new manager Brendan Rodgers, as he acknowledged that the midfielder has been ‘unfortunate’ at Celtic. The 24-year-old is in the final 12 months of his contract at Parkhead and you would imagine if he doesn’t impress Rodgers here then his time at the champions ...
The post "I like the kid" - Peter Grant backs 'unfortunate' Celtic man to thrive under Rodgers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Fanzine TV back for new season]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58106</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-fanzine-tv-back-for-new-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T19:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic Soul Podcast returns on the Celtic Fanzine TV as Celtic embark on a pre-season in Japan. Japan Times journalist Dan Orlowitz https://www.japantimes.co.jp/author/dan-orlowitz/ joins host Andrew Milne to get the view from Japan on Celtic’s upcoming friendlies Yokahama and Gamba Osaka.
The post Celtic Fanzine TV back for new season appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aberdeen's latest transfer update could end fringe player's chance for Celtic exit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167664</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/aberdeens-latest-transfer-update-could-end-liam-scales-chance-for-celtic-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liam Scales has certainly had a mixed time of it since moving to Celtic. A goalscoring debut when he came on as a substitute in Celtic’s 3-0 away win to Dundee United should have been a catalyst for the Irish defender to kick on and build on a good start to his Celtic career. But ...
The post Aberdeen's latest transfer update could end fringe player's chance for Celtic exit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic make move for Brazilian winger to replace Jota]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42730</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/18/celtic-brazilian-winger-replace-jota/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T19:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jota leaving Celtic this summer was a major blow for the Hoops. Yes, they did receive a transfer fee believed to be around £25 million. But at the same time, they lost one of their best players and a nailed on starter. Thus, the club will need make sure that they bring in a replacement […]
Celtic make move for Brazilian winger to replace Jota - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The new Brendan Rodgers Celtic era should feel a lot more real tomorrow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167704</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-new-brendan-rodgers-celtic-era-should-feel-a-lot-more-real-tomorrow/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are back playing to a crowd and television cameras for the first time in over six weeks tomorrow. The Hoops are in Japan for the first of two matches. We face reigning J1 League champions Yokohama F. Marinos at the Nissan Stadium at 11am Scottish time. The vast arena holds 70,000 and has played ...
The post The new Brendan Rodgers Celtic era should feel a lot more real tomorrow appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Excitement builds in Japan as fans take an unusual step to see Celtic in action]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167644</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/excitement-builds-in-japan-as-fans-take-an-unusual-step-to-see-celtic-in-action/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With less than 24 hours to go until Celtic take the field in the first leg of the Japan tour, the excitement is already building as the Japanese public look forward to seeing Celtic take on Yokohama at the Nissan Stadium. Kick-off for the match is at 7pm local time (11am BST) and in order ...
The post Excitement builds in Japan as fans take an unusual step to see Celtic in action appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Furuhashi shares what he's commonly asked about Shunsuke Nakamura at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167689</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kyogo-furuhashi-shares-what-hes-commonly-asked-about-shunsuke-nakamura-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic forward Kyogo Furuhashi has shared what people commonly ask him about Shunsuke Nakamura in Glasgow. The pair were together at Yokohama F. Marinos’ Nissan Stadium on Tuesday. Kyogo and Celtic‘s four other current Japanese stars were joined by Nakamura for a fan and media event run by Adidas. They spoke about a range of ...
The post Kyogo Furuhashi shares what he's commonly asked about Shunsuke Nakamura at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manchester United have signed Celtic-linked defender]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42727</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/18/manchester-united-celtic-linked-defender/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T17:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Brendan Rodgers returned to Celtic for a second stint in the Parkhead hot seat, rumours broke out that the club were ready to back the Northern Irishman in the summer transfer window. Since then, they have completed the signings of Odin Thiago Holm and Marco Tilio, while it is only a matter of time […]
Manchester United have signed Celtic-linked defender - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gangwon president's class comments on Yang Hyun-jun will excite the Celtic fans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167615</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/gangwon-presidents-class-comments-on-yang-hyun-jun-will-excite-the-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With every new signing, comes excitement, hope and expectation. Especially when a player comes to Celtic. Because as fans, we expect only the best players that the club can afford to walk through the Parkhead doors. And we haven’t been left disappointed over the last two seasons. Celtic’s recruitment has been superb and it has ...
The post Gangwon president's class comments on Yang Hyun-jun will excite the Celtic fans appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NO-GO JONNY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109979</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/no-go-jonny/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T16:49:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MISGUIDED reports linking veteran defender Jonny Evans with a reunion with Brendan Rodgers at Celtic have finally been put to bed. The 35-year-old 102 times-capped Northern Ireland internal centre-back will NOT be joining his ex-Leicester City boss at the treble winners. The speculation ended when Evans signed a short-term deal with his former club Manchester [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Celtic appeal shown again as new signing and right-back option appear in Japan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167670</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/global-celtic-appeal-shown-again-as-odin-thiago-holm-and-new-right-back-option-appear-in-japan/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There were a few interesting appearances at Celtic training in Yokohama on Tuesday. Brendan Rodgers‘ side are in Japan, preparing to take on Yokohama F. Marinos and Gamba Osaka over the coming days. The high-profile matches will be important for the team as they continue to step up preparations for the new competitive season. Celtic ...
The post Global Celtic appeal shown again as new signing and right-back option appear in Japan appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The last time Celtic faced Yokohama F Marinos and why it left Shunsuke Nakamura 'ashamed']]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167573</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-last-time-celtic-faced-yokohama-f-marinos-and-why-it-left-shunsuke-nakamura-ashamed/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic prepare to face Yokohama F Marinos in the first leg of the Japan Tour tomorrow, the Celtic fans eagerly await the first glimpse of the team under Brendan Rodgers since the Irishman took over for his second spell at the club. Many fans will be wondering if the style of football we have ...
The post The last time Celtic faced Yokohama F Marinos and why it left Shunsuke Nakamura 'ashamed' appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic give us the Rodgers and Nakamura meeting we didn't know we needed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167616</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-give-us-the-rodgers-and-nakamura-meeting-we-didnt-know-we-needed/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic eras collided in Yokohama on Tuesday as Brendan Rodgers and Shunsuke Nakamura met. The pair were both at the iconic Nissan Stadium. Rodgers was there to lead Celtic first-team training while Nakamura was a special guest at a media and supporter event earlier in the day. When Celtic ventured over to Japan, many supporters ...
The post Celtic give us the Rodgers and Nakamura meeting we didn't know we needed appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic suffer blow in transfer race for €20m-rated Tete]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42724</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/18/celtic-blow-transfer-race-tete/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T15:35:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are rumoured to be looking to make a few marquee signings this summer. And they definitely need to strengthen on the wings, following the exit of Jota in a £25 million move to Al-Ittihad. The Portuguese winger had been a nailed on starter for the Hoops for the past couple of seasons and played […]
Celtic suffer blow in transfer race for €20m-rated Tete - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why incoming Celtic player's long term career ambition is good news for the fans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167630</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/why-kwon-hyeok-kyus-long-term-career-ambition-is-good-news-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have added three permanent names to the first-team squad this summer and there seems to be the promise of more to come. Odin Thiago Holm, Marco Tilio and Tomoki Iwata have already permanently joined the club with the additions of Yang Hyun-jun and Kwon Hyeok-kyu all but confirmed by Celtic. But it was Hyeok-kyu’s ...
The post Why incoming Celtic player's long term career ambition is good news for the fans appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic effect that helped SPFL club attract new summer signing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167623</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-clear-celtic-influence-that-helped-spfl-club-attract-new-summer-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s transfer business has been lauded for the last couple of decades as the club continues to be a platform for players to move onto bigger leagues. There is no shame in admitting that our club is viewed as a stepping stone for players to come and display their talents in the hope that, if ...
The post The Celtic effect that helped SPFL club attract new summer signing appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three current Celtic players that could flourish under Brendan Rodgers - Opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167610</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/three-current-celtic-players-that-could-flourish-under-brendan-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The arrival of a new manager always brings fresh hope that new faces will soon follow him through the door. When Brendan Rodgers joined Celtic, it was reported that the Irishman was guaranteed a significant transfer budget to allow him to continue to not only dominate Scottish football but to also make his mark in ...
The post Three current Celtic players that could flourish under Brendan Rodgers - Opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The special surroundings that Celtic got to sample on Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167589</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-special-surroundings-that-celtic-got-to-sample-on-tuesday/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic first-team got to sample some pretty special surroundings at training on Tuesday. The Hoops are at the start of a week-long visit to Japan. The trip will see the team face top-flight sides Yokohama F. Marinos and Gamba Osaka before they return back to Scotland. As we covered yesterday, some players seemed pretty ...
The post The special surroundings that Celtic got to sample on Tuesday appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arriving hungry to own the place]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109970</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/arriving-hungry-to-own-the-place/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T10:56:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You don’t really want players who pitch up at Celtic Park hoping to do OK, you want them hungry to own the place.  Kwon Hyeok-kyu, who has not yet been paraded in the customary hoops, pinned his colours to the mast saying, “I will become the best player in Celtic and go to higher places [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers speaks in first press conference of Japan Tour; the test ahead for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167588</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-speaks-in-first-press-conference-of-japan-tour-the-test-ahead-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Japan Tour is now finally underway. The Celtic players landed in the country yesterday and can now look forward to preparing for the first match against Yokohama F Marinos tomorrow. The tour holds a lot of intrigue for the country with Celtic having six players from the country at the club with five currently ...
The post Brendan Rodgers speaks in first press conference of Japan Tour; the test ahead for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bemz on being left star-struck at the Celtic POTY awards; how the Jota song changed his career]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167584</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/bemz-on-being-left-star-struck-at-the-celtic-poty-awards-how-the-jota-song-changed-his-career/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘Jota on the Wing’ is a song that was synonymous with Celtic last season. The song, which was dreamt up by the Celtic fans to the tune of O-Zone’s Dragostea din Tei, was covered in a TikTok release by Ellie Dixon which took the Celtic support by storm and launched the musician into almost overnight ...
The post Bemz on being left star-struck at the Celtic POTY awards; how the Jota song changed his career appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans unhappy with the club’s morning announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42711</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/18/celtic-fans-unhappy-morning-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T09:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have enjoyed a lot of success on the pitch over the past couple of seasons, winning five of the last six domestic trophies. And with Brendan Rodgers arriving as the manager of the club this summer, they are expected to continue on that path. Unfortunately, the phrase ‘doing it in style’ might not be […]
Celtic fans unhappy with the club’s morning announcement - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shunsuke Nakamura makes a class appearance at Celtic event in Japan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167571</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/shunsuke-nakamura-makes-a-class-appearance-at-celtic-event-in-japan/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T09:03:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shunsuke Nakamura has met with the five Japanese Celtic players for a special event. Celtic posted the surprise video on their Instagram stories on Tuesday morning. The first video shows Tomoki Iwata, Yuki Kobayashi, Reo Hatate, Kyogo Furuhashi and Daizen Maeda walking on to the pitch at the Nissan Stadium. The quintet are wearing the ...
The post Shunsuke Nakamura makes a class appearance at Celtic event in Japan appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The updated Celtic television picture as new UK channel launches]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167567</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-celtic-and-tnt-sports-situation-as-major-new-television-channel-launches/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic matches will be shown on the TNT Sports channel which launched in the UK on Tuesday. The new channel has replaced the now defunct BT Sport after it merged with Warner Bros Discovery last year. (WBD Sports) TNT Sports is now likely to be on your television, if you previously had access to BT ...
The post The updated Celtic television picture as new UK channel launches appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic star Jota named by Cristiano Ronaldo in defence of Saudi League]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167551</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ex-celtic-star-jota-named-by-cristiano-ronaldo-in-defence-of-saudi-league/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is absolutely no doubt that the plundering of some of Europe’s top talent from the teams in the Saudi League has ruffled a few feathers across Europe. Their ability to, seemingly, easily tempt names like Karim Benzema and N’Golo Kante to strut their stuff in the Middle East has caught all the major teams ...
The post Ex-Celtic star Jota named by Cristiano Ronaldo in defence of Saudi League appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The interesting Glasgow inspiration as another new Celtic kit is launched]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167550</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-interesting-glasgow-inspiration-as-another-new-celtic-kit-is-launched/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have launched yet another new kit this morning. So far this summer we’ve seen a controversial green-and-white hooped home shirt and a slick looking all-black away number unveiled and released to the public. Celtic have even worn the former in a couple of friendly matches. But now they are stepping things up further. On ...
The post The interesting Glasgow inspiration as another new Celtic kit is launched appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers delivers verdict on the current state of the Celtic squad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167547</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-delivers-verdict-on-the-current-state-of-the-celtic-squad/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T06:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has stated that one of the big reasons he returned to Celtic was because of the current state of the squad and the potential it holds – both in terms of individuals and as a collective. Rodgers has been working with the squad up close for the last two weeks and has been ...
The post Brendan Rodgers delivers verdict on the current state of the Celtic squad appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic facing 'step up' this week as Brendan Rodgers pushes players out of comfort zone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167543</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-facing-step-up-this-week-as-brendan-rodgers-pushes-players-out-of-comfort-zone/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T06:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers thinks the matches against Yokohama F.Marinos and Gamba Osaka will be a ‘step up’ in intensity for his Celtic squad as they continue to prepare for the kick-off of the Scottish Premiership. The Bhoys played two training matches against Portuguese top-flight side Portimonense while at their warm weather camp, drawing the first 0-0 ...
The post Celtic facing 'step up' this week as Brendan Rodgers pushes players out of comfort zone appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SALES TALK: ‘YES, THERE IS MONEY THERE,’ ADMITS RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109958</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/sales-talk-yes-there-is-money-there-admits-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T06:06:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS broke the Celtic transfer signing record when he splashed £9million on Odsonne Edouard in the summer of 2018. The French international striker convinced the Irishman to make the deal after his impressive season-long loan from Paris Saint-Germain. Neil Lennon made Christopher Jullien the most expensive defender in Hoops’ history when he brough him [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers addresses Anthony Ralston's Celtic future]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167545</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-addresses-anthony-ralstons-celtic-future/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T05:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has insisted that Anthony Ralston will be a big part of his squad moving forward, having been left impressed with his progress since he was last in charge of the Bhoys. It’s easy to forget that Ralston actually got his first real run in the team during the first Rodgers era, ...
The post Brendan Rodgers addresses Anthony Ralston's Celtic future appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…DU WEI?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109933</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-du-wei/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T05:15:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CHINESE central defender Du Wei suffered the ignominy of being substituted at half-time of his debut – and the Celtic fans never got another glimpse of the loan signing from Shanghai Shenhua. Gordon Strachan brought in the 23-year-old international captain, who won 71 caps for his country, on a temporary transfer and handed him an [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers really impressed with Nicholson and Lawwell; significant Celtic business ahead]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167541</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-really-impressed-with-nicholson-and-lawwell-significant-celtic-business-ahead/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T05:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has reiterated he is really impressed with what he’s seeing behind the scenes from Celtic, as supporters wait on some big signings during the summer transfer window. The Bhoys have already added Odin Thiago Holm and Marco Tilio to the squad, with a South Korean duo on the brink of being announced as ...
The post Brendan Rodgers really impressed with Nicholson and Lawwell; significant Celtic business ahead appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UNSEEN ANGE: IMAGES OF POSTECOGLOU IN PARADISE – THREE DECADES AGO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109952</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/unseen-ange-images-of-postecoglou-in-paradise-three-decades-ago/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T05:04:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU got his hands on the European Cup at Celtic Park – almost THREE DECADES before he took over as team manager. A new biography of the Greek-Australian displays previously unseen images of the ex-boss touring Paradise with a friend in 1993. There is one intriguing snap of Postecoglou and his chum, Steve Blair, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: BIG JOCK v THE DOC: EVAN WILLIAMS REVEALS ALL (Part Four)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=93916</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-big-jock-v-the-doc-evan-williams-reveals-all-part-four/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T05:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EVAN WILLIAMS was a worthy successor to the legendary Ronnie Simpson at Celtic after signing for his boyhood favourites in October 1969. However, the keeper, who celebrated his 80th birthday at the weekend, did not emulate the achievements of the veteran shotsopper with the Scotland international team. Simpson made his debut at the highest level [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEW-LOOK CELTIC – AND MISSING OUT ON LENNY: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Seven)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=93903</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/new-look-celtic-and-missing-out-on-lenny-the-tommy-burns-story-part-seven/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T04:30:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS celebrated his return to Celtic as manager on July 12 1994 by winning the Scottish Cup with the club’s 1-0 win over Airdrie the following year. The league title, though, was the iconic Celt’s main target as he prepared for his second term in charge of the team that was always closest to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[€20 million Tete drops hint amid Celtic transfer rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42688</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/17/tete-drops-hint-celtic-transfer-rumours/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T22:35:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers looks set to have a busy week at Celtic. The pre-season matches in Japan are set to take place and the Hoops have already landed in the Land of the Rising Sun. The club are expected to have a couple of new signings joining soon too, in the form of Yang Hyun-jun and […]
€20 million Tete drops hint amid Celtic transfer rumours - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New signing declares he will become Celtic’s best player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42700</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/17/new-signing-celtic-best-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T21:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There were concerns that Celtic might move away from the transfer policy that brought them so much success under the management of Ange Postecoglou, following the Australian’s departure and the arrival of Brendan Rodgers as his replacement in the Parkhead hot seat. Till now, that has not been the case though. This summer, Celtic have […]
New signing declares he will become Celtic’s best player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans get a glimpse of Champions League options as UEFA get the ball rolling]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167510</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-fans-get-a-glimpse-of-champions-league-options-as-uefa-get-the-ball-rolling/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T20:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Champions League group stage draw is still over six weeks away, but UEFA are clearly keen to get people talking. European football’s governing body have been pretty quiet about the group stage over the summer. But they got the ball rolling on Monday evening by posting the first graphic of the 26 teams who ...
The post Celtic fans get a glimpse of Champions League options as UEFA get the ball rolling appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The amusing side to Daizen Maeda as Yokohama star talks up Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167531</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-amusing-side-to-daizen-maeda-as-yokohama-star-talks-up-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the Celtic side look to settle and make themselves at home in Japan, the Japanese members of the squad will be looking forward to a return to their homeland and meet up with friends and family over the next few days. But Celtic’s Daizen Maeda has already met up with an old friend in ...
The post The amusing side to Daizen Maeda as Yokohama star talks up Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton backs up Premier League boss' Celtic take]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167478</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-backs-up-premier-league-boss-celtic-take/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton has stated on Twitter that West Ham United boss David Moyes is ‘spot on’ to suggest that new Tottenham boss Ange Postecoglou will ‘never get more pressure than he did managing Celtic’. The Treble-winning coach for the Bhoys is now experiencing life as a Premier League manager and taking to the dugout of ...
The post Chris Sutton backs up Premier League boss' Celtic take appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[View from Japan]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58097</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/view-from-japan/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T19:05:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic Soul Podcast returns as Celtic embark on a pre-season in Japan. Japan Times journalist Dan Orlowitz https://www.japantimes.co.jp/author/dan-orlowitz/ joins host Andrew Milne to get the view from Japan on Celtic’s upcoming friendlies Yokahama and Gamba Osaka.
The post View from Japan appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Reo Hatate stands during Celtic huddle comes to light]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42698</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/17/reo-hatate-stands-celtic-huddle/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T19:05:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The huddle is one of the most recognisable things about Celtic. Some might think that it has always been part of the fabric of the club but that is not the case. In fact, it became a tradition during the run of Tony Mowbray as the Hoops’ captain and has continued from there on forward. […]
Why Reo Hatate stands during Celtic huddle comes to light - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mikel Arteta expecting Arsenal exits as Celtic wait on Kieran Tierney situation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167518</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/mikel-artetas-transfer-comments-and-what-it-could-mean-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s apparent interest in Kieran Tierney has been well-documented over the last few weeks. In fact, the chatter about a possible return was fueled by Brendan Rodgers over the weekend as the Celtic manager addressed the rumours that the Arsenal full-back may be open to a Parkhead return. Obviously, the wages that Tierney currently commands ...
The post Mikel Arteta expecting Arsenal exits as Celtic wait on Kieran Tierney situation appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key Celtic stars seem captivated by Japan just hours after arriving]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167504</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/key-celtic-stars-seem-captivated-by-tokyo-just-hours-after-arriving/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic first-team squad arrived in Japan on Monday evening. Led by Brendan Rodgers, the team flew from Scotland to Japan at the start of a week-long tour. On Tuesday they will train at Yokohama F. Marinos’ Nissan Stadium before facing the reigning J1 League champions 24 hours later. The team will then travel around ...
The post Key Celtic stars seem captivated by Japan just hours after arriving appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports man confirms another Celtic summer signing]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42695</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/17/sky-sports-man-celtic-summer-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T17:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Ange Postecoglou left Celtic in order to join Tottenham Hotspur, it was viewed as a massive problem for the club. After all, the Australian had guided them to five trophies in two seasons despite arriving in tough circumstances. The Hoops went out and brought in the best replacement available though, as Brendan Rodgers was […]
Sky Sports man confirms another Celtic summer signing - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So Farewell Then……]]></title>
        <id>http://celticunderground.net/?p=6622</id>
        <link href="http://celticunderground.net/so-farewell-then/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T17:07:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you had said to me two months ago that Ange Postecoglu would be at Spurs and Brendan Rodgers would be manager again at Celtic, I (and every other Celtic fan that I know) would have said, “Aye, Very Good!!” Firstly, I assumed that even with the appointment of fellow Australian, Scott Nunn, Spurs would […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Critical Bill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£850,000 KWON’S ‘DREAM COME TRUE’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109947</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/850000-kwons-dream-come-true/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T16:42:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOUTH KOREAN Kwon Hyeok-kyu will cost £850,000 as he prepares for his switch to Celtic. The 22-year-old midfielder is poised to team up with countryman Yang Hyun-jun as soon as his transfer is rubber-stamped, probably later this week. Kwon and Yang will join their nation’s international striker Oh Hyeon-gyu at the treble winners as they prepare [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The reason why Celtic CEO Michael Nicholson stepped down from the SPFL board]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167498</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-reason-why-celtic-ceo-michael-nicholson-stepped-down-from-the-spfl-board/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Nicholson has stepped down from the board of the SPFL and been replaced by Rangers CEO James Bisgrove. The announcement was made this afternoon as the 42 member clubs of the SPFL elected a new board for the coming season ahead. [SPFL] What must be made clear is that there is no conspiracy regarding ...
The post The reason why Celtic CEO Michael Nicholson stepped down from the SPFL board appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic influence clear as SPFL announce new TV deals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167483</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-influence-clear-as-spfl-announce-new-tv-deals/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SPFL announced a new television deal that will continue its partnership with the BBC and international TV rights agency, Infront. [SPFL] Under the new agreement, BBC Scotland will see its current contract, which was due to expire in 2025, increased to 2029 which means it comes into line with the SPFL’s contract with Sky ...
The post Celtic influence clear as SPFL announce new TV deals appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The reason why Reo Hatate stands in the Celtic huddle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167456</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-reason-why-reo-hatate-stands-in-the-celtic-huddle/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate has answered a lot of questions since arriving at Celtic 18 months ago. The Japan international has been a revelation since his move from Kawasaki Frontale. He’s netted vital derby goals, produced moments of magic against Europe’s best and dazzled us with his close control and passing. But one less important matter has ...
The post The reason why Reo Hatate stands in the Celtic huddle appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic have a Japan plan for latest summer signings as amusing situation arises]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167476</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-have-a-japan-plan-for-latest-summer-signings-as-amusing-situation-arises/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are still to officially announce the signings of Hyun-jun Yang and Kwon Hyeok-kyu. Deals for the South Korean pair are done, with both of their current clubs confirming that the players would soon be off to Scotland. Both players have been in the Korean media too, speaking about their moves to the champions. That ...
The post Report: Celtic have a Japan plan for latest summer signings as amusing situation arises appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The fringe players continuing the pre-season journey with Celtic in Japan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167475</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-fringe-players-continuing-the-pre-season-journey-with-celtic-in-japan/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Japan Tour is one that is not only being met with excitement by the Japanese public but also the Celtic fans. Over the course of the next week, we will get the opportunity to see what will be a new-look Celtic under the tutelage of Brendan Rodgers. With new players like Odin Thago Holm ...
The post The fringe players continuing the pre-season journey with Celtic in Japan appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anti Celtic tactic suffers a blow as the SPFL approve pleasing new guidance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167468</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/anti-celtic-tactic-suffers-a-blow-as-the-spfl-approve-pleasing-new-guidance/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T13:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In some pleasing news for Celtic, the SPFL have approved a recommendation making the multi-ball system compulsory next season. The guidance will apply to Premiership clubs and was announced by the SPFL on Monday afternoon. Hidden away at the bottom of their statement it was revealed that clubs had voted “unanimously” to approve: “a recommendation ...
The post Anti Celtic tactic suffers a blow as the SPFL approve pleasing new guidance appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midfielder confirms he is set to join Celtic this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42691</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/17/midfielder-confirms-join-celtic-summer/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T13:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Things appear to be picking up pace for Celtic in the summer transfer window. The club got deals done for Odin Thiago Holm and Marco Tilio early. And after a slow few days, now it looks like they are closing in on a double announcement. It is believed that they have gotten a deal over […]
Midfielder confirms he is set to join Celtic this summer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bullet train and big stadium opportunities; Celtic announce finer Japan details]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167462</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/bullet-train-and-big-stadium-opportunities-celtic-announce-finer-japan-details/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T12:40:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have announced some of the finer details for the first-team’s week-long visit to Japan. The Hoops touched down in Tokyo on Monday, with a familiar green-and-white sight greeting them at Narita International Airport. Yokohama, the base for our first few days, is around an hours drive from the airport. As Celtic say in an ...
The post Bullet train and big stadium opportunities; Celtic announce finer Japan details appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 'amazing' ex-Celtic player that inspired Kwon Hyeok-kyu's football career]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167453</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-amazing-ex-celtic-player-that-inspired-kwon-hyeok-kyus-football-career/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic look set to confirm the capture of Korean midfielder, Kwon Hyeok-kyu, any day now. With reports claiming that a deal is done between Busan and Celtic, all we are waiting for, for now, is the official confirmation from the club. When the transfer speculation surrounding the 22-year-old defensive midfielder broke last week, the Celtic ...
The post The 'amazing' ex-Celtic player that inspired Kwon Hyeok-kyu's football career appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's Champions League reward will be felt strongly on Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167434</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-champions-league-reward-will-be-felt-strongly-on-wednesday/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few years ago, the thought of Celtic being able to saunter off to Japan in mid-July would have been about as unlikely as Brendan Rodgers returning as manager. This week, however, Rodgers will take his Celtic charges to Asia to play a couple of high-profile friendly matches. With Champions League group stage football already ...
The post Celtic's Champions League reward will be felt strongly on Wednesday appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic defender trials with SPFL side in search for a new club]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167441</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/efe-ambrose-trials-with-spfl-side-as-former-celtic-defender-searches-for-new-club/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What can you say about former Celtic defender, Efe Ambrose? A transfer deadline day capture by Neil Lennon in 2012, the Nigerian international enjoyed a trophy-laden five years at the club. The 34-year-old made 169 appearances for Celtic picking up four league titles, a Scottish Cup and a League Cup. He also won the African ...
The post Former Celtic defender trials with SPFL side in search for a new club appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demographics, Asia and Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109935</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/demographics-asia-and-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T11:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ask any group why Scotland produces so few great players now, compared to where we were as recently as the 1980s and you will get a familiar list of reasons.  Clubs no longer promote youth prospects at the same rate, facilities here have been overtaken by those in similar small countries and have been left [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic touch down in Japan and there's a familiar green-and-white sight]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167439</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-touch-down-in-japan-and-theres-a-familiar-green-and-white-sight/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T10:47:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have touched down in Japan ahead of an important week in our pre-season preparations. The first-team squad landed at Narita International Airport on Monday evening, Japanese time. The players will have flown around ten hours to Tokyo, and face a couple of high-profile friendly matches over the coming week. On Wednesday they face the ...
The post Celtic touch down in Japan and there's a familiar green-and-white sight appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nakamura question, Ibrox link, Brazilians; What to expect from Yokohama F. Marinos vs Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167419</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/nakamura-question-ibrox-link-brazilians-what-to-expect-from-yokohama-f-marinos-vs-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will play their first proper pre-season friendly on Wednesday against Yokohama F. Marinos. So far, the Hoops have faced Portuguese outfit Portimonense on two occasions with the latter clash receiving only moderate coverage from the club. But things will step up a gear this week as Brendan Rodgers‘ team face their first fixtures in ...
The post Nakamura question, Ibrox link, Brazilians; What to expect from Yokohama F. Marinos vs Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic at the Women's World Cup; FIFA tip two players to shine, fixture list, TV details]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167418</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-at-the-womens-world-cup-fifa-on-shen-mengyu-fixture-list-tv-details/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the Celtic first team’s pre-season training camp in Portugal and the upcoming Japan Tour grabbing all the headlines this week, it is easy to forget that there is other news surrounding the club coming up. Like the FIFA Women’s World Cup for example. The tournament is being jointly held in Australia and New Zealand ...
The post Celtic at the Women's World Cup; FIFA tip two players to shine, fixture list, TV details appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers makes Kieran Tierney to Celtic claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42685</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/17/brendan-rodgers-kieran-tierney-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T09:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rumours have suggested that Celtic could make one or more marquee signings this summer. That has led to them being linked with several big names in recent times. One that certainly falls under that category is that of Kieran Tierney. The left-back came through the ranks at Parkhead before making the move to Arsenal back […]
Brendan Rodgers makes Kieran Tierney to Celtic claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Early kick-offs, immense stadia, Celtic homecomings, TV; Japan details you need to know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167400</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/early-kick-offs-immense-stadia-celtic-homecomings-tv-japan-details-you-need-to-know/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will continue their preparations for the new season this week in Japan. Yes, it may have crept up on some of you, but the team are venturing over to Asia for some more training and a couple of relatively high-profile matches. Straight Champions League qualification has afforded the club the luxury of an Asian ...
The post Early kick-offs, immense stadia, Celtic homecomings, TV; Japan details you need to know appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EPL manager brilliantly talks up Celtic in pre-season press conference]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167401</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/david-moyes-brilliantly-talks-up-celtic-during-west-hams-promotional-press-conference/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans know exactly just how big our club is. There are Celtic supporters clubs all over the globe and when the club are on their travels in Europe, there is always a strong contingent of fans that will follow them wherever they go. But this is not new news to us. The scenes when ...
The post EPL manager brilliantly talks up Celtic in pre-season press conference appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TIERNEY: ‘WHO KNOWS WHAT MIGHT HAPPEN?’ ADMITS CELTIC BOSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109921</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/tierney-who-knows-what-might-happen-admits-celtic-boss/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T07:32:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has refused to close the door on a dramatic return to Celtic for Kieran Tierney. The former fans’ favourite has been linked with a Parkhead reunion alongside the returning manager after leaving for Arsenal in a £25million deal in the summer of 2018. However, the Scotland international left-back is on his way out [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS CLEAR-OUT ON WAY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109917</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-clear-out-on-way/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T06:46:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is ready to kick-start his Celtic clear-out as the new season looms into view. The Hoops boss has already spoken to some of the fringe players who will be heading for the Parkhead exit over the next six weeks. Rodgers is determined to streamline the numbers and has revealed he has already begun [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston is loving Celtic Wimbledon final moment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167394</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alistair-johnston-is-loving-celtic-wimbledon-final-moment/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T06:44:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re a lover of sport, and not just Celtic, then like me you were probably glued to Sunday’s engrossing five-set epic Wimbledon final between Novak Djokovic and champion Carlos Alcaraz. It was a magical afternoon and, like many major events around the world, a proud Celtic fan managed to find his way into the ...
The post Alistair Johnston is loving Celtic Wimbledon final moment appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers talks up Celtic's Champions League bonus]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167392</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-talks-up-celtics-champions-league-bonus/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T06:12:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers sounds like a man positively delighted he doesn’t have to face any UEFA Champions League qualifiers this summer, in stark contrast to his first spell at the club. Rodgers had to navigate the perilous summer European gauntlet in each of his seasons as Celtic boss and was successful on two occasions. ...
The post Brendan Rodgers talks up Celtic's Champions League bonus appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers ready to make Celtic cuts; honest discussions being held]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167386</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-ready-to-make-celtic-cuts-honest-discussions-being-held/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T05:41:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers is ready to trim some of the fat off the wider Celtic squad this summer after a period of assessment during pre-season training. As we discussed yesterday, there are multiple contenders to be moved on from the Bhoys before the end of the window before even big tough decisions have to be made. ...
The post Brendan Rodgers ready to make Celtic cuts; honest discussions being held appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…OLIVIER KAPO?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109912</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-olivier-kapo/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T05:15:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OLIVIER KAPO had enjoyed a colourful career – including a period with Italian giants Juventus – by the time he turned up at Celtic. The attacking midfielder spent a mere three months at Parkhead after arriving on a short-term contract following his release by Wigan in early November 2010. The Ivory Coast-born French international, at [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers left impressed by Celtic duo in Portugal as he discusses box office rumour]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167384</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-left-impressed-by-celtic-duo-in-portugal-as-he-discusses-box-office-rumour/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T05:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has admitted that the financials involved in a move for Kieran Tierney are difficult for Celtic, but hasn’t ruled out his return to the Bhoys. It was reported earlier this month that Tierney was open to a move back to Celtic given his difficulties remaining as a first-choice pick under Mikel Arteta at ...
The post Brendan Rodgers left impressed by Celtic duo in Portugal as he discusses box office rumour appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: FACING THE IBROX FOES: EVAN WILLIAMS REVEALS ALL (Part Three)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=93809</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-facing-the-ibrox-foes-evan-williams-reveals-all-part-three/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T05:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EVAN WILLIAMS, who celebrated his 80th birthday on Saturday, may have had his run-ins with Jock Stein, but Celtic’s legendary manager never hesitated in giving the keeper the nod to play in Old Firm encounters. The games against the club’s fiercest foes brought out the best in the netminder who recalled: “I played against Rangers [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘UNBELIEVABLE’ CUP TRIUMPH: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Six)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=93805</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/unbelievable-cup-triumph-the-tommy-burns-story-part-six/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T04:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS was just 90 minutes away from his first silverware in his debut season as Celtic manager after returning to the club on July 12 1994. The League Cup had been lost in a sensational penalty-kick shoot-out to Raith Rovers in November, the league was blown, but the Scottish Cup was tantalisingly close. In [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midfielder has confirmed Celtic interest in signing him]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42660</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/16/midfielder-confirmed-celtic-interest-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T22:35:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With official news from Celtic still to come to confirm the signing of South Korean winger, Yang Hyun-jun, from Gangwon FC, there is another player expected to join the club very soon. And it is very possible that the club might be aiming for a double announcement. Let’s see how things play out over the […]
Midfielder has confirmed Celtic interest in signing him - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports man links £16 million winger with Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42678</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/16/sky-sports-man-16-million-winger-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T21:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will need to strengthen their ranks this summer. The club have continued to add to their squad, having already brought in Odin Thiago Holm and Marco Tilio. On the other hand, moves for Yang Hyun-jun and Kwon Hyeok-kyu are believed to be close as well. These are positive moves from the Hoops, but at […]
Sky Sports man links £16 million winger with Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Dalglish reckons "every manager dreams" of what Celtic star offers; lauds club action]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167366</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kenny-dalglish-lauds-celtic-contract-move/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T20:41:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend Kenny Dalglish has lauded the club’s move to tie down captain Callum McGregor for five more years in the Hoops. McGregor’s new deal was announced last Monday and has been warmly received by the vast majority of the Celtic support. We’re keeping a player in his prime and utilising the years of experience ...
The post Kenny Dalglish reckons "every manager dreams" of what Celtic star offers; lauds club action appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Hyoengyu Oh told incoming Yang Hyun-jun about life at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167376</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-hyoengyu-oh-told-incoming-yang-hyun-jun-about-life-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Barring the official announcement from Celtic, I think we can all agree that South Korean winger, Yang Hyun-jun will be a Celtic player over the coming days. Gangwon CEO, Kim Byung-ji confirmed yesterday that Celtic will be paying €2.5m for the 21-year-old and today, Hyun-Jun made his final appearance for the club and said his ...
The post What Hyoengyu Oh told incoming Yang Hyun-jun about life at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jonny Evans to Celtic transfer update amid rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42674</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/16/jonny-evans-celtic-transfer-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T19:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with plenty of players this summer who played under the management of Brendan Rodgers at Leicester City over the past several years. Some such names are Wilfred Ndidi, Tete and Daniel Amartey. And now, the latest name to be added to that quickly growing list is that of Jonny Evans. The […]
Jonny Evans to Celtic transfer update amid rumours - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers praises Rocco Vata; issues challenge to young Celtic winger]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167370</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-praises-rocco-vata-issues-challenge-to-young-celtic-winger/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T19:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has praised young Celtic attacking midfielder, Rocco Vata, and issued a challenge to the winger if he has designs of trying to make it into the Hoops first team. Vata was taken to the Portugal training camp and has clearly impressed the Celtic boss. But although Vata has developed well since the last ...
The post Brendan Rodgers praises Rocco Vata; issues challenge to young Celtic winger appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Premier League Celtic transfer links quashed by new report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167374</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/jonny-evans-and-scott-mctominay-transfer-links-to-celtic-quashed-by-new-report/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T18:47:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic won’t be making a move for Jonny Evans or Scott McTominay this summer, it has been reported this evening. The Liverpool Echo stated this weekend that Brendan Rodgers was keen on reuniting with free agent Evans, who played under the new Celtic boss at Leicester City. Manchester United midfielder McTominay, meanwhile, has been a ...
The post Two Premier League Celtic transfer links quashed by new report appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manchester United hero admits to being a Celtic fan]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42671</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/16/manchester-united-hero-celtic-fan/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T18:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are one of the biggest clubs in world football. People often fail to recognise the sheer size of the fan base simply because of the fact that they play in the Scottish Premiership, which admittedly is not one of the best leagues in Europe and neither does it have the popularity of a Premier […]
Manchester United hero admits to being a Celtic fan - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 6 main contenders to be axed from Celtic's growing squad this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167362</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-6-main-contenders-to-be-axed-from-celtics-growing-squad-this-summer/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T17:10:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While plenty of Celtic fans are clamouring for fresh blood and new signings, it’s worth noting the club still have plenty to do to move on the players who just haven’t cut it over the last couple of years. The Bhoys are on the brink of announcing their third and fourth signings of the summer, ...
The post The 6 main contenders to be axed from Celtic's growing squad this summer appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic gearing up for more transfer reveals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167359</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-gearing-up-for-more-transfer-announcements/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T16:30:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems clear by now that the moves for South Korean duo Yang Hyun-jun and Kwon Hyeok-kyu are complete and that the only thing we are now awaiting is a double announcement from Celtic. Gangwon FC gave the game away with regards to Yang yesterday, with their club chief confirming the move and even the ...
The post Celtic gearing up for more transfer reveals appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant highlights three 'vital' areas Celtic will strengthen this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167353</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/peter-grant-highlights-three-vital-areas-celtic-will-strengthen-this-summer/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already made some additions to the first-team squad this summer. Odin Thiago Holm, Marco Tilio and the permanent signing of Tomoki Iwata have helped to add more depth to the squad. But the recent injuries this week to Tilio, Alistair Johnston and Mikey Johnston have convinced former Celtic player, Peter Grant, that the ...
The post Peter Grant highlights three 'vital' areas Celtic will strengthen this summer appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Miller's bizarre assessment of Celtic's treble winning season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167356</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kenny-millers-bizarre-assessment-of-celtics-treble-winning-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s record-breaking treble-winning season was quite remarkable. Up until the title was signed, sealed and delivered with a 2-0 win over Hearts at Tynecastle on the 7th of May, Celtic had only dropped five points all season. Our superior goal difference was effectively like having another point advantage but at no point did the title ...
The post Kenny Miller's bizarre assessment of Celtic's treble winning season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic close to making another signing after Yang Hyun-jun]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42667</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/16/celtic-close-signing-yang-hyun-jun/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T14:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have not made the signing of Yang Hyun-jun official yet although Gangwon FC have released a statement on their Instagram already. Thus, it is only a matter of time and it seems like the Hoops are waiting for the right opportunity to break the news to the fans. In fact, the possibility of a […]
Celtic close to making another signing after Yang Hyun-jun - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic favourite on his next career move; why Parkhead return never materialised]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167350</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/aiden-mcgeady-on-his-next-career-move-why-celtic-return-never-materialised/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aiden McGeady was, without a doubt, one of the most naturally gifted wingers Celtic had seen in the first team for a long time. Beginning his career at Queens Park, McGeady tried to follow a career path in England. And after a trial at Arsenal failed to produce a move, the Glasgow-born winger signed for ...
The post Former Celtic favourite on his next career move; why Parkhead return never materialised appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['The way he plays': Peter Grant thinks PL star open to securing transfer to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167305</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/it-wouldnt-surprise-me-peter-grant-makes-exciting-kieran-tierney-and-celtic-transfer-claim/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant says he ‘wouldn’t be surprised’ if Kieran Tierney wants to make a return to Celtic this summer as questions remain over his future at Arsenal. The Scotland international has had his fair share of injury issues during the past 18 months and it hasn’t helped that Oleksandr Zinchenko has also pushed ahead of ...
The post 'The way he plays': Peter Grant thinks PL star open to securing transfer to Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dutch defender speaks on his future as previous Celtic links seem to have cooled]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167345</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/xavier-mbuyamba-speaks-on-his-future-as-previous-celtic-links-seem-to-have-cooled/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with a number of players over the past few months. Even prior to Brendan Rodgers taking over at the club, the summer transfer window did promise to be a big one as Celtic looked to improve their fortunes in Europe. But Xavier Mbuyamba, who was previously linked to the club has ...
The post Dutch defender speaks on his future as previous Celtic links seem to have cooled appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reported Celtic target seals move to join Fenerbache]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167341</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/reported-celtic-target-dominik-livakovic-seals-move-to-join-fenerbache/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After all the excitement over the transfer rumour that Celtic held an interest in Croatian international goalkeeper Dominik Livaković, it seems now that can be put to bed after the 28-year-old is set to join Turkish club, Fenerbache. 67 Hail Hail discussed yesterday that Livaković had agreed personal terms with the Turks but a deal ...
The post Reported Celtic target seals move to join Fenerbache appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Joe Hart told Conor Hazard after sealing Celtic exit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167322</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-joe-hart-told-conor-hazard-after-sealing-celtic-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conor Hazard’s move from Celtic to Plymouth Argyle this week was one that the former Hoops keeper needed at this stage of his career. At 24 years old, Hazard had just returned from a successful loan spell at HJK Helsinki where he enjoyed a lengthy run in the Finnish club’s first team. After nine years ...
The post What Joe Hart told Conor Hazard after sealing Celtic exit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£7.7m LIVAKOVIC: NO DEAL, SAY HOOPS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109905</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/7-7m-livakovic-no-deal-say-hoops/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T09:22:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS will not be pursuing initial interest in Croatia World Cup keeper Dominik Livakovic. The Celtic manager had been linked with the Dinamo Zagreb No.1 who is coming out of contract next summer as has been linked with several clubs in recent weeks. Rodgers, though, will not take the consideration any further with reports claiming [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano confirms €9 million Celtic transfer fail]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42657</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/16/fabrizio-romano-celtic-transfer-fail/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T09:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were handed a major transfer blow this summer when Jota left the club in order to join Al-Ittihad in a £25 million deal. While the Hoops received a big fee, they also ended up losing arguably their most creative player in the team. The hope was that they would reinvest that figure and bring […]
Fabrizio Romano confirms €9 million Celtic transfer fail - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“I’m a fan and always have been” – Ex-Manchester United hero makes Celtic admission]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167301</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/im-a-fan-and-always-have-been-ex-manchester-united-hero-makes-celtic-admission/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[European nights at Celtic Park always have that ability to capture the imagination of some of the world’s best players. Players like Lionel Messi, Xavi and Paolo Maldini have all waxed lyrical about the atmosphere in Paradise and, here, we have another legend of the game speaking about his experience playing in one of those ...
The post “I’m a fan and always have been” – Ex-Manchester United hero makes Celtic admission appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Republic of Ireland legend explains why Mikey Johnston will get a chance at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167296</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-republic-of-ireland-legend-explains-why-mikey-johnston-will-get-a-chance-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mikey Johnston has been one of those Celtic players that have risen through the academy and shown a lot of promise. He broke into the first team under Brendan Rodgers back in 2017 when he made his debut in a 4-1 win over St Johnstone. And on that very same afternoon it was announced that ...
The post Former Republic of Ireland legend explains why Mikey Johnston will get a chance at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: WHAT NOW FOR CELTIC’S MISSING LINK?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109896</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-what-now-for-celtics-missing-link/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T07:38:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I CONFESS I have followed James McCarthy’s career with a fair degree of diligence for one very good reason – his dad was one of my best pals as we both grew up in Castlemilk. My schooldays were not quite around the time fire was invented, but I admit it was a long time ago. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nir Bitton backs former Celtic teammate to make history]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167293</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/nir-bitton-backs-former-celtic-teammate-to-make-history/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T06:11:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nir Bitton reckons Callum McGregor can become the club’s most decorated player in history after signing his new contract with Celtic. McGregor has already won an incredible 20 major honours during his time at the Bhoys. In terms of volume, he remains just five trophies behind the all-time leader Bobby Lennox, who admittedly won the ...
The post Nir Bitton backs former Celtic teammate to make history appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic target speaks out; excited by Bhoys transfer link]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167291</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-target-speaks-out-excited-by-bhoys-transfer-link/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T05:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer target Kwon Hyeok-kyu has confirmed he knows all about the Bhoys’ interest in his services and that he is excited about the potential opportunity to move to Scotland. Kwon is widely reported to be the subject of a £1m offer from Celtic, who have contacted his club Busan about signing him up during ...
The post Celtic target speaks out; excited by Bhoys transfer link appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…RAMI GERSHON?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109894</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-rami-gershon/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T05:17:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RAMI GERSHON’S scoring ratio for a full-back at Celtic was even more prolific than that of Lisbon Lion Tommy Gemmell, the swashbuckling hero of Jock Stein’s all-conquering team. The 25-year-old Israeli left-sided defender fired in a goal every three games. Unfortunately, Gershon only made three first-team appearances for the Hoops after joining on loan from Standard [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[English side hoping for Celtic windfall bonus but Bhoys hold all the cards]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167287</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/english-side-hoping-for-celtic-windfall-bonus-but-bhoys-hold-all-the-cards/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T05:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MK Dons boss Graham Alexander has admitted he is hoping another club comes in for Celtic midfielder Matt O’Riley this summer, so he can get a cut to spend on improving his own squad. Like most transfer deals these days, MK inserted a clause in the O’Riley sale to pocket a percentage of the profit ...
The post English side hoping for Celtic windfall bonus but Bhoys hold all the cards appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: ‘BIG JOCK AND ME’: EVAN WILLIAMS REVEALS ALL (Part Two)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=93735</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-big-jock-and-me-evan-williams-reveals-all-part-two/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T05:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EVAN WILLIAMS, who celebrated his 80th birthday yesterday, was a goalkeeper decades ahead of his time. The popular former netminder, who joined the Hoops from Wolves in October 1969 as the club searched for a long-term replacement for veteran Ronnie Simpson, used to have Jock Stein waving wildly on the touchline to get back into [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘WE HAVE LEARNED FROM THE EXPERIENCE’: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Five)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=93708</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/we-have-learned-from-the-experience-the-tommy-burns-story-part-five/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T04:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS was determined to win silverware in his first season as Celtic manager after returning to the club on July 12 1994. The chance to achieve his goal after only four months was obliterated in a dramatic penalty-kick shoot-out to First Division Raith Rovers in the League Cup Final at Ibrox. With the league [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers and Celtic fans handed even more good news]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42637</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/15/brendan-rodgers-celtic-fans-news/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T22:30:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It looks like fans should be expecting an official Celtic announcement soon about the signing of South Korean youth international, Yang Hyun-jun, from K-League side Gangwon FC. There was some more good news on Saturday morning for Brendan Rodgers’ side as well, as they continue their preparations for the 2023/24 campaign. Gangwon FC released a […]
Brendan Rodgers and Celtic fans handed even more good news - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports man makes superb Celtic transfer claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42652</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/15/sky-sports-man-celtic-transfer-claim/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T20:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou’s run at Celtic might have only lasted a couple of seasons, but nobody can deny the impact that he made during that period of time. A lot of things changed at Parkhead and for the better. One of the biggest changes was felt on their transfer strategy, as they spread their network further […]
Sky Sports man makes superb Celtic transfer claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic urged to bring box office factor to summer transfer window]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167285</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-urged-to-bring-wow-factor-to-summer-transfer-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T20:22:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton wants Celtic to step up their summer transfer window business, feeling they’ve done little to strengthen last season’s treble-winning squad. The Bhoys have completed the signings of Odin Thiago Holm, Marco Tilio and Yang Hyun-jun, but crucially have sold one of the squad’s best, most popular players in Jota. Sutton understands that patience ...
The post Celtic urged to bring box office factor to summer transfer window appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic want Premier League title winner; echo of first Rodgers spell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167279</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-are-interested-in-signing-premier-league-free-agent-echo-of-first-brendan-rodgers-spell/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T19:04:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with a move for Premier League free agent Jonny Evans, who left Leicester City at the end of his contract last month. The Liverpool Echo reports that new manager Brendan Rodgers is ‘keen’ on signing the player, who he worked with at the Foxes and even made his club captain. The ...
The post Report: Celtic want Premier League title winner; echo of first Rodgers spell appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer talks over deal to sign midfielder confirmed]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42648</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/15/celtic-talks-deal-sign-midfielder/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T19:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Ange Postecoglou decided to leave Celtic after the end of the previous season, many fans feared that it would lead to a change in the transfer policy which had brought the club so much success over the past couple of campaigns. Brendan Rodgers has ended up replacing the Australian in the Parkhead hot seat […]
Celtic transfer talks over deal to sign midfielder confirmed - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic linked with former Manchester United player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42644</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/15/celtic-former-manchester-united-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T17:30:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already brought in a couple of players this summer in the form of Marco Tilio and Odin Thiago Holm. On the other hand, a move for Yang Hyun-jun also appears to be on the verge of completion. All of them are decent additions to the side and have the potential to be great […]
Celtic linked with former Manchester United player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Youngsters shine, Daizen press; Celtic goal highlights from 4-1 win over Portuguese side]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167273</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/youngsters-shine-daizen-press-celtic-goal-highlights-from-4-1-win-over-portuguese-side/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T15:40:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have delighted fans with a look at today’s 4-1 win over Portuguese top-flight side Portimonense. The Bhoys played the same team on Wednesday night but nothing was seen or heard about that 0-0 draw outside of unofficial updates from fans on the ground in Portugal. Reo Hatate, Liel Abada, Ben Summers and Hyeongyu Oh ...
The post Youngsters shine, Daizen press; Celtic goal highlights from 4-1 win over Portuguese side appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean club chief confirms Celtic transfer fee; incoming recruit says his goodbyes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167270</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/south-korean-club-chief-confirms-celtic-transfer-fee-incoming-recruit-says-his-goodbyes/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T15:18:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have paid a fee of €2.5m [£2.15m] for Yang Hyun-jun, Gangwon FC club chief Kim Byung-ji has confirmed today. The South Korean side surprised everyone with their own announcement that Yang will be heading to the Bhoys this summer, with no Celtic comment yet made on the situation. Now, more details about the transfer ...
The post South Korean club chief confirms Celtic transfer fee; incoming recruit says his goodbyes appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS ‘REALLY PLEASED’ AS CELTIC TRIUMPH – AND THEN SEAL KOREAN DEAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109868</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-really-pleased-as-celtic-triumph-and-then-seal-korean-deal/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T14:19:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS declared himself “really pleased” after Celtic eased to a 4-1 win over Portimonense SC today as they completed a positive week in Portugal. The returning Hoops boss beamed as he watched Reo Hatate net the opening goal from the penalty spot with Liel Abada, Ben Summers and Oh Hyeon-gyu also getting on the scoresheet [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers reacts as Oh and co fire 'intense' Celtic to pre-season win]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167264</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-reacts-as-oh-and-co-fire-intense-celtic-to-pre-season-win/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T12:11:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers was delighted with the work of his side in this morning’s pre-season friendly against Portimonense in Portugal. The Bhoys took on the top-flight side for the second time in three days behind closed doors at The Campus training centre. Celtic came out on top by a 4-1 margin thanks to goals ...
The post Brendan Rodgers reacts as Oh and co fire 'intense' Celtic to pre-season win appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano confirms Dominik Livakovic blow for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42632</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/15/fabrizio-romano-dominik-livakovic-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T12:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans were delighted when the club were recently linked with a move for Croatian international number one, Dominik Livakovic. The goalkeeper was arguably his national team’s best performer at the World Cup last year, as they finished third in the competition, exceeded all expectations. Celtic can certainly do with a goalkeeper like Livakovic. They […]
Fabrizio Romano confirms Dominik Livakovic blow for Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four different scorers as Celtic punish Portimonense in Saturday morning pre-season match]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167262</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/four-different-scorers-as-celtic-punish-portimonense-in-saturday-morning-pre-season-match/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T10:50:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic clicked into gear against Portuguese top-flight side Portimonense this morning, winning 4-1 in a behind-closed-doors match at The Campus training centre. The Bhoys played the same side on Wednesday with a weakened group, made up of players who completed a first week of training at Lennoxtown prior to the trip to Portugal. That one ...
The post Four different scorers as Celtic punish Portimonense in Saturday morning pre-season match appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano offers disappointing Dominik Livakovic update amidst Celtic interest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167260</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/fabrizio-romano-offers-disappointing-dominik-livakovic-update-amidst-celtic-interest/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T10:24:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Renowned transfer journalist Fabrizio Romano has reported that Dominik Livakovic has agreed personal terms with Fenerbahce, as the Turkish club look to finalise a deal with Dinamo Zagreb. There was excitement amongst some Bhoys fans on Friday night when Sky Sports reported that Celtic were closely monitoring the Croatian international star, with the goalkeeping position ...
The post Fabrizio Romano offers disappointing Dominik Livakovic update amidst Celtic interest appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic next signing official in early morning announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42629</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/15/celtic-next-signing-official-early-morning-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T10:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have continued to strengthen their squad this summer. The club have already brought in two very highly rated young talents in the form of Odin Thiago Holm and Marco Tilio. And now, the Hoops look set to make a third signing in this window as well, after being linked with him for several weeks […]
Celtic next signing official in early morning announcement - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gangwon FC confirm Yang Hyun-jun is moving to Celtic in official statement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167255</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/gangwon-fc-confirm-yang-hyun-jun-is-moving-to-celtic-in-official-statement/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T09:57:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean side Gangwon FC have confirmed on Instagram that attacker Yang Hyun-jun will become a Celtic player this summer. The club say he will make a farewell statement to fans after their match at home to FC Seoul today. The statement read: “[OFFICIAL] Yang Hyun-jun to Celtic’s transfer has been confirmed. There is a ...
The post Gangwon FC confirm Yang Hyun-jun is moving to Celtic in official statement appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX ANGLE: ANGE’S LONELY WALK, BUCKET LIST AND THE LOST CHALLENGE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109864</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alex-angle-anges-lonely-walk-bucket-list-and-the-lost-challenge/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T09:49:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A FORTNIGHT before he departed Celtic for Spurs, Ange Postecoglou walked to the centre circle at Parkhead and waved to the Celtic supporters. It was a lonely manoeuvre in the immediate aftermath of the drab 2-2 draw with St Mirren where the champions had played in slow motion without a spark of ingenuity. It was [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: ANGE’S LONELY WALK, BUCKET LIST AND THE LOST CHALLENGE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109864</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-anges-lonely-walk-bucket-list-and-the-lost-challenge/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T09:49:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A FORTNIGHT before he departed Celtic for Spurs, Ange Postecoglou walked to the centre circle at Parkhead and waved to the Celtic supporters. It was a lonely manoeuvre in the immediate aftermath of the drab 2-2 draw with St Mirren where the champions had played in slow motion without a spark of ingenuity. It was [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: THE LONELY WALK, ANGE’S BUCKET LIST AND THE LOST CHALLENGE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109864</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-the-lonely-walk-anges-bucket-list-and-the-lost-challenge/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T09:49:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A FORTNIGHT before he departed Celtic for Spurs, Ange Postecoglou walked to the centre circle at Parkhead and waved to the Celtic supporters. It was a lonely manoeuvre in the immediate aftermath of the drab 2-2 draw with St Mirren where the champions had played in slow motion without a spark of ingenuity. It was [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The first Celtic goals of the new Brendan Rodgers era have been scored]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167251</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtics-first-goal-of-the-new-brendan-rodgers-era-has-been-scored/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T09:36:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s one for budding quiz enthusiasts. Who scored the very first goal of Brendan Rodgers’ second era at Celtic? The answer is Reo Hatate, in a Saturday morning match against Portuguese top-flight side Portimonense. Celtic played the same opposition on Wednesday evening with a pretty youthful and inexperienced side, dotted with the players who didn’t ...
The post The first Celtic goals of the new Brendan Rodgers era have been scored appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: The bargain fees Celtic will pay to land third and fourth summer signings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167246</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/the-bargain-fees-celtic-will-pay-to-land-next-summer-signings/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T09:11:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are closing in on Brendan Rodgers’ third and fourth signings of the summer transfer window, with more South Koreans set to join the squad in Glasgow. It’s long been known that the Bhoys have been looking at the K-League market for additions and eventually moved for striker Hyeongyu Oh in January. He’s proven to ...
The post Report: The bargain fees Celtic will pay to land third and fourth summer signings appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INVINCIBLE IN DEMAND]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109860</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/invincible-in-demand/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T07:53:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC Invincible Stuart Armstrong is on the verge of quitting relegated Southampton. The 31-year-old Scotland international midrielder is reportedly a target for Serie A sides Torino and Lazio. Armstrong, who cost the south coast club £7million when he joined from the Hoops in 2018, has a year left on his contract to run, but is [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘GET A MOVE ON,’ RODGERS URGED TO SPLASH THE CASH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109852</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/get-a-move-on-rodgers-urged-to-splash-the-cash/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T07:04:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CHRIS SUTTON has urged Brendan Rodgers “to get a move on” in bringing in top signings to Celtic. The former Hoops hero insists the returning manager urgently requires new faces to provide the “wow factor” at the champions as they prepare for life after Filipe Jota. Sutton emphasises the Portuguese maverick was a pivotal figure [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC IN WORLD CUP HERO LINK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109848</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-in-world-cup-hero-link/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T06:33:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have been linked with Croatia World Cup keeper Dominik Livakovic. Brendan Rodgers has already backed 36-year-old former England international No.1 Joe Hart who has Benji Siegrist and Scott Bain as back-up. The veteran has been a mainstay in the Hoops first team since he arrived in a £1million switch from Spurs in August 2021. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>