<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2024-01-05T20:11:04.237Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Celtic transfer bulletin: Scott McKenna 'interest' & Paulo Bernardo revelation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185475</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-transfer-news-bulletin-scott-mckenna-interest-paulo-bernardo-release-clause/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The very latest Celtic transfer news. We bring you news regarding Nottingham Forest defender Scott McKenna and Hoops loanee Paulo Bernardo as part of Friday’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Ange Postecoglou buys nearing Celtic exits, time to rank all 29 of his signings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185448</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/ange-postecoglou-celtic-signings-as-49m-transfer-outlay-ranked/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here, we rank all Ange Postecoglou Celtic signings made during his incredibly successful two-year Parkhead stint. Much of Ange Postecoglou’s fantastic success at the Hoops...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC IN PREMIERSHIP SWITCH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116247</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-in-premiership-switch/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T12:43:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S Premiership match against Hearts at Tynecastle has been switched to Sunday March 3 with a midday kick-off. The game was scheduled to be played the previous day with a 3pm start, but has been moved with Sky Sports electing to show the action live. It will be the third time the teams have met [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['The answer is': Kieran Tierney issues a clear message about his future amid Celtic declaration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185442</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kieran-tierney-responds-to-arsenal-loan-recall-murmurs-amid-celtic-declaration/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kieran Tierney has been opening up to the Spanish press recently in which he addressed his immediate future with Real Sociedad and Arsenal amid a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spoiled Child FC have their Trump Jan 6 moment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116245</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/spoiled-child-fc-have-their-trump-jan-6-moment/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T12:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SFA issued a statement yesterday afternoon in response to Newco’s comments implying inappropriate action by the VAR adversely affected them during their recent defeat to Celtic.  It addressed three matters: The Newco penalty claim was a “Subjective handball… that the VAR did not deem it a sufficiently clear and obvious error”.  The VAR did [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic keeping track of Oscar Zambrano but face very stiff Premier League competition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185435</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/oscar-zambrano-linked-with-celtic-transfer-but-bournemouth-in-advanced-talks/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Both Celtic and Rangers have reportedly been tracking Ecuadorian wonderkid midfielder likened to Chelsea star Moises Caicedo, Oscar Zambrano. But the Hoops face extremely stiff...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harry Kewell set for reunion with failed Celtic signing at Yokohama F. Marinos - report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185430</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/yuki-kobayashi-set-to-reunite-with-former-celtic-coach-harry-kewell-at-yokohama-f-marinos/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harry Kewell was one of Celtic’s first-team coaches under Ange Postecoglou and then Brendan Rodgers for the first half of this season. He enjoyed great...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE LAUGH-IN: ‘I’VE GOT REAL PICTURES, MATE’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116239</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ange-laugh-in-ive-got-real-pictures-mate/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T10:01:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SILVER-TONGUED Ange Postecoglou had a smart retort for an unsuspecting English newspaper reporter as he met the media before tonight’s FA Cup-tie against Burnley in London. The naive scribe displayed his ignorance of the Greek-Australian’s previous achievements outside the Big Smoke. “Do you ever picture yourself lifting trophies?” asked the ill-prepared hack. Postecoglou didn’t miss [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou's brilliant Celtic success reminder to English press, they were in hysterics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185423</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-brilliant-celtic-success-reminder-has-english-press-in-hysterics/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic supporters across the globe know all too well that Ange Postecoglou can be rather spiky with the press. That was certainly the case when...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC CLEAR-OUT: ‘IT’S A CHALLENGE,’ ADMITS BOSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116234</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-clear-out-its-a-challenge-admits-boss/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T08:06:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORGOTTEN Celt Yuki Kobayashi is poised to be one of the first players through the exit in this month’s transfer window. The left-sided centre-back joined a year ago as a free agent after coming out of contract at Vissel Kobe. Kobayashi played a handful of first-team games for Ange Postecoglou, but dropped out of the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘THERE’S STILL A WAY FOR US TO GO,’ WARNS RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116232</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/theres-still-a-way-for-us-to-go-warns-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T07:24:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS surveyed the first half of a turbulent campaign and admitted his Celtic jigsaw is still in the process of coming together. The champions have had some unexpected and careless stumbles during the Irishman’s second coming, notably the back-to-back defeats from Kilmarnock and Hearts which severely dented their points advantage over their nearest challengers. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REVEALED: HOW CELTIC MISSED OUT ON £105m STAR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116228</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/revealed-how-celtic-missed-out-on-105m-star/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T06:11:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has revealed Celtic came close to signing £105million England international Declan Rice during his first spell in charge at Parkhead. The future big-money Arsenal star was coming through the ranks at West Ham when he was identified by the Hoops as a player of genuine potential. Rodgers, who had brought striker Moussa Dembele [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: SEASON’S BLEATINGS AND THE MASTERFUL LACK OF LOGIC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116225</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-seasons-bleatings-and-the-masterful-lack-of-logic/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T06:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE small object which has been detected orbiting the globe since around 3pm on Saturday appears to have been identified as a dummy belonging to a Mr P Clement of Govan. Oh dear, the Ibrox manager is not a happy chappie. It didn’t take too long for a crack to appear in the veneer, did [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…CRISTIAN GAMBOA?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=108778</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-cristian-gamboa/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T05:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CRISTIAN GAMBOA endured the worst possible debut for Celtic – a 7-0 Champions League trouncing from Barcelona in the Camp Nou in September 2016. The Costa Rican right-back had just arrived in a £1.2million deal from West Brom the previous month and Brendan Rodgers had high hopes for the attacking full-back. The Irishman, who had just [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I’m not convinced’: Andy Walker makes it clear and states Celtic simply can't sign 28-year-old]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185401</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/andy-walker-sends-clear-transfer-message-to-celtic-about-lawrence-shankland/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems likely that Celtic will dip into the January transfer market for an attacking player of some kind. There has been a lot of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Wilson nails why Rangers are complaining so much about the SFA after Celtic defeat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185393</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/mark-wilson-completely-nails-why-rangers-are-complaining-so-much-about-the-sfa-after-celtic-park-defeat/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T20:10:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rangers deflection tactics in the wake of their second derby defeat to Celtic this season have worked perfectly. They’ve sown up the media cycle...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Another': Stephen Welsh drops Matt O'Riley transfer message that Celtic fans will just love]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185354</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/stephen-welsh-drops-matt-oriley-transfer-message-that-celtic-fans-will-just-love/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O’Riley raised his Celtic bat in style on Tuesday when he hit 100 appearances by scoring during the 3-0 win over St Mirren. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I'm amazed’: Andy Walker reacts to what he’s hearing about Celtic star Kyogo Furuhashi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185372</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/andy-walker-says-he-is-amazed-by-what-hes-hearing-about-celtic-star-kyogo-furuhashi/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Both positive and negative news about Kyogo Furuhashi, and depends on which way you look at it. From Celtic’s perspective, he isn’t going to go...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Disappointed' Scottish FA release statement on Celtic Park penalty drama stirred up by Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185368</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/disappointed-scottish-fa-release-statement-on-celtic-park-penalty-drama-stirred-up-by-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T17:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Scottish FA have released a statement on the phantom penalty claim from Rangers during the recent 2-1 Celtic derby win. The ball hit Alistair...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thursday Celtic transfer bulletin: Kvistgaarden & Beck updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185344</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-transfer-news-bulletin-mathias-kvistgaarden-owen-beck/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The very latest Celtic transfer news. We bring you reports regarding Brondby striker Mathias Kvistgaarden and Liverpool wonderkid Owen Beck as part of Thursday’s January...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O'Riley reaches 100 Celtic games, we rank his stunning top five goals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185290</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/feature/matt-oriley-best-celtic-goals-including-sublime-hearts-volley/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here, we rank Celtic star Matt O’Riley’s top five goals in a Hoops shirt after the midfielder racked up 100 appearances for the club during...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EX-CELTIC BOSS POISED FOR QUICKFIRE RETURN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116223</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ex-celtic-boss-poised-for-quickfire-return/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T13:14:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic boss Tony Mowbray is poised for a quickfire return to management – exactly a month after being sacked by Sunderland. The one-time Hoops central defender is due to have talks with Birmingham City, according to a Daily Mail report. The Midlands club axed Wayne Rooney on Tuesday after the Manchester United legend had [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘A new level of respect’: Andy Walker says the perception of Celtic star has changed within a week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185322</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/andy-walker-says-the-perception-of-on-loan-benfica-star-paulo-bernardo-has-changed-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paulo Bernardo is going from strength to strength in Celtic colours. It goes to show what a few starts, some confidence and a goal can...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘At least three’: Celtic and Brendan Rodgers sent an exciting January transfer message]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185292</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/at-least-three-celtic-sent-exciting-transfer-message-after-january-window-opens/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Hartson thinks ‘at least three’ players will be on the radar of Celtic during the January transfer window.  Brendan Rodgers watched his team outclass...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIZARRE: MATT O’RILEY TRANSFER TALE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116219</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/bizarre-matt-oriley-transfer-tale/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T12:29:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WE accept this is the silly season as far as transfer speculation is concerned. Until the end of the month, the wonderful and weird merry-go-round of rumours will spin furiously and the tittle-tattle grapevine will veer towards meltdown. There will be some eyebrow-raising tales from “sources” that you just know will never see the light [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Brutal': Pundit delivers scathing swipe when comparing Maik Nawrocki and Carl Starfelt]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185283</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/maik-nawrocki-vs-carl-starfelt-celtic-comparison-made-as-one-branded-brutal/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Wilson has made a ‘brutal’ comparison when discussing the abilities of Maik Nawrocki and former Celtic star Carl Starfelt. The Polish centre-back was signed...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angry, bitter and ugly consequences for us all]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116218</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/angry-bitter-and-ugly-consequences-for-us-all/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T12:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No one has directly suggested Newco should have had a penalty when the ball struck Alistair Johnston’s hand moments before halftime on Saturday.  Abdallah Sima was offside, the attacking move effectively ended when he tried to win possession.  This fact is being overlooked by the losing club and instead, it is being implied they were [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Wilson 'wasn't having' Celtic 21-year-old, now pundit is raving about him]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185259</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/mark-wilson-admits-his-celtic-opinion-of-paulo-bernardo-has-drastically-changed/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paulo Bernardo had started just two Scottish Premiership games before the home win over Livingston just before Christmas. The on-loan midfielder from Benfica was in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confirmed Celtic January 2024 transfer ins and outs, signings & done deals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185254</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-january-2024-transfer-ins-and-outs-signings-done-deals/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here, we list all of the confirmed Celtic January 2024 transfer ins and outs, including permanent deals and loan moves. Brendan Rodgers effectively explained earlier...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘There is’: Chris Sutton shuts down Kris Boyd after snubbing Celtic star in Team of the Season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185262</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-shuts-down-kris-boyd-after-fresh-claim-about-celtic-star-kyogo-furuhashi/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T10:30:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even after Kris Boyd was humbled by Kyogo Furuhashi during Celtic’s 2-1 win over Rangers recently, he still can’t seem to acknowledge his brilliance. Both...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART, VAR AND THE RED CARD MYSTERY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116210</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/joe-hart-var-and-the-red-card-mystery/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T10:04:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART must have been left mystified when St Mirren’s Toyosi Olusanya was red-carded following a dangerous challenge on the keeper in Celtic’s 3-0 win in Paisley. The striker was originally booked by referee Nick Walsh before VAR intervened to instruct the official to review the incident on the touchline monitor. There was no surprise [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton says Celtic 23-year-old has been an ‘absolute bargain’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185217</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-makes-matt-oriley-transfer-claim-that-every-celtic-fan-would-agree-with/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best player at Celtic this season. And the best player in Scotland. Matt O’Riley is transforming into some player. The 23-year-old showcased high-quality performances...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…STEFAN SCEPOVIC?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=108775</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-stefan-scepovic/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T05:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RONNY DELIA paid £2.3million for Sporting Gijon striker Stefan Scepovic in September 2014 as the new Celtic manager urgently required to beef up his attack. Unfortunately, the Serbian hitman failed to hit the ground running after making a quickfire debut against Aberdeen at Parkhead. The Hoops won 2-1, but the new Bhoy failed to convince anyone [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Put himself in the shop window’: Scott Brown thinks Celtic star has now made Rodgers think twice]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185194</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/scott-brown-explains-why-paulo-bernardo-has-put-himself-in-the-shop-window-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic started 2024 with a bang by seeing off St Mirren in an emphatic fashion to continue the club’s recent strong form. After beating Rangers...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[’Things haven’t’: Chris Sutton names Celtic star who struggled despite 3-0 win over St Mirren]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185175</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/chris-suttons-brutally-honest-verdict-on-luis-palma-despite-celtics-3-0-win-at-st-mirren/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton thinks Luis Palma struggled to put in a strong showing despite Celtic’s 3-0 win over St Mirren on Tuesday. The 23-year-old started the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[’This is unreal’: James McFadden blown away by Celtic duo against St Mirren]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185159</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/james-mcfadden-delivers-verdict-on-celtic-duo-matt-oriley-and-paulo-bernardo-after-st-mirren-win/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What a way to start 2024 for Celtic. A comprehensive 3-0 win at St Mirren. Paulo Bernardo is having the time of his life because...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['They played long': Rod Stewart shuts down Simon Jordan’s claim about Celtic's win over Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185121</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/rod-stewart-shuts-down-simon-jordans-claim-about-celtics-recent-win-over-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic-mad Rod Stewart was sure to defend the quality of the Glasgow derby over the weekend and the manner of the Bhoys’ victory. Brendan Rodgers’...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘RUTHLESS,’ CENTURY BHOY PINPOINTS REASON FOR REVIVAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116175</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ruthless-century-bhoy-pinpoints-reason-for-revival/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T12:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY celebrated becoming a Century Bhoy by going into double figures with a neat goal in the 3-0 win over St Mirren in Paisley. The on-fire midfielder claimed a meagre four last season, but he has wasted no time in reaching 10 with the second part of the campaign still to come. The impressive O’Riley [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WATCH AGAIN: TEN OUT OF TEN, CELTIC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116173</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/watch-again-ten-out-of-ten-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T12:21:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC were under awesome pressure from all angles after two consecutive stumbles in the 2-1 loss to Kilmarnock and the 2-0 defeat from Hearts at Parkhead a week later. Back-to-back failures hadn’t been anticipated as Brendan Rodgers’ side seemingly headed uninterrupted towards their twelfth title in 13 years while leaving their rivals in their slipstream. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recruit, develop, reputation: the virtuous cycle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116166</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/recruit-develop-reputation-the-virtuous-cycle/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T12:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The thing about signing footballers who can transform you, those with real talent which has yet to be realised by the wider market, is that they are unbelievably difficult to find.  Getting this right is not the only requirement in propelling a club forward, but it is a necessary one. You also need to transform [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THREE CHEERS FOR ‘UNIQUE’ CELT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116160</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/three-cheers-for-unique-celt/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T11:34:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAIZEN MAEDA surely fired himself into the Celtic history books in the 3-0 triumph over St Mirren in Paisley last night. The Japanese striker thumped the champions into the lead in only 54 SECONDS – and became the first Hoops player to score the club’s first goal in three successive years. Maeda kicked off his special [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRIBUTE TO SHANE & THE MUSIC OF THE POGUES]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58588</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/tribute-to-shane-the-music-of-the-pogues/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T10:53:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Sheridan (pictured with Shane backstage in the Barrowlands, along with Alan from Shebeen) travels from Glasgow to join us on Saturday 06 Jan for our tribute night to the late, great Shane MacGowan and the music of the Pogues. Paul has been performing as a musician for over 20 years. Best known as […]
The post TRIBUTE TO SHANE & THE MUSIC OF THE POGUES appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘He looked back to his best’: Chris Sutton impressed by ‘powerful’ Celtic star v St Mirren]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185106</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/chris-sutton-delivers-verdict-on-daizen-maedas-performance-after-celtic-beat-st-mirren/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T10:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It didn’t take Celtic long to break the deadlock against St Mirren, with Daizen Maeda helping himself to a first-minute goal. The 26-year-old’s clever run...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Van Persie’: Gustaf Lagerbielke wowed by Celtic teammate after win over St Mirren]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185086</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/gustaf-lagerbielke-compares-celtic-teammate-to-robin-van-persie-after-3-0-win-over-st-mirren/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T09:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After beating Rangers over the weekend, the Celtic players did even better to respond with a comprehensive 3-0 win over St Mirren.  A brilliant start...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘QUITE EMOTIONAL,’ BOSS EXPLAINS HATATE HUG]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116157</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/quite-emotional-boss-explains-hatate-hug/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T08:33:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS and comeback Bhoy Reo Hatate were locked in an emotional embrace in the aftermath of Celtic’s 3-0 win over St Mirren in Paisley last night. The influential Japanese midfielder came on the 71st minute for Paulo Bernardo as the champions eased to three points with strikes from Daizen Maeda, Matt O’Riley and Greg [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘DEMANDS ARE SO MUCH,’ COLD COMFORT FOR RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116154</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/demands-are-so-much-cold-comfort-for-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T07:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S spirited bounce back from back-to-back defeats has seen the team win four games on the trot, score 10 goals and concede only one to restore their eight-point advantage at the Premiership pinnacle. It’s nothing to sneeze at as Brendan Rodgers leads his side into a welcome winter shutdown after admitting he has been fighting [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HIGH FIVES: THE DAY BIG YOGI DESTROYED GERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=61599</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/high-fives-the-day-big-yogi-destroyed-gers/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T06:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend John ‘Yogi’ Hughes passed away in August 2022 at the age of 79. The eighth-highest scoring player in the club’s history with 189 strikes left everyone with a treasure trove of wonderful memories. One of his most unforgettable performances came in an Old Firm encounter on January 3 1966 when Yogi was simply [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REVEALED: CELTIC AND JOHN McGINN: THE TRUTH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=100907</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/revealed-celtic-and-john-mcginn-the-truth/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T06:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WAYWARD tales of how Celtic failed to sign John McGinn from Hibs in August 2018 still abound in football circles. It seemed certain the Scotland international powerhouse, a boyhood Hoops fan, was heading for Parkhead until he was whisked across the border to Aston Villa. The dramatic change of direction in the player’s future stunned [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…OLI BURKE?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=108552</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-oli-burke/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T05:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OLI BURKE came to Celtic with a big reputation when he signed a short-term loan deal from West Brom in January 2019. The 26-year-old Scotland international striker, who had been involved in £28million worth of transfer deals involving Nottingham Forest, RB Leipzig and the Hawthorns outfit, flopped in the east end of Glasgow. Burke was [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ST MIRREN 0 CELTIC 3: HOOPY NEW YEAR AS LIGHTNING MAEDA LEADS THE WAY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116105</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/st-mirren-0-celtic-3-hoopy-new-year-as-lightning-maeda-leads-the-way/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T19:16:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ST MIRREN 0 CELTIC 3 CELTIC were as relentless as the rain in Paisley as they swept St Mirren aside in ruthless fashion to restore their eight-point advantage at the Premiership pinnacle before the winter break. It was breathtaking stuff from non-stop Hoops as they came out the traps at a ferocious pace in a [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[St Mirren v Celtic, GG Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116099</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/st-mirren-v-celtic-gg-live-updates/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T16:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 17:00.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: NAWROCKI IN, LAGERBIELKE ON STAND-BY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116084</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-nawrocki-in-lagerbielke-on-stand-by/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T15:49:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MAIK NAWROCKI will start his first game for Celtic since August when he faces St Mirren in Paisley tonight. The Polish centre-back, a £4.3million recruit from Legia Warsaw in the summer, came on for the injured Stephen Welsh in the Hoops’ 2-1 derby win at Parkhead at the weekend. Gustaf Lagerbielke, who cost £3million from [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[’The man of the season’: Peter Grant hails Celtic 25-year-old who dominated Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185072</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/liam-scales-receives-the-most-glowing-of-verdicts-as-celtic-put-rangers-to-the-sword/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What a season Liam Scales is having for Celtic!  Not even the player himself envisaged such a situation where he is now, not only one...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nawrocki breaking the lines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116098</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/nawrocki-breaking-the-lines/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T12:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The St Mirren result at Aberdeen dropped as you and I glowed in reflective glory from the result at the weekend.  0-3 away from home is an excellent return at any venue for any side, Saturday’s result is a signal that this evening’s opponents are to be taken seriously. Even against a side below them [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I'm not': Celtic boss delivers Liel Abada & Reo Hatate message ahead of St Mirren clash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185056</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-delivers-liel-abada-and-reo-hatate-update-ahead-of-celtics-trip-to-st-mirren/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has confirmed that Liel Abada is further ahead of Reo Hatate in earning minutes for Celtic. The duo have been out for long...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NAT OUT, NIC IN?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116088</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/nat-out-nic-in/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T10:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NAT PHILLIPS has returned to Liverpool after failing to convince during his short-term loan at Celtic, a move revealed by CQN over a fortnight ago. The centre-back answered an SOS from the champions in the summer when there were injury concerns over Cameron Carter-Vickers, Stephen Welsh and £7.3million recruits Maik Nawrocki and Gustaf Lagerbielke. Phillips, 26, made [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weeks after it looked like his Celtic career was over, £4.3m star must now start at St Mirren]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185040</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-message-is-clear-with-maik-nawrocki-after-his-performance-for-celtic-against-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T09:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You have to tip your hat to, Maik Nawrocki. It wasn’t so long ago that the summer signing’s future at Celtic was looking like it...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ST MIRREN v CELTIC: 5-MINUTE QUIZ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116082</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/st-mirren-v-celtic-5-minute-quiz-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T08:51:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC kick off 2024 against St Mirren in Paisley tonight with a 5pm kick-off. The previous meeting between the clubs at Parkhead on November 1 proved to be laced with anxiety as the visitors took an early lead. It was still poised on a tirghtrope at 1-1 with seven minutes of the regulation 90 to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I am surprised’: Celtic legend Chris Sutton blasts Rangers' latest actions after derby day fallout]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185017</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-reacts-to-rangers-actions-amid-criticism-at-sfa-after-celtics-glasgow-derby-day-win/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton delivered a dose of reality to Rangers after they were beaten 2-1 by Brendan Rodgers’ Celtic in the Glasgow derby on Saturday. In...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘VERY HUNGRY,’ RODGERS SPELLS IT OUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116063</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/very-hungry-rodgers-spells-it-out/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T07:58:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is well aware of the threat posed by tonight’s opponents St Mirren. The champions have one hurdle to clear before their well-earned break with their next encounter due on Sunday January 21 in the intriguing Scottish Cup meeting with Highland outfit Buckie Thistle at Parkhead. Stephen Robinson’s side lie in wait in Paisley [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GONE IN 12 MONTHS: FIVE STARS – AND A MANAGER]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115793</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/gone-in-12-months-five-stars-and-a-manager/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T06:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FIVE of the Celtic squad who earned a 2-2 draw at Ibrox EXACTLY a year ago today have left Celtic over the 12-month period. Ange Postecoglou utilised 16 players in the first game of 2023 with Canadian World Cup star Alistair Johnston, a £3.5million recruit from MLS outfit CF Montreal in the January window, making his debut [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEW YEAR PICTURE QUIZ: ALL IS REVEALED]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115269</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/new-year-picture-quiz-all-is-revealed/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T06:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HOW did you get on with CQN‘s Bumper New Year Picture Quiz? We asked you if you could identify the former Celtic players in our six images to test your knowledge. Today we provide the identities of the mystery men. PIC A It’s a young Neil Lennon, of course, sporting a blond look shortly after [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…JOHN GUIDETTI?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=108549</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-john-guidetti/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T05:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOHN GUIDETTI became an instant hit with the Celtic fans after arriving on a season-long loan from Manchester City in September 2014. Ronny Deila urgently required firepower and the Swedish striker looked to be the answer when he scored his first goal in his second appearance, a 3-0 League Cup win over Hearts in Glasgow. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO OVERLOOKED: GOOD NEWS FOR RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116053</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kyogo-overlooked-good-news-for-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T12:35:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC were handed some surprise good news with the shock omission of Kyogo Furuhashi from Japan’s squad for the Asian Cup which starts on January 14. Daizen Maeda and Reo Hatate are included, despite the fact the midfielder has been struggling to overcome a muscular problem after limping off early in the 2-2 Champions League draw [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neil McCann reckons Celtic hero just schooled hyped Rangers man]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185012</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/neil-mccann-reckons-celtic-hero-just-schooled-hyped-rangers-man/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T11:51:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are basking in the aftermath of another derby victory over Rangers and while some are outwardly raging at phantom penalties, the reality is that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DERBY FALL-OUT: 3 QUESTIONS FOR VAR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116024</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/derby-fall-out-3-questions-for-var/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T11:11:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have maintained a dignified silence in the fall-out of the second Glasgow derby of the campaign. The champions, of course, have notched up back-to-back triumphs with Kyogo Furuhashi hitting spectacular winners on both occasions, 1-0 at Ibrox on September 3 and 2-1 at Parkhead at the weekend. There are still some bitter ramifications coming [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Striker boost for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185009</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kyogo-boost-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T10:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Furuhashi will not be travelling around the world mid-season to play for Japan, instead staying in Glasgow to focus on Celtic fixtures. The Japanese...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic want to sign £4 million-rated player in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45945</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-4-million-player-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T23:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The defeat at the hands of Lazio was further proof of Celtic’s need to strengthen in the January transfer window. The club might have brought in nine new faces in the summer but a lot of people feel that the team has taken a step back since last season, when they breezed past the competition […]
Celtic want to sign £4 million-rated player in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers sends clear message Celtic board must not ignore]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45941</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/brendan-rodgers-message-celtic-board/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T21:35:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s fate in Europe for this season is sealed after their 2-0 defeat at the hands of Lazio. The result means that the Hoops are guaranteed to finish bottom of their group in the UEFA Champions League. That also means that they will not be dropping down to the Europa League, something that should have […]
Brendan Rodgers sends clear message Celtic board must not ignore - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton publicly criticises Celtic after loss to Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45938</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/chris-sutton-celtic-loss-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T20:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic lost 2-0 away in Rome to Lazio. The Hoops were in the match for a long time before Ciro Immobile came off the bench to score a brace and put the game to bed. The result means that not only are Brendan Rodgers’ side out of the Champions League following the group stages but […]
Chris Sutton publicly criticises Celtic after loss to Lazio - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed £7 million Jeremie Frimpong windfall news]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45933</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-jeremie-frimpong-windfall-news/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremie Frimpong’s rise at Bayer Leverkusen has been fascinating, to say the least. The Dutchman had shown a lot of quality going forward at Celtic as well but not many could have foreseen him becoming one of the most prolific wingbacks in Europe just a few years later. That is exactly what has happened under […]
Celtic handed £7 million Jeremie Frimpong windfall news - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic told 29-goal striker is good enough amid links]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45930</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-told-29-goal-striker-good-enough/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T13:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to add to their options up top this January. Kyogo has done well once again but he is not scoring as frequently as he was last season. On the other hand, Oh Hyeon-gyu has been inconsistent as well and is not at the level required to start for the Hoops right now. There […]
Celtic told 29-goal striker is good enough amid links - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anderlecht consider making offer for Celtic standout in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45927</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/anderlecht-offer-celtic-standout-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T11:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have not had the greatest campaign till now. They were eliminated early from the Scottish League Cup and while they do lead the Premiership, their performances and results have been somewhat inconsistent. Almost half a season on, it feels like the Hoops are still finding their feet under the management of Brendan Rodgers and […]
Anderlecht consider making offer for Celtic standout in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serie A club want to sign Celtic player amid contract worry]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45907</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/serie-club-want-celtic-player-contract/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T22:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic fans hope for more quality players arriving there could be a problem with others heading for the exit door. It seems pretty clear that Brendan Rodgers wants to make the size of the squad more manageable over the next couple of transfer windows and departures are expected. But there is a risk of […]
Serie A club want to sign Celtic player amid contract worry - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur step up bid to sign Celtic-linked player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45918</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/tottenham-hotspur-bid-sign-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur made a fantastic start to the season under the management of Ange Postecoglou. With Harry Kane leaving the club in the summer for Bayern Munich, most expected them to struggle. Instead, they appeared to be putting up an unlikely title challenge and were sitting atop the Premier League table not too long ago. […]
Tottenham Hotspur step up bid to sign Celtic-linked player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boost in race to sign £11 million Real Madrid player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45914</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/celtic-boost-real-madrid-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to sign a goalkeeper in the near future. It is quite clear that Joe Hart is not the long-term solution between the posts. The Englishman’s performances have been criticised lately. Also, he is set to turn 37 years of age before this season comes to an end. So, while he has done a […]
Celtic boost in race to sign £11 million Real Madrid player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio boss Maurizio Sarri makes fantastic Celtic claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45910</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/lazio-boss-maurizio-sarri-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T18:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By now, Celtic fans have accepted that Brendan Rodgers’ side are most probably not going through or even finishing third in their group in the UEFA Champions League. It would be a positive step to get a win in the competition though. It has been quite some time since the Hoops won at this level. […]
Lazio boss Maurizio Sarri makes fantastic Celtic claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic tipped to go for 28-year-old Premiership striker]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45904</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/celtic-tipped-go-premiership-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T12:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans breathed a sigh of relief as the Rangers dropped points at the weekend against Aberdeen. In fact, it took a late penalty for them to even come out with a draw from the game. That means that the Hoops will maintain their strong position at the top of the Scottish Premiership table. That […]
Celtic tipped to go for 28-year-old Premiership striker - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£7.5 million Mathias Kvistgaarden to Celtic transfer update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45900</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/mathias-kvistgaarden-celtic-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T10:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to sign a striker in January. On one hand, we have seen the club struggle for goals in some games this season. When the opposition puts up a resolute defence, the Hoops do not appear to have a lot of answers other than Kyogo, Matt O’Riley or Luis Palma. On the other hand, […]
£7.5 million Mathias Kvistgaarden to Celtic transfer update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur have been eyeing Celtic superstar]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45896</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/tottenham-hotspur-eyeing-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T23:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou made the move to Tottenham Hotspur in the summer and it was only a matter of time before the Australian was linked with a reunion with some Celtic players. The manager enjoyed a lot of success at Parkhead, even though he was at the club for just two seasons, and won five trophies […]
Tottenham Hotspur have been eyeing Celtic superstar - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John McGinn claims he spoke to Celtic players about manager]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45890</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/john-mcginn-spoke-celtic-players/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T21:35:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most Celtic fans will remember how the club missed out on the opportunity to sign John McGinn some years back. The Scot grew up supporting the Hoops but a move to Parkhead failed to materialise even though it had looked close and he ended up moving down south to join Aston Villa. McGinn has risen […]
John McGinn claims he spoke to Celtic players about manager - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic must consider signing striker from Premiership rivals]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45886</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-signing-striker-premiership-rivals/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T20:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there is one position where Celtic need to strengthen during the upcoming January transfer window, it is striker. The Hoops have been pretty inconsistent in front of goal this season so far. Of course, there are games when they can go out and score six times. But then, on days they are having a […]
Celtic must consider signing striker from Premiership rivals - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend takes dig at Rangers player for diving]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45884</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-legend-rangers-player-diving/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T18:35:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Celtic drew 1-1 against Motherwell, the Rangers were handed a major chance to get back into the title race. All they needed to do was win their games in hand and they would be just three points behind the Hoops in the league table. We have seen the Ibrox side not perform at their […]
Celtic legend takes dig at Rangers player for diving - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player criticised after draw against Motherwell]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45881</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-player-criticised-draw-motherwell/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T12:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Titles are not decided this early in the season. That has been proven once again. Not too long ago, Celtic were sitting seven points clear at the top of the Premiership table and most fans felt that the league was pretty much in the bag with the Rangers struggling for any kind of form.  It […]
Celtic player criticised after draw against Motherwell - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgio Chiellini makes superb claim about Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45874</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/giorgio-chiellini-claim-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T10:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Giorgio Chiellini is one of the best defenders of all time and he had some pretty positive comments about Celtic Park recently. The 39-year-old spent the majority of his career playing for Juventus and won more silverware there than one should try to count. Overall, he made more […]
Giorgio Chiellini makes superb claim about Celtic Park - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s problem is very clear and needs solving quick]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45870</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/celtic-problem-needs-solving-quick/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T19:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two more dropped points mean that Celtic have well and truly allowed the Rangers to get back into the title race. A lead which once stood at seven points, could be reduced to three if Philippe Clement’s side are able to win their games in hand. And the sad thing is that the Hoops have […]
Celtic’s problem is very clear and needs solving quick - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic problem after draw]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45866</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/brendan-rodgers-celtic-problem-draw/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T18:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was not the result Celtic were looking for, as they dropped two valuable points against Motherwell. David Turnbull’s goal appeared to have won it for the Hoops but the visitors equalised in the 90th minute and it ended 1-1. That means that if the Rangers win their games in hand, the gap will be […]
Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic problem after draw - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hollywood superstar pictured wearing Celtic jersey]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45861</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/hollywood-pictured-wearing-celtic-jersey/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T12:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Celtic have their fair share of famous fans. Rod Stewart is the first name that comes to most people’s minds, one of the best-selling music artists in history. Lewis Capaldi is another popular musician known to support the Hoops. And several A-list celebrities like Gerard Butler, Snoop Dogg, […]
Hollywood superstar pictured wearing Celtic jersey - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic pushing for priority signing in January window]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45859</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/celtic-priority-signing-january-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T09:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s January transfer window is expected to be a busy one. The club might have made nine signings in the summer, seven arriving on a permanent basis and two on loan, but there are still holes in Brendan Rodgers’ squad that need to be filled. On the other hand, there are way too many players […]
Celtic pushing for priority signing in January window - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable source offers Sydney van Hooijdonk to Celtic update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45854</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/reliable-sydney-van-hooijdonk-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T22:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are believed to be on the lookout for a striker in the January transfer window. There might be a few reasons behind that. Firstly, both Kyogo and Oh Hyeon-gyu might be unavailable for a considerable length of time early next year due to the AFC Asian Cup. They are the club’s two options to […]
Reliable source offers Sydney van Hooijdonk to Celtic update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou claims Celtic success gets dismissed]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45852</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/ange-postecoglou-claims-celtic-success/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T21:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has proven to be a major success in the Premier League since swapping Celtic for Tottenham Hotspur. Of course, a lot of fans were not happy to see him depart after just two years at Parkhead. But he has been very respectful about the club even after leaving. And it is hard not […]
Ange Postecoglou claims Celtic success gets dismissed - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>