<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2024-01-09T12:19:48.038Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic at AFC Asian Cup: Players, key dates & times, how to watch, return timelines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185702</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-at-2023-afc-asian-cup-players-key-dates-times-how-to-watch-return-timelines/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you were not aware already, Celtic have some players heading to the 2023 AFC Asian Cup in January. The Qatar tournament was originally scheduled...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marlborough, Murray, Ideguchi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116335</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/marlborough-murray-ideguchi/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T12:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A little appreciated determinant of the rise and fatal fall of Rangers under Lawrence Marlborough and then David Murray was the effect of an inflating, then deflating market for player transfers.  Betting on an inflating asset was a guaranteed success and the bigger you bet, the more successful you became.  Celtic eventually tried to copy [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BENJI SETBACK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116330</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/benji-setback/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T11:28:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BENJI SIEGRIST’S loan move to Austrian club Sturm Graz has been scuppered. Celtic’s third-choice keeper looked to be heading out on a temporary transfer to get much-needed game-time with first-team opportunities severely restricted at the champions. Siegrist, who joined the Hoops in August 2022 as a free agent after coming out of contract at Dundee [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC EXODUS: IDEGUCHI FIRST TO MOVE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116327</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-exodus-ideguchi-first-to-move/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T10:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YOSUKE IDEGUCHI’S anticipated return to Japan has been confirmed by Celtic. The former international anchorman finally ended his misery at Parkhead with a move back to his homeland, a deal forecast by CQN THIRTEEN months ago! Ideguchi, who spent last year on loan at Avispa Fukuoka, has sealed a permanent switch to J-League champions Vissel Kobe [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic loanee concedes Wigan penalty vs Man Utd and fans are all saying the same thing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185696</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/fans-fume-as-celtic-loanee-liam-shaw-concedes-wigan-penalty-vs-man-utd/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T09:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may be forgiven if you’re struggling to remember who Celtic midfielder Liam Shaw is. The 22-year-old was one of Ange Postecoglou’s first signings as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SALES TALK: ROBBIE KEANE AND ALL THAT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116321</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/sales-talk-robbie-keane-and-all-that/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T08:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THERE was a fanfare of trumpets in the east end of Glasgow late on the evening of January 31 2010 as Robbie Keane was welcomed to Celtic. In the midst of a hulabaloo of excitement, the Republic of Ireland’s legendary striker signed a short-term loan deal from Spurs. The Hoops, with new manager Tony Mowbray [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Talks expected': Fabrizio Romano drops Celtic transfer message last night]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185676</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/fabrizio-romano-drops-celtic-transfer-update-about-highly-rated-star-rocco-vata/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nine days into the January transfer window and there has been no movement at Celtic, both in terms of incomings or outgoings. But, in terms...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…LOGAN BAILLY?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=108807</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-logan-bailly/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-09T05:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LOGAN BAILLY was a low-key £250,000 signing in July 2015 as back-up keeper to Craig Gordon. Ronny Deila was searching for a new deputy netminder to the Scotland international after the release of Polish star Lukasz Zaluska. Bailly caught the Norwegian’s eye and he was duly signed from Belgian outfit Oh Leuven. First-team opportunities were [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Viva Bellahouston 1982 – Etims Podcast]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18563</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18563"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T22:20:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Monty, Hector and Desi get together to discuss a certain few games just before the New Year and a certain aftermath or possibly aftermass! They…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Desi Mond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Imagine going there’: Micah Richards make Celtic admission that won’t become a reality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185662</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/micah-richards-delivers-an-honest-answer-on-whether-he-wants-celtic-in-the-english-premier-league/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Micah Richards has admitted that it would be ‘brilliant’ if Celtic could leave Scottish football and join up with the English Premier League. It has...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monday Celtic transfer bulletin: Championship striker interest, Sutton's January priority]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185651</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/monday-celtic-transfer-bulletin-championship-striker-interest-suttons-january-priority/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T16:52:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic supporters are still waiting on the Bhoys committing to any January transfer activity but the club will undoubtedly be working on several potential deals...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Potential Serie A January exit route for struggling £3m summer Celtic signing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185647</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/potential-serie-a-january-exit-route-for-celtic-defender-gustaf-lagerbielke/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T12:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gustaf Lagerbielke has had a difficult first few months at Celtic and amidst speculation the club will listen to offers for him, a Serie A...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scales and the Great Left Back Consistency since 2010]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116312</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/scales-and-the-great-left-back-consistency-since-2010/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T12:05:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[18 months from the end of his contract, it’s good to read Brendan Rodgers talk about securing Liam Scales on a long-term deal.  The player is unrecognisable from the man who struggled against St Johnstone in August and is a testament to what happens when you develop a player properly. Successive Aberdeen managers, Jim Goodwin [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER CELTIC BOSS REPLACES ROONEY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116308</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/former-celtic-boss-replaces-rooney/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T11:27:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic boss Tony Mowbray has been named as Wayne Rooney’s successor at Birmingham City. The much-travelled gaffer, 60, signed a two-year deal at the Midlands club – just over a month after being sacked by Sunderland. Mowbray takes over at St Andrews only six days after the club axed Manchester United and England legend [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report states Nat Phillips’ teammate ‘caught the attention’ of Celtic for possible January move]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185626</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/report-states-nat-phillips-teammate-caught-the-attention-of-celtic-for-possible-january-move/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Taylor has been a solid performer for Celtic in recent years and has continued that under the stewardship of Brendan Rodgers. Despite that, it...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart's Celtic future just became clearer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185620</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/joe-harts-celtic-future-just-became-clearer-as-brendan-rodgers-poses-key-question/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T08:55:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has suggested Joe Hart may not be his number-one choice goalkeeper next season even if he ends up staying at the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers explains ongoing issue for Kyogo at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185615</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-explains-ongoing-issue-for-kyogo-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers has addressed the situation regarding Kyogo Furuhashi and a shoulder issue that he is currently managing, refuting the suggestion he needs...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SALES TALK: JORDAN HENDERSON FOR CELTIC? WHY?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116295</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/sales-talk-jordan-henderson-for-celtic-why/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T07:26:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A TALE has emerged from across the border linking Jordan Henderson with a possible reunion with his former Liverpool boss Brendan Rodgers at Celtic. We can dismiss the story as a load of waffle from a newspaper filling some column inches on a quiet news day. Henderson’s dream cash-laden move to Saudi Arabia has crashed [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Dalglish delivers verdict on Celtic Park controversy stirred up by Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185610</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kenny-dalglish-delivers-verdict-on-celtic-park-controversy-stirred-up-by-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T07:20:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Scotland legend Kenny Dalglish reckons Rangers have been unfair to the officials at the centre of the phantom penalty controversy at Celtic Park...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: WHEN RANGERS COMPLAINT LED TO 8-WEEK BAN FOR OLD FIRM REF]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=61430</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-when-rangers-complaint-led-to-8-week-ban-for-old-firm-ref/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T06:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE reported request by Rangers that Willie Collum be disqualified from refereeing any of their future fixtures is as inflammatory as it is ludricrous. The Ibrox club were clearly miffed the VAR official did not spot a so-called handball from Alistair Johnston during the champions’ 2-1 triumph on December 30, despite pictorial proof their own [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…JUNINHO?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=108805</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-juninho/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T05:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRAZIL’S World Cup winner Juninho was given a standing ovation on his Celtic debut on August 29 2004 – just four days after arriving from Middlesbrough. The 31-year-old winger had starred as a blistering long-range drive from Alan Thompson exploded behind Rangers keeper Stefan Klos for the late winner in the first Glasgow derby of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers addresses Liel Abada's happiness at Celtic right now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185607</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-addresses-liel-abadas-happiness-at-celtic-right-now/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-07T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has dismissed the idea of Liel Abada leaving Celtic in January despite a tough season for the player. Abada has had a significant...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['All of a sudden it's changed': Paul Lambert wowed by Celtic youngster who has 'raised his levels']]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185586</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/paul-lambert-shares-thoughts-on-possible-permanent-deal-for-paulo-bernardo-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-07T16:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After those back-to-back defeats for Celtic in December, one of the big plus points for the team after that has been the form of Paulo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘AMAZING STORY,’ RODGERS SUMS UP CELTIC STAR’S ABOUT-TURN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116290</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/amazing-story-rodgers-sums-up-celtic-stars-about-turn/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-07T12:33:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIAM SCALES is on the verge of agreeing a contract extension at Celtic. Brendan Rodgers has revealed the 24-year-old Republic of Ireland international is poised to pledge his future to the club as he continues his “amazing story” at the champions. Scales, whose current deal runs until June next year, looked to be on his [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I’M THERE FOR HIM,’ BRENDAN BACKS ABADA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116285</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/im-there-for-him-brendan-backs-abada/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-07T11:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIEL ABADA is in “a very good place” insists Brendan Rodgers during a challenging period for the Israeli winger. The 22-year-old goalscoring wide Bhoy has struggled since returning from international duty with an injury in September, as CQN reported. Abada has played just over half an hour of first team football during that three-month interlude, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UPS AND DOWNS OF KYOGO: RODGERS’ EXPLANATION]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116281</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-ups-and-downs-of-kyogo-rodgers-explanation/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-07T11:09:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO FURUHASHI brought down the curtain on 2023 with his breathtaking derby winner at Parkhead last weekend. It was the second time this season the Japanese speedster had fired in a spectacular points-clincher against the Govan club after doing likewise at Ibrox on September 3. The latest strike against Celtic’s city rivals was his tenth [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[’Never going to happen’: Alan Shearer expresses Celtic disappointment that he will never see]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185568</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alan-shearer-delivers-honest-verdict-on-if-he-wants-celtic-in-the-english-premier-league/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-07T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine Celtic in the English Premier League? It has been a question many have asked for decades now. Given the global size of Celtic, you...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘REALLY GOOD PLAYER,’ BOSS PRAISE FOR NEW BHOY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116267</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/really-good-player-boss-praise-for-new-bhoy/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-07T10:16:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MAIK NAWROCKI will celebrate his 23rd birthday next month with the wish he has won over Brendan Rodgers. The German-born former Polish Under-23 international central defender has rarely figured since his £4.3million arrival from Legia Warsaw in the summer, as CQN reported yesterday. Injury didn’t help his efforts to get game time as Liam Scales [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘So far ahead’: Michael Beale continues to take brutal Celtic hits, months after leaving Glasgow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185541</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-delivers-brutal-michael-beale-dig-with-celtic-reference-after-newcastle-win/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-07T09:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Beale still seems to be taking hits from Celtic, even though he has been out of the Glasgow spotlight for a few months now. ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S No.1 PROBLEM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116264</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtics-no-1-problem-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-07T08:57:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART has missed only three Premiership games since joining Celtic from Spurs in August 2021. The 36-year-old 75 times-capped England international keeper was forced to serve a one-game ban and miss the 2-1 stoppage-time win over Motherwell earlier this season after his ludicrous red card in the 3-0 victory at Livingston the previous week. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE PLAYER HAILED AS ‘PLEASANT SURPRISE’ BY CELTIC LEGEND]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116260</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-player-hailed-as-pleasant-surprise-by-celtic-legend/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-07T06:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic goal hero Chris Sutton has named the Hoops star who has been “a really pleasant surprise” this season. The one-time England international striker admitted he had reservations about on-loan Benfica midfielder Paulo Bernardo after his early appearances for the champions. However, the Portuguese playmaker has sparked to life in recent weeks with the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…FILIP BENKOVIC?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=108767</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-filip-benkovic/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-07T05:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FILIP BENKOVIC became a Celtic fans’ favourite after joining on a season-long loan deal from Leicester City in 2018/19. The accomplished Croatian centre-back, now 25, made 20 appearances in a treble-winning season under the guidance of Brendan Rodgers. Benkovic had been bought by the Midlands club for £13million from Dinamo Zagreb just before they agreed to move [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton absolutely nails it as Celtic hero decries 'very dangerous' Rangers request]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185533</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-celtic-hero-decries-very-dangerous-rangers-willie-collum-request/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic striker Chris Sutton has rightfully slammed Rangers for their alleged request asking referee Willie Collum not to officiate in any of their games in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers fans won't like what Graeme Souness thinks of Celtic Park on derby day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185528</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/graeme-souness-believes-there-is-none-to-match-celtic-park-atmosphere-on-derby-day-vs-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It doesn’t take a genius to work out that Celtic Park on Glasgow derby day or on Champions League nights creates the most intense atmosphere...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nat Phillips now sends Celtic fans a message after Liverpool loan return]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185522</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/nat-phillips-sends-celtic-fans-message-after-liverpool-loan-recall/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s safe to say Nat Phillips’ time at Celtic Park was pretty forgettable. Brendan Rodgers signed the 26-year-old from Liverpool at the end of the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's position in top 20 best supported clubs in world revealed, above Ajax & Man City]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185495</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-beat-man-city-and-ajax-as-2023-world-average-attendances-revealed/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans across the globe know full well that we are one of the most followed football teams on the planet – it’s a fact....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘DANGEROUS,’ SUTTON ACCUSES IBROX BOSSES IN ‘BLAME GAME’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116258</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/dangerous-sutton-accuses-ibrox-bosses-in-blame-game/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T10:13:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CHRIS SUTTON has accused the Ibrox hierarchy of setting “a very dangerous precedent” in their meltdown following the derby defeat to the champions at Parkhead a week ago. The losers are pointing fingers at everyone else for the responsibility of their failure against Brendan Rodgers’ side as the hosts won 2-1 to move eight points [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou snaps during Spurs presser, Celtic fans will love his cutting reply to reporter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185489</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-snaps-as-tottenham-boss-and-celtic-hero-loses-his-cool-at-reporters-eric-dier-question/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou was surely a happy man at the full-time whistle on Friday as his Tottenham Hotspur side beat Burnley in the FA Cup. Spurs...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic not in contention to sign 27-year-old Premier League outcast - report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185483</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/scott-mckenna-nottingham-forest-to-celtic-transfer-not-happening/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scott McKenna was linked with Celtic just 24 hours ago as the Nottingham Forest defender looks for a way out of the Premier League side....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NO DEAL: McKENNA NOT ON RODGERS HIT-LIST]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116252</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/no-deal-mckenna-not-on-rodgers-hit-list/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T07:44:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC boss Brendan Rodgers is NOT interested in Scotland international centre-back Scott McKenna. The champions have been linked with the former Aberdeen defender who is on the verge of quitting Nottingham Forest in this transfer window. McKenna, though, is not on Rodgers’ transfer wish list, according to a report in the Daily Record. That line [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: GO ON, BIG MAN, MAIK MY DAY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116246</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-go-on-big-man-maik-my-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T06:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT WOULD be an understatement of monumental proportions to say Maik Nawrocki has had a false start to his Celtic career. The centre-back arrived as the champions’ most expensive signing in the summer at £4.3million from Legia Warsaw. Nawrocki has played the full 90 minutes only twice – the 3-1 win over Aberdeen at Pittodrie [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…MARVIN COMPPER?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109014</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-marvin-compper/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T05:30:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THERE can be no more bizarre and bewildering transfer in Celtic history than that of Marvin Compper. Brendan Rodgers paid £1million to RB Leipzig for the one-time German international central defender in January 2018 and the Hoops fans were eager to get a first look at the new Bhoy. Compper, 33, was brought in to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Celtic transfer bulletin: Scott McKenna 'interest' & Paulo Bernardo revelation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185475</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-transfer-news-bulletin-scott-mckenna-interest-paulo-bernardo-release-clause/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The very latest Celtic transfer news. We bring you news regarding Nottingham Forest defender Scott McKenna and Hoops loanee Paulo Bernardo as part of Friday’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Ange Postecoglou buys nearing Celtic exits, time to rank all 29 of his signings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185448</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/ange-postecoglou-celtic-signings-as-49m-transfer-outlay-ranked/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here, we rank all Ange Postecoglou Celtic signings made during his incredibly successful two-year Parkhead stint. Much of Ange Postecoglou’s fantastic success at the Hoops...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC IN PREMIERSHIP SWITCH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116247</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-in-premiership-switch/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T12:43:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S Premiership match against Hearts at Tynecastle has been switched to Sunday March 3 with a midday kick-off. The game was scheduled to be played the previous day with a 3pm start, but has been moved with Sky Sports electing to show the action live. It will be the third time the teams have met [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['The answer is': Kieran Tierney issues a clear message about his future amid Celtic declaration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185442</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kieran-tierney-responds-to-arsenal-loan-recall-murmurs-amid-celtic-declaration/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kieran Tierney has been opening up to the Spanish press recently in which he addressed his immediate future with Real Sociedad and Arsenal amid a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spoiled Child FC have their Trump Jan 6 moment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116245</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/spoiled-child-fc-have-their-trump-jan-6-moment/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T12:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SFA issued a statement yesterday afternoon in response to Newco’s comments implying inappropriate action by the VAR adversely affected them during their recent defeat to Celtic.  It addressed three matters: The Newco penalty claim was a “Subjective handball… that the VAR did not deem it a sufficiently clear and obvious error”.  The VAR did [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic keeping track of Oscar Zambrano but face very stiff Premier League competition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185435</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/oscar-zambrano-linked-with-celtic-transfer-but-bournemouth-in-advanced-talks/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Both Celtic and Rangers have reportedly been tracking Ecuadorian wonderkid midfielder likened to Chelsea star Moises Caicedo, Oscar Zambrano. But the Hoops face extremely stiff...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harry Kewell set for reunion with failed Celtic signing at Yokohama F. Marinos - report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185430</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/yuki-kobayashi-set-to-reunite-with-former-celtic-coach-harry-kewell-at-yokohama-f-marinos/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harry Kewell was one of Celtic’s first-team coaches under Ange Postecoglou and then Brendan Rodgers for the first half of this season. He enjoyed great...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE LAUGH-IN: ‘I’VE GOT REAL PICTURES, MATE’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116239</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ange-laugh-in-ive-got-real-pictures-mate/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T10:01:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SILVER-TONGUED Ange Postecoglou had a smart retort for an unsuspecting English newspaper reporter as he met the media before tonight’s FA Cup-tie against Burnley in London. The naive scribe displayed his ignorance of the Greek-Australian’s previous achievements outside the Big Smoke. “Do you ever picture yourself lifting trophies?” asked the ill-prepared hack. Postecoglou didn’t miss [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou's brilliant Celtic success reminder to English press, they were in hysterics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185423</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-brilliant-celtic-success-reminder-has-english-press-in-hysterics/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic supporters across the globe know all too well that Ange Postecoglou can be rather spiky with the press. That was certainly the case when...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC CLEAR-OUT: ‘IT’S A CHALLENGE,’ ADMITS BOSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116234</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-clear-out-its-a-challenge-admits-boss/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T08:06:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORGOTTEN Celt Yuki Kobayashi is poised to be one of the first players through the exit in this month’s transfer window. The left-sided centre-back joined a year ago as a free agent after coming out of contract at Vissel Kobe. Kobayashi played a handful of first-team games for Ange Postecoglou, but dropped out of the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘THERE’S STILL A WAY FOR US TO GO,’ WARNS RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116232</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/theres-still-a-way-for-us-to-go-warns-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T07:24:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS surveyed the first half of a turbulent campaign and admitted his Celtic jigsaw is still in the process of coming together. The champions have had some unexpected and careless stumbles during the Irishman’s second coming, notably the back-to-back defeats from Kilmarnock and Hearts which severely dented their points advantage over their nearest challengers. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REVEALED: HOW CELTIC MISSED OUT ON £105m STAR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116228</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/revealed-how-celtic-missed-out-on-105m-star/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T06:11:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has revealed Celtic came close to signing £105million England international Declan Rice during his first spell in charge at Parkhead. The future big-money Arsenal star was coming through the ranks at West Ham when he was identified by the Hoops as a player of genuine potential. Rodgers, who had brought striker Moussa Dembele [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: SEASON’S BLEATINGS AND THE MASTERFUL LACK OF LOGIC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116225</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-seasons-bleatings-and-the-masterful-lack-of-logic/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T06:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE small object which has been detected orbiting the globe since around 3pm on Saturday appears to have been identified as a dummy belonging to a Mr P Clement of Govan. Oh dear, the Ibrox manager is not a happy chappie. It didn’t take too long for a crack to appear in the veneer, did [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…CRISTIAN GAMBOA?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=108778</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-cristian-gamboa/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T05:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CRISTIAN GAMBOA endured the worst possible debut for Celtic – a 7-0 Champions League trouncing from Barcelona in the Camp Nou in September 2016. The Costa Rican right-back had just arrived in a £1.2million deal from West Brom the previous month and Brendan Rodgers had high hopes for the attacking full-back. The Irishman, who had just [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic want to sign £4 million-rated player in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45945</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-4-million-player-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T23:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The defeat at the hands of Lazio was further proof of Celtic’s need to strengthen in the January transfer window. The club might have brought in nine new faces in the summer but a lot of people feel that the team has taken a step back since last season, when they breezed past the competition […]
Celtic want to sign £4 million-rated player in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers sends clear message Celtic board must not ignore]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45941</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/brendan-rodgers-message-celtic-board/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T21:35:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s fate in Europe for this season is sealed after their 2-0 defeat at the hands of Lazio. The result means that the Hoops are guaranteed to finish bottom of their group in the UEFA Champions League. That also means that they will not be dropping down to the Europa League, something that should have […]
Brendan Rodgers sends clear message Celtic board must not ignore - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton publicly criticises Celtic after loss to Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45938</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/chris-sutton-celtic-loss-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T20:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic lost 2-0 away in Rome to Lazio. The Hoops were in the match for a long time before Ciro Immobile came off the bench to score a brace and put the game to bed. The result means that not only are Brendan Rodgers’ side out of the Champions League following the group stages but […]
Chris Sutton publicly criticises Celtic after loss to Lazio - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed £7 million Jeremie Frimpong windfall news]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45933</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-jeremie-frimpong-windfall-news/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremie Frimpong’s rise at Bayer Leverkusen has been fascinating, to say the least. The Dutchman had shown a lot of quality going forward at Celtic as well but not many could have foreseen him becoming one of the most prolific wingbacks in Europe just a few years later. That is exactly what has happened under […]
Celtic handed £7 million Jeremie Frimpong windfall news - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic told 29-goal striker is good enough amid links]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45930</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-told-29-goal-striker-good-enough/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T13:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to add to their options up top this January. Kyogo has done well once again but he is not scoring as frequently as he was last season. On the other hand, Oh Hyeon-gyu has been inconsistent as well and is not at the level required to start for the Hoops right now. There […]
Celtic told 29-goal striker is good enough amid links - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anderlecht consider making offer for Celtic standout in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45927</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/anderlecht-offer-celtic-standout-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T11:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have not had the greatest campaign till now. They were eliminated early from the Scottish League Cup and while they do lead the Premiership, their performances and results have been somewhat inconsistent. Almost half a season on, it feels like the Hoops are still finding their feet under the management of Brendan Rodgers and […]
Anderlecht consider making offer for Celtic standout in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serie A club want to sign Celtic player amid contract worry]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45907</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/serie-club-want-celtic-player-contract/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T22:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic fans hope for more quality players arriving there could be a problem with others heading for the exit door. It seems pretty clear that Brendan Rodgers wants to make the size of the squad more manageable over the next couple of transfer windows and departures are expected. But there is a risk of […]
Serie A club want to sign Celtic player amid contract worry - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur step up bid to sign Celtic-linked player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45918</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/tottenham-hotspur-bid-sign-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur made a fantastic start to the season under the management of Ange Postecoglou. With Harry Kane leaving the club in the summer for Bayern Munich, most expected them to struggle. Instead, they appeared to be putting up an unlikely title challenge and were sitting atop the Premier League table not too long ago. […]
Tottenham Hotspur step up bid to sign Celtic-linked player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boost in race to sign £11 million Real Madrid player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45914</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/celtic-boost-real-madrid-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to sign a goalkeeper in the near future. It is quite clear that Joe Hart is not the long-term solution between the posts. The Englishman’s performances have been criticised lately. Also, he is set to turn 37 years of age before this season comes to an end. So, while he has done a […]
Celtic boost in race to sign £11 million Real Madrid player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio boss Maurizio Sarri makes fantastic Celtic claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45910</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/lazio-boss-maurizio-sarri-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T18:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By now, Celtic fans have accepted that Brendan Rodgers’ side are most probably not going through or even finishing third in their group in the UEFA Champions League. It would be a positive step to get a win in the competition though. It has been quite some time since the Hoops won at this level. […]
Lazio boss Maurizio Sarri makes fantastic Celtic claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic tipped to go for 28-year-old Premiership striker]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45904</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/celtic-tipped-go-premiership-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T12:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans breathed a sigh of relief as the Rangers dropped points at the weekend against Aberdeen. In fact, it took a late penalty for them to even come out with a draw from the game. That means that the Hoops will maintain their strong position at the top of the Scottish Premiership table. That […]
Celtic tipped to go for 28-year-old Premiership striker - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£7.5 million Mathias Kvistgaarden to Celtic transfer update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45900</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/mathias-kvistgaarden-celtic-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T10:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to sign a striker in January. On one hand, we have seen the club struggle for goals in some games this season. When the opposition puts up a resolute defence, the Hoops do not appear to have a lot of answers other than Kyogo, Matt O’Riley or Luis Palma. On the other hand, […]
£7.5 million Mathias Kvistgaarden to Celtic transfer update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur have been eyeing Celtic superstar]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45896</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/tottenham-hotspur-eyeing-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T23:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou made the move to Tottenham Hotspur in the summer and it was only a matter of time before the Australian was linked with a reunion with some Celtic players. The manager enjoyed a lot of success at Parkhead, even though he was at the club for just two seasons, and won five trophies […]
Tottenham Hotspur have been eyeing Celtic superstar - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John McGinn claims he spoke to Celtic players about manager]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45890</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/john-mcginn-spoke-celtic-players/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T21:35:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most Celtic fans will remember how the club missed out on the opportunity to sign John McGinn some years back. The Scot grew up supporting the Hoops but a move to Parkhead failed to materialise even though it had looked close and he ended up moving down south to join Aston Villa. McGinn has risen […]
John McGinn claims he spoke to Celtic players about manager - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic must consider signing striker from Premiership rivals]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45886</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-signing-striker-premiership-rivals/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T20:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there is one position where Celtic need to strengthen during the upcoming January transfer window, it is striker. The Hoops have been pretty inconsistent in front of goal this season so far. Of course, there are games when they can go out and score six times. But then, on days they are having a […]
Celtic must consider signing striker from Premiership rivals - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend takes dig at Rangers player for diving]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45884</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-legend-rangers-player-diving/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T18:35:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Celtic drew 1-1 against Motherwell, the Rangers were handed a major chance to get back into the title race. All they needed to do was win their games in hand and they would be just three points behind the Hoops in the league table. We have seen the Ibrox side not perform at their […]
Celtic legend takes dig at Rangers player for diving - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player criticised after draw against Motherwell]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45881</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-player-criticised-draw-motherwell/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T12:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Titles are not decided this early in the season. That has been proven once again. Not too long ago, Celtic were sitting seven points clear at the top of the Premiership table and most fans felt that the league was pretty much in the bag with the Rangers struggling for any kind of form.  It […]
Celtic player criticised after draw against Motherwell - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgio Chiellini makes superb claim about Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45874</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/giorgio-chiellini-claim-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T10:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Giorgio Chiellini is one of the best defenders of all time and he had some pretty positive comments about Celtic Park recently. The 39-year-old spent the majority of his career playing for Juventus and won more silverware there than one should try to count. Overall, he made more […]
Giorgio Chiellini makes superb claim about Celtic Park - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s problem is very clear and needs solving quick]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45870</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/celtic-problem-needs-solving-quick/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T19:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two more dropped points mean that Celtic have well and truly allowed the Rangers to get back into the title race. A lead which once stood at seven points, could be reduced to three if Philippe Clement’s side are able to win their games in hand. And the sad thing is that the Hoops have […]
Celtic’s problem is very clear and needs solving quick - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic problem after draw]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45866</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/brendan-rodgers-celtic-problem-draw/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T18:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was not the result Celtic were looking for, as they dropped two valuable points against Motherwell. David Turnbull’s goal appeared to have won it for the Hoops but the visitors equalised in the 90th minute and it ended 1-1. That means that if the Rangers win their games in hand, the gap will be […]
Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic problem after draw - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hollywood superstar pictured wearing Celtic jersey]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45861</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/hollywood-pictured-wearing-celtic-jersey/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T12:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Celtic have their fair share of famous fans. Rod Stewart is the first name that comes to most people’s minds, one of the best-selling music artists in history. Lewis Capaldi is another popular musician known to support the Hoops. And several A-list celebrities like Gerard Butler, Snoop Dogg, […]
Hollywood superstar pictured wearing Celtic jersey - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic pushing for priority signing in January window]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45859</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/celtic-priority-signing-january-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T09:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s January transfer window is expected to be a busy one. The club might have made nine signings in the summer, seven arriving on a permanent basis and two on loan, but there are still holes in Brendan Rodgers’ squad that need to be filled. On the other hand, there are way too many players […]
Celtic pushing for priority signing in January window - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable source offers Sydney van Hooijdonk to Celtic update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45854</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/reliable-sydney-van-hooijdonk-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T22:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are believed to be on the lookout for a striker in the January transfer window. There might be a few reasons behind that. Firstly, both Kyogo and Oh Hyeon-gyu might be unavailable for a considerable length of time early next year due to the AFC Asian Cup. They are the club’s two options to […]
Reliable source offers Sydney van Hooijdonk to Celtic update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou claims Celtic success gets dismissed]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45852</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/ange-postecoglou-claims-celtic-success/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T21:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has proven to be a major success in the Premier League since swapping Celtic for Tottenham Hotspur. Of course, a lot of fans were not happy to see him depart after just two years at Parkhead. But he has been very respectful about the club even after leaving. And it is hard not […]
Ange Postecoglou claims Celtic success gets dismissed - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>