<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2024-04-07T04:14:15.581Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TITLE FEVER: MARTIN’S FIRST IN RECORD-BREAKING CAMPAIGN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=89921</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/title-fever-martins-first-in-record-breaking-campaign/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-07T04:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MARTIN O’NEILL’S first championship success – and Celtic’s thirty-seventh in their glorious history – was delivered EXACTLY 23 years ago today. There were five games still to be played when St Mirren turned up at Parkhead to perform in front of a crowd of 60,440, the biggest in Scotland that season, in the forlorn hope [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kolo Toure tells Jake Humphrey what was so "incredible" about Celtic and battering Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194045</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kolo-toure-tells-jake-humphrey-what-was-so-incredible-about-celtic-and-battering-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-06T17:22:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kolo Toure has been reflecting on his entire career with broadcaster Jake Humphrey and naturally his short spell at Celtic came up. The defender played...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate's pleasing Celtic statement of intent ahead of high-stakes derby match]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193946</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/reo-hatates-pleasing-celtic-statement-of-intent-ahead-of-high-stakes-derby-match/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-06T16:35:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate has given a fascinating interview to Japanese media this week discussing how he has been impacted by injuries this season and his philosophy...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charlie Mulgrew points out the key strength Celtic have over Rangers right now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194036</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/charlie-mulgrew-points-out-the-key-strength-celtic-have-over-rangers-right-now/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-06T15:15:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Given some of the chatter heading into Sunday’s match between Celtic and Rangers, you’d be forgiven for thinking that the Bhoys haven’t held the power...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon makes his big Celtic vs Rangers derby prediction ahead of Sunday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194033</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/neil-lennon-makes-his-big-celtic-vs-rangers-derby-prediction-ahead-of-sunday/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-06T13:34:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re less than 24 hours away from Sunday’s massive match between Celtic and Rangers at Ibrox in the Scottish Premiership. Final training sessions have been...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: SPARE ME THE ‘FORTRESS IBROX’ BALONEY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119292</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-spare-me-the-fortress-ibrox-baloney/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-06T09:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ONLY the churlish among us would deny Philippe Clement the praise he deserves for propelling a wayward team back on track. The Belgian arrived in November with the Ibrox outfit displaying all the directional awareness of a blindfolded drunken sailor tasked with negotiating his way through a minefield. They were clueless, guileless and aimless as [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘IT’S MENTAL – THE INTENSITY OF IT,’ CELT RELISHES IBROX RETURN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119285</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/its-mental-the-intensity-of-it-celt-relishes-ibrox-return/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-06T06:29:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIAM SCALES is looking forward to a return to his finest hour and a half as a Celtic player when the champions perform at Ibrox tomorrow. The Republic of Ireland international was pitched in at Govan in early September as Brendan Rodgers had put his first-team jigsaw together after being hit by a freak series [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WIN? ‘WE DON’T NEED TO,’ INSISTS RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119284</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/win-we-dont-need-to-insists-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-06T05:36:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS insists Celtic do NOT need to win at Ibrox tomorrow. The champions, bidding for their twelfth title in 13 years, go into the third derby of the campaign with a one-point advantage over their city rivals who have a game in hand. Rodgers has enjoyed success in his two fixtures in this rarefied [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO’S SEVEN FROM HEAVEN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115036</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kyogos-seven-from-heaven/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-06T05:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO FURUHASHI had to wait until January 2 last year to claim his first goal against Ibrox opposition. The Japanese international striker fired blanks against Celtic’s city foes – then managed by Steven Gerrard – when he made his derby debut in Govan on August 29 2021,  just under a month after his £4.6million arrival [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS v RANGERS: Part Seven]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119238</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-v-rangers-part-seven/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-06T05:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is preparing for his players for the visit to Ibrox tomorrow, his third derby encounter since returning to Celtic in June last year. The Irishman has already enjoyed a double triumph in the previous meetings – 1-0 at Ibrox on September 3 and 2-1 at Parkhead on December 30. Now Rodgers is gearing up [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TITLE FEVER: HENRIK HAT-TRICK v LIVI IS CROWNING GLORY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=76637</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/title-fever-henrik-hat-trick-v-livi-is-crowning-glory/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-06T04:30:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MARTIN O’NEILL joined the legendary Jock Stein as the only Celtic manager to win the spectacular domestic treble when he swept the boards in his debut season after arriving from Leicester City in the summer of 2000. Trailblazer Stein had achieved the feat twice – in seasons 1966/67 and 1968/69 – and was out on [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou sends message of support to Celtic ahead of Rangers derby]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194026</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-sends-message-of-support-to-celtic-ahead-of-rangers-derby/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T15:04:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou says he will be watching this Sunday’s derby when the Bhoys visit Ibrox to face Rangers. Postecoglou enjoyed two dominant...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers takes deliberate note of what people are saying about Celtic heading into Ibrox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194020</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-takes-deliberate-note-of-what-people-are-saying-about-celtic-heading-into-ibrox/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T14:35:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers is relishing the chance to upset the ongoing narrative about his team in another derby against Rangers. The Bhoys took care...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FINAL CALL FOR McGREGOR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119278</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/final-call-for-mcgregor/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T14:22:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has revealed he will make a final call tomorrow on skipper Callum McGregor’s chances of playing at Ibrox on Sunday. The Hoops’ inspirational onfield leader has been missing since the 7-1 win over Dundee at Parkhead on February 28 when he was replaced at the interval with teen ace Daniel Kelly. McGregor missed [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic team news vs Rangers in full as Brendan Rodgers delivers Friday update on McGregor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194001</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-news-vs-rangers-in-full-as-brendan-rodgers-delivers-friday-update-on-callum-mcgregor/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T13:50:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s excitement and tension in the build towards Celtic’s trip to Ibrox on Sunday. Some fans understandably don’t enjoy this part of the derby week....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers reacts to John Beaton appointment for Celtic vs Rangers derby]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194004</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-reacts-to-john-beaton-appointment-for-celtic-vs-rangers-derby/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T13:24:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has been giving his thoughts on the upcoming derby away to Rangers on Sunday and the appointment of John Beaton as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kolo Toure explains the mid-season moment Celtic teammate made him realise he had to retire]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193995</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kolo-toure-explains-the-mid-season-moment-celtic-teammate-made-him-realise-he-had-to-retire/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T11:06:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Kolo Toure arrived at Celtic in 2016 it was well-acknowledged that he was coming towards the end of his career. The Ivorian signed for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic, experienced winners at Ibrox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119277</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-experienced-winners-at-ibrox/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T11:03:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You will remember being concerned going into ‘these games’ in the past with too many Celtic players who have either no experience of them, or mainly poor experiences.  Not so on Sunday.  The Celtic side and those in the dugout have  experienced overwhelmingly positive outcomes when facing Newco, including at Ibrox. The same is not [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘WHAT A WASTE,’ GOALIE GURU’S VERDICT ON HART]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119274</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/what-a-waste-goalie-gurus-verdict-on-hart/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T10:18:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART’S three years as Celtic’s unopposed No.1 goalkeeper will end next month. The 75 times-capped England international shotstopper has announced he will call it a day and hang up his gloves when the final whistle sounds at the completion of an engrossing campaign. Hart will again be the champions’ guardian between the posts when [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Virgil van Dijk tells Gary Lineker and Micah Richards what was so "perfect" about Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193990</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/virgil-van-dijk-tells-gary-lineker-and-micah-richards-what-was-so-perfect-about-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T09:47:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic defender Virgil van Dijk has had an incredible football career full of success and silverware at the elite level of the game. He...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I was good enough"; NFL legend believes he could have had a 15-year career at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193985</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-was-good-enough-nfl-legend-believes-he-could-have-had-a-15-year-career-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T09:09:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two-time Super Bowl winner Lawrence Tynes had NFL success that most can only dream of but his boyhood ambition was to pull on the green...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: NO-GO YANG]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119271</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-no-go-yang/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T08:21:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have confirmed Yang Hyun-jun will NOT be joining the South Korean international set-up this month. The winger was named in his country’s squad for the AFC Under-23 Asian Cup in Qatar, a competition which doubles as a qualifier for this summer’s Olympic games in Paris. However, the champions have informed the South Korean FA [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scottish FA sharply criticised for latest blunder involving Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193981</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/scottish-fa-sharply-criticised-for-latest-needless-blunder-involving-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T08:15:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there’s a significant furore around refereeing and the Scottish FA in the wake of the upcoming Celtic and Rangers derby, then the Hampden association...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I’VE GOT EVERY FAITH,’ KT BACKS RODGERS TO DELIVER AGAIN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119269</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ive-got-every-faith-kt-backs-rodgers-to-deliver-again/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T07:52:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KIERAN TIERNEY insists Brendan Rodgers is the ideal man to lead Celtic into the white heat of a crucial derby battle at Ibrox on Sunday. The former Hoops fans’ favourite, who departed Parkhead in a £25million switch to Arsenal in August 2019, is backing the Irishman to continue his excellent record against the city rivals. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic firmly rebuff national FA after recent international call-up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193976</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-firmly-rebuff-national-fa-after-recent-international-call-up/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T07:36:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been confirmed that Celtic won’t be without Hyunjun Yang for much of April, despite being called up by the Korea FA for an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton names his under-the-radar matchwinners for Celtic against Rangers this Sunday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193972</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-names-his-2-under-the-radar-matchwinners-for-celtic-against-rangers-this-sunday/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T07:08:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker Chris Sutton has called on those out with the Bhoys’ established group of difference-makers to step up and make an impact against...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘RECKLESS’, ‘IRRESPONSIBLE’ AND ‘DAFT’: SUTTON SIDESWIPE AT ALLY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119267</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/reckless-irresponsible-and-daft-sutton-sideswipe-at-ally/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T07:06:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CHRIS SUTTON has taken a sideswipe at Ally McCoist after recent comments from the Rangers goalscoring hero on Scotland’s new hate speech act. The Celtic legend had his say on controversial remarks made by his ex-BT Sport colleague ahead of the third Glasgow derby of the season at Ibrox on Sunday. Responding to the declaration [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kieran Tierney sends class Celtic message ahead of big derby against Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193967</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kieran-tierney-sends-class-celtic-message-ahead-of-big-derby-against-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T06:34:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic defender Kieran Tierney has every faith in the Bhoys to get the job done against Rangers on Sunday in a massive Scottish Premiership...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HAPPY ANNIVERSARY: CELTIC’S TROPHY TREBLE IN 21 DAYS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=76016</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/happy-anniversary-celtics-trophy-treble-in-21-days/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T06:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC enjoyed one of their most sensational silverware sequences in their glorious history when they embarked upon a breathtakingly victorious trek as season 1968/69 came close to its conclusion. Even by the remarkable standards set by Jock Stein’s great side, this was exceptional. A collection of gifted and highly-motivated individuals sparked in unison to see off [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS v RANGERS: Part Six]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=115778</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-v-rangers-part-six/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T05:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS got the Glasgow derby-winning show on the road again when he masterminded the 1-0 triumph at Ibrox on September 3 last year. Following 10 victories, two draws and a solitary loss in his first stint, the Irishman returned to the fixture for the first time following an absence of over four and a [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS v RANGERS: Part Five]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111583</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-v-rangers-part-five/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-05T05:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT’S BEEN smiles  better for Brendan Rodgers in his derby encounters this season. After an absence of over four and a half years from the fixture, the second time-around Celtic manager has seen talisman Kyogo Furuhashi fire in two spectacular winners at Ibrox on September 3 and Parkhead on December 30. Now the 51-year-old is [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday  Sunday…Bring it on!! – Podcast with transcript]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18587</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18587"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T21:26:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hector, Monty and Desi get together to discuss the recent games and how they will impact the future big game at Ibrox on Sunday. They…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Desi Mond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tomoki Iwata explains where his big improvement at Celtic has stemmed from]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193960</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/tomoki-iwata-explains-his-where-his-vast-improvement-at-celtic-has-stemmed-from/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder Tomoki Iwata has managed to establish himself as a reliable option in the number six position since returning from injury. The Japan international...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Henrik Larsson to open up on special relationship with Celtic fans in new interview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193957</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/henrik-larsson-opens-up-on-special-relationship-with-celtic-fans-during-interview-snippet/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans are in for a pre-derby treat this weekend after an interview snippet with Henrik Larsson started to circulate via Sky Sports. The King...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tomoki Iwata eyeing new Celtic role amid recent burst of form]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193953</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/tomoki-iwata-eyeing-new-celtic-role-amid-recent-burst-of-form/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers had had to rotate his squad this season amid injury problems that have mounted over the last few months. For once,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The harsh Celtic switch Brendan Rodgers could make vs Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193948</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-harsh-celtic-call-brendan-rodgers-could-make-vs-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers will have his work cut out as he deliberates on his starting line-up for this Sunday’s crucial match against Rangers. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Green Brigade and Bhoys fan groups announce encouraging Glasgow Derby plans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193937</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/green-brigade-and-bhoys-announce-encouraging-glasgow-derby-plans-for-big-celtic-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic travel to Rangers this weekend in a crucial fixture examining the context of our Scottish Premiership title hopes. At this stage, we hold a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SPFL club win appeal against John Beaton decision ahead of pressure Celtic vs Rangers derby]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193935</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/spfl-club-win-appeal-against-john-beaton-decision-ahead-of-pressure-celtic-vs-rangers-derby/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T13:01:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Beaton’s decision-making has come under scrutiny again just days before the referee takes charge of this weekend’s huge Celtic vs Rangers game. Beaton was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alan Stubbs thinks player who is 'so important' can hand Celtic an advantage over Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193932</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alan-stubbs-thinks-player-who-is-so-important-can-hand-celtic-an-advantage-over-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are gearing up for an enormous Glasgow Derby clash this weekend, which could give Brendan Rodgers’ side a major boost in their hunt to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MAKE MINE A DOUBLE: CCV’S TARGET]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119257</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/make-mine-a-double-ccvs-target/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T11:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CAMERON CARTER-VICKERS and Liam Scales will team up for the first time in the Glasgow derby at Ibrox on Sunday. Injury has ruled out the USA World Cup Finals centre-back from the two previous encounters, the 1-0 away win on September 3 and the 2-1 triumph at Parkhead just before the turn of the year. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star Luis Palma reacts to funny Darwin Nunez moment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193927</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-star-luis-palma-reacts-to-funny-darwin-nunez-moment/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are preparing to travel to Ibrox on Sunday ahead of a crunch Glasgow Derby against Rangers, on a day where the Scottish Premiership title...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Penalty records, Clement on precipice]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119256</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/penalty-records-clement-on-precipice/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T11:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Newco’s remarkable run of penalty kicks, given and not received, has been covered far better than I have elsewhere, so I will not dig into the main issue today.  What we need to concern ourselves with it that penalty kicks is one of their main sources of wins in domestic football. This is a jeopardy [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maik Nawrocki seen dropping into iconic Celtic bar on Glasgow Derby week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193923</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/maik-nawrocki-seen-dropping-into-iconic-celtic-bar-on-glasgow-derby-week/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T09:49:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans will have their chosen establishments where they head to before or after matches for a drink with their friends and family. In Glasgow,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic loanee gains exciting international recognition, could play in Paris 2024 Olympics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193920</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-loanee-gains-exciting-international-recognition-could-play-in-paris-2024-olympics/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are in the midst of a climactic end to the season as they look to edge closer to claiming silverware under Brendan Rodgers. With...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘CELTIC NEED REO HATATE,’ JINXED ACE’S COMEBACK WISH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119253</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-need-reo-hatate-jinxed-aces-comeback-wish/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T08:20:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE is preparing to start only his second game in almost SIX months in the crucial derby encounter at Ibrox on Sunday. The injury-jinxed Japanese midfielder was in Brendan Rodgers’ line-up at kick-off in the 3-0 win at Livingston at the weekend. Amazingly, that was Hatate’s first inclusion in a starting eleven since the 2-2 Champions League [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alan Stubbs lauds the 'calmness' one Celtic individual can bring to the table vs Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193917</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alan-stubbs-lauds-the-calmness-one-celtic-individual-can-bring-to-the-table-vs-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic take on Rangers this weekend as they look to hammer home their title-winning credentials on our rivals’ own patch. Anticipation is building ahead of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS v RANGERS: Part Four]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111571</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-v-rangers-part-four/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T05:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS celebrated his return to the rarified atmosphere of a Glasgow derby this season after an absence of over four and a half years. The second time-around Celtic boss was all smiles as he watched Kyogo Furuhashi volley in the only goal of the encounter at Ibrox in early September to seal his comeback. And [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jackie McNamara says Brendan Rodgers may use surprising Celtic tactical ploy vs Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193911</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/jackie-mcnamara-says-brendan-rodgers-may-use-surprising-celtic-tactical-ploy-vs-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T05:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans will be gearing up for their side to face Rangers this Sunday in a match with huge ramifications in the Scottish Premiership title...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS v RANGERS: Part Three]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111506</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-v-rangers-part-three/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-04T05:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is preparing for Sunday’s third derby of the season on the back of successive victories. Kyogo Furuhashi has been the champions’ matchwinner in the previous triumphs at Ibrox on September 3 and Parkhead on December 30. The second time-around Hoops gaffer enjoyed phenomenal success against the city rivals in his first spell between [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Stewart explains why Celtic could claim Glasgow Derby result amid 'real positives']]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193897</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/michael-stewart-explains-why-celtic-could-claim-glasgow-derby-result-amid-real-positives/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic travel to face Rangers at Ibrox this weekend in a match with sizeable ramifications regarding the Scottish Premiership title race. Brendan Rodgers’ men head...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jackie McNamara explains why Kyogo Furuhashi's Celtic form has improved significantly]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193908</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/jackie-mcnamara-explains-why-kyogo-furuhashis-celtic-form-has-improved-significantly/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic striker Kyogo Furuhashi has enjoyed a slightly different role at times this season under the stewardship of Brendan Rodgers. As we head into the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Warnock issues transfer verdict involving Celtic and Bojan Miovski live on talkSPORT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193903</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/neil-warnock-issues-transfer-verdict-involving-celtic-and-bojan-miovski-live-on-talksport/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will be in the market for some fresh blood this summer as Brendan Rodgers makes some alterations to his squad. Positionally, the goalkeeping area...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Curve Celtic reply with simple four-word message to Livingston Tifo anger]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193900</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/north-curve-celtic-reply-with-simple-four-word-message-to-livingston-tifo-anger/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T14:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans found out earlier today that Livingston released a statement regarding Tifo displays on show at the Tony Macaroni Arena last weekend. The West...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Livingston release statement over Green Brigade Tifo display at Celtic clash last weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193894</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/livingston-release-statement-over-tifo-displays-at-celtic-clash-last-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defeated Livingston 3-0 at the Tony Macaroni Arena last weekend to maintain their one-point advantage at the Scottish Premiership summit. Now, Livingston have released...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Warnock calls out how Scottish media handle Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193890</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/neil-warnock-calls-out-how-scottish-media-handle-celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers has endured a varied first campaign back in charge at Parkhead after replacing Ange Postecoglou in the dugout. As we canter...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: WHEN BRENDAN MET BEATON]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119241</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-when-brendan-met-beaton/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T11:05:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YOU only get one chance to make a first impression. It took Brendan Rodgers just over half an hour to determine the refereeing qualities of John Beaton. It was August 7 2016, on a radiantly sunny afternoon in Edinburgh, when the new Celtic manager witnessed the whistler in action for the first time. Arms folded and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hate, an odd hill to fight on]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119242</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hate-an-odd-hill-to-fight-on/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T11:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m no fan of the new Hate Crime Law (clearly, I’m against hate crime, that’s not the point), but I have no intention to break its terms at a football game, nor do I have any fears that thousands of Celtic fans would do so.  After announcing he and 48,000 others would break the law [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart opens up on emotional Celtic retirement ahead of penultimate Rangers clash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193879</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/joe-hart-opens-up-on-emotional-celtic-retirement-ahead-of-penultimate-rangers-clash/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will need to source a new goalkeeper in the summer due to Joe Hart’s impending retirement from professional football. The 36-year-old has enjoyed a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The strongest Celtic XI Brendan Rodgers must go with for Scottish Premiership title run-in]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193882</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-strongest-celtic-xi-brendan-rodgers-must-go-with-for-scottish-premiership-title-run-in/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just seven games remain for Celtic in the Scottish Premiership season, starting with a huge trip to face Rangers at Ibrox on Sunday. This is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lubo Moravcik talks up big "shot in the arm" Celtic could now get for Rangers game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193877</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/lubo-moravcik-talks-up-big-shot-in-the-arm-celtic-could-now-get-for-rangers-game/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T09:11:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic icon Lubomir Moravcik is no stranger to performing in the derby against Rangers and he has been speaking about the upcoming title race clash...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former England international thinks 'magnificent' attacker could be 'huge success' at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193874</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-england-international-thinks-magnificent-attacker-could-be-huge-success-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers will be in the market for quality additions this summer to bolster his side’s prospects heading into 2024/25. The Irishman will...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers set for another major Celtic injury boost ahead of Glasgow Derby]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193871</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-set-for-another-major-celtic-injury-boost-ahead-of-glasgow-derby/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers will be keen to ensure he has as many options as possible to choose from during the season run-in. Last weekend,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE:  ‘WRITE OFF CELTIC AT YOUR PERIL,’ WARNS LEGEND]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119239</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-write-off-celtic-at-your-peril-warns-legend/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T07:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAVIE HAY was almost a lone voice as he warned critics about the perils of writing off Celtic in the aftermath of the inexplicable downfall of the team in season 2020/21. The feeble performances and the abysmal failure to seal the historic tenth successive title brought an avalanche of scathing comments. The Hoops stumbled through [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS v RANGERS: Part Two]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111476</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-v-rangers-part-two/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T05:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is preparing for his third derby encounter since returning to Celtic in June last year. The Irishman has already enjoyed a double triumph in the previous meetings – 1-0 at Ibrox on September 3 and 2-1 at Parkhead on December 30. Now Rodgers is gearing up to go again in the High Noon [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alan Thompson names the experienced men who can inspire Celtic to defeat Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193868</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alan-thompson-names-the-experienced-men-who-can-inspire-celtic-to-defeat-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T20:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic travel to Ibrox this weekend knowing nothing but a victory will do in their quest to win the Scottish Premiership title. The Bhoys travel...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea Under-23 boss speaks out on Hyunjun Yang hope amid potential Celtic absence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193865</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/south-korea-under-23-boss-speaks-out-on-hyunjun-yang-hope-amid-potential-celtic-absence/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers will be satisfied with the options he has at his disposal as the season run-in hits full swing. The Bhoys saw...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Big boost’: Chris Sutton says Brendan Rodgers has got a lift ahead of Celtic’s trip to Ibrox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193853</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-says-brendan-rodgers-got-a-big-boost-ahead-of-celtics-trip-to-ibrox/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton believes that Celtic boss, Brendan Rodgers, has received a big boost this week ahead of the trip to Rangers on Sunday for the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Highly rated player Celtic want to sign once rejected Rangers and Steven Gerrard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193858</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/highly-rated-player-celtic-want-to-sign-once-rejected-rangers-and-steven-gerrard/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic look to have already cast one eye on their potential summer transfer activity under Brendan Rodgers. Earlier this week, reports emerged from south of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Terrific’: John Kennedy in awe of Celtic star who's been ‘worked really hard’ in training recently]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193840</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/john-kennedy-has-been-seriously-impressed-with-terrific-celtic-star-in-training/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s win over Livingston on Sunday gave John Kennedy the opportunity to take charge of the team as Brendan Rodgers served his one-match ban. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Unbelievable'... Nicolas Kuhn sheds light on what he loved about Celtic's win over Livingston]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193846</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/unbelievable-nicolas-kuhn-sheds-light-on-what-he-loved-about-celtics-win-over-livingston/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defeated lowly Livingston last weekend in a comprehensive victory ahead of our trip to face Rangers at Ibrox this Sunday. Jamie Brandon’s own goal...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shaun Maloney explains what Gordon Strachan changed that made him a success at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=193837</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/shaun-maloney-explains-what-gordon-strachan-changed-that-made-him-a-success-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wigan Athletic boss, Shaun Maloney, has shared how Gordon Strachan made him a success at Celtic back in his playing days. Maloney was a Parkhead...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic want to sign £4 million-rated player in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45945</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-4-million-player-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T23:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The defeat at the hands of Lazio was further proof of Celtic’s need to strengthen in the January transfer window. The club might have brought in nine new faces in the summer but a lot of people feel that the team has taken a step back since last season, when they breezed past the competition […]
Celtic want to sign £4 million-rated player in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers sends clear message Celtic board must not ignore]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45941</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/brendan-rodgers-message-celtic-board/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T21:35:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s fate in Europe for this season is sealed after their 2-0 defeat at the hands of Lazio. The result means that the Hoops are guaranteed to finish bottom of their group in the UEFA Champions League. That also means that they will not be dropping down to the Europa League, something that should have […]
Brendan Rodgers sends clear message Celtic board must not ignore - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton publicly criticises Celtic after loss to Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45938</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/chris-sutton-celtic-loss-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T20:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic lost 2-0 away in Rome to Lazio. The Hoops were in the match for a long time before Ciro Immobile came off the bench to score a brace and put the game to bed. The result means that not only are Brendan Rodgers’ side out of the Champions League following the group stages but […]
Chris Sutton publicly criticises Celtic after loss to Lazio - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed £7 million Jeremie Frimpong windfall news]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45933</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-jeremie-frimpong-windfall-news/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremie Frimpong’s rise at Bayer Leverkusen has been fascinating, to say the least. The Dutchman had shown a lot of quality going forward at Celtic as well but not many could have foreseen him becoming one of the most prolific wingbacks in Europe just a few years later. That is exactly what has happened under […]
Celtic handed £7 million Jeremie Frimpong windfall news - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic told 29-goal striker is good enough amid links]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45930</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-told-29-goal-striker-good-enough/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T13:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to add to their options up top this January. Kyogo has done well once again but he is not scoring as frequently as he was last season. On the other hand, Oh Hyeon-gyu has been inconsistent as well and is not at the level required to start for the Hoops right now. There […]
Celtic told 29-goal striker is good enough amid links - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anderlecht consider making offer for Celtic standout in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45927</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/anderlecht-offer-celtic-standout-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T11:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have not had the greatest campaign till now. They were eliminated early from the Scottish League Cup and while they do lead the Premiership, their performances and results have been somewhat inconsistent. Almost half a season on, it feels like the Hoops are still finding their feet under the management of Brendan Rodgers and […]
Anderlecht consider making offer for Celtic standout in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serie A club want to sign Celtic player amid contract worry]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45907</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/serie-club-want-celtic-player-contract/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T22:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic fans hope for more quality players arriving there could be a problem with others heading for the exit door. It seems pretty clear that Brendan Rodgers wants to make the size of the squad more manageable over the next couple of transfer windows and departures are expected. But there is a risk of […]
Serie A club want to sign Celtic player amid contract worry - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur step up bid to sign Celtic-linked player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45918</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/tottenham-hotspur-bid-sign-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur made a fantastic start to the season under the management of Ange Postecoglou. With Harry Kane leaving the club in the summer for Bayern Munich, most expected them to struggle. Instead, they appeared to be putting up an unlikely title challenge and were sitting atop the Premier League table not too long ago. […]
Tottenham Hotspur step up bid to sign Celtic-linked player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boost in race to sign £11 million Real Madrid player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45914</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/celtic-boost-real-madrid-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to sign a goalkeeper in the near future. It is quite clear that Joe Hart is not the long-term solution between the posts. The Englishman’s performances have been criticised lately. Also, he is set to turn 37 years of age before this season comes to an end. So, while he has done a […]
Celtic boost in race to sign £11 million Real Madrid player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio boss Maurizio Sarri makes fantastic Celtic claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45910</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/lazio-boss-maurizio-sarri-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T18:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By now, Celtic fans have accepted that Brendan Rodgers’ side are most probably not going through or even finishing third in their group in the UEFA Champions League. It would be a positive step to get a win in the competition though. It has been quite some time since the Hoops won at this level. […]
Lazio boss Maurizio Sarri makes fantastic Celtic claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic tipped to go for 28-year-old Premiership striker]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45904</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/celtic-tipped-go-premiership-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T12:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans breathed a sigh of relief as the Rangers dropped points at the weekend against Aberdeen. In fact, it took a late penalty for them to even come out with a draw from the game. That means that the Hoops will maintain their strong position at the top of the Scottish Premiership table. That […]
Celtic tipped to go for 28-year-old Premiership striker - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£7.5 million Mathias Kvistgaarden to Celtic transfer update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45900</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/mathias-kvistgaarden-celtic-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T10:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to sign a striker in January. On one hand, we have seen the club struggle for goals in some games this season. When the opposition puts up a resolute defence, the Hoops do not appear to have a lot of answers other than Kyogo, Matt O’Riley or Luis Palma. On the other hand, […]
£7.5 million Mathias Kvistgaarden to Celtic transfer update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur have been eyeing Celtic superstar]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45896</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/tottenham-hotspur-eyeing-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T23:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou made the move to Tottenham Hotspur in the summer and it was only a matter of time before the Australian was linked with a reunion with some Celtic players. The manager enjoyed a lot of success at Parkhead, even though he was at the club for just two seasons, and won five trophies […]
Tottenham Hotspur have been eyeing Celtic superstar - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John McGinn claims he spoke to Celtic players about manager]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45890</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/john-mcginn-spoke-celtic-players/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T21:35:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most Celtic fans will remember how the club missed out on the opportunity to sign John McGinn some years back. The Scot grew up supporting the Hoops but a move to Parkhead failed to materialise even though it had looked close and he ended up moving down south to join Aston Villa. McGinn has risen […]
John McGinn claims he spoke to Celtic players about manager - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic must consider signing striker from Premiership rivals]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45886</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-signing-striker-premiership-rivals/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T20:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there is one position where Celtic need to strengthen during the upcoming January transfer window, it is striker. The Hoops have been pretty inconsistent in front of goal this season so far. Of course, there are games when they can go out and score six times. But then, on days they are having a […]
Celtic must consider signing striker from Premiership rivals - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend takes dig at Rangers player for diving]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45884</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-legend-rangers-player-diving/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T18:35:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Celtic drew 1-1 against Motherwell, the Rangers were handed a major chance to get back into the title race. All they needed to do was win their games in hand and they would be just three points behind the Hoops in the league table. We have seen the Ibrox side not perform at their […]
Celtic legend takes dig at Rangers player for diving - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player criticised after draw against Motherwell]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45881</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-player-criticised-draw-motherwell/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T12:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Titles are not decided this early in the season. That has been proven once again. Not too long ago, Celtic were sitting seven points clear at the top of the Premiership table and most fans felt that the league was pretty much in the bag with the Rangers struggling for any kind of form.  It […]
Celtic player criticised after draw against Motherwell - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgio Chiellini makes superb claim about Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45874</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/giorgio-chiellini-claim-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T10:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Giorgio Chiellini is one of the best defenders of all time and he had some pretty positive comments about Celtic Park recently. The 39-year-old spent the majority of his career playing for Juventus and won more silverware there than one should try to count. Overall, he made more […]
Giorgio Chiellini makes superb claim about Celtic Park - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s problem is very clear and needs solving quick]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45870</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/celtic-problem-needs-solving-quick/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T19:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two more dropped points mean that Celtic have well and truly allowed the Rangers to get back into the title race. A lead which once stood at seven points, could be reduced to three if Philippe Clement’s side are able to win their games in hand. And the sad thing is that the Hoops have […]
Celtic’s problem is very clear and needs solving quick - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic problem after draw]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45866</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/brendan-rodgers-celtic-problem-draw/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T18:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was not the result Celtic were looking for, as they dropped two valuable points against Motherwell. David Turnbull’s goal appeared to have won it for the Hoops but the visitors equalised in the 90th minute and it ended 1-1. That means that if the Rangers win their games in hand, the gap will be […]
Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic problem after draw - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hollywood superstar pictured wearing Celtic jersey]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45861</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/hollywood-pictured-wearing-celtic-jersey/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T12:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Celtic have their fair share of famous fans. Rod Stewart is the first name that comes to most people’s minds, one of the best-selling music artists in history. Lewis Capaldi is another popular musician known to support the Hoops. And several A-list celebrities like Gerard Butler, Snoop Dogg, […]
Hollywood superstar pictured wearing Celtic jersey - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic pushing for priority signing in January window]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45859</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/celtic-priority-signing-january-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T09:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s January transfer window is expected to be a busy one. The club might have made nine signings in the summer, seven arriving on a permanent basis and two on loan, but there are still holes in Brendan Rodgers’ squad that need to be filled. On the other hand, there are way too many players […]
Celtic pushing for priority signing in January window - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable source offers Sydney van Hooijdonk to Celtic update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45854</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/reliable-sydney-van-hooijdonk-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T22:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are believed to be on the lookout for a striker in the January transfer window. There might be a few reasons behind that. Firstly, both Kyogo and Oh Hyeon-gyu might be unavailable for a considerable length of time early next year due to the AFC Asian Cup. They are the club’s two options to […]
Reliable source offers Sydney van Hooijdonk to Celtic update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou claims Celtic success gets dismissed]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45852</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/ange-postecoglou-claims-celtic-success/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T21:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has proven to be a major success in the Premier League since swapping Celtic for Tottenham Hotspur. Of course, a lot of fans were not happy to see him depart after just two years at Parkhead. But he has been very respectful about the club even after leaving. And it is hard not […]
Ange Postecoglou claims Celtic success gets dismissed - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>