<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2024-03-10T10:09:21.666Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Biggest gripe': Alistair Johnston shares what really annoyed him about Celtic's VAR controversy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=192063</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alistair-johnston-shares-what-really-annoyed-him-about-celtics-var-controversy/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A week has passed and the fallout from VAR continues as Celtic defender Alistair Johnston has his say on what happened last Sunday at Tynecastle....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers 'excited' by Adam Idah's Celtic future but transfer reality acknowledged]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=192082</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-excited-by-adam-idahs-celtic-future-but-transfer-reality-acknowledged/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans will be excited to see what direction their side go down in the transfer market this summer following a frustrating couple of windows....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alex Cochrane actions back up Brendan Rodgers' issue with SFA and the evidence is clear]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=192073</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alex-cochrane-actions-back-up-brendan-rodgers-issue-with-sfa-and-the-evidence-is-clear/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic VAR controversy took a sharp turn this week after the SFA charged Brendan Rodgers for his post-match comments after the 2-0 defeat to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘HORRIBLY WRONG,’ CELTIC LEGEND BACKS BRENDAN IN SFA ROW]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=118422</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/horribly-wrong-celtic-legend-backs-brendan-in-sfa-row/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T08:29:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LEGENDARY Celt Sir Kenny Dalglish has waded into is old club’s SFA VAR row and thrown his support solidly behind Brendan Rodgers. The Hoops boss has been summoned by the Scottish football rulers to answer a complaint following his comments after the champions’ controversial 2-0 loss to Hearts at Tynecastle a week ago. Rodgers was incensed [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers' telling comments on his return to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=192079</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-telling-comments-on-his-return-to-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T08:10:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers has candidly shared that this season has been his most challenging as a manager across his entire career. When Rodgers walked...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘FIRE UP THE SQUAD,’ RODGERS’ SUMMER TRANSFER PLEDGE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=118420</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/fire-up-the-squad-rodgers-summer-transfer-pledge/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T07:53:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS insists he will “fire up the squad again” as he promises to delve into the summer transfer market. The Celtic manager arrived in June last year just as Filipe Jota and Carl Starfelt were on the brink of moves and Aaron Mooy had just announced his retirement. Recruits such as Maik Nawrocki, Gustaf [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston shares his experience of living with Celtic rivalry out and about in Glasgow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=192067</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alistair-johnston-shares-his-experience-of-living-with-celtic-rivalry-out-and-about-in-glasgow/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T07:40:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Alistair Johnston has paid tribute to teammates such as Callum McGregor and James Forrest for living with such an intense rivalry in Glasgow...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["One of the worst"... Kenny Dalglish doesn't hold back on SFA referees after Celtic drama]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=192059</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/one-of-the-worst-kenny-dalglish-doesnt-hold-back-with-verdict-on-sfa-referees-after-celtic-drama/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T07:10:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend Kenny Dalglish has sharply criticised the Scottish FA, as well as referees Don Robertson and John Beaton after last week’s drama at Tynecastle....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE RETURN OF BIG JOCK: PART ONE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=118369</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-return-of-big-jock-part-one/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T06:40:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EXACTLY 59 years ago today, Jock Stein took his place in a dug-out as Celtic’s new manager for the first time. The club’s former centre-half and reserve team coach had arrived as Jimmy McGrory’s successor on the previous day, March 9 1965. Twenty-four hours later he was on the touchline for the league match against Airdrie [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY GEMMELL AND THE FINAL FAREWELL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=33363</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/tommy-gemmell-and-the-final-farewell/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T06:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY GEMMELL bade a final farewell seven years ago today as his funeral cortege left Celtic Park en route for Daldowie Crematorium. The unforgettable Lisbon Lion had passed away the previous week at the age of 73. The Celtic Family turned out to say a last goodbye to a fabulous character who had played such [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC v LIVINGSTON: 5-MINUTE QUIZ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=118372</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-livingston-5-minute-quiz-4/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T05:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC switch their focus to the Scottish Cup when they face Livingston in the quarter-final in this afternoon’s encounter at Parkhead. Brendan Rodgers’ side have beaten the West Lothian outfit twice in the Premiership twice without the loss of a goal this season. How much can you remember about past connections with Livi? Have a [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crunch time for SPFL rule change that Celtic and Brendan Rodgers want]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=192056</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/crunch-time-for-spfl-rule-change-that-celtic-and-brendan-rodgers-want/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T20:38:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A date has been set for clubs to vote on banning artificial pitches in the Scottish Premiership, a rule change that Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paris 2024 Olympic athlete shares his surprising love for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=192048</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/paris-2024-olympic-athlete-reveals-his-surprising-love-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T19:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Spanish Olympian, set to represent his country at the upcoming Paris 2024 games, has been speaking about his unlikely relationship with Celtic. The Bhoys...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liam Scales hits back at "unfair" Celtic critics ahead of Livingston]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=192045</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/liam-scales-hits-back-at-unfair-celtic-critics-ahead-of-livingston/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T19:20:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liam Scales reckons criticism about the lack of leadership within the Celtic squad is unfair as the Bhoys continue to do without captain Callum McGregor....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic team news, injuries, absences and Predicted XI for Scottish Cup match vs Livingston]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=192042</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-news-injuries-absences-and-predicted-xi-for-scottish-cup-match-vs-livingston/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T18:26:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic host Livingston in the Scottish Cup quarter-finals on Sunday hoping to book a place at Hampden for the first time this season. The holders...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers cites Connor Goldson incident as example of SFA inconsistency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=192038</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-manager-brendan-rodgers-cites-connor-goldson-incident-as-example-of-sfa-inconsistency/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T17:36:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers has continued to present his case that there are issues with refereeing in Scotland, a week after his post-match comments at...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gijs Smal and Celtic's transfer search for a quality left-back]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=192033</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/gijs-smal-and-celtics-transfer-search-for-a-quality-left-back/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T16:59:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that Alexandro Bernabei has left Celtic on loan to Brazilian side SC Internacional, attention will turn to what the Bhoys plan to do with...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers gets into John Beaton issue again; more context on a "bigger worry"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=192030</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-gets-into-john-beaton-issue-again-with-more-context-on-a-bigger-worry/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T15:57:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has provided more context to his comments about John Beaton after last week’s defeat to Hearts at Tynecastle. Rodgers blasted the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic injuries and suspensions open the door for 2 Academy talents vs Livingston]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=192025</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/celtic-injuries-and-suspensions-open-the-door-for-2-academy-talents-vs-livingston/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T15:12:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After an injury to Callum McGregor ruled him out of the Celtic trip to Hearts last week, two further players have dropped out of contention...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Bhoys star left baffled by Brendan Rodgers decision; raises Celtic title run-in concern]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=192022</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-left-baffled-by-brendan-rodgers-call-as-he-raises-celtic-title-run-in-concern/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T14:28:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton has raised concerns about Celtic’s squad depth heading into the latter stages of the season after developments this week. The Bhoys have allowed...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: ‘THERE IS ENOUGH STUPIDITY AT THE SFA TO START A NEW COUNTRY’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=118364</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-there-is-enough-stupidity-at-the-sfa-to-start-a-new-country/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T12:20:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWAY from intrusive television cameras and pesky microphones, I have often heard managers speak about the qualities of those in power at the SFA. One prominent team boss often insisted: “There is enough stupidity at the SFA to start a new country.” These were the days when an off-the-record comment remained unseen and unheard. Undoubtedly, back [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not a gimmie]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=118360</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/its-not-a-gimmie/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T12:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If your think this is a gimmie, think again.  This is a cup. You and I have seen Morton (bottom of the championship at the time), Partick, Falkirk, the Highlanders and more come to our Holy Ground and win. We’ll need our game face on, or ‘the best gram for gram’ manager in the league [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE KELLY CONUNDRUM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=118359</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-kelly-conundrum/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T10:20:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DANIEL KELLY is standing by for his first Celtic start in the Scottish Cup quarter-final tie against Livingston at Parkhead tomorrow afternoon. The 18-year-old midfielder has had a meteoric rise at the champions since coming on as a late substitute in the 5-0 romp against Buckie Thistle in the previous round in January. The powerhouse [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘MADNESS,’ SUTTON QUERIES CELTIC DECISION]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=118357</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/madness-sutton-queries-celtic-decision/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T09:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic goal hero Chris Sutton has branded his old club’s decision to allow Alexandro Bernabei to leave on loan as “madness”. The Argentinian defender completed a temporary transfer to Brazilian top-flight club SC Nacional until the end of the year, as CQN reported yesterday. Bernabei’s exit leaves the champions without cover for Greg Taylor as [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘ABSOLUTELY NO WAY ON THIS EARTH THAT IT’S A PENALTY,’ RODGERS RAMPS UP SFA ROW]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=118354</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/absolutely-no-way-on-this-earth-that-its-a-penalty-rodgers-ramps-up-sfa-row/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T08:48:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has ramped up the tension ahead of his appearance at Hampden on March 28. The Celtic boss, of course, has been summoned by the SFA to explain his remarks following the champions’ controversial 2-0 loss to Hearts at Tynecastle last weekend. The encounter was peppered with perplexing decisions from referee Don Robertson after bizarre [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart, Alistair Johnston, Liam Scales and more react to Liel Abada's Celtic exit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=192015</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/joe-hart-alistair-johnston-liam-scales-and-more-react-to-liel-abada-leaving-celtic-for-charlotte-fc/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T18:54:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liel Abada has become the latest member of Celtic’s successful trophy-winning squad to leave the club and head elsewhere. The Bhoys have said goodbye to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer upheaval predicted at Celtic as former Bhoys star points finger at the board]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=192010</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/transfer-upheaval-predicted-at-celtic-as-former-bhoys-star-points-finger-at-the-board/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T17:20:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s fair to say that the two transfer windows following Brendan Rodgers’ return to Celtic were underwhelming for plenty of supporters. In a position of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dean Smith left buzzing with Celtic deal as Rodgers makes it clear Bhoys miss out on "asset age"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=192005</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/dean-smith-left-buzzing-with-celtic-deal-as-brendan-rodgers-makes-it-clear-bhoys-miss-out-on-asset-age/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T16:47:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Charlotte FC head coach Dean Smith has been talking up his club’s move for Liel Abada as Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers laments his exit. Abada...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liam Scales sums up Celtic dressing room reaction to costly Tynecastle controversy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=192002</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/liam-scales-sums-up-celtic-dressing-room-reaction-to-costly-tynecastle-controversy/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T16:17:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Liam Scales has been left confused about the application of the handball rule in Scottish football after a controversial 90 minutes at Tynecastle last...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers breaks Celtic silence on Alexandro Bernabei situation and left-back depth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191998</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-breaks-celtic-silence-on-alexandro-bernabei-situation-and-left-back-depth/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T15:36:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Left-back Alexandro Bernabei has left Celtic on loan to Brazilian side SC Internacional until the end of their 2024 season. There’s been no word of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DEFIANT RODGERS TELLS SFA: ‘WE WILL DEFEND IT VIGOROUSLY’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=118348</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/defiant-rodgers-tells-sfa-we-will-defend-it-vigorously/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T15:13:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS remains defiant after his comments over the incompetence of match officals in the controversial 2-0 loss to Hearts at Tynecastle at the weekend. The Celtic manager insists he has no regrets over remarks about the alarming performances of referee Don Robertson and VAR assistant John Beaton after the champions had been on the receiving [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic suffer new pre-Livingston injury blow; Rodgers also provides McGregor scan update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191994</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-gives-update-on-callum-mcgregor-after-celtic-scan-luis-palma-injury-issue/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T15:03:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has been discussing the status of Callum McGregor after the midfielder missed last week’s match against Hearts. The Bhoys captain missed...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers publicly challenges what the SFA have told Celtic about recent controversy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191991</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-publicly-challenges-what-the-sfa-have-told-celtic-about-recent-controversy/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T14:33:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers isn’t backing down in his war of words with the Scottish FA, insisting their report on the red card given to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Livingston boss David Martindale makes candid admission ahead of Celtic Park trip]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191984</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/livingston-boss-david-martindale-makes-candid-admission-ahead-of-celtic-park-trip/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T14:06:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Livingston manager David Martindale says this weekend’s Scottish Cup trip to Celtic Park is a distraction for his team and that he’d prefer to be...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Departing star speaks out on "personal challenge" at Celtic; record fee and details]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191979</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/liel-abada-speaks-out-on-personal-challenge-at-celtic-after-exit-record-fee-and-details/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T13:34:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liel Abada has sent a lengthy goodbye message to Celtic and the club’s supporters after a big-money exit to Major League Soccer side Charlotte FC....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Abada, ability, discretion, memories]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=118310</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/abada-ability-discretion-memories/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T12:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In leaving the club yesterday to continue his career in the MLS, Liel Adaba closed the door on so much for us. There are memories to cherish.  That 10-man 89th minute winner against Dundee United, which made it positive for us to go top of the league next time out, for the first time under [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: £3.75m MISFIT’S 8-MONTH DEAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=118306</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-3-75m-misfits-8-month-deal/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T08:58:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S £3.75m misfit Alexandro Bernabei has completed his loan deal to Brazilian top-flight side SC Internacional. The Argentinian left-back made just 28 appearances in 18 months for the champions after his big-money switch from Lanus in the summer of 2022 and has been offloaded by Brendan Rodgers, as CQN forecast earlier in the week. Bernabei has failed [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘JINXED’ TILIO IN NEW SETBACK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=118305</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/jinxed-tilio-in-new-setback/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T08:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MARCO TILIO has suffered another setback as his dream season turns into a nightmare. The Australian international joined Celtic in a £2million five-year deal from Melbourne City in June, but the 22-year-old winger was sidelined shortly after his arrival when it was discovered he had sustained a torn quad thigh muscle. Tilio was out of the first-team [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STAND BY FOR CELTIC CLEAR-OUT, WARNS EX-HOOPS HERO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=118303</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/stand-by-for-celtic-clear-out-warns-ex-hoops-hero/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T07:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is preparing for a massive Celtic clear-out in the summer. That is the view of former Hoops hero Alan Stubbs who believes changes are inevitable following season in which the champions have stumbled several times to concede the prized pole position in the Premiership. Rodgers has seen his side blow a seven-point adavantage [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ABADA IN EMOTIONAL FAREWELL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=118299</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/abada-in-emotional-farewell/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T21:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIEL ABADA signed off his Celtic career with an emotional farewell after his £8million move to MLS outfit Charlotte FC was confirmed. The 22-year-old Israel international winger made an instant impact when he joined the Hoops in July 2021 and scored the first goal in Ange Postecoglou’s reign. Abada flashed one into the FC Midtjylland net [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Lambert opens up on 'special' Celtic occasion as European giants set to arrive at Parkhead]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191969</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/paul-lambert-opens-up-on-special-celtic-occasion-as-european-giants-set-to-arrive-at-parkhead/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T21:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are currently locked in a battle to try and win a domestic double in Brendan Rodgers’ first campaign back at the club. Since returning...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£8m ABADA SEALS DEAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=118298</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/8m-abada-seals-deal/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T21:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIEL ABADA has sealed his £8million switch from Celtic to MLS outfit Charlotte FC. The 22-year-old Israeli international winger has been missing from recent Hoops squads with boss Brendan Rodgers stating the player was not mentally attuned. In September, Abada signed an extension to keep him at the champions until 2027, but the player, bought by Ange [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I was close': Former Celtic boss Neil Lennon shares the real reason he didn't get the Republic of Ireland job]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191950</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-boss-neil-lennon-shares-the-real-reason-he-missed-out-on-the-republic-of-ireland-job/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T20:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon is clearly looking to get back into football management as the former Celtic boss recently detailed his interest in the Aberdeen job. We...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen McGinn shares how he really thinks Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers' SFA hearing will go]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191976</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/stephen-mcginn-shares-how-he-really-thinks-celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-sfa-hearing-will-go/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T20:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have endured a controversial few days in the wake of last Sunday’s defeat away to Heart of Midlothian that has created a storm surrounding...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Obviously’: Barry Bannan shares who he thinks is going to win the title - Celtic or Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191947</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/barry-bannan-shares-who-he-thinks-is-going-to-win-the-scottish-title-celtic-or-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The defeats suffered by Celtic and Rangers last weekend have opened up a huge debate amongst pundits and former players about who they think will...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three surprise changes Brendan Rodgers could make to reshuffle his Celtic side vs Livingston]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191954</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/three-surprise-changes-brendan-rodgers-could-make-to-reshuffle-his-celtic-side-vs-livingston/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic face Livingston this weekend in the quarter-final of the Scottish Cup as Brendan Rodgers’ men look to book a place at Hampden for the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘My view’: SPFL manager shares what he really thinks about the SFA’s decision on Celtic’s red card appeal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191942</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ian-mccall-shares-what-he-really-thinks-about-the-sfas-decision-on-celtics-red-card-appeal/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Celtic privately seething about the SFA’s decision not to overturn Hyunjun Yang’s red card, the manager now needs to plan for the next three...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['A joke'... Peter Grant hints Hearts man was lucky not to see red in Celtic's Tynecastle defeat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191965</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/a-joke-peter-grant-hints-hearts-man-was-lucky-not-to-see-red-in-celtics-tynecastle-defeat/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans will be keen to move on from a frustrating 2-0 loss to Heart of Midlothian last weekend that has dominated headlines due to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Honestly’: Alan Brazil shares how he really felt after what he saw at Celtic vs Hearts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191935</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/honestly-alan-brazil-shares-how-he-really-felt-after-what-he-saw-at-celtic-vs-hearts/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a big Scottish Cup fixture coming up this weekend but the headlines are still dominated by what went on at Hearts last Sunday....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic ratify Alexandro Bernabei loan departure; remaining left-back options come to light]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191972</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-ratify-alexandro-bernabei-loan-departure-remaining-left-back-options-come-to-light/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T16:56:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers is continuing his squad cull mission at Parkhead as he aims to streamline the squad. In January, David Turnbull, Mikey Johnston...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WAIT FOR IT: CUP SEMI-FINAL DRAW DELAY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=118295</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/wait-for-it-cup-semi-final-draw-delay/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T13:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC will face a delay of over 24 hours to discover their Scottish Cup semi-final opponents – if, of course, the holders avert disaster in Sunday afternoon’s last-eight tie against Livingston at Parkhead. Brendan Rodgers is chasing a league and Cup double on his return to the champions and he is determined to lead the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Brendan Rodgers SFA hearing can’t be fast-tracked as Celtic boss faces Ibrox ban]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191938</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/why-brendan-rodgers-sfa-hearing-cant-be-fast-tracked-as-celtic-boss-faces-ibrox-ban/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The news that Brendan Rodgers now faces an SFA charge for what he said about John Beaton’s VAR performance at Hearts is one that could...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant says Celtic man deserves major credit for performances since return to line-up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191931</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/peter-grant-says-celtic-man-deserves-major-credit-for-performances-since-return-to-line-up/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have endured an up and down last few weeks as they aim to keep pace in their battle to win the Scottish Premiership title....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘The biggest problem’: Peter Grant shares major referee dilemma after Celtic’s VAR controversy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191929</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/peter-grant-shares-the-biggest-problem-with-referees-after-celtics-var-controversy/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant is in no doubt that there is a huge issue with referees that must be addressed after watching Celtic’s VAR controversy at Hearts...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic boss Neil Lennon interested in Scottish Premiership return, hits back at perceptions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191926</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ex-celtic-boss-neil-lennon-interested-in-scottish-premiership-return-hits-back-at-perceptions/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic boss Neil Lennon is on the lookout for a new challenge as he bids to open the next chapter of his colourful managerial...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SFA: officials and administrators out of their depth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=118294</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/sfa-officials-and-administrators-out-of-their-depth/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T12:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t mention John Beaton’s name, apparently.  Referees and VARs are not open to scrutiny.  Brendan Rodgers did not say Beaton was corrupt, he did not say Sunday’s VAR was fond of celebrating at hostelries hostile to Celtic, he simply called out what he saw was “poor officiating”. As a consequence, Brendan faces an SFA disciplinary [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC DUO ON COLLISION COURSE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=118290</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-duo-on-collision-course/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T11:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC loan stars Mikey Johnston and Sead Haksabanovic are on a collision course next month. The Republic of Ireland international winger is tearing up the English Championship with some eye-catching displays and goals since joining West Brom on a temporary transfer in January. Johnston took centre stage again last night when he thumped in a [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Livingston hero sends defiant message on their chances of claiming shock result against Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191917</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/livingston-hero-sends-defiant-message-on-their-chances-of-claiming-shock-result-against-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic take a break from league duty this weekend as they lay the groundwork in training to face Livingston in the Scottish Cup quarter-final. Brendan...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXPLAIN YOURSELVES: CELTIC LEGEND’S MESSAGE TO SFA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=118276</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/explain-yourselves-celtic-legends-message-to-sfa/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T09:50:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic hero Peter Grant reckons the SFA should be explaining themselves to Brendan Rodgers and not the other way around. The Hoops boss has been hit with a notice of complaint by the Scottish football rulers and will be hauled to Hampden in three weeks’ time following his criticims of the officials in the champions’ [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I can see why': Jordan Pickford says he knows why Celtic fans love £15k-a-week player]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191919</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/jordan-pickford-says-he-can-see-why-celtic-fans-love-joe-hart/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T09:43:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[England international goalkeeper, Jordan Pickford, has shared how he really feels about Celtic favourite, Joe Hart. Hart announced his intention to retire at the end...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon drops Celtic title verdict as he thinks one quality is required above all to prevail]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191914</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/neil-lennon-drops-celtic-title-verdict-as-he-thinks-one-quality-is-required-above-all-to-prevail/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic take a break from Scottish Premiership duty this weekend as they prepare to take on Livingston in the Scottish Cup quarter-final. The Bhoys face...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports pundit says Celtic target would be a 'very attractive' transfer option this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191909</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/sky-sports-pundit-says-celtic-target-would-be-a-very-attractive-transfer-option-this-summer/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers will be keen to ensure he adequately strengthens his player pool once the summer transfer window gets underway. Despite the Scottish...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: BREAKING NEWS: MAN LANDS ON MOON]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=118273</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-breaking-news-man-lands-on-moon/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T08:21:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE Scottish football rulers will be delighted to know John Logie Baird has perfected the transmission of moving images of people on a screen. The invention is to be known as broadcast television. Charles Dickens has also completed the final draft of ‘A Christmas Carol‘, slavery has been abolished in the United States and man [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Really harsh': Stephen McGinn says Celtic have a B team player who is much better than Alexandro Bernabei]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191906</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/stephen-mcginn-says-celtic-have-a-b-team-player-who-is-much-better-than-alexandro-bernabei/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pundit, Stephen McGinn, has said that Celtic have a youth player who he believes is much better than Alexandro Bernabei. The Argentine defender has really...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Disgusted’: Peter Grant doesn’t hold back when he hears the latest Celtic update from the SFA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191902</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/peter-grant-disgusted-after-hearing-the-latest-celtic-update-from-the-sfa/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T07:44:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic red card furore rumbles on as Peter Grant lets the SFA have it both barrels after hearing the latest update from the games’...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['A real star': Sky Sports pundit suggests Celtic have a quality player out on loan right now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191791</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/sky-sports-pundit-suggests-celtic-have-a-real-star-out-on-loan-right-now/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T20:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a plethora of players out on loan from the club right now. With such a huge squad depth and competition for first-team places...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gordon Dalziel thinks Brendan Rodgers has a worrying lack of depth in crucial position at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191899</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/gordon-dalziel-thinks-brendan-rodgers-has-a-worrying-lack-of-depth-in-crucial-position-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T20:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s strength in depth has been questioned this campaign amid a spate of injury problems alongside varying levels of impact from some of their newer...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I think': John Hartson believes Brendan Rodgers will bench 'outstanding' player for Celtic's next match]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191875</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/john-hartson-believes-brendan-rodgers-will-bench-outstanding-player-for-celtics-next-match/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Hartson has made a huge call regarding one of Celtic’s best players for the upcoming Scottish Cup match against Livingston. Celtic still have a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic man John Hartson is fuming at matter that is 'completely spoiling' the Scottish game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191896</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ex-celtic-man-john-hartson-is-fuming-at-matter-that-is-completely-spoiling-the-scottish-game/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been in the middle of a controversy over the last few days following their indecent-ridden 2-0 defeat to Heart of Midlothian last weekend....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Come on’: John Hartson delivers a superb answer as he berates radio presenter’s ‘daft’ Celtic question]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191871</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/john-hartson-delivers-a-superb-answer-as-he-berates-radio-presenters-daft-celtic-question/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The pressure to win the Scottish Premiership is really ramping up and as both Celtic and Rangers suffered defeats this weekend, it really is a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I think'... Kenny Miller issues surprising verdict on Hyunjun Yang's red card in Celtic defeat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191884</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-think-kenny-miller-issues-surprising-verdict-on-hyunjun-yangs-red-card-in-celtic-defeat/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been at the centre of the latest VAR controversy in Scottish football following their 2-0 defeat to Heart of Midlothian last weekend. As...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Definitely’: Ally McCoist shares interesting title prediction after Celtic and Rangers dropped points]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191844</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ally-mccoist-shares-interesting-title-prediction-after-celtic-and-rangers-dropped-points/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ally McCoist has shared his thoughts on how the race for the Scottish Premiership is likely to go after watching Celtic and Rangers drop points...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston sheds honest light on how Celtic players distract themselves from title battle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191869</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alistair-johnston-sheds-honest-light-on-how-celtic-players-distract-themselves-from-title-battle/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are in a battle for the Scottish Premiership crown that could go to the wire over the coming months. The Bhoys sit two points...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[English club have now expressed strong interest in Celtic forward; fee details emerge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191893</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/english-club-have-now-expressed-strong-interest-in-celtic-forward-fee-details-emerge/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T15:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have struggled to retain prodigious talent over recent years amid the lure of first-team opportunities for youngsters elsewhere. Brendan Rodgers has made a point...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Completed': Celtic exit nears as player finalises medical ahead of £10m move - journalist]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191888</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-exit-nears-as-player-completes-medical-ahead-of-10m-move/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T14:21:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Liel Abada story at Celtic edges closer to its conclusion this afternoon as the Israeli winger completes his medical ahead of a £10m move...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BYE, BYE BERNABEI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=118271</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/bye-bye-bernabei/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T14:04:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S £3.75million misfit Alexandro Bernabei is heading for a quickfire exit from the champions. The Argentinian defender, who was bought by Ange Postecoglou from top-flight outfit Lanus in the summer of 2022, looks to be on his way back to South America. Bernabei, who made just four starts in his nine appearances for the Hoops since [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I think I did': Ange Postecoglou makes claim about what he believes he achieved at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191794</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-makes-claim-about-what-he-believes-he-achieved-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has spoken out about his time at Celtic and said he believes he made a ‘real impact’ in Scotland during his two seasons...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Livingston goalkeeper Shamal George issues verdict on side's chances of cup upset against Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191846</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/livingston-goalkeeper-shamal-george-issues-verdict-on-sides-chances-of-cup-upset-against-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic return to Scottish Cup action this Sunday and can progress to the last four of the competition if they defeat Livingston at Parkhead. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘To be honest’: Alan Shearer admits he’s shocked at what Chris Sutton has done since leaving Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191862</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alan-shearer-admits-hes-shocked-at-what-chris-sutton-has-done-since-leaving-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T12:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a number of players leave the club and go on and have pretty mundane careers. But not Chris Sutton. The former Celtic hero...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Journalist claims that Alexandro Bernabei is on his way out of Celtic in surprise transfer update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191859</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/journalist-claims-that-alexandro-bernabei-is-on-his-way-out-of-celtic-in-surprise-transfer-update/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T12:18:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic look to be continuing a trend of filtering down Brendan Rodgers’ squad despite the transfer window in Scotland being closed for business. In light...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic left speechless by the outcome of SFA appeal, explanation timeline emerges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191855</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-left-speechless-by-the-outcome-of-sfa-appeal-explanation-timeline-emerges/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been left to lick their wounds following a dramatic 2-0 defeat away to Heart of Midlothian last weekend. Of course, controversy surrounding the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Predictable SFA back their team]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=118256</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/predictable-sfa-back-their-team/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T12:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As predicted yesterday, the SFA appeals process rejected Celtic’s application to have Yang’s red card, awarded at Tynecastle on Sunday, rescinded.  The merits of the case can be set aside.  The SFA were being asked to consider whether one of their senior referees intervened unfairly in a manner which changed which team was top of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OH, WHAT CAN THE MATTER BE?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=118257</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/oh-what-can-the-matter-be/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T10:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OH HYEON-GYU is in danger of becoming Celtic’s forgotten man after a dramatic fade from the first-team picture. The South Korean striker has rarely figured since returning from the Asian Cup in Qatar last month. Brendan Rodgers overlooked the powerful frontman for his squads in the 2-0 loss at Hearts and the 7-1 win over [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen McGowan issues damning verdict on what hindered Celtic in Tynecastle defeat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191839</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/stephen-mcgowan-issues-damning-verdict-on-what-hindered-celtic-in-tynecastle-defeat/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic suffered a 2-0 defeat away to Heart of Midlothian last weekend in a fixture that served up its fair share of controversy. Brendan Rodgers...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Never’: Barry Ferguson's strange Celtic player claim; completely misses the point over VAR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191829</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/barry-fergusons-strange-hyunjun-yang-celtic-penalty-claim-completely-misses-the-point-over-var/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T09:43:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic discovered the outcome of Hyunjun Yang’s red card penalty appeal last night, Brendan Rodgers is now going to be without his winger for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pundit says Celtic target is 'very unlikely' to sign a new deal, could be a free agent in summer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191834</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/pundit-says-celtic-target-is-very-unlikely-to-sign-a-new-deal-could-be-a-free-agent-in-summer/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers is likely to have one eye on potential summer transfer activity despite his side’s ongoing battle for the Scottish Premiership title....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘ANYTHING IS POSSIBLE,’ JOHNSTON’S FIGHTING TALK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=118242</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/anything-is-possible-johnstons-fighting-talk/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T08:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ALISTAIR JOHNSTON insists “anything is possible” as Celtic prepare for a gruelling run-in to rollercoaster campaign. The Hoops still have eyes on retaining their league title and Scottish Cup in the countdown to the season’s finale on the iconic date of May 25, scheduled for the national competition soccer showpiece at Hampden. Brendan Rodgers’ side [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Wait a minute’: Ally McCoist can't believe what Alan Brazil has said about Celtic’s Tynecastle referee]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191832</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ally-mccoist-cant-believe-what-alan-brazil-has-said-about-celtics-tynecastle-referee/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T08:39:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the Celtic VAR contoversy continues this week, Brendan Rodgers is coming to terms with losing his appeal on Hyunjun Yang’s red card and dealing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic man Alan Stubbs says one side are 'slight favourites' for Scottish Premiership title]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191821</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ex-celtic-man-alan-stubbs-says-one-side-are-slight-favourites-for-scottish-premiership-title/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic know that they are in a battle for the Scottish Premiership title that could go to the wire under Brendan Rodgers. With nine games...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Interesting’: Alistair Johnston reacts to a rumour he’s just heard about the Celtic dressing room]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=191824</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alistair-johnston-reacts-to-an-interesting-rumour-about-the-celtic-dressing-room/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T07:42:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston has reacted after being told about a rumour about the Celtic Park dressing room that’s been doing the rounds. The Canadian right-back looks...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘CULPRIT’ COCHRANE’S CELTIC RED-CARD HISTORY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=118240</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/culprit-cochranes-celtic-red-card-history/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T07:35:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IN THE midst of all the furore surrounding Celtic’s controversial 2-0 setback against Hearts at Tynecastle on Sunday, one significant factor has been overlooked. Alex Cochrane was the man at the centre of the bewildering sending-off storm that saw winger Yang Hyun-jun dismissed in the 14th minute following an equally-baffling VAR intervention. No-one mentioned that [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic want to sign £4 million-rated player in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45945</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-4-million-player-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T23:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The defeat at the hands of Lazio was further proof of Celtic’s need to strengthen in the January transfer window. The club might have brought in nine new faces in the summer but a lot of people feel that the team has taken a step back since last season, when they breezed past the competition […]
Celtic want to sign £4 million-rated player in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers sends clear message Celtic board must not ignore]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45941</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/brendan-rodgers-message-celtic-board/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T21:35:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s fate in Europe for this season is sealed after their 2-0 defeat at the hands of Lazio. The result means that the Hoops are guaranteed to finish bottom of their group in the UEFA Champions League. That also means that they will not be dropping down to the Europa League, something that should have […]
Brendan Rodgers sends clear message Celtic board must not ignore - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton publicly criticises Celtic after loss to Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45938</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/chris-sutton-celtic-loss-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T20:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic lost 2-0 away in Rome to Lazio. The Hoops were in the match for a long time before Ciro Immobile came off the bench to score a brace and put the game to bed. The result means that not only are Brendan Rodgers’ side out of the Champions League following the group stages but […]
Chris Sutton publicly criticises Celtic after loss to Lazio - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed £7 million Jeremie Frimpong windfall news]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45933</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-jeremie-frimpong-windfall-news/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremie Frimpong’s rise at Bayer Leverkusen has been fascinating, to say the least. The Dutchman had shown a lot of quality going forward at Celtic as well but not many could have foreseen him becoming one of the most prolific wingbacks in Europe just a few years later. That is exactly what has happened under […]
Celtic handed £7 million Jeremie Frimpong windfall news - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic told 29-goal striker is good enough amid links]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45930</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-told-29-goal-striker-good-enough/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T13:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to add to their options up top this January. Kyogo has done well once again but he is not scoring as frequently as he was last season. On the other hand, Oh Hyeon-gyu has been inconsistent as well and is not at the level required to start for the Hoops right now. There […]
Celtic told 29-goal striker is good enough amid links - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anderlecht consider making offer for Celtic standout in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45927</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/anderlecht-offer-celtic-standout-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T11:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have not had the greatest campaign till now. They were eliminated early from the Scottish League Cup and while they do lead the Premiership, their performances and results have been somewhat inconsistent. Almost half a season on, it feels like the Hoops are still finding their feet under the management of Brendan Rodgers and […]
Anderlecht consider making offer for Celtic standout in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serie A club want to sign Celtic player amid contract worry]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45907</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/serie-club-want-celtic-player-contract/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T22:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic fans hope for more quality players arriving there could be a problem with others heading for the exit door. It seems pretty clear that Brendan Rodgers wants to make the size of the squad more manageable over the next couple of transfer windows and departures are expected. But there is a risk of […]
Serie A club want to sign Celtic player amid contract worry - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur step up bid to sign Celtic-linked player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45918</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/tottenham-hotspur-bid-sign-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur made a fantastic start to the season under the management of Ange Postecoglou. With Harry Kane leaving the club in the summer for Bayern Munich, most expected them to struggle. Instead, they appeared to be putting up an unlikely title challenge and were sitting atop the Premier League table not too long ago. […]
Tottenham Hotspur step up bid to sign Celtic-linked player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boost in race to sign £11 million Real Madrid player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45914</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/celtic-boost-real-madrid-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to sign a goalkeeper in the near future. It is quite clear that Joe Hart is not the long-term solution between the posts. The Englishman’s performances have been criticised lately. Also, he is set to turn 37 years of age before this season comes to an end. So, while he has done a […]
Celtic boost in race to sign £11 million Real Madrid player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio boss Maurizio Sarri makes fantastic Celtic claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45910</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/lazio-boss-maurizio-sarri-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T18:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By now, Celtic fans have accepted that Brendan Rodgers’ side are most probably not going through or even finishing third in their group in the UEFA Champions League. It would be a positive step to get a win in the competition though. It has been quite some time since the Hoops won at this level. […]
Lazio boss Maurizio Sarri makes fantastic Celtic claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic tipped to go for 28-year-old Premiership striker]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45904</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/celtic-tipped-go-premiership-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T12:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans breathed a sigh of relief as the Rangers dropped points at the weekend against Aberdeen. In fact, it took a late penalty for them to even come out with a draw from the game. That means that the Hoops will maintain their strong position at the top of the Scottish Premiership table. That […]
Celtic tipped to go for 28-year-old Premiership striker - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£7.5 million Mathias Kvistgaarden to Celtic transfer update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45900</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/mathias-kvistgaarden-celtic-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T10:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to sign a striker in January. On one hand, we have seen the club struggle for goals in some games this season. When the opposition puts up a resolute defence, the Hoops do not appear to have a lot of answers other than Kyogo, Matt O’Riley or Luis Palma. On the other hand, […]
£7.5 million Mathias Kvistgaarden to Celtic transfer update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur have been eyeing Celtic superstar]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45896</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/tottenham-hotspur-eyeing-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T23:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou made the move to Tottenham Hotspur in the summer and it was only a matter of time before the Australian was linked with a reunion with some Celtic players. The manager enjoyed a lot of success at Parkhead, even though he was at the club for just two seasons, and won five trophies […]
Tottenham Hotspur have been eyeing Celtic superstar - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John McGinn claims he spoke to Celtic players about manager]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45890</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/john-mcginn-spoke-celtic-players/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T21:35:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most Celtic fans will remember how the club missed out on the opportunity to sign John McGinn some years back. The Scot grew up supporting the Hoops but a move to Parkhead failed to materialise even though it had looked close and he ended up moving down south to join Aston Villa. McGinn has risen […]
John McGinn claims he spoke to Celtic players about manager - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic must consider signing striker from Premiership rivals]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45886</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-signing-striker-premiership-rivals/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T20:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there is one position where Celtic need to strengthen during the upcoming January transfer window, it is striker. The Hoops have been pretty inconsistent in front of goal this season so far. Of course, there are games when they can go out and score six times. But then, on days they are having a […]
Celtic must consider signing striker from Premiership rivals - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend takes dig at Rangers player for diving]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45884</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-legend-rangers-player-diving/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T18:35:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Celtic drew 1-1 against Motherwell, the Rangers were handed a major chance to get back into the title race. All they needed to do was win their games in hand and they would be just three points behind the Hoops in the league table. We have seen the Ibrox side not perform at their […]
Celtic legend takes dig at Rangers player for diving - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player criticised after draw against Motherwell]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45881</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-player-criticised-draw-motherwell/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T12:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Titles are not decided this early in the season. That has been proven once again. Not too long ago, Celtic were sitting seven points clear at the top of the Premiership table and most fans felt that the league was pretty much in the bag with the Rangers struggling for any kind of form.  It […]
Celtic player criticised after draw against Motherwell - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgio Chiellini makes superb claim about Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45874</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/giorgio-chiellini-claim-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T10:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Giorgio Chiellini is one of the best defenders of all time and he had some pretty positive comments about Celtic Park recently. The 39-year-old spent the majority of his career playing for Juventus and won more silverware there than one should try to count. Overall, he made more […]
Giorgio Chiellini makes superb claim about Celtic Park - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s problem is very clear and needs solving quick]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45870</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/celtic-problem-needs-solving-quick/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T19:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two more dropped points mean that Celtic have well and truly allowed the Rangers to get back into the title race. A lead which once stood at seven points, could be reduced to three if Philippe Clement’s side are able to win their games in hand. And the sad thing is that the Hoops have […]
Celtic’s problem is very clear and needs solving quick - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic problem after draw]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45866</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/brendan-rodgers-celtic-problem-draw/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T18:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was not the result Celtic were looking for, as they dropped two valuable points against Motherwell. David Turnbull’s goal appeared to have won it for the Hoops but the visitors equalised in the 90th minute and it ended 1-1. That means that if the Rangers win their games in hand, the gap will be […]
Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic problem after draw - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hollywood superstar pictured wearing Celtic jersey]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45861</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/hollywood-pictured-wearing-celtic-jersey/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T12:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Celtic have their fair share of famous fans. Rod Stewart is the first name that comes to most people’s minds, one of the best-selling music artists in history. Lewis Capaldi is another popular musician known to support the Hoops. And several A-list celebrities like Gerard Butler, Snoop Dogg, […]
Hollywood superstar pictured wearing Celtic jersey - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic pushing for priority signing in January window]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45859</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/celtic-priority-signing-january-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T09:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s January transfer window is expected to be a busy one. The club might have made nine signings in the summer, seven arriving on a permanent basis and two on loan, but there are still holes in Brendan Rodgers’ squad that need to be filled. On the other hand, there are way too many players […]
Celtic pushing for priority signing in January window - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable source offers Sydney van Hooijdonk to Celtic update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45854</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/reliable-sydney-van-hooijdonk-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T22:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are believed to be on the lookout for a striker in the January transfer window. There might be a few reasons behind that. Firstly, both Kyogo and Oh Hyeon-gyu might be unavailable for a considerable length of time early next year due to the AFC Asian Cup. They are the club’s two options to […]
Reliable source offers Sydney van Hooijdonk to Celtic update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou claims Celtic success gets dismissed]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45852</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/ange-postecoglou-claims-celtic-success/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T21:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has proven to be a major success in the Premier League since swapping Celtic for Tottenham Hotspur. Of course, a lot of fans were not happy to see him depart after just two years at Parkhead. But he has been very respectful about the club even after leaving. And it is hard not […]
Ange Postecoglou claims Celtic success gets dismissed - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>