<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-07-18T04:12:26.732Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[€20 million Tete drops hint amid Celtic transfer rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42688</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/17/tete-drops-hint-celtic-transfer-rumours/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T22:35:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers looks set to have a busy week at Celtic. The pre-season matches in Japan are set to take place and the Hoops have already landed in the Land of the Rising Sun. The club are expected to have a couple of new signings joining soon too, in the form of Yang Hyun-jun and […]
€20 million Tete drops hint amid Celtic transfer rumours - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New signing declares he will become Celtic’s best player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42700</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/17/new-signing-celtic-best-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T21:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There were concerns that Celtic might move away from the transfer policy that brought them so much success under the management of Ange Postecoglou, following the Australian’s departure and the arrival of Brendan Rodgers as his replacement in the Parkhead hot seat. Till now, that has not been the case though. This summer, Celtic have […]
New signing declares he will become Celtic’s best player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans get a glimpse of Champions League options as UEFA get the ball rolling]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167510</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-fans-get-a-glimpse-of-champions-league-options-as-uefa-get-the-ball-rolling/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T20:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Champions League group stage draw is still over six weeks away, but UEFA are clearly keen to get people talking. European football’s governing body have been pretty quiet about the group stage over the summer. But they got the ball rolling on Monday evening by posting the first graphic of the 26 teams who ...
The post Celtic fans get a glimpse of Champions League options as UEFA get the ball rolling appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The amusing side to Daizen Maeda as Yokohama star talks up Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167531</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-amusing-side-to-daizen-maeda-as-yokohama-star-talks-up-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the Celtic side look to settle and make themselves at home in Japan, the Japanese members of the squad will be looking forward to a return to their homeland and meet up with friends and family over the next few days. But Celtic’s Daizen Maeda has already met up with an old friend in ...
The post The amusing side to Daizen Maeda as Yokohama star talks up Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton backs up Premier League boss' Celtic take]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167478</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-backs-up-premier-league-boss-celtic-take/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton has stated on Twitter that West Ham United boss David Moyes is ‘spot on’ to suggest that new Tottenham boss Ange Postecoglou will ‘never get more pressure than he did managing Celtic’. The Treble-winning coach for the Bhoys is now experiencing life as a Premier League manager and taking to the dugout of ...
The post Chris Sutton backs up Premier League boss' Celtic take appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[View from Japan]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58097</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/view-from-japan/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T19:05:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic Soul Podcast returns as Celtic embark on a pre-season in Japan. Japan Times journalist Dan Orlowitz https://www.japantimes.co.jp/author/dan-orlowitz/ joins host Andrew Milne to get the view from Japan on Celtic’s upcoming friendlies Yokahama and Gamba Osaka.
The post View from Japan appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Reo Hatate stands during Celtic huddle comes to light]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42698</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/17/reo-hatate-stands-celtic-huddle/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T19:05:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The huddle is one of the most recognisable things about Celtic. Some might think that it has always been part of the fabric of the club but that is not the case. In fact, it became a tradition during the run of Tony Mowbray as the Hoops’ captain and has continued from there on forward. […]
Why Reo Hatate stands during Celtic huddle comes to light - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mikel Arteta expecting Arsenal exits as Celtic wait on Kieran Tierney situation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167518</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/mikel-artetas-transfer-comments-and-what-it-could-mean-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s apparent interest in Kieran Tierney has been well-documented over the last few weeks. In fact, the chatter about a possible return was fueled by Brendan Rodgers over the weekend as the Celtic manager addressed the rumours that the Arsenal full-back may be open to a Parkhead return. Obviously, the wages that Tierney currently commands ...
The post Mikel Arteta expecting Arsenal exits as Celtic wait on Kieran Tierney situation appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key Celtic stars seem captivated by Japan just hours after arriving]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167504</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/key-celtic-stars-seem-captivated-by-tokyo-just-hours-after-arriving/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic first-team squad arrived in Japan on Monday evening. Led by Brendan Rodgers, the team flew from Scotland to Japan at the start of a week-long tour. On Tuesday they will train at Yokohama F. Marinos’ Nissan Stadium before facing the reigning J1 League champions 24 hours later. The team will then travel around ...
The post Key Celtic stars seem captivated by Japan just hours after arriving appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports man confirms another Celtic summer signing]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42695</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/17/sky-sports-man-celtic-summer-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T17:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Ange Postecoglou left Celtic in order to join Tottenham Hotspur, it was viewed as a massive problem for the club. After all, the Australian had guided them to five trophies in two seasons despite arriving in tough circumstances. The Hoops went out and brought in the best replacement available though, as Brendan Rodgers was […]
Sky Sports man confirms another Celtic summer signing - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So Farewell Then……]]></title>
        <id>http://celticunderground.net/?p=6622</id>
        <link href="http://celticunderground.net/so-farewell-then/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T17:07:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you had said to me two months ago that Ange Postecoglu would be at Spurs and Brendan Rodgers would be manager again at Celtic, I (and every other Celtic fan that I know) would have said, “Aye, Very Good!!” Firstly, I assumed that even with the appointment of fellow Australian, Scott Nunn, Spurs would […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Critical Bill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£850,000 KWON’S ‘DREAM COME TRUE’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109947</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/850000-kwons-dream-come-true/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T16:42:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOUTH KOREAN Kwon Hyeok-kyu will cost £850,000 as he prepares for his switch to Celtic. The 22-year-old midfielder is poised to team up with countryman Yang Hyun-jun as soon as his transfer is rubber-stamped, probably later this week. Kwon and Yang will join their nation’s international striker Oh Hyeon-gyu at the treble winners as they prepare [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The reason why Celtic CEO Michael Nicholson stepped down from the SPFL board]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167498</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-reason-why-celtic-ceo-michael-nicholson-stepped-down-from-the-spfl-board/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Nicholson has stepped down from the board of the SPFL and been replaced by Rangers CEO James Bisgrove. The announcement was made this afternoon as the 42 member clubs of the SPFL elected a new board for the coming season ahead. [SPFL] What must be made clear is that there is no conspiracy regarding ...
The post The reason why Celtic CEO Michael Nicholson stepped down from the SPFL board appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic influence clear as SPFL announce new TV deals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167483</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-influence-clear-as-spfl-announce-new-tv-deals/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SPFL announced a new television deal that will continue its partnership with the BBC and international TV rights agency, Infront. [SPFL] Under the new agreement, BBC Scotland will see its current contract, which was due to expire in 2025, increased to 2029 which means it comes into line with the SPFL’s contract with Sky ...
The post Celtic influence clear as SPFL announce new TV deals appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The reason why Reo Hatate stands in the Celtic huddle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167456</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-reason-why-reo-hatate-stands-in-the-celtic-huddle/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate has answered a lot of questions since arriving at Celtic 18 months ago. The Japan international has been a revelation since his move from Kawasaki Frontale. He’s netted vital derby goals, produced moments of magic against Europe’s best and dazzled us with his close control and passing. But one less important matter has ...
The post The reason why Reo Hatate stands in the Celtic huddle appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic have a Japan plan for latest summer signings as amusing situation arises]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167476</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-have-a-japan-plan-for-latest-summer-signings-as-amusing-situation-arises/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are still to officially announce the signings of Hyun-jun Yang and Kwon Hyeok-kyu. Deals for the South Korean pair are done, with both of their current clubs confirming that the players would soon be off to Scotland. Both players have been in the Korean media too, speaking about their moves to the champions. That ...
The post Report: Celtic have a Japan plan for latest summer signings as amusing situation arises appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The fringe players continuing the pre-season journey with Celtic in Japan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167475</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-fringe-players-continuing-the-pre-season-journey-with-celtic-in-japan/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Japan Tour is one that is not only being met with excitement by the Japanese public but also the Celtic fans. Over the course of the next week, we will get the opportunity to see what will be a new-look Celtic under the tutelage of Brendan Rodgers. With new players like Odin Thago Holm ...
The post The fringe players continuing the pre-season journey with Celtic in Japan appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anti Celtic tactic suffers a blow as the SPFL approve pleasing new guidance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167468</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/anti-celtic-tactic-suffers-a-blow-as-the-spfl-approve-pleasing-new-guidance/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T13:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In some pleasing news for Celtic, the SPFL have approved a recommendation making the multi-ball system compulsory next season. The guidance will apply to Premiership clubs and was announced by the SPFL on Monday afternoon. Hidden away at the bottom of their statement it was revealed that clubs had voted “unanimously” to approve: “a recommendation ...
The post Anti Celtic tactic suffers a blow as the SPFL approve pleasing new guidance appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midfielder confirms he is set to join Celtic this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42691</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/17/midfielder-confirms-join-celtic-summer/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T13:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Things appear to be picking up pace for Celtic in the summer transfer window. The club got deals done for Odin Thiago Holm and Marco Tilio early. And after a slow few days, now it looks like they are closing in on a double announcement. It is believed that they have gotten a deal over […]
Midfielder confirms he is set to join Celtic this summer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bullet train and big stadium opportunities; Celtic announce finer Japan details]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167462</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/bullet-train-and-big-stadium-opportunities-celtic-announce-finer-japan-details/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T12:40:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have announced some of the finer details for the first-team’s week-long visit to Japan. The Hoops touched down in Tokyo on Monday, with a familiar green-and-white sight greeting them at Narita International Airport. Yokohama, the base for our first few days, is around an hours drive from the airport. As Celtic say in an ...
The post Bullet train and big stadium opportunities; Celtic announce finer Japan details appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 'amazing' ex-Celtic player that inspired Kwon Hyeok-kyu's football career]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167453</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-amazing-ex-celtic-player-that-inspired-kwon-hyeok-kyus-football-career/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic look set to confirm the capture of Korean midfielder, Kwon Hyeok-kyu, any day now. With reports claiming that a deal is done between Busan and Celtic, all we are waiting for, for now, is the official confirmation from the club. When the transfer speculation surrounding the 22-year-old defensive midfielder broke last week, the Celtic ...
The post The 'amazing' ex-Celtic player that inspired Kwon Hyeok-kyu's football career appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's Champions League reward will be felt strongly on Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167434</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-champions-league-reward-will-be-felt-strongly-on-wednesday/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few years ago, the thought of Celtic being able to saunter off to Japan in mid-July would have been about as unlikely as Brendan Rodgers returning as manager. This week, however, Rodgers will take his Celtic charges to Asia to play a couple of high-profile friendly matches. With Champions League group stage football already ...
The post Celtic's Champions League reward will be felt strongly on Wednesday appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic defender trials with SPFL side in search for a new club]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167441</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/efe-ambrose-trials-with-spfl-side-as-former-celtic-defender-searches-for-new-club/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What can you say about former Celtic defender, Efe Ambrose? A transfer deadline day capture by Neil Lennon in 2012, the Nigerian international enjoyed a trophy-laden five years at the club. The 34-year-old made 169 appearances for Celtic picking up four league titles, a Scottish Cup and a League Cup. He also won the African ...
The post Former Celtic defender trials with SPFL side in search for a new club appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demographics, Asia and Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109935</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/demographics-asia-and-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T11:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ask any group why Scotland produces so few great players now, compared to where we were as recently as the 1980s and you will get a familiar list of reasons.  Clubs no longer promote youth prospects at the same rate, facilities here have been overtaken by those in similar small countries and have been left [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic touch down in Japan and there's a familiar green-and-white sight]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167439</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-touch-down-in-japan-and-theres-a-familiar-green-and-white-sight/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T10:47:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have touched down in Japan ahead of an important week in our pre-season preparations. The first-team squad landed at Narita International Airport on Monday evening, Japanese time. The players will have flown around ten hours to Tokyo, and face a couple of high-profile friendly matches over the coming week. On Wednesday they face the ...
The post Celtic touch down in Japan and there's a familiar green-and-white sight appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nakamura question, Ibrox link, Brazilians; What to expect from Yokohama F. Marinos vs Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167419</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/nakamura-question-ibrox-link-brazilians-what-to-expect-from-yokohama-f-marinos-vs-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will play their first proper pre-season friendly on Wednesday against Yokohama F. Marinos. So far, the Hoops have faced Portuguese outfit Portimonense on two occasions with the latter clash receiving only moderate coverage from the club. But things will step up a gear this week as Brendan Rodgers‘ team face their first fixtures in ...
The post Nakamura question, Ibrox link, Brazilians; What to expect from Yokohama F. Marinos vs Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic at the Women's World Cup; FIFA tip two players to shine, fixture list, TV details]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167418</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-at-the-womens-world-cup-fifa-on-shen-mengyu-fixture-list-tv-details/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the Celtic first team’s pre-season training camp in Portugal and the upcoming Japan Tour grabbing all the headlines this week, it is easy to forget that there is other news surrounding the club coming up. Like the FIFA Women’s World Cup for example. The tournament is being jointly held in Australia and New Zealand ...
The post Celtic at the Women's World Cup; FIFA tip two players to shine, fixture list, TV details appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers makes Kieran Tierney to Celtic claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42685</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/17/brendan-rodgers-kieran-tierney-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T09:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rumours have suggested that Celtic could make one or more marquee signings this summer. That has led to them being linked with several big names in recent times. One that certainly falls under that category is that of Kieran Tierney. The left-back came through the ranks at Parkhead before making the move to Arsenal back […]
Brendan Rodgers makes Kieran Tierney to Celtic claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Early kick-offs, immense stadia, Celtic homecomings, TV; Japan details you need to know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167400</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/early-kick-offs-immense-stadia-celtic-homecomings-tv-japan-details-you-need-to-know/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will continue their preparations for the new season this week in Japan. Yes, it may have crept up on some of you, but the team are venturing over to Asia for some more training and a couple of relatively high-profile matches. Straight Champions League qualification has afforded the club the luxury of an Asian ...
The post Early kick-offs, immense stadia, Celtic homecomings, TV; Japan details you need to know appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EPL manager brilliantly talks up Celtic in pre-season press conference]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167401</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/david-moyes-brilliantly-talks-up-celtic-during-west-hams-promotional-press-conference/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans know exactly just how big our club is. There are Celtic supporters clubs all over the globe and when the club are on their travels in Europe, there is always a strong contingent of fans that will follow them wherever they go. But this is not new news to us. The scenes when ...
The post EPL manager brilliantly talks up Celtic in pre-season press conference appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TIERNEY: ‘WHO KNOWS WHAT MIGHT HAPPEN?’ ADMITS CELTIC BOSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109921</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/tierney-who-knows-what-might-happen-admits-celtic-boss/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T07:32:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has refused to close the door on a dramatic return to Celtic for Kieran Tierney. The former fans’ favourite has been linked with a Parkhead reunion alongside the returning manager after leaving for Arsenal in a £25million deal in the summer of 2018. However, the Scotland international left-back is on his way out [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS CLEAR-OUT ON WAY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109917</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-clear-out-on-way/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T06:46:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is ready to kick-start his Celtic clear-out as the new season looms into view. The Hoops boss has already spoken to some of the fringe players who will be heading for the Parkhead exit over the next six weeks. Rodgers is determined to streamline the numbers and has revealed he has already begun [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston is loving Celtic Wimbledon final moment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167394</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alistair-johnston-is-loving-celtic-wimbledon-final-moment/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T06:44:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re a lover of sport, and not just Celtic, then like me you were probably glued to Sunday’s engrossing five-set epic Wimbledon final between Novak Djokovic and champion Carlos Alcaraz. It was a magical afternoon and, like many major events around the world, a proud Celtic fan managed to find his way into the ...
The post Alistair Johnston is loving Celtic Wimbledon final moment appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers talks up Celtic's Champions League bonus]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167392</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-talks-up-celtics-champions-league-bonus/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T06:12:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers sounds like a man positively delighted he doesn’t have to face any UEFA Champions League qualifiers this summer, in stark contrast to his first spell at the club. Rodgers had to navigate the perilous summer European gauntlet in each of his seasons as Celtic boss and was successful on two occasions. ...
The post Brendan Rodgers talks up Celtic's Champions League bonus appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers ready to make Celtic cuts; honest discussions being held]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167386</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-ready-to-make-celtic-cuts-honest-discussions-being-held/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T05:41:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers is ready to trim some of the fat off the wider Celtic squad this summer after a period of assessment during pre-season training. As we discussed yesterday, there are multiple contenders to be moved on from the Bhoys before the end of the window before even big tough decisions have to be made. ...
The post Brendan Rodgers ready to make Celtic cuts; honest discussions being held appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…OLIVIER KAPO?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109912</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-olivier-kapo/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T05:15:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OLIVIER KAPO had enjoyed a colourful career – including a period with Italian giants Juventus – by the time he turned up at Celtic. The attacking midfielder spent a mere three months at Parkhead after arriving on a short-term contract following his release by Wigan in early November 2010. The Ivory Coast-born French international, at [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers left impressed by Celtic duo in Portugal as he discusses box office rumour]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167384</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-left-impressed-by-celtic-duo-in-portugal-as-he-discusses-box-office-rumour/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T05:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has admitted that the financials involved in a move for Kieran Tierney are difficult for Celtic, but hasn’t ruled out his return to the Bhoys. It was reported earlier this month that Tierney was open to a move back to Celtic given his difficulties remaining as a first-choice pick under Mikel Arteta at ...
The post Brendan Rodgers left impressed by Celtic duo in Portugal as he discusses box office rumour appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: FACING THE IBROX FOES: EVAN WILLIAMS REVEALS ALL (Part Three)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=93809</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-facing-the-ibrox-foes-evan-williams-reveals-all-part-three/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T05:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EVAN WILLIAMS, who celebrated his 80th birthday on Saturday, may have had his run-ins with Jock Stein, but Celtic’s legendary manager never hesitated in giving the keeper the nod to play in Old Firm encounters. The games against the club’s fiercest foes brought out the best in the netminder who recalled: “I played against Rangers [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘UNBELIEVABLE’ CUP TRIUMPH: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Six)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=93805</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/unbelievable-cup-triumph-the-tommy-burns-story-part-six/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T04:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS was just 90 minutes away from his first silverware in his debut season as Celtic manager after returning to the club on July 12 1994. The League Cup had been lost in a sensational penalty-kick shoot-out to Raith Rovers in November, the league was blown, but the Scottish Cup was tantalisingly close. In [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midfielder has confirmed Celtic interest in signing him]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42660</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/16/midfielder-confirmed-celtic-interest-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T22:35:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With official news from Celtic still to come to confirm the signing of South Korean winger, Yang Hyun-jun, from Gangwon FC, there is another player expected to join the club very soon. And it is very possible that the club might be aiming for a double announcement. Let’s see how things play out over the […]
Midfielder has confirmed Celtic interest in signing him - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports man links £16 million winger with Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42678</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/16/sky-sports-man-16-million-winger-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T21:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will need to strengthen their ranks this summer. The club have continued to add to their squad, having already brought in Odin Thiago Holm and Marco Tilio. On the other hand, moves for Yang Hyun-jun and Kwon Hyeok-kyu are believed to be close as well. These are positive moves from the Hoops, but at […]
Sky Sports man links £16 million winger with Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Dalglish reckons "every manager dreams" of what Celtic star offers; lauds club action]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167366</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kenny-dalglish-lauds-celtic-contract-move/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T20:41:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend Kenny Dalglish has lauded the club’s move to tie down captain Callum McGregor for five more years in the Hoops. McGregor’s new deal was announced last Monday and has been warmly received by the vast majority of the Celtic support. We’re keeping a player in his prime and utilising the years of experience ...
The post Kenny Dalglish reckons "every manager dreams" of what Celtic star offers; lauds club action appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Hyoengyu Oh told incoming Yang Hyun-jun about life at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167376</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-hyoengyu-oh-told-incoming-yang-hyun-jun-about-life-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Barring the official announcement from Celtic, I think we can all agree that South Korean winger, Yang Hyun-jun will be a Celtic player over the coming days. Gangwon CEO, Kim Byung-ji confirmed yesterday that Celtic will be paying €2.5m for the 21-year-old and today, Hyun-Jun made his final appearance for the club and said his ...
The post What Hyoengyu Oh told incoming Yang Hyun-jun about life at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jonny Evans to Celtic transfer update amid rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42674</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/16/jonny-evans-celtic-transfer-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T19:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with plenty of players this summer who played under the management of Brendan Rodgers at Leicester City over the past several years. Some such names are Wilfred Ndidi, Tete and Daniel Amartey. And now, the latest name to be added to that quickly growing list is that of Jonny Evans. The […]
Jonny Evans to Celtic transfer update amid rumours - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers praises Rocco Vata; issues challenge to young Celtic winger]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167370</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-praises-rocco-vata-issues-challenge-to-young-celtic-winger/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T19:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has praised young Celtic attacking midfielder, Rocco Vata, and issued a challenge to the winger if he has designs of trying to make it into the Hoops first team. Vata was taken to the Portugal training camp and has clearly impressed the Celtic boss. But although Vata has developed well since the last ...
The post Brendan Rodgers praises Rocco Vata; issues challenge to young Celtic winger appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Premier League Celtic transfer links quashed by new report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167374</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/jonny-evans-and-scott-mctominay-transfer-links-to-celtic-quashed-by-new-report/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T18:47:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic won’t be making a move for Jonny Evans or Scott McTominay this summer, it has been reported this evening. The Liverpool Echo stated this weekend that Brendan Rodgers was keen on reuniting with free agent Evans, who played under the new Celtic boss at Leicester City. Manchester United midfielder McTominay, meanwhile, has been a ...
The post Two Premier League Celtic transfer links quashed by new report appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manchester United hero admits to being a Celtic fan]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42671</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/16/manchester-united-hero-celtic-fan/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T18:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are one of the biggest clubs in world football. People often fail to recognise the sheer size of the fan base simply because of the fact that they play in the Scottish Premiership, which admittedly is not one of the best leagues in Europe and neither does it have the popularity of a Premier […]
Manchester United hero admits to being a Celtic fan - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 6 main contenders to be axed from Celtic's growing squad this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167362</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-6-main-contenders-to-be-axed-from-celtics-growing-squad-this-summer/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T17:10:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While plenty of Celtic fans are clamouring for fresh blood and new signings, it’s worth noting the club still have plenty to do to move on the players who just haven’t cut it over the last couple of years. The Bhoys are on the brink of announcing their third and fourth signings of the summer, ...
The post The 6 main contenders to be axed from Celtic's growing squad this summer appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic gearing up for more transfer reveals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167359</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-gearing-up-for-more-transfer-announcements/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T16:30:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems clear by now that the moves for South Korean duo Yang Hyun-jun and Kwon Hyeok-kyu are complete and that the only thing we are now awaiting is a double announcement from Celtic. Gangwon FC gave the game away with regards to Yang yesterday, with their club chief confirming the move and even the ...
The post Celtic gearing up for more transfer reveals appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant highlights three 'vital' areas Celtic will strengthen this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167353</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/peter-grant-highlights-three-vital-areas-celtic-will-strengthen-this-summer/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already made some additions to the first-team squad this summer. Odin Thiago Holm, Marco Tilio and the permanent signing of Tomoki Iwata have helped to add more depth to the squad. But the recent injuries this week to Tilio, Alistair Johnston and Mikey Johnston have convinced former Celtic player, Peter Grant, that the ...
The post Peter Grant highlights three 'vital' areas Celtic will strengthen this summer appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Miller's bizarre assessment of Celtic's treble winning season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167356</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kenny-millers-bizarre-assessment-of-celtics-treble-winning-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s record-breaking treble-winning season was quite remarkable. Up until the title was signed, sealed and delivered with a 2-0 win over Hearts at Tynecastle on the 7th of May, Celtic had only dropped five points all season. Our superior goal difference was effectively like having another point advantage but at no point did the title ...
The post Kenny Miller's bizarre assessment of Celtic's treble winning season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic close to making another signing after Yang Hyun-jun]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42667</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/16/celtic-close-signing-yang-hyun-jun/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T14:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have not made the signing of Yang Hyun-jun official yet although Gangwon FC have released a statement on their Instagram already. Thus, it is only a matter of time and it seems like the Hoops are waiting for the right opportunity to break the news to the fans. In fact, the possibility of a […]
Celtic close to making another signing after Yang Hyun-jun - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic favourite on his next career move; why Parkhead return never materialised]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167350</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/aiden-mcgeady-on-his-next-career-move-why-celtic-return-never-materialised/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aiden McGeady was, without a doubt, one of the most naturally gifted wingers Celtic had seen in the first team for a long time. Beginning his career at Queens Park, McGeady tried to follow a career path in England. And after a trial at Arsenal failed to produce a move, the Glasgow-born winger signed for ...
The post Former Celtic favourite on his next career move; why Parkhead return never materialised appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['The way he plays': Peter Grant thinks PL star open to securing transfer to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167305</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/it-wouldnt-surprise-me-peter-grant-makes-exciting-kieran-tierney-and-celtic-transfer-claim/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant says he ‘wouldn’t be surprised’ if Kieran Tierney wants to make a return to Celtic this summer as questions remain over his future at Arsenal. The Scotland international has had his fair share of injury issues during the past 18 months and it hasn’t helped that Oleksandr Zinchenko has also pushed ahead of ...
The post 'The way he plays': Peter Grant thinks PL star open to securing transfer to Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dutch defender speaks on his future as previous Celtic links seem to have cooled]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167345</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/xavier-mbuyamba-speaks-on-his-future-as-previous-celtic-links-seem-to-have-cooled/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with a number of players over the past few months. Even prior to Brendan Rodgers taking over at the club, the summer transfer window did promise to be a big one as Celtic looked to improve their fortunes in Europe. But Xavier Mbuyamba, who was previously linked to the club has ...
The post Dutch defender speaks on his future as previous Celtic links seem to have cooled appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reported Celtic target seals move to join Fenerbache]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167341</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/reported-celtic-target-dominik-livakovic-seals-move-to-join-fenerbache/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After all the excitement over the transfer rumour that Celtic held an interest in Croatian international goalkeeper Dominik Livaković, it seems now that can be put to bed after the 28-year-old is set to join Turkish club, Fenerbache. 67 Hail Hail discussed yesterday that Livaković had agreed personal terms with the Turks but a deal ...
The post Reported Celtic target seals move to join Fenerbache appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Joe Hart told Conor Hazard after sealing Celtic exit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167322</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-joe-hart-told-conor-hazard-after-sealing-celtic-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conor Hazard’s move from Celtic to Plymouth Argyle this week was one that the former Hoops keeper needed at this stage of his career. At 24 years old, Hazard had just returned from a successful loan spell at HJK Helsinki where he enjoyed a lengthy run in the Finnish club’s first team. After nine years ...
The post What Joe Hart told Conor Hazard after sealing Celtic exit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£7.7m LIVAKOVIC: NO DEAL, SAY HOOPS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109905</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/7-7m-livakovic-no-deal-say-hoops/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T09:22:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS will not be pursuing initial interest in Croatia World Cup keeper Dominik Livakovic. The Celtic manager had been linked with the Dinamo Zagreb No.1 who is coming out of contract next summer as has been linked with several clubs in recent weeks. Rodgers, though, will not take the consideration any further with reports claiming [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano confirms €9 million Celtic transfer fail]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42657</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/16/fabrizio-romano-celtic-transfer-fail/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T09:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were handed a major transfer blow this summer when Jota left the club in order to join Al-Ittihad in a £25 million deal. While the Hoops received a big fee, they also ended up losing arguably their most creative player in the team. The hope was that they would reinvest that figure and bring […]
Fabrizio Romano confirms €9 million Celtic transfer fail - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“I’m a fan and always have been” – Ex-Manchester United hero makes Celtic admission]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167301</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/im-a-fan-and-always-have-been-ex-manchester-united-hero-makes-celtic-admission/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[European nights at Celtic Park always have that ability to capture the imagination of some of the world’s best players. Players like Lionel Messi, Xavi and Paolo Maldini have all waxed lyrical about the atmosphere in Paradise and, here, we have another legend of the game speaking about his experience playing in one of those ...
The post “I’m a fan and always have been” – Ex-Manchester United hero makes Celtic admission appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Republic of Ireland legend explains why Mikey Johnston will get a chance at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167296</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-republic-of-ireland-legend-explains-why-mikey-johnston-will-get-a-chance-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mikey Johnston has been one of those Celtic players that have risen through the academy and shown a lot of promise. He broke into the first team under Brendan Rodgers back in 2017 when he made his debut in a 4-1 win over St Johnstone. And on that very same afternoon it was announced that ...
The post Former Republic of Ireland legend explains why Mikey Johnston will get a chance at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: WHAT NOW FOR CELTIC’S MISSING LINK?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109896</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-what-now-for-celtics-missing-link/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T07:38:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I CONFESS I have followed James McCarthy’s career with a fair degree of diligence for one very good reason – his dad was one of my best pals as we both grew up in Castlemilk. My schooldays were not quite around the time fire was invented, but I admit it was a long time ago. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nir Bitton backs former Celtic teammate to make history]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167293</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/nir-bitton-backs-former-celtic-teammate-to-make-history/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T06:11:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nir Bitton reckons Callum McGregor can become the club’s most decorated player in history after signing his new contract with Celtic. McGregor has already won an incredible 20 major honours during his time at the Bhoys. In terms of volume, he remains just five trophies behind the all-time leader Bobby Lennox, who admittedly won the ...
The post Nir Bitton backs former Celtic teammate to make history appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic target speaks out; excited by Bhoys transfer link]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167291</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-target-speaks-out-excited-by-bhoys-transfer-link/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T05:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer target Kwon Hyeok-kyu has confirmed he knows all about the Bhoys’ interest in his services and that he is excited about the potential opportunity to move to Scotland. Kwon is widely reported to be the subject of a £1m offer from Celtic, who have contacted his club Busan about signing him up during ...
The post Celtic target speaks out; excited by Bhoys transfer link appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…RAMI GERSHON?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109894</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-rami-gershon/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T05:17:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RAMI GERSHON’S scoring ratio for a full-back at Celtic was even more prolific than that of Lisbon Lion Tommy Gemmell, the swashbuckling hero of Jock Stein’s all-conquering team. The 25-year-old Israeli left-sided defender fired in a goal every three games. Unfortunately, Gershon only made three first-team appearances for the Hoops after joining on loan from Standard [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[English side hoping for Celtic windfall bonus but Bhoys hold all the cards]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167287</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/english-side-hoping-for-celtic-windfall-bonus-but-bhoys-hold-all-the-cards/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T05:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MK Dons boss Graham Alexander has admitted he is hoping another club comes in for Celtic midfielder Matt O’Riley this summer, so he can get a cut to spend on improving his own squad. Like most transfer deals these days, MK inserted a clause in the O’Riley sale to pocket a percentage of the profit ...
The post English side hoping for Celtic windfall bonus but Bhoys hold all the cards appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: ‘BIG JOCK AND ME’: EVAN WILLIAMS REVEALS ALL (Part Two)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=93735</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-big-jock-and-me-evan-williams-reveals-all-part-two/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T05:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EVAN WILLIAMS, who celebrated his 80th birthday yesterday, was a goalkeeper decades ahead of his time. The popular former netminder, who joined the Hoops from Wolves in October 1969 as the club searched for a long-term replacement for veteran Ronnie Simpson, used to have Jock Stein waving wildly on the touchline to get back into [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘WE HAVE LEARNED FROM THE EXPERIENCE’: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Five)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=93708</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/we-have-learned-from-the-experience-the-tommy-burns-story-part-five/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T04:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS was determined to win silverware in his first season as Celtic manager after returning to the club on July 12 1994. The chance to achieve his goal after only four months was obliterated in a dramatic penalty-kick shoot-out to First Division Raith Rovers in the League Cup Final at Ibrox. With the league [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers and Celtic fans handed even more good news]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42637</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/15/brendan-rodgers-celtic-fans-news/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T22:30:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It looks like fans should be expecting an official Celtic announcement soon about the signing of South Korean youth international, Yang Hyun-jun, from K-League side Gangwon FC. There was some more good news on Saturday morning for Brendan Rodgers’ side as well, as they continue their preparations for the 2023/24 campaign. Gangwon FC released a […]
Brendan Rodgers and Celtic fans handed even more good news - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports man makes superb Celtic transfer claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42652</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/15/sky-sports-man-celtic-transfer-claim/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T20:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou’s run at Celtic might have only lasted a couple of seasons, but nobody can deny the impact that he made during that period of time. A lot of things changed at Parkhead and for the better. One of the biggest changes was felt on their transfer strategy, as they spread their network further […]
Sky Sports man makes superb Celtic transfer claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic urged to bring box office factor to summer transfer window]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167285</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-urged-to-bring-wow-factor-to-summer-transfer-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T20:22:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton wants Celtic to step up their summer transfer window business, feeling they’ve done little to strengthen last season’s treble-winning squad. The Bhoys have completed the signings of Odin Thiago Holm, Marco Tilio and Yang Hyun-jun, but crucially have sold one of the squad’s best, most popular players in Jota. Sutton understands that patience ...
The post Celtic urged to bring box office factor to summer transfer window appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic want Premier League title winner; echo of first Rodgers spell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167279</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-are-interested-in-signing-premier-league-free-agent-echo-of-first-brendan-rodgers-spell/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T19:04:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with a move for Premier League free agent Jonny Evans, who left Leicester City at the end of his contract last month. The Liverpool Echo reports that new manager Brendan Rodgers is ‘keen’ on signing the player, who he worked with at the Foxes and even made his club captain. The ...
The post Report: Celtic want Premier League title winner; echo of first Rodgers spell appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer talks over deal to sign midfielder confirmed]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42648</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/15/celtic-talks-deal-sign-midfielder/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T19:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Ange Postecoglou decided to leave Celtic after the end of the previous season, many fans feared that it would lead to a change in the transfer policy which had brought the club so much success over the past couple of campaigns. Brendan Rodgers has ended up replacing the Australian in the Parkhead hot seat […]
Celtic transfer talks over deal to sign midfielder confirmed - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic linked with former Manchester United player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42644</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/15/celtic-former-manchester-united-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T17:30:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already brought in a couple of players this summer in the form of Marco Tilio and Odin Thiago Holm. On the other hand, a move for Yang Hyun-jun also appears to be on the verge of completion. All of them are decent additions to the side and have the potential to be great […]
Celtic linked with former Manchester United player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Youngsters shine, Daizen press; Celtic goal highlights from 4-1 win over Portuguese side]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167273</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/youngsters-shine-daizen-press-celtic-goal-highlights-from-4-1-win-over-portuguese-side/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T15:40:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have delighted fans with a look at today’s 4-1 win over Portuguese top-flight side Portimonense. The Bhoys played the same team on Wednesday night but nothing was seen or heard about that 0-0 draw outside of unofficial updates from fans on the ground in Portugal. Reo Hatate, Liel Abada, Ben Summers and Hyeongyu Oh ...
The post Youngsters shine, Daizen press; Celtic goal highlights from 4-1 win over Portuguese side appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean club chief confirms Celtic transfer fee; incoming recruit says his goodbyes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167270</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/south-korean-club-chief-confirms-celtic-transfer-fee-incoming-recruit-says-his-goodbyes/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T15:18:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have paid a fee of €2.5m [£2.15m] for Yang Hyun-jun, Gangwon FC club chief Kim Byung-ji has confirmed today. The South Korean side surprised everyone with their own announcement that Yang will be heading to the Bhoys this summer, with no Celtic comment yet made on the situation. Now, more details about the transfer ...
The post South Korean club chief confirms Celtic transfer fee; incoming recruit says his goodbyes appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS ‘REALLY PLEASED’ AS CELTIC TRIUMPH – AND THEN SEAL KOREAN DEAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109868</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-really-pleased-as-celtic-triumph-and-then-seal-korean-deal/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T14:19:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS declared himself “really pleased” after Celtic eased to a 4-1 win over Portimonense SC today as they completed a positive week in Portugal. The returning Hoops boss beamed as he watched Reo Hatate net the opening goal from the penalty spot with Liel Abada, Ben Summers and Oh Hyeon-gyu also getting on the scoresheet [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers reacts as Oh and co fire 'intense' Celtic to pre-season win]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167264</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-reacts-as-oh-and-co-fire-intense-celtic-to-pre-season-win/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T12:11:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers was delighted with the work of his side in this morning’s pre-season friendly against Portimonense in Portugal. The Bhoys took on the top-flight side for the second time in three days behind closed doors at The Campus training centre. Celtic came out on top by a 4-1 margin thanks to goals ...
The post Brendan Rodgers reacts as Oh and co fire 'intense' Celtic to pre-season win appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano confirms Dominik Livakovic blow for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42632</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/15/fabrizio-romano-dominik-livakovic-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T12:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans were delighted when the club were recently linked with a move for Croatian international number one, Dominik Livakovic. The goalkeeper was arguably his national team’s best performer at the World Cup last year, as they finished third in the competition, exceeded all expectations. Celtic can certainly do with a goalkeeper like Livakovic. They […]
Fabrizio Romano confirms Dominik Livakovic blow for Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four different scorers as Celtic punish Portimonense in Saturday morning pre-season match]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167262</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/four-different-scorers-as-celtic-punish-portimonense-in-saturday-morning-pre-season-match/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T10:50:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic clicked into gear against Portuguese top-flight side Portimonense this morning, winning 4-1 in a behind-closed-doors match at The Campus training centre. The Bhoys played the same side on Wednesday with a weakened group, made up of players who completed a first week of training at Lennoxtown prior to the trip to Portugal. That one ...
The post Four different scorers as Celtic punish Portimonense in Saturday morning pre-season match appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano offers disappointing Dominik Livakovic update amidst Celtic interest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167260</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/fabrizio-romano-offers-disappointing-dominik-livakovic-update-amidst-celtic-interest/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T10:24:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Renowned transfer journalist Fabrizio Romano has reported that Dominik Livakovic has agreed personal terms with Fenerbahce, as the Turkish club look to finalise a deal with Dinamo Zagreb. There was excitement amongst some Bhoys fans on Friday night when Sky Sports reported that Celtic were closely monitoring the Croatian international star, with the goalkeeping position ...
The post Fabrizio Romano offers disappointing Dominik Livakovic update amidst Celtic interest appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic next signing official in early morning announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42629</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/15/celtic-next-signing-official-early-morning-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T10:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have continued to strengthen their squad this summer. The club have already brought in two very highly rated young talents in the form of Odin Thiago Holm and Marco Tilio. And now, the Hoops look set to make a third signing in this window as well, after being linked with him for several weeks […]
Celtic next signing official in early morning announcement - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gangwon FC confirm Yang Hyun-jun is moving to Celtic in official statement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167255</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/gangwon-fc-confirm-yang-hyun-jun-is-moving-to-celtic-in-official-statement/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T09:57:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean side Gangwon FC have confirmed on Instagram that attacker Yang Hyun-jun will become a Celtic player this summer. The club say he will make a farewell statement to fans after their match at home to FC Seoul today. The statement read: “[OFFICIAL] Yang Hyun-jun to Celtic’s transfer has been confirmed. There is a ...
The post Gangwon FC confirm Yang Hyun-jun is moving to Celtic in official statement appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX ANGLE: ANGE’S LONELY WALK, BUCKET LIST AND THE LOST CHALLENGE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109864</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alex-angle-anges-lonely-walk-bucket-list-and-the-lost-challenge/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T09:49:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A FORTNIGHT before he departed Celtic for Spurs, Ange Postecoglou walked to the centre circle at Parkhead and waved to the Celtic supporters. It was a lonely manoeuvre in the immediate aftermath of the drab 2-2 draw with St Mirren where the champions had played in slow motion without a spark of ingenuity. It was [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: ANGE’S LONELY WALK, BUCKET LIST AND THE LOST CHALLENGE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109864</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-anges-lonely-walk-bucket-list-and-the-lost-challenge/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T09:49:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A FORTNIGHT before he departed Celtic for Spurs, Ange Postecoglou walked to the centre circle at Parkhead and waved to the Celtic supporters. It was a lonely manoeuvre in the immediate aftermath of the drab 2-2 draw with St Mirren where the champions had played in slow motion without a spark of ingenuity. It was [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: THE LONELY WALK, ANGE’S BUCKET LIST AND THE LOST CHALLENGE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109864</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-the-lonely-walk-anges-bucket-list-and-the-lost-challenge/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T09:49:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A FORTNIGHT before he departed Celtic for Spurs, Ange Postecoglou walked to the centre circle at Parkhead and waved to the Celtic supporters. It was a lonely manoeuvre in the immediate aftermath of the drab 2-2 draw with St Mirren where the champions had played in slow motion without a spark of ingenuity. It was [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The first Celtic goals of the new Brendan Rodgers era have been scored]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167251</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtics-first-goal-of-the-new-brendan-rodgers-era-has-been-scored/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T09:36:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s one for budding quiz enthusiasts. Who scored the very first goal of Brendan Rodgers’ second era at Celtic? The answer is Reo Hatate, in a Saturday morning match against Portuguese top-flight side Portimonense. Celtic played the same opposition on Wednesday evening with a pretty youthful and inexperienced side, dotted with the players who didn’t ...
The post The first Celtic goals of the new Brendan Rodgers era have been scored appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: The bargain fees Celtic will pay to land third and fourth summer signings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167246</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/the-bargain-fees-celtic-will-pay-to-land-next-summer-signings/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T09:11:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are closing in on Brendan Rodgers’ third and fourth signings of the summer transfer window, with more South Koreans set to join the squad in Glasgow. It’s long been known that the Bhoys have been looking at the K-League market for additions and eventually moved for striker Hyeongyu Oh in January. He’s proven to ...
The post Report: The bargain fees Celtic will pay to land third and fourth summer signings appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INVINCIBLE IN DEMAND]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109860</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/invincible-in-demand/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T07:53:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC Invincible Stuart Armstrong is on the verge of quitting relegated Southampton. The 31-year-old Scotland international midrielder is reportedly a target for Serie A sides Torino and Lazio. Armstrong, who cost the south coast club £7million when he joined from the Hoops in 2018, has a year left on his contract to run, but is [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘GET A MOVE ON,’ RODGERS URGED TO SPLASH THE CASH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109852</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/get-a-move-on-rodgers-urged-to-splash-the-cash/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T07:04:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CHRIS SUTTON has urged Brendan Rodgers “to get a move on” in bringing in top signings to Celtic. The former Hoops hero insists the returning manager urgently requires new faces to provide the “wow factor” at the champions as they prepare for life after Filipe Jota. Sutton emphasises the Portuguese maverick was a pivotal figure [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC IN WORLD CUP HERO LINK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109848</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-in-world-cup-hero-link/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T06:33:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have been linked with Croatia World Cup keeper Dominik Livakovic. Brendan Rodgers has already backed 36-year-old former England international No.1 Joe Hart who has Benji Siegrist and Scott Bain as back-up. The veteran has been a mainstay in the Hoops first team since he arrived in a £1million switch from Spurs in August 2021. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…MO BANGURA?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109843</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-mo-bangura/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T05:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S talent-spotters were suitably impressed by Mo Bangura’s strike rate at AIK Stockholm to draw him to the attention of manager Neil Lennon. The Sierre Leone international fired in 14 goals in 35 games for the Swedish club and that tally persuaded the Hoops boss to part with £2.2million in August 2011 to add him [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘JOCK DIDN’T LIKE GOALIES’: HAPPY 80th BIRTHDAY, EVAN WILLIAMS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=93688</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/jock-didnt-like-goalies-happy-80th-birthday-evan-williams/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T05:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EVAN WILLIAMS, who celebrates his 80th birthday today, was left in tears after the game of his life on May 6 1970. The goalkeeper, who had been brought to the club from Wolves the previous year, was probably the only Celtic player to emerge from the European Cup Final loss to Feyenoord at the San [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE BID FOR HAMPDEN GLORY: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Four)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=93686</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-bid-for-hampden-glory-the-tommy-burns-story-part-four/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-15T04:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS set his sights on silverware in his first season as Celtic manager after returning to the club on July 12 1994. The fans’ favourite had winced as he witnessed the Hoops losing in a dramatic penalty-kick shoot-out to First Division Raith Rovers in the League Cup Final at Ibrox only four months after his [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liverpool’s Fabinho transfer update is great for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42624</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/14/liverpool-fabinho-transfer-update-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T22:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are expected to make plenty of signings in this summer transfer window, and hopefully a few marquee ones as well. At the same time, it will also be important for the club to hold onto their best players as well. We have already seen Jota make the move to Al-Ittihad and several others have […]
Liverpool’s Fabinho transfer update is great for Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic suffer €9 million Dominik Livakovic transfer blow]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42620</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/14/celtic-dominik-livakovic-transfer-blow/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T20:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are expected to strengthen their squad this summer, as they aim to retain all three domestic titles next season and also have their eyes set on making an impact in the Champions League group stages, following the appointment of Brendan Rodgers as the manager of the club for the second time. And one area […]
Celtic suffer €9 million Dominik Livakovic transfer blow - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Current Celtic star posts a throwback to the day it all started]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167231</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/liel-abada-posts-a-celtic-throwback-ahead-of-an-interesting-summer/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liel Abada has shared a throwback to his first day at Celtic, exactly two years on. On 14 July 2021 the Israel international was signed from Maccabi Petah Tikva on a five-year deal. Abada was the first proper signing of the summer after a number of youth deals had been sealed. Few knew a great ...
The post Current Celtic star posts a throwback to the day it all started appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic submit €1 million offer for defensive midfielder]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42617</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/14/celtic-1-million-offer-midfielder/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T19:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been excellent in recent times when it comes to identifying top talents from leagues all over the world and bringing them to Glasgow. That is one of the biggest reasons that they have been successful in winning five out of the last six domestic competitions in Scotland, when you consider that situation that […]
Celtic submit €1 million offer for defensive midfielder - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dinamo Zagreb receive substantial offer for Dominik Livakovic but it's not from Celtic yet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167238</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/dinamo-zagreb-receive-substantial-offer-for-dominik-livakovic-but-its-not-from-celtic-yet/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fenerbahce look to be the main rivals to Celtic on any move for Dinamo Zagreb goalkeeper Dominik Livakovic, if reports coming out of Turkey today are accurate. It was reported by Sky Sports earlier that the Bhoys are closely monitoring the well-regarded Croatian international, with the goalkeeping position a priority to the recruitment staff at ...
The post Dinamo Zagreb receive substantial offer for Dominik Livakovic but it's not from Celtic yet appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Brendan Rodgers has said about Joe Hart as exciting Celtic transfer link emerges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167230</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/what-brendan-rodgers-has-said-about-joe-hart-as-exciting-celtic-transfer-link-emerges/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans have been waiting a while for a box office transfer rumour this summer, so the links to Dominik Livakovic have understandably caught the imagination of many. Sky Sports have reported that the Bhoys are ‘closely monitoring’ the Croatian international goalkeeper, whose arrival would be a box office statement signing. Clearly, there is a ...
The post What Brendan Rodgers has said about Joe Hart as exciting Celtic transfer link emerges appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic want to sign Croatia’s superstar at World Cup]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42613</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/14/celtic-croatia-superstar-world-cup/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T17:30:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are expected to make a few big signings in this summer transfer window in order to make sure that Brendan Rodgers’ squad is ready to defend all three titles next season and also can make an impact in the Champions League, which they failed to do in the previous campaign. And a few positions […]
Celtic want to sign Croatia’s superstar at World Cup - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic squad is being taken to the limit in Portugal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167210</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-celtic-squad-is-being-taken-to-the-limit-in-portugal/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T17:19:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has hailed the intensity and quality of his squad’s pre-season work in Portugal, stating that the heat and schedule are bringing the players to some “uncomfortable” places. Celtic have been at the state-of-the-art Campus facility on the Algarve since Sunday and depart this weekend before making a trip to Japan for ...
The post The Celtic squad is being taken to the limit in Portugal appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Saudi Comes they GO – Jota no longer on the wing]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58091</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/when-saudi-comes-they-go-jota-no-longer-on-the-wing/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T17:06:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We had Jota on the wing, he was a pleasure to watch from the stands. Celtic’s recruitment has been excellent over the past 2 seasons and the Portuguese winger was one of the stand out players alongside Kyogo and Carter Vickers. One season on loan before he signed a permanent deal. Little did Celtic know […]
The post When Saudi Comes they GO – Jota no longer on the wing appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic closely monitoring goalkeeper who dazzled at the World Cup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167219</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/report-celtic-closely-monitoring-goalkeeper-dominik-livakovic-dazzled-at-the-world-cup/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T16:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are closely monitoring Croatia goalkeeper Dominik Livakovic, according to a report. Sky Sports journalist Anthony Joseph has shared an update on the club’s transfer intentions, with the goalkeeping position seemingly high on the agenda. Joseph tweeted on Friday evening, saying: “Celtic are in the market for a goalkeeper this summer. “It’s understood one target ...
The post Report: Celtic closely monitoring goalkeeper who dazzled at the World Cup appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic dodge a bullet as Asian Games squad is announced]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167215</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-dodge-a-bullet-as-south-korea-announce-their-asian-games-squad/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T16:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have received some good news in the form of the South Korea squad for the Asian Games. The Koreans announced their 22 player selection for the competition that will take place in China from September 19 to October 7. The Asian Games are not to be confused with the Asian Cup — which takes ...
The post Celtic dodge a bullet as Asian Games squad is announced appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers may be about to get wish from first Celtic media day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167209</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-may-be-about-to-get-wish-from-first-celtic-media-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers may be about to get an important wish at Celtic. The Hoops boss will still be in the process of evaluating his new squad. The first-team are currently in Portugal, and will travel to Japan next week as they step-up preparations for the new season. Recruitment will continue to be a major topic ...
The post Brendan Rodgers may be about to get wish from first Celtic media day appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic announce fixture change as tricky early season test is selected by Sky Sports]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167204</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-announce-fixture-change-as-difficult-early-season-test-is-selected-by-sky-sports/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T14:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As expected, Celtic’s match away to Livingston in the Scottish Premiership this September has been selected by Sky Sports, meaning Brendan Rodgers’ team face another lunchtime kick-off in the opening weeks of the season. The game away to David Martindale’s side had been scheduled in for 3pm on Saturday 23rd September, but will now kick-off ...
The post Celtic announce fixture change as tricky early season test is selected by Sky Sports appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rodgers talks Kennedy and Kewell; explains how Celtic training will be different]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167198</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/rodgers-talks-kennedy-and-kewell-explains-how-celtic-training-will-be-different/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T13:43:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers has praised John Kennedy and explained his role in training. The first-team squad are currently in Portugal, being put through their paces as they prepare for the new season. It’s still very early on in Rodgers‘ second spell at the club, but the early signs are positive with standards already high. ...
The post Rodgers talks Kennedy and Kewell; explains how Celtic training will be different appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic player involved as women's match makes unlikely headlines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167191</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-player-involved-as-womens-match-makes-unlikely-headlines/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T12:46:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently departed Celtic player Claire O’Riordan has been caught up in some strange goings-on. The Republic of Ireland international is busy preparing for her country’s tilt at the 2023 FIFA Women’s World Cup in Australia and New Zealand. Ireland have had plenty of warm-up matches, with their most recent a closed-door clash against Colombia. The ...
The post Former Celtic player involved as women's match makes unlikely headlines appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic look set to sign midfielder compared to Rodri]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42607</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/14/celtic-sign-midfielder-compared-rodri/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T12:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a fantastic record in recent years, when it comes to identifying the right talents from around the world. The club have brought in the likes of Kyogo, Jota, Reo Hatate, Cameron Carter-Vickers, Josip Juranovic, Alistair Johnston, Matt O’Riley and many more superb players, just over the past couple of seasons. Thus, fans would […]
Celtic look set to sign midfielder compared to Rodri - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Encouraging signs as Brendan Rodgers names two Celtic stars who have set early standards]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167183</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/encouraging-signs-as-brendan-rodgers-names-two-celtic-stars-who-have-set-early-standards/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T12:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has praised the international contingent for bringing added quality to Celtic training. It’s been a staggered start to pre-season over the past few weeks. Sessions started at Lennoxtown without Celtic‘s international players, before they joined up for work in Portugal. Rodgers reckons they have brought some additional quality to proceedings, as he named ...
The post Encouraging signs as Brendan Rodgers names two Celtic stars who have set early standards appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC KOREAN SWOOP – AT THE DOUBLE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109840</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-korean-swoop-at-the-double/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T11:14:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC are on the brink of a daring double swoop for South Korean pair Yang Hyun-Jun and Kwon Hyeok-kyu. The Hoops have been chasing Yang for over a month and the £2.1million deal is about to be sealed, according to a report in local media outlet Sports Chosun. The 21-year-old highly-rated winger has insisted in recent weeks [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summer signing shares what everyone has been telling him about Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167175</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/marco-tilio-shares-what-everyone-has-been-telling-him-about-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marco Tilio couldn’t even make it out of the airport before being told about Celtic Park. The Australian arrived in Glasgow last week after signing from Melbourne City seven days earlier. Since then he has been thrust into the media spotlight, flown out to Portugal with his team-mates and confirmed to be missing the first ...
The post Summer signing shares what everyone has been telling him about Celtic Park appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why we might need a pool of 7 wingers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109839</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/why-we-might-need-a-pool-of-7-wingers/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T11:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[News from Korea today suggests we have agreed the transfer of Yang Hyun-jun from Gangwon.  The player turned 21 two days before our last league game of the season against Aberdeen.  Gangwon have won only two of their 22 league games and sit well adrift of safety in the relegation zone. He is young and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic's Asian influence to grow further as December interest pays off]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167167</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-asian-influence-to-grow-further-as-december-interest-pays-off/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T10:14:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are set to complete two more signings from South Korea, according to a report. Korean daily newspaper The Chosun Ilbo report that deals for Hyun-jun Yang and Kwon Hyeok-kyu have been completed. They include some quotes from an “official in the transfer market” who says: “Yang Hyun-jun’s transfer to Celtic has been confirmed. After ...
The post Report: Celtic's Asian influence to grow further as December interest pays off appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic agree £2.1 million deal for third summer signing]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42604</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/14/celtic-agree-deal-third-summer-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T09:35:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After completing moves for Odin Thiago Holm and Marco Tilio early on in the summer transfer window, things have moved a bit slowly for Celtic over the past few days. Now though, it looks like a third signing is not far away either and the Hoops appear to have agreed a deal, as they continue […]
Celtic agree £2.1 million deal for third summer signing - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘FOOTBALL’S MAD,’ INSISTS HART]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109834</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/footballs-mad-insists-hart/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T09:20:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART has gone into overdrive as he prepares for yet another campaign as a new season looms into view. The 36-year-old 75 times-capped England international keeper has seen it all before at Manchester City and his stops at Shrewsbury, Burnley and Spurs while he experienced it, too, in Italy during a loan season at [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘FIGHT FOR OUR LIVES,’ CELTIC BOSS IN EURO VOW]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109825</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/fight-for-our-lives-celtic-boss-in-euro-vow/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T08:07:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DETERMINED Brendan Rodgers insists Celtic “will fight for our lives in the Champions League”. However, the manager is savvy enough to realise that success in the group stages of Europe’s elite competition may be a step too far for his team at the moment. European football after the turn of the year is crucial to the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘THAT DOESN’T BOTHER ME ONE BIT,’ SCOFFS RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109823</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/that-doesnt-bother-me-one-bit-scoffs-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T07:31:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS scoffs at the old adage of never going back. The Irishman returned to Celtic last month after leaving the champions over four-and-a-half years earlier in abrupt fashion to take over Leicester City in February 2019. However, Rodgers, 50, had no hesitation in coming back to Parkhead to succeed Spurs-bound Ange Postecoglou when the call [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SALES TALK: RODGERS REMAINS FOCUSED]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109822</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/sales-talk-rodgers-remains-focused/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T07:15:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is remaining focused amid transfer speculation as the Premiership looms into view with the big kick-off due on Flag Day against Ross County at Parkhead three weeks tomorrow. The returning Celtic boss will be without three of the stars who helped the club make world history with an eighth treble last season. Canada [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS BACKS ‘UNDERVALUED’ CELT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109819</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-backs-undervalued-celt/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T06:17:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has given veteran keeper Joe Hart a massive vote of confidence – for the time being. The returning Celtic manager has been assessing the squad of players he inherited from Ange Postecoglou to compile the strongest group for the rigours that lie ahead. Portuguese maverick Filipe Jota has already quit the treble winners for [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers sets out 3 basic rules as he shares what Celtic formations and tactics to expect]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167163</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-sets-out-3-basic-rules-as-he-shares-what-celtic-formation-and-tactics-to-expect/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T06:11:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic supporters are pretty well accustomed to the kind of football Brendan Rodgers plays, but there are still a few tactical unknowns heading into the new season – primarily how the existing squad built by Ange Postecoglou fit into those plans. From an approach standpoint, however, it seems not much will change from Rodgers’ first ...
The post Brendan Rodgers sets out 3 basic rules as he shares what Celtic formations and tactics to expect appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[McCarthy and fringe players discussed by Brendan Rodgers; strength of Celtic squad is assessed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167160</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/mccarthy-and-fringe-players-discussed-by-brendan-rodgers-strength-of-celtic-squad-is-assessed/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T05:42:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers is using this initial period on his return to Celtic to assess the strength of the squad, from its top stars to the fringe players who have struggled to get a look in under Ange Postecoglou. Amongst those being put through their paces in Portugal are James McCarthy and Liam Scales, both signed ...
The post McCarthy and fringe players discussed by Brendan Rodgers; strength of Celtic squad is assessed appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC TRIPLE SETBACK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109815</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-triple-setback/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T05:31:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MARCO TILIO has joined Alistair and Mikey Johnston on the Celtic crocked list who will miss the start of the new season. The Canada World Cup right-back could be out for six to eight weeks after undergoing an ankle operation. Johnston was injured playing for his nation against America where he was forced to limp off [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers provides disappointing update on new Celtic signing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167157</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-provides-disappointing-update-on-new-celtic-signing-marco-tilio/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T05:11:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans will have to wait to see Marco Tilio in action after Brendan Rodgers revealed he is suffering from an injury that will keep him out of the first few weeks of the season. Tilio signed from Melbourne City on a five-year deal earlier this month and it was hoped he could start to ...
The post Brendan Rodgers provides disappointing update on new Celtic signing appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…MIKU?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109796</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-miku/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T05:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEIL LENNON reckoned he had pulled off a signing coup when he brought Venezualan striker Miku to Celtic on loan on the last day of the transfer window on August 31 2012. The 27-year-old frontman was surprisingly allowed to leave Spanish outfit Getafe where he had been their top scorer in La Liga the previous [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FRUGAL McCANN AND BIG PIERRE: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Three)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=93609</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/frugal-mccann-and-big-pierre-the-tommy-burns-story-part-three/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T04:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS had to revive Celtic after their sensational penalty-kick loss to Raith Rovers in the League Cup Final at Ibrox on the fateful Sunday afternoon of November 27 1994. The shock waves reverberated around the whole of football and Parkhead and the manager realised he would have to spend big money to help turn [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable journalist offers Donny van de Beek to Celtic news]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42600</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/13/journalist-donny-van-de-beek-celtic-news/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T22:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with quite a few big names in recent times, as rumours have suggested that the club are interested in making a few marquee signings this summer. One player who would fall under that category is Donny van de Beek. The Manchester United midfielder is someone the Hoops are rumoured to hold […]
Reliable journalist offers Donny van de Beek to Celtic news - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player ruled out for three months with new injury]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42597</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/13/celtic-player-three-months-injury/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T20:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers’ start to his second stint as Celtic manager has not been the smoothest at all. The club have already lost arguably their most creative player in the form of Jota. Alistair Johnston has undergone a surgery as well, which means that he looks set to miss the start of next season. And now, […]
Celtic player ruled out for three months with new injury - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart's telling insight on behind-closed-doors Celtic match and 6-a-side training tournament]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167153</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/joe-harts-telling-insight-on-behind-closed-doors-celtic-match-and-6-a-side-training-tournament/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T20:18:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been delivering regular video and social media content from the club’s training camp in Portugal; tonight it was Joe Hart’s turn to face the cameras and give supporters an update. Hart was one of the players involved in Wednesday’s 0-0 bounce game against Portuguese top-flight side Portimonense and also took part in a ...
The post Joe Hart's telling insight on behind-closed-doors Celtic match and 6-a-side training tournament appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 6 Celtic players who won Thursday's Portugal training tournament]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167150</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-6-celtic-players-who-won-thursdays-portugal-training-tournament/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T19:42:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic players are hard at work in Portugal preparing for the new season, but they’re also having plenty of fun too, if the club’s social media updates are anything to go by. The official Celtic Twitter account posted this evening that the squad took part in a six-a-side training tournament at ‘The Campus’ centre on ...
The post The 6 Celtic players who won Thursday's Portugal training tournament appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers gives 17-year-old Celtic chance after interest from Newcastle and Spurs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167131</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/brendan-rodgers-gives-17-year-old-celtic-chance-after-interest-from-newcastle-and-spurs/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic prospect Mitchel Frame is one of the Bhoys prospects getting a big chance in Portugal this week as Brendan Rodgers takes a look at talents from all levels at the club. Earlier this week we brought you seven names who were spotted in training pictures including Rocco Vata, Ben Summers, Josh Dede and Daniel ...
The post Brendan Rodgers gives 17-year-old Celtic chance after interest from Newcastle and Spurs appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic offered superb Kieran Tierney transfer boost]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42594</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/13/celtic-kieran-tierney-transfer-boost/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T19:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody would have expected Kieran Tierney to be linked with a return to Celtic this summer, even though he is expected to leave Arsenal. It was in 2019 that he had left his boyhood club in order to join the Premier League giants in a Scottish record £25 million move. A lot has happened since […]
Celtic offered superb Kieran Tierney transfer boost - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upcoming coverage after a strange start; the Celtic TV situation for the rest of pre-season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167056</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/upcoming-coverage-after-a-strange-start-the-celtic-tv-situation-for-the-rest-of-pre-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic supporters should be able to see more of the team in action later this pre-season. The Hoops played their first organised match on Wednesday evening as things got off to a strange start. There was no video, audio or text coverage of the clash against Portimonense. Numerous score applications have the result down as ...
The post Upcoming coverage after a strange start; the Celtic TV situation for the rest of pre-season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steven Gerrard wants ex-Celtic star who terrorised Rangers; Fabrizio Romano update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167126</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/steven-gerrard-wants-ex-celtic-star-who-terrorised-rangers-fabrizio-romano-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T18:11:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker, Moussa Dembele has been approached by Saudi Arabain club, Al Ettifaq according to Italian transfer specialist, Fabrizio Romano. The Saudi club have recently hired former Rangers manager, Steven Gerrard as their manager. The Frenchman is still a free agent after leaving Lyon when his contract expired at the end of the season. ...
The post Steven Gerrard wants ex-Celtic star who terrorised Rangers; Fabrizio Romano update appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking forward to getting back to see Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58086</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/looking-forward-to-getting-back-to-see-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T18:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s nice to be back writing about Celtic after the summer break. We look forward to another season following Celtic home and away. Thanks to everyone who bought the latest More than 90 Minutes. The print edition is heading for another sell out with less than 5 copies left as I write. Work will begin […]
The post Looking forward to getting back to see Celtic appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers states the achievable UEFA Champions League goal for Celtic this season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167121</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-states-the-achievable-uefa-champions-league-goal-for-celtic-this-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T17:40:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the hype around Brendan Rodgers’ return to Celtic last month, there were some pretty big claims and ambitions being reported by journalists around Scotland about the manager’s expectations of the future. One columnist suggested that Rodgers’ private aim was to bring the Bhoys to a European final. Publicly, the Celtic boss is never going ...
The post Brendan Rodgers states the achievable UEFA Champions League goal for Celtic this season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic starter undergoes surgery and out for 6-8 weeks]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42591</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/13/celtic-starter-surgery-6-8-weeks/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T17:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are just days into pre-season training and there is already worrying injury news for Celtic. But the club have faced fitness issues for some time now and that has not stopped them from being successful on the pitch. They are coming off of a treble-winning campaign after all. This is not the start that […]
Celtic starter undergoes surgery and out for 6-8 weeks - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Got to give respect to Ronny" - Rodgers brings up Deila in Celtic media response]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167111</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/got-to-give-respect-to-ronny-rodgers-brings-up-deila-in-celtic-media-response/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ronny Deila got a mention from Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers at Thursday’s press conference. The current Hoops boss was speaking to the media from Portugal where his first-team stars are being put through their paces. Rodgers returned to Celtic almost a month ago, over four years on from his first spell at the club. At ...
The post "Got to give respect to Ronny" - Rodgers brings up Deila in Celtic media response appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tomoki Iwata's encouraging, self-critical Celtic appraisal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167071</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/tomoki-iwatas-encouraging-but-pretty-harsh-celtic-appraisal/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tomoki Iwata is the latest Celtic player to speak to club media in Portugal. As we’ve been covering over the past few days, a number of the first-team squad have been put in front of the Celtic TV cameras for a chat. The likes of Daizen Maeda, Carl Starfelt and Daniel Kelly have all given ...
The post Tomoki Iwata's encouraging, self-critical Celtic appraisal appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>