<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-08-24T18:12:24.394Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic now identifying "magic" in closing stages of summer transfer window]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172155</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-now-identifying-magic-in-closing-stages-of-summer-transfer-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T17:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers is confident the club will do business in the final week of the summer transfer window, suggesting that they are looking...
The post Celtic now identifying "magic" in closing stages of summer transfer window appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms fringe player will get an opportunity at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172139</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-confirms-fringe-player-will-get-an-opportunity-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[News of Celtic’s defensive injury crisis has spread like wildfire today. With Brendan Rodgers confirming that Cameron Carter-Vickers and Maik Nawrocki will be out for...
The post Brendan Rodgers confirms fringe player will get an opportunity at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers' intriguing new answer on Celtic transfer target as his club take firm stance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172146</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-intriguing-thursday-answer-on-kieran-tierney-as-celtic-hero-is-frozen-out-at-arsenal/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T16:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers wouldn’t be drawn on specific Celtic links to Arsenal defender Kieran Tierney today but did say that the left-back will want to be...
The post Brendan Rodgers' intriguing new answer on Celtic transfer target as his club take firm stance appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Owen Moffat rocks up at surprising Scottish club one year on from Celtic departure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172095</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/owen-moffat-rocks-up-at-surprising-scottish-club-one-year-on-from-celtic-departure/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic youngster Owen Moffat is looking for his next club. The 21-year-old departed the Hoops for a move to Blackpool almost exactly a year...
The post Owen Moffat rocks up at surprising Scottish club one year on from Celtic departure appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disappointing Hatate blow as Celtic boss provides return timelines for Oh, Kobayashi, Johnston]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172136</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/disappointing-hatate-news-as-rodgers-provides-celtic-return-timelines-for-oh-kobayashi-johnston/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T15:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alongside previous updates on Cameron Carter-Vickers and Maik Nawrocki, Brendan Rodgers has also confirmed that Reo Hatate will be missing for Celtic’s upcoming derby clash....
The post Disappointing Hatate blow as Celtic boss provides return timelines for Oh, Kobayashi, Johnston appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic duo will miss Glasgow Derby]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43629</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/24/brendan-rodgers-celtic-duo-glasgow-derby/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T15:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been handed one injury blow after another another at the start of the 2023/24 campaign. This is not the start that Brendan Rodgers would have been hoping for. Not only are several key players out on the sidelines but the Hoops are already out of the Scottish League Cup as well. Unfortunately, there […]
Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic duo will miss Glasgow Derby - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BAD TIMING: RODGERS FAVOURITE SET FOR UNITED]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111328</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/bad-timing-rodgers-favourite-set-for-united/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T14:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JONNY EVANS, who played for Brendan Rodgers at Leicester City, is poised to agree with a one-year deal at Manchester United. The 35-year-old Northern Ireland international centre-back could have been a player to answer an SOS from the Celtic manager. Rodgers revealed earlier today that Cameron Carter-Vickers and Maik Nawrocki will both be out for [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eric Dier's Spurs stance could come at a crucial time for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172134</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/eric-diers-spurs-stance-could-come-at-a-crucial-time-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T14:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will still be reeling from the news that Cameron Carter-Vickers and Maik Nawrocki are set to miss two months of the season due to...
The post Eric Dier's Spurs stance could come at a crucial time for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart shares the story from inside the Celtic camp after damaging weekend loss]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172108</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/joe-hart-shares-the-story-from-inside-the-celtic-camp-after-damaging-kilmarnock-loss/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart has been speaking about the Celtic camp’s reaction to Sunday’s cup loss to Kilmarnock. It was an afternoon to forget for Brendan Rodgers‘...
The post Joe Hart shares the story from inside the Celtic camp after damaging weekend loss appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic transfer re-assessment in final days of window]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172110</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-confirms-celtic-transfer-re-assessment-in-final-days-of-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T13:45:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has confirmed the club will be looking at the central defensive position in the final days of the transfer window after...
The post Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic transfer re-assessment in final days of window appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC DOUBLE SETBACK: CCV AND NAWROCKI OUT EIGHT WEEKS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111317</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-double-setback-ccv-and-nawrocki-out-eight-weeks/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T13:45:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have been dealt a severe double injury setback with Cameron Carter-Vickers AND Maik Nawrocki ruled out for TWO months. It’s a massive blow for Brendan Rodgers who will also be without back-up central defender Stephen Welsh for three to four months after a freak training ground accident on Friday. The Hoops will now move [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms bitter Celtic injury blows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172106</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-confirms-bitter-celtic-injury-blows/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T13:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has confirmed that Cameron Carter-Vickers and Maik Nawrocki will be out for a prolonged period of time. The Celtic manager has confirmed that...
The post Brendan Rodgers confirms bitter Celtic injury blows appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Door open as exciting Celtic transfer target now not even training with first team]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172097</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-will-be-watching-as-kieran-tierney-now-not-even-included-in-arsenal-training/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T12:40:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kieran Tierney is increasingly finding himself on the sidelines at Arsenal after it was reported he is now not even taking part in Mikel Arteta’s...
The post Door open as exciting Celtic transfer target now not even training with first team appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good signs for Rodgers and Celtic as we all prepare for a different feeling this weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172082</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/good-signs-for-rodgers-and-celtic-as-we-all-prepare-for-a-different-feeling-this-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T12:10:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will be aiming for a big response this weekend against St. Johnstone. It’s been a fair old period of time since there was a...
The post Good signs for Rodgers and Celtic as we all prepare for a different feeling this weekend appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic talks for seventh signing of the summer confirmed]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43626</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/24/celtic-talks-seventh-signing-summer/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T12:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been pretty busy during the course of the summer transfer window. While fans are not happy with the lack of big-name, experienced and established additions, the Hoops have brought in six new players to the club regardless. They are Odin Thiago Holm, Marco Tilio, Yang Hyun-jun, Kwon Hyeok-kyu, Maik Nawrocki and Gustaf Lagerbielke. […]
Celtic talks for seventh signing of the summer confirmed - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Celtic have done the right thing"; ex-Hoops hero backs high-profile transfer exit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172078</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-have-done-the-right-thing-ex-hoops-hero-backs-high-profile-transfer-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s transfer business has come under scrutiny over the past few days amid the current injury crisis and the team’s current performances. The club have...
The post "Celtic have done the right thing"; ex-Hoops hero backs high-profile transfer exit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: European side eye Jota move; could team up with a few familiar Celtic names]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172073</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/european-side-eye-jota-move-could-team-up-with-a-few-familiar-celtic-names/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T11:13:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic winger Jota is a target for Fenerbahce, according to a report. Turkish outlet Sporx say that the Super Lig side are ready to...
The post Report: European side eye Jota move; could team up with a few familiar Celtic names appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Helicoptering in central defenders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111315</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/helicoptering-in-central-defenders/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T11:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I know we are all concerned about the injury crisis affecting central defence, but it is difficult to move the dial here in the short term.  Central defence is overwhelmingly about partnerships.  You can try to helicopter someone into the team (think Carl Starfelt two years ago) but it seldom provides an immediate return. If [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant pinpoints the one tactic that is causing Celtic creative problems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172069</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/peter-grant-pinpoints-the-one-tactic-that-is-causing-celtic-creative-problems/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were, and still are, under the microscope this week after the club’s exit from the league cup against Kilmarnock. The 1-0 defeat ended Brendan...
The post Peter Grant pinpoints the one tactic that is causing Celtic creative problems appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O'Riley offers some sound reasoning for Celtic's early season form]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172065</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/matt-oriley-offers-some-sound-reasoning-for-celtics-early-season-form/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s early season form has been a little inconsistent, shall we say? Despite two wins the SPFL, the team hasn’t quite the heights of performance...
The post Matt O'Riley offers some sound reasoning for Celtic's early season form appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Thursday August 24: We Have Stopped]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18465</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18465"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T09:21:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a crisis looming in the centre of the Celtic defence, the board have swung into action and made a bid for Honduran winger Luis…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Malph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic face another battle with Saudi Arabian cash in fresh transfer pursuit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172038</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-face-another-battle-with-saudi-arabian-cash-in-fresh-transfer-pursuit/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic could face another battle with Saudi Arabian cash in their pursuit of Luis Palma. Earlier on Thursday we told you about our fresh move...
The post Report: Celtic face another battle with Saudi Arabian cash in fresh transfer pursuit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Women are flying as Fran Alonso's side lay down early season marker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172061</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/celtic-women-are-flying-as-fran-alonsos-side-lay-down-early-season-marker/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Away from the trials and tribulations that face Brendan Rodgers for a minute, Celtic Women are flying this season as Fran Alonso‘s side continues their...
The post Celtic Women are flying as Fran Alonso's side lay down early season marker appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic close to next signing after making €4.1 million bid]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43620</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/24/celtic-close-next-signing-million-bid/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T08:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic could certainly do with more reinforcements before the summer transfer window slams shut. Their performances over the first three games of the season have shown that this side is missing a creative spark at the moment. They were not able to score against Kilmarnock and got knocked out of the Scottish League Cup in […]
Celtic close to next signing after making €4.1 million bid - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic discover new price tag for Mathias Kvistgaarden as demand for striker rises]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172048</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-discover-new-price-tag-for-mathias-kvistgaarden-as-demand-for-striker-rises/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the news that Celtic are looking to strengthen before the end of the summer window and targets are being reported in the media, it...
The post Report: Celtic discover new price tag for Mathias Kvistgaarden as demand for striker rises appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: European club seriously considering Celtic offer for goalscoring talent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172050</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-move-for-luis-palma-looks-a-goer-after-fresh-report-arrives-from-greece/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s move for Luis Palma looks like it could be a good one after a fresh report from Greece. Celtic fans may only just be...
The post Report: European club seriously considering Celtic offer for goalscoring talent appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DEAL OR NO DEAL? CELTIC TOLD NEW PRICE FOR STRIKER]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111308</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/deal-or-no-deal-celtic-told-new-price-for-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T07:34:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have been told they will have to stump up almost £6million for Danish striker Mathias Kvistgaarden – who was valued at £2million in January. The 21-year-old Brondby hitman has seen his value leap almost 300 percent in eight months after signing a four-year contract extension in June which more than doubled his wages. The [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Current Celtic star offers an important reminder after disheartening 2023 departures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172002</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/matt-oriley-offers-an-important-celtic-reminder-after-disheartening-2023-departures/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T06:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O’Riley has been speaking about the joy he feels playing in front of Celtic supporters. The Denmark youth international has been in Glasgow for...
The post Current Celtic star offers an important reminder after disheartening 2023 departures appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: The Arsenal Kieran Tierney stance that could encourage late Celtic transfer move]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172029</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/the-arsenal-kieran-tierney-stance-that-could-encourage-late-celtic-transfer-move/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T06:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arsenal are open to offers for former Celtic defender Kieran Tierney this summer, according to a report. Tierney has endured a rough start to the...
The post Report: The Arsenal Kieran Tierney stance that could encourage late Celtic transfer move appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC IN £3.5m PALMA RAID]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111303</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-in-3-5m-palma-raid/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T05:43:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have launched a £3.5million raid to sign Honduran international winger Luis Palma. The 23-year-old Aris Thessaloniki flanker could be heading to the champions with just a week remaining before the transfer deadline, according to a report in the Scottish Daily Mail. Palma is one of the hottest young properties in Europe at the moment [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic heading for busy end to summer transfer window]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172020</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-heading-for-busy-end-to-summer-transfer-window-after-encouraging-report/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T05:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are hoping to conclude multiple deals in the final week of the transfer window, according to a report. The Hoops have under nine days...
The post Report: Celtic heading for busy end to summer transfer window appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic launch fresh winger move but there's less encouraging Podence and Fraser news]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172011</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-launch-fresh-winger-move-but-theres-a-hurdle-to-overcome-for-podence-and-fraser/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T05:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have launched a move for winger Luis Palma while there are hurdles to overcome in the chase for Daniel Podence and Ryan Fraser, according...
The post Report: Celtic launch fresh winger move but there's less encouraging Podence and Fraser news appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic launch fresh winger move but there's less encouraging Podence and Fraser news]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172011</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-launch-fresh-winger-move-but-theres-a-hurdle-to-overcome-for-podence-and-fraser/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T05:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have launched a move for winger Luis Palma while there are hurdles to overcome in the chase for Daniel Podence and Ryan Fraser, according...
The post Report: Celtic launch fresh winger move but there's less encouraging Podence and Fraser news appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans offered superb late night triple transfer news]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43617</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/23/celtic-late-night-triple-transfer-news/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T22:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans are not completely satisfied with how this summer transfer window has played out for the Hoops. It is easily understandable why. When Brendan Rodgers was brought back for a second stint in the Parkhead hot seat, there were suggestions in the media that the club were ready to hand him a significant budget […]
Celtic fans offered superb late night triple transfer news - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed Reo Hatate boost as situation takes twist]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43614</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/23/celtic-reo-hatate-boost-twist/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T21:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans were left worried earlier as it emerged that Reo Hatate had turned down a contract offer from the club. Many supporters were quick to point out the similarities between the situation of the Japanese midfielder and that of former players like Josip Juranovic and Giorgos Giakoumakis. Rumours had broken out that they had […]
Celtic handed Reo Hatate boost as situation takes twist - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘We ask an awful lot’: John Hartson says Celtic rely on two players a bit too much]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171986</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/we-ask-an-awful-lot-john-hartson-says-celtic-rely-on-two-players-a-bit-too-much/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T20:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Hartson wants the pressure eased on Celtic duo Kyogo Furuhashi and Callum McGregor. The duo have been pivotal to Celtic’s dominance in recent years,...
The post ‘We ask an awful lot’: John Hartson says Celtic rely on two players a bit too much appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic named favourites to bring back Kieran Tierney]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43611</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/23/celtic-favourites-back-kieran-tierney/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T19:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the Kieran Tierney to Celtic rumours first broke out, it seemed nothing but mere fantasy. Creation of the rumour mill. Yet, after the first few matchdays of the 2023/24 campaign and as we head towards the end of the summer transfer window, it looks like there is a real possibility that the Scottish left-back […]
Celtic named favourites to bring back Kieran Tierney - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How much Celtic charged for Champions League tickets last season as fans brace for official news]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171939</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/how-much-celtic-charged-for-champions-league-tickets-last-season-as-fans-brace-for-official-news/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans will find out how much the club are charging for UEFA Champions League tickets very soon. The club could have a home Champions...
The post How much Celtic charged for Champions League tickets last season as fans brace for official news appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports man offers Reo Hatate news amid Celtic exit fears]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43607</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/23/sky-sports-reo-hatate-celtic-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T18:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate arrived at Celtic in the January transfer window of 2022 and has been one of the best players in Scottish football ever since. The Japanese midfielder has proven to be a class apart and has not looked out of place even when playing in the Champions League. The start to life in the […]
Sky Sports man offers Reo Hatate news amid Celtic exit fears - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two free former Celtic stars still looking for a club; one could do a job for Brendan Rodgers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171972</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/two-free-former-celtic-stars-still-looking-for-a-club-one-could-do-a-job-for-brendan-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the transfer window draws to a close, there will be many players in the game wanting a move who will be looking anxiously towards...
The post Two free former Celtic stars still looking for a club; one could do a job for Brendan Rodgers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic stars feature in official UEFA fantasy football; highest value, most picked, goals issue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171949</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-stars-feature-in-official-uefa-fantasy-football-highest-value-most-picked-goals-issue/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are back in the Champions League group stage again this season, and that means the club will also be featured in the official fantasy...
The post Celtic stars feature in official UEFA fantasy football; highest value, most picked, goals issue appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers' transfer comments could be a cause for concern for Celtic fans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171936</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/brendan-rodgers-transfer-comments-could-be-a-cause-for-concern-or-a-case-of-business-as-usual/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With less than ten days to go in the transfer window, the Celtic support will be looking to the club to add a few more...
The post Brendan Rodgers' transfer comments could be a cause for concern for Celtic fans appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic cult hero tips summer signing for international call-up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171978</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-cult-hero-tips-summer-signing-for-international-call-up/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender, Maik Nawrocki, has been tipped to make the international breakthrough for Poland by former Celtic striker, Dariusz Dziekanowski. Dziekanowski became a cult hero...
The post Former Celtic cult hero tips summer signing for international call-up appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer preference may have to change as deadline day drama approaches - opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171963</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/celtic-transfer-preference-may-have-to-change-as-deadline-day-drama-approaches-opinion/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have developed a real preference for permanent transfers in recent seasons. Since the summer of 2021, the club have made a conscious effort to...
The post Celtic transfer preference may have to change as deadline day drama approaches - opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report offers hope over Reo Hatate contract talks at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171951</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/report-offers-hope-over-reo-hatate-contract-talks-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This morning, 67 Hail Hail discussed that Reo Hatate had turned down the opportunity to sign a new contract at Celtic. The report from The...
The post Report offers hope over Reo Hatate contract talks at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms important Celtic injury boost]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43601</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/23/rodgers-confirms-celtic-injury-boost/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T12:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic find themselves in a terrible spot right now when it comes to injuries. They have several key players out of action like Cameron Carter-Vickers, Reo Hatate and Stephen Welsh. Maik Nawrocki picked up a problem in the last game against Kilmarnock as well. Thus, Brendan Rodgers’ options have become limited when it comes to […]
Brendan Rodgers confirms important Celtic injury boost - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Hartson reacts to possible Celtic return for Jota amid Al-Ittihad issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171904</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/delighted-john-hartson-reacts-to-possible-celtic-return-for-jota-amid-al-ittihad-issues/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Hartson has played down Jota’s chances of making a sensational return to Celtic after only leaving this summer. Celtic’s Treble-winning hero jumped on the...
The post John Hartson reacts to possible Celtic return for Jota amid Al-Ittihad issues appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers could improve Celtic's midfield creativity 'problem' with one obvious change]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171922</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/brendan-rodgers-could-improve-celtics-midfield-creativity-problem-with-one-obvious-change/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s lack of creativity on Sunday was ultimately the reason why Brendan Rodgers’ men found themselves out of the cup. But Brendan Rodgers could solve...
The post Brendan Rodgers could improve Celtic's midfield creativity 'problem' with one obvious change appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recruiting players of CCV and Jota quality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111299</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/recruiting-players-of-ccv-and-jota-quality/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T11:01:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last summer Celtic concluded the permanent transfers of Cameron Carter-Vickers and Jota, both previously on loan at the club, early in the summer, as did free agent Aaron Mooy.  We did not need to contend with selling clubs for any of these deals, as options had already been signed with Tottenham and Benfica. The only [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rodgers on "frustrating" Celtic trend out of his control; surprisingly early Ibrox question]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171865</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/rodgers-on-frustrating-celtic-trend-thats-out-of-his-control-surprisingly-early-ibrox-question/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers admits that the recent spate of Celtic first-team injuries has been frustrating. The Hoops boss is still very early on in his second...
The post Rodgers on "frustrating" Celtic trend out of his control; surprisingly early Ibrox question appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN HAILS ‘SCREEN GEM’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111288</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/brendan-hails-screen-gem/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T10:24:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ALISTAIR JOHNSTON was a screen gem the first time Brendan Rodgers witnessed him in action. The future Celt was performing for Canada in the winter World Cup Finals in Qatar when the second time-around Hoops boss took notice of his defensive skills while watching on television four months before he left Leicester City. Johnston looked comfortable [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans get a welcome Marco Tilio reminder online; when long-awaited debut could arrive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171886</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-fans-get-a-welcome-marco-tilio-reminder-online-when-long-awaited-debut-could-arrive/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans were given a welcome reminder about Marco Tilio on social media on Wednesday morning. It’s easy to forget about the Australian summer arrival...
The post Celtic fans get a welcome Marco Tilio reminder online; when long-awaited debut could arrive appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy talked up as Socceroo tells of admiration for the former Celtic midfielder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171899</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/aaron-mooy-talked-up-as-socceroo-tells-of-admiration-for-the-former-celtic-midfielder/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy came to Celtic in the latter stages of his career and it is fair to say his arrival wasn’t met with much enthusiasm...
The post Aaron Mooy talked up as Socceroo tells of admiration for the former Celtic midfielder appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player rejects the club’s contract extension offer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43598</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/23/celtic-player-rejects-contract-offer/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T09:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a number of worries at this point in time. Just three games into the 2023/24 season and they are already out of the Scottish League Cup, something which nobody would have expected when Brendan Rodgers was reappointed as the club’s manager. After all, he had not lost a single domestic competition in Scotland […]
Celtic player rejects the club’s contract extension offer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charlie Mulgrew backs Celtic star Joe Hart to deliver for Brendan Rodgers; but with a caveat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171889</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/charlie-mulgrew-backs-celtic-star-joe-hart-to-deliver-for-brendan-rodgers-but-with-a-caveat/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart has found himself under a bit of pressure at Celtic over the last few weeks. The Hoops goalkeeper has done a sterling job...
The post Charlie Mulgrew backs Celtic star Joe Hart to deliver for Brendan Rodgers; but with a caveat appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Celtic deal with the Reo Hatate situation depends on two scenarios]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171876</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/how-celtic-deal-with-the-reo-hatate-situation-depends-on-two-scenarios/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The news of Reo Hatate turning down a new contract will come as a disappointing blow to the club and the Celtic supporters. The Japanese...
The post How Celtic deal with the Reo Hatate situation depends on two scenarios appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Wednesday August 23: Rumours….]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18463</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18463"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T08:03:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the great things about the internet , especially where Celtic is concerned, is that you don’t have to look very far to find…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Malph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Context is key as Celtic B continue to struggle in Lowland League standings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171857</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/context-is-key-as-celtic-b-continue-to-struggle-in-lowland-league-standings/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Lowland League is not a pretty picture as far as Celtic B are concerned right now. The Hoops stars of the future are currently...
The post Context is key as Celtic B continue to struggle in Lowland League standings appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘REAL CHALLENGE,’ RODGERS’ TRANSFER CONFESSION]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111281</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/real-challenge-rodgers-transfer-confession/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T07:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has revealed the transfer challenges he is facing as the Irishman scours the market before the midnight signing deadline a week tomorrow. It’s clear the Celtic boss has to strengthen an injury-stricken squad of players with only three games – against St Johnstone and Dundee at Parkhead and the first derby of the season [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Fam reunion"; recently departed Celtic duo meet up after moving to the same country]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171869</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/fam-reunion-recently-departed-celtic-duo-meet-up-after-moving-to-the-same-country/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T06:42:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently departed Celtic pair Josip Juranovic and Moritz Jenz have met up in Berlin. The duo were Hoops team-mates this time last year, but both...
The post "Fam reunion"; recently departed Celtic duo meet up after moving to the same country appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘VERY FRUSTRATING,’ ADMITS RODGERS AFTER PROBLEM PILE-UP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111279</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/very-frustrating-admits-rodgers-after-problem-pile-up/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T06:19:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS admits he is exasperated at the growing injury pile-up as he plots to get Celtic back on track after the massive setback at Kilmarnock on Sunday. The Hoops boss is preparing his squad for the match against St Johnstone at Parkhead on Saturday ahead of their trip to Ibrox for the first derby [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rodgers explains how Celtic have changed since 2019; now fans want to see something different]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171844</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-backs-new-found-celtic-transfer-strategy-now-fans-want-to-see-something-different/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T06:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers has been speaking about the club’s recently-found recruitment strategy. Over the past five transfer windows Celtic have signed players from all...
The post Rodgers explains how Celtic have changed since 2019; now fans want to see something different appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NO DEAL: HATATE KNOCKS BACK CELTIC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111277</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/no-deal-hatate-knocks-back-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T05:44:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE has knocked back a contract extension at Celtic. The rejection from the Japanese midfielder has sparked speculation he will be quitting the champions before the end of his current deal which runs until June 2026. The Hoops hierarchy made similar offers to Hatate’s countrymen Kyogo Furuhashi and Daizen Maeda last month with both [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic man turns down new contract as club make their intentions clear]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171850</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/disappointing-reo-hatate-update-as-celtic-make-future-intentions-clear/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T05:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder Reo Hatate has rejected a new contract offer, according to a report. The Scottish Sun say that the Japanese midfielder has turned down...
The post Report: Celtic man turns down new contract as club make their intentions clear appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers paves the way for significant injury return at just the right time for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171835</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-picks-his-moment-for-big-alistair-johnston-talk-significant-celtic-boost-coming/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T05:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has picked his moment to talk up Celtic full-back Alistair Johnston, with his return from injury imminent. The Canadian defender hasn’t featured yet...
The post Brendan Rodgers paves the way for significant injury return at just the right time for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE BIRTH OF A LEGEND: BILLY McNEILL: PART FOUR: MIKE JACKSON REMEMBERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=65856</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-birth-of-a-legend-billy-mcneill-part-four-mike-jackson-remembers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T04:03:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Billy McNeill made his first team debut exactly SIXTY-FIVE  years ago today and took his first steps into club folklore. Author Alex Gordon paid tribute to his friend in his publication, ‘BILLY McNEILL: In Praise of Caesar‘, which was published in 2018. In the fourth and concluding part of CQN’S EXCLUSIVE series, we [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE BIRTH OF A LEGEND: BILLY McNEILL: PART THREE: JOHN FALLON REMEMBERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=65855</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-birth-of-a-legend-billy-mcneill-part-three-john-fallon-remembers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T04:02:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Billy McNeill made his first team debut exactly SIXTY-FIVE years ago today and took his first steps into club folklore. Author Alex Gordon paid tribute to his friend in his publication, ‘BILLY McNEILL: In Praise of Caesar‘, which was published in 2018. In Part Three of CQN’S EXCLUSIVE series, we continue our walk down [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE BIRTH OF A LEGEND: BILLY McNEILL: PART TWO: PAT CRERAND REMEMBERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=65853</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-birth-of-a-legend-billy-mcneill-part-two-pat-crerand-remembers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T04:01:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Billy McNeill made his first team debut exactly SIXTY-FIVE years ago today and took his first steps into club folklore. Author Alex Gordon paid tribute to his friend in his publication, ‘BILLY McNEILL: In Praise of Caesar‘, which was published in 2018. In Part Two of CQN’S EXCLUSIVE series, we continue our walk [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE BIRTH OF A LEGEND: BILLY McNEILL: PART ONE: ICON’S DEBUT 65 YEARS AGO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=65849</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-birth-of-a-legend-billy-mcneill-part-one-icons-debut-65-years-ago/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T04:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Billy McNeill made his first team debut exactly SIXTY-FIVE years ago today and took his first steps into club folklore. The iconic former manager and player, who sadly passed away on April 22 2019 at the age of seventy-nine, played 790 games for his only club, winning nine league championships, seven Scottish Cups, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fulham could hand cash boost to Celtic by signing former player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43580</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/22/fulham-celtic-signing-former-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T22:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic try to get some deals done for quality signings before the summer transfer window closes, there’s news of a potential boost that could help the club. The club have done well in the past with sell-on clauses when they have parted ways with players and another may be about to come into play. […]
Fulham could hand cash boost to Celtic by signing former player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers admits frustration at Celtic situation]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43590</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/22/brendan-rodgers-admits-celtic-situation/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T21:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers had never lost a domestic competition as Celtic manager during his first stint at the club. Three games into his second run at Parkhead and that is no longer the case. The Northern Irishman saw his team being knocked out of the Scottish League Cup at the weekend, following a 1-0 defeat at […]
Brendan Rodgers admits frustration at Celtic situation - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘You will see’: Neil Lennon makes encouraging transfer claim about Rodgers & Celtic board]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171815</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/you-will-see-neil-lennon-makes-encouraging-transfer-claim-about-brendan-rodgers-celtic-board/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon thinks, before the 2023 summer transfer slams shut, Celtic will bring in ‘quality players’ for Brendan Rodgers. The former Celtic boss even stated...
The post ‘You will see’: Neil Lennon makes encouraging transfer claim about Rodgers & Celtic board  appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic open negotiations to sign £60k-a-week winger]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43586</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/22/celtic-open-negotiations-sign-60k-week-winger/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T19:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there is one thing that has become clear over the first few weeks of the 2023/24 campaign, it is that Celtic need to add some creativity and inspiration to this team quickly. The Hoops have looked like a shell of their treble-winning selves from last season. And they are already out of the Scottish […]
Celtic open negotiations to sign £60k-a-week winger - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic change transfer plans after recent injury blow]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43583</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/22/celtic-change-transfer-plans-injury/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T18:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are not in a good position right now to be very honest. It is not just about the fact that they were knocked out of the Scottish League Cup at the hands of Kilmarnock this early in the campaign. Winning a treble every season is not possible and fans will recognise that. Their biggest […]
Celtic change transfer plans after recent injury blow - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The fee Celtic were expecting to get for Liam Scales as Aberdeen move on]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171803</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-fee-celtic-were-expecting-to-get-for-liam-scales-as-aberdeen-move-on/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liam Scales’ time at Celtic has certainly been a mixed bag of fortune for the Irishman. Earlier on 67 Hail Hail we discussed how Scales...
The post The fee Celtic were expecting to get for Liam Scales as Aberdeen move on appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["They are a fantastic young side"; Celtic B team talked up ahead of Lowland league fixture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171787</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/they-are-a-fantastic-young-side-celtic-b-team-earns-praise-ahead-of-lowland-league-fixture/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Away from first-team duties for a minute, Darren O’Dea and Stephen McManus’ Celtic side are set to face East Kilbride tonight in the Lowland League....
The post "They are a fantastic young side"; Celtic B team talked up ahead of Lowland league fixture appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four young Celtic talents earn recognition as Scotland announce u19 squad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171810</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/four-young-celtic-talents-earn-recognition-as-scotland-announce-u19-squad/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Four young Celtic prospects have been called up to Scotland’s u19 squad ahead of the friendlies against Belgium and the Czech Republic next month. In...
The post Four young Celtic talents earn recognition as Scotland announce u19 squad appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hibernian man compares Celtic to Aston Villa as Neil Lennon weighs in with alternative tactic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171795</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/hibernian-man-compares-celtic-to-aston-villa-as-neil-lennon-weighs-in-with-alternative-tactic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are not in action this midweek or next as the UEFA qualifiers reach their end point for another season. As we’ve already covered, there...
The post Hibernian man compares Celtic to Aston Villa as Neil Lennon weighs in with alternative tactic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hope for Celtic fans as transfer tension continues to rise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171776</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/2021-example-offers-celtic-fans-hope-as-transfer-tension-continues-to-rise/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s fair to say that tension has risen amongst the Celtic support during this transfer window. While that has been the case over the past...
The post Hope for Celtic fans as transfer tension continues to rise appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC JURANOVIC WINDFALL?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111271</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-juranovic-windfall/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T12:15:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC are standing by for a cash windfall with former right-back Josip Juranovic linked with a £10million move to Fulham. The Croatia defender left the champions in January in a £7.5million switch to Union Berlin, as CQN reported at the time. Juranovic spent only 18 months at Parkhead after he had been snapped up for [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A huge opportunity has opened up for Celtic fringe player amid unfortunate injury crisis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171768</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/a-huge-opportunity-has-opened-up-for-celtic-fringe-player-amid-unfortunate-injury-crisis/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s recent injury crisis has come at an already difficult time of the season. After news broke last night of Maik Nawrocki’s injury, the Celtic...
The post A huge opportunity has opened up for Celtic fringe player amid unfortunate injury crisis appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The four Champions League playoff sides who could bring Celtic an on-pitch reward]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171731</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/remote-possibility-the-four-champions-league-playoff-sides-celtic-fans-should-be-supporting/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UEFA Champions League has reached the playoff round, with Celtic up soon. As you will surely be aware, the Hoops have bypassed Champions League...
The post The four Champions League playoff sides who could bring Celtic an on-pitch reward appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed chance to bring back Jota as free agent]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43577</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/22/celtic-bring-back-jota-free-agent/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T11:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last month, Jota completed a move away from Celtic, joining Al-Ittihad in a £25 million deal. The Hoops might have pocketed a large transfer fee out of his exit but they have had a hard time filling the void left behind by the Portuguese winger. In his absence, the team seem to have lost a […]
Celtic handed chance to bring back Jota as free agent - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are lucky regarding central def injuries]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111269</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-are-lucky-regarding-central-def-injuries/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T11:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[48 hours ago, Celtic fans were in relative equilibrium.  Defeat in the League Cup and an injury crisis in central defence put paid to that.  Maik Nawrocki injured his hamstring at Rugby Park.  He played until the end of the game, doubtlessly conflicted by the team’s predicament, but as Oh did earlier this month, almost [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rectifying the glaring midfield issue from the early weeks of Celtic's season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171753</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/rectifying-the-glaring-midfield-issue-from-the-early-weeks-of-celtics-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the Celtic defence has come in for deserved criticism in the early weeks of the season, the midfield has been an area of concern...
The post Rectifying the glaring midfield issue from the early weeks of Celtic's season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Celtic are not firing on all cylinders under Brendan Rodgers; Charlie Mulgrew nails it]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171758</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/why-celtic-are-not-firing-on-all-cylinders-under-brendan-rodgers-charlie-mulgrew-nails-it/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pundits and ex-Celtic players have had plenty to say over the past few days on why Celtic don’t seem to be at their best under...
The post Why Celtic are not firing on all cylinders under Brendan Rodgers; Charlie Mulgrew nails it appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confirmed: Referee handed Celtic debut as SFA announce officials vs St Johnstone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171748</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/confirmed-referee-handed-celtic-debut-as-sfa-announce-officials-vs-st-johnstone/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The games are coming thick and fast for Celtic as the new season gets well underway. Next up for Brendan Rodgers’ men is the visit...
The post Confirmed: Referee handed Celtic debut as SFA announce officials vs St Johnstone appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor explains why Celtic's old guard will be pivotal in the coming weeks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171742</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/callum-mcgregor-explains-why-celtics-old-guard-will-be-pivotal-in-the-coming-weeks/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have added six new summer signings and with the promise of more to come from Brendan Rodgers, there will be a period of prolonged...
The post Callum McGregor explains why Celtic's old guard will be pivotal in the coming weeks appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Injured Celtic defender could return in time to face Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43573</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/22/celtic-defender-return-time-face-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T09:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are facing an injury crisis just three games into the new season. Every match, something new seems to crop up. Cameron Carter-Vickers and Reo Hatate got injured against Aberdeen away at the Pittodrie Stadium. And Maik Nawrocki picked up an issue in the defeat to Kilmarnock away at Rugby Park. Stephen Welsh ended up […]
Injured Celtic defender could return in time to face Rangers - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Tuesday August 22: Same Sad Story]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18460</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18460"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T08:40:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a stunningly inept performance at Rugby Park on Sunday, Celtic crashed out of the League cup at the first hurdle.   It wasn’t very…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Malph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton discusses Celtic's Kilmarnock issues that could become a 'problem' at Ibrox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171729</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-discusses-celtics-kilmarnock-issue-that-could-become-a-problem-at-ibrox/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the fallout over Celtic’s cup exit to Kilmarnock continues, attention is already starting to turn to the first Glasgow Derby match of the season....
The post Chris Sutton discusses Celtic's Kilmarnock issues that could become a 'problem' at Ibrox appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Celtic's defence is shaping up for Ibrox trip after latest injury update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171721</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/how-celtics-defence-is-shaping-up-for-ibrox-trip-after-latest-injury-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just how unlucky can one manager be when it comes to injuries? Brendan Rodgers now has four central defenders on the treatment table at an...
The post How Celtic's defence is shaping up for Ibrox trip after latest injury update appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Greg Taylor quandary facing Brendan Rodgers and Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171713</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-greg-taylor-quandary-facing-brendan-rodgers-and-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T06:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic full-back Greg Taylor hasn’t looked half the player he was last season so far this campaign. The Scotland international has struggled to replicate his...
The post The Greg Taylor quandary facing Brendan Rodgers and Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star didn't forget his Hoops upbringing with class May visit to Ibrox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171697</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/stephen-welsh-didnt-forget-his-celtic-upbringing-with-class-may-visit-to-ibrox/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T06:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scot Gemmill has been talking up Celtic defender Stephen Welsh in the media. The Scotland under-21 manager knows Welsh well from their time together in...
The post Celtic star didn't forget his Hoops upbringing with class May visit to Ibrox appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I don't': Chris Sutton responds as Manchester United fan asks his side to sign Celtic star]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171690</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/i-dont-chris-sutton-responds-as-manchester-united-fan-asks-his-side-to-sign-celtic-star/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T05:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton responded to a Manchester United fan wanting his club to sign Celtic’s superstar forward, Kyogo Furuhashi. The former striker made it clear and...
The post 'I don't': Chris Sutton responds as Manchester United fan asks his side to sign Celtic star appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic first-team injury situation gets even more concerning; full picture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171682</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-latest-on-every-current-celtic-first-team-injury-as-situation-gets-more-concerning/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T05:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic find themselves in the midst of a bit of an injury crisis at present. The Hoops are in a pretty unfortunate place after a...
The post Celtic first-team injury situation gets even more concerning; full picture appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS’ DRAMATIC SOS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111265</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-dramatic-sos/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T04:48:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is poised to send a dramatic SOS to Liam Scales as Celtic central defensive injuries pile up. New Bhoy Maik Nawrocki, who has played only three games since his £4.3million arrival from Legia Warsaw, sustained a hamstring pull in the closing stages of the Viaplay League Cup exit at Kilmarnock on Sunday. The [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player suffered hamstring injury vs Kilmarnock]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43568</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/21/celtic-player-suffered-hamstring-injury/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T23:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic find themselves in deep trouble at the moment. We are just two weeks into the season and their injury list is already significant. And no area of the pitch has been more hurt by this than centre-back. Carl Starfelt left earlier in order to join Celta Vigo. Since then, three centre-backs have ended up […]
Celtic player suffered hamstring injury vs Kilmarnock - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed blow in race for Manchester City player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43564</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/21/celtic-race-manchester-city-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T21:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic seem to be concentrating on signing highly-rated young players from all around the globe at the moment. They have already signed six of them this summer and continue to be linked with several others. It remains to be seen how things play out in that regard, with less than two weeks left in the […]
Celtic handed blow in race for Manchester City player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic struck by yet another injury blow; major doubts for Ibrox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171634</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-struck-by-another-defensive-injury-blow-major-doubts-for-derby/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T20:45:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Maik Nawrocki has suffered a hamstring injury and is a major doubt for the upcoming trip to Ibrox on September 3rd. The Scottish...
The post Celtic struck by yet another injury blow; major doubts for Ibrox appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Any Celtic path to signing Man City man is looking a little clearer after events in England]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171665</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/any-celtic-path-to-signing-tommy-doyle-is-looking-a-little-clearer-after-events-in-england/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T20:20:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tommy Doyle’s preferred summer move back to Sheffield United is looking more and more distant, journalist Alan Nixon has reported. Nixon believes that the Blades...
The post Any Celtic path to signing Man City man is looking a little clearer after events in England appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arsenal hand Kieran Tierney transfer boost to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43559</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/21/arsenal-kieran-tierney-transfer-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T20:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with quite a few big names over the summer even though they are yet to make any high-profile additions to their roster. One of the more surprising rumours from this window has seen the Hoops being linked with a move for Kieran Tierney, who finds himself in an unenviable position at […]
Arsenal hand Kieran Tierney transfer boost to Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Celtic should be cheering on Panathinaikos and Rakow in UEFA Champions League this week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171660</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/why-celtic-should-be-cheering-on-panathinaikos-and-rakow-in-uefa-champions-league-this-week/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T19:47:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are, thankfully, not involved in UEFA qualifiers this summer but that doesn’t mean there isn’t interest for the Bhoys in these matches as the...
The post Why Celtic should be cheering on Panathinaikos and Rakow in UEFA Champions League this week appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers suggests he's about to make a big change for upcoming Celtic match]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171654</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-suggests-changes-are-coming-to-celtic-for-weekend-clash/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T19:10:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the only Celtic players to take any credit out of Sunday’s defeat to Kilmarnock was new signing Hyunjun Yang. The South Korean came...
The post Brendan Rodgers suggests he's about to make a big change for upcoming Celtic match appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic could have to pay £4 million fee to sign striker]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43555</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/21/celtic-4-million-fee-sign-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T18:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already suffered their first big blow of the season as they were knocked out of the Scottish League Cup at the hands of Kilmarnock in the second round. It goes without saying that it was a major disappointed for the fans and also ends Brendan Rodgers’ run of winning every domestic trophy that […]
Celtic could have to pay £4 million fee to sign striker - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star gets serious and ups the stakes for Bhoys dressing room with firm address]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171649</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/callum-mcgregor-gets-serious-and-ups-the-stakes-for-celtic-dressing-room-with-firm-address/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T18:13:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will need their most experienced players and dressing room leaders to come to the fore over the coming days after the shock Scottish League...
The post Celtic star gets serious and ups the stakes for Bhoys dressing room with firm address appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers delivers verdict on first Celtic starts for Lagerbielke and Holm]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171644</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-delivers-verdict-on-first-celtic-starts-for-lagerbielke-and-holm/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T17:11:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic fans come to terms with a shock defeat in Kilmarnock on Sunday, it’s important to keep things in perspective. The cup exit was...
The post Brendan Rodgers delivers verdict on first Celtic starts for Lagerbielke and Holm appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Noises from Celtic that a different kind of player is about arrive in summer transfer window]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171640</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-comments-suggest-a-different-profile-of-signing-could-be-on-the-way-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T16:40:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers insists that the club are happy to sign up a more experienced, older player to the Bhoys this summer if he feels they...
The post Noises from Celtic that a different kind of player is about arrive in summer transfer window appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Premier League clubs 'signal interest' in former Celtic defender]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171632</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/premier-league-clubs-signal-interest-in-former-celtic-favourite-josip-juranovic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic favourite, Josip Juranovic is reportedly attracting interest from English Premier League side, Fulham. A report from German outlet Kicker has claimed that the...
The post Report: Premier League clubs 'signal interest' in former Celtic defender appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["We spoke to Celtic"; Premier League striker discusses why move to Paradise never materialised]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171618</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/we-spoke-to-celtic-ivan-toney-tells-why-move-to-paradise-never-happened/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brentford striker, Ivan Toney, has opened up on why his proposed move to Celtic never materialised in 2020. The Englishman was a target for former...
The post "We spoke to Celtic"; Premier League striker discusses why move to Paradise never materialised appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Brondby's Director of Football speaks as Celtic learn price tag for Mathias Kvistgaarden]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171621</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brondbys-director-of-football-speaks-as-celtic-learn-price-tag-for-mathias-kvistgaarden/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recent transfer rumour of Celtic’s interest in Brondby striker, Mathias Kvistgaarden, has been given a shot in the arm as a report names the...
The post Report: Brondby's Director of Football speaks as Celtic learn price tag for Mathias Kvistgaarden appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton asks questions of Celtic after cup disappointment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171612</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-raises-concerns-over-celtics-transfer-business-after-cup-disappointment/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the fallout over Celtic’s cup exit to Kilmarnock rumbles on, former Celtic hero, Chris Sutton, has asked serious questions about the club’s transfer business...
The post Chris Sutton asks questions of Celtic after cup disappointment appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ivan Toney explains why he decided not to join Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43549</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/21/ivan-toney-explains-decided-join-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T12:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ivan Toney is currently out of the game due to a ban and will not be back in action this year. Despite that, nobody can deny his quality and when he does return to the pitch, one would expect him to start scoring goals once again. In recent years, he has proven to be one […]
Ivan Toney explains why he decided not to join Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers delivers Treble reality check after Celtic's disappointing cup defeat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171607</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-delivers-treble-reality-check-after-celtics-disappointing-cup-defeat/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic supporters, we have gotten used to winning trebles over the past decade or so. So much so that whenever we don’t manage to...
The post Brendan Rodgers delivers Treble reality check after Celtic's disappointing cup defeat appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stinging defeat leaves us pondering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111264</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/stinging-defeat-leaves-us-pondering/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T11:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No excuses, Celtic were poor and deserved nothing more than they got at Kilmarnock yesterday.  Too often a new central defensive partnership looked for a forward pass and were faced with statuesque targets.  Kilmarnock went man-to-man and were mostly able to keep the contest in the middle of the park until very late in the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS AND THE £30m QUESTION]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111261</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/brendan-rodgers-and-the-30m-question/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T10:50:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS pledged to spend to add quality to his Celtic squad with only TEN days left until the August 31 transfer deadline. The Hoops boss was bitterly disappointed following the inept and unacceptable display from his team as the holders crashed out of the Viaplay League Cup against Kilmarnock yesterday. It was a disjointed [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former referee makes bizarre verdict on Celtic's penalty claim vs Kilmarnock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171604</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/former-referees-bizarre-verdict-on-celtics-penalty-claim-vs-kilmarnock/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T10:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the fallout over Celtic’s defeat to Kilmarnock in the cup continues, the fans will be picking over the bones of the result to understand...
The post Former referee makes bizarre verdict on Celtic's penalty claim vs Kilmarnock appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BBC pundit 'expects' significant transfer movement after Celtic's cup exit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171599</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/pat-bonner-expects-significant-transfer-movement-after-celtics-cup-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic hero, Pat Bonner, has said he expects Brendan Rodgers to tap into the transfer market before the window closes after yesterday’s cup exit...
The post BBC pundit 'expects' significant transfer movement after Celtic's cup exit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arsenal make Kieran Tierney decision amid Celtic links]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43546</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/21/arsenal-kieran-tierney-celtic-links/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T09:05:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with quite a few players as we head towards the end of the summer transfer window. As the result against Kilmarnock showed, with Brendan Rodgers’ side being knocked out of the Scottish League Cup in the second round itself, the club need to bring some quality in. They have seen key […]
Arsenal make Kieran Tierney decision amid Celtic links - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic hero considers ambitious future career move]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171590</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ex-celtic-hero-aiden-mcgeady-considers-ambitious-future-career-move/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic winger, Aiden McGeady has told how he would consider a move into football management when he officially hangs up his playing boots. The...
The post Ex-Celtic hero considers ambitious future career move  appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fergus McCann scheduled for visit to boost high-profile Celtic Foundation initiative]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171508</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/fergus-mccann-scheduled-for-visit-to-boost-high-profile-celtic-foundation-initiative/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taking a welcome break from the football for just a minute, it’s great to report that Fergus McCann is scheduled in for a welcomed visit...
The post Fergus McCann scheduled for visit to boost high-profile Celtic Foundation initiative appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BBC pundits deliver interesting assessment of Celtic’s Rugby Park penalty flashpoint]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171581</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/bbc-pundits-deliver-interesting-assessment-of-celtics-rugby-park-penalty-flashpoint/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before I start, let’s get this off the bat straight away. Celtic didn’t deserve anything out of the cup fixture against Kilmarnock yesterday afternoon. We...
The post BBC pundits deliver interesting assessment of Celtic’s Rugby Park penalty flashpoint appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘ONE OR TWO OF THEM WENT DOWN A LITTLE EASILY,’ McINNES’ SHOCKING CELTIC CLAIM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111241</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/one-or-two-of-them-went-down-a-little-easily-mcinnes-shocking-celtic-claim/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T07:01:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC players were accused of going “down a little easily” by Kilmarnock boss Derek McInnes after his side’s 1-0 dismissal of the Viaplay League Cup holders at Rugby Park yesterday. The Ayrshire club’s gaffer admitted to being anxious after Sead Haksabanovic had been sent tumbling following an awkward outstretched-leg challenge from Lewis Mayo deep in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘YOU DON’T GET ANY SECOND CHANCES,’ McGREGOR’S CROSSROADS ADMISSION]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111237</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/you-dont-get-any-second-chances-mcgregors-crossroads-admission/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T06:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CRESTFALLEN Callum McGregor admits Celtic are at a crucial crossroads after the disappointment of failing to clear the first Viaplay League Cup hurdle against Kilmarnock. The holders saw their two-year grip on ths silverware loosened in a distinctly off-colour and uninspired performance at Rugby Park where they collapsed 1-0 to Marley Watkins’ strike just before [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton sends blunt message about Celtic recruitment]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43544</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/20/chris-sutton-sends-blunt-message-celtic-recruitment/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T21:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If any Celtic fans were hoping to see the club repeat a treble, those are already over. Brendan Rodgers’ side were knocked out from the second round of the Scottish League Cup, as they lost 1-0 against Kilmarnock away at Rugby Park. It was a result that not many would have seen coming and yet, […]
Chris Sutton sends blunt message about Celtic recruitment - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Common sense’: Roy Keane drops Celtic comment about Ange Postecoglou on Sky]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171559</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/common-sense-what-roy-keane-said-about-celtic-and-ange-postecoglou-on/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roy Keane used Celtic as an example to heap praise on Ange Postecoglou after his Tottenham Hotspur side beat Manchester United 2-0 on Saturday. The...
The post ‘Common sense’: Roy Keane drops Celtic comment about Ange Postecoglou on Sky appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BBC pundit left 'stunned' at Celtic's cup performance; one player gets pass marks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171553</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/pat-bonner-left-stunned-at-celtics-cup-performance-one-player-gets-pass-marks/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pat Bonner has delivered his verdict on Celtic’s defeat at Kilmarnock as the BBC pundit admits he was left ‘stunned’ at his former club’s performance....
The post BBC pundit left 'stunned' at Celtic's cup performance; one player gets pass marks appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic player needs surgery]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43541</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/20/brendan-rodgers-celtic-player-surgery/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T19:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already suffered their first big blow of the season. They lost 1-0 away to Kilmarnock to crash out of the Scottish League Cup in the second round. The club’s hopes of repeating the treble are already over. And even more worrying was the performance on the day. Brendan Rodgers’ side are looking tired […]
Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic player needs surgery - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Now the lads realise"; Callum McGregor addresses cup defeat with 'reminder' to Celtic squad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171548</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/now-the-lads-realise-callum-mcgregor-addresses-cup-defeat-with-reminder-to-celtic-squad/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s going to be a long week ahead for Celtic and fans as the realisation that the team have already relinquished a trophy so early...
The post "Now the lads realise"; Callum McGregor addresses cup defeat with 'reminder' to Celtic squad appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic boss offers straight-forward assessment of cup performance vs Kilmarnock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171541</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/neil-lennon-offers-straight-forward-assessment-of-celtics-performance-vs-kilmarnock/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic fans will have left Rugby Park today with more questions than answers as they watched their team crash out of the cup this...
The post Ex-Celtic boss offers straight-forward assessment of cup performance vs Kilmarnock appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton reacts to League Cup disappointment with blunt verdict on Celtic squad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171526</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/chris-sutton-reacts-to-league-cup-disappointment-with-blunt-verdict-on-celtic-squad/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s defeat to Kilmarnock at Rugby Park is clearly a disappointing blow to Brendan Rodgers and his attempt at defending last season’s treble. The team’s...
The post Chris Sutton reacts to League Cup disappointment with blunt verdict on Celtic squad appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers makes plea as Celtic knocked out of Cup]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43537</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/20/brendan-rodgers-plea-celtic-cup/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T18:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rugby Park is always a difficult place to travel to but even then, this is a result that not many Celtic fans would have seen coming. The Hoops were knocked out of the Scottish League Cup in the second round itself. There will be no treble for Brendan Rodgers this time around. And the first […]
Brendan Rodgers makes plea as Celtic knocked out of Cup - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic star will be out for 3 to 4 months]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171532</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-confirms-stephen-welsh-will-miss-next-3-to-4-months-of-celtic-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T17:38:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen Welsh has damaged ligaments in his ankle and will require surgery, ruling him out of the next three to four months of Celtic action....
The post Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic star will be out for 3 to 4 months appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘WE NEED THAT QUALITY,’ RODGERS IN TRANSFER VOW]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111227</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/we-need-that-quality-rodgers-in-transfer-vow/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T17:18:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is poised to plunge into the transfer market to strengthen his Celtic squad after a lacklustre and error-strewn display as the holders crashed out of the Viaplay League Cup this afternoon. The second time-around Hoops boss suffered defeat for the first time in 25 domestic Cup-ties as his team flopped 1-0 to Kilmarnock [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers calls for quality to arrive in late stages of Celtic transfer window]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171523</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-calls-for-quality-to-arrive-in-late-stages-of-celtic-transfer-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T16:45:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers recognises Celtic need some quality signings in the door in the closing stages of the transfer window after watching his team get knocked...
The post Brendan Rodgers calls for quality to arrive in late stages of Celtic transfer window appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers reacts as Celtic crash out of cup in Kilmarnock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171515</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-reacts-as-celtic-crash-out-of-cup-in-kilmarnock/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T16:23:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a deeply disappointing Sunday for Celtic after Kilmarnock beat the reigning Scottish League Cup holders 1-0 at Rugby Park to knock them out...
The post Brendan Rodgers reacts as Celtic crash out of cup in Kilmarnock appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KILMARNOCK 1 CELTIC 0: SWITCHED-OFF HOOPS’ CUP CALAMITY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111215</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kilmarnock-1-celtic-0-switched-off-hoops-cup-calamity/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T16:18:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KILMARNOCK 1 CELTIC 0 ALL good things must come to an end – and so it proved for Brendan Rodgers and Celtic at Rugby Park this afternoon. The second time-around Hoops manager went into this Viaplay League Cup encounter with an impeccable record in domestic Cup competitions in his previous spell at the club. Twenty-four [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kilmarnock v Celtic, Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111210</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kilmarnock-v-celtic-live-updates-18/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T13:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 15.00.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: GUSTAF DEBUT, HOLM IN FROM START]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111211</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-gustaf-debut-holm-in-from-start/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T12:56:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEW bhoy Gustaf Lagerbiekle makes his Celtic debut this afternoon – just four days after sealing his £3million move from Elfsborg. The Swedish centre-back will line up alongside Maik Nawrocki in the heart of the Hoops rearguard for the Viaplay League Cup-tie against Kilmarnock at Rugby Park. Norwegian midfielder Odin Thiago Holm also takes the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic XI confirmed: 2 changes bring excitement, global TV details, instant reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171507</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-vs-kilmarnock-confirmed-big-debut-first-start-global-tv-details-instant-reaction/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T12:51:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manager Brendan Rodgers has named his Celtic team vs Kilmarnock for today’s Scottish League Cup clash at Rugby Park. The full match squad is as...
The post Celtic XI confirmed: 2 changes bring excitement, global TV details, instant reaction appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic eye transfer move for 21-year-old Danish player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43533</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/20/celtic-eye-transfer-move-danish-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T12:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been pretty active in the summer transfer window, adding new faces to their squad till now. Those are Odin Thiago Holm, Marco Tilio, Yang Hyun-jun, Kwon Hyeok-kyu, Maik Nawrocki and Gustaf Lagerbielke. All of them are highly-rated players with a lot of potential. And it looks like the Hoops will be sticking to […]
Celtic eye transfer move for 21-year-old Danish player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers defends criticised Celtic star]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171503</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-defends-criticised-celtic-star/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T11:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers sounds happy with the contributions of Joe Hart as speculation continues about his future at Celtic. Some observers and supporters consider the goalkeeping...
The post Brendan Rodgers defends criticised Celtic star appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers comments cast doubt on Sunday Celtic transfer rumour]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171490</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-comments-cast-doubt-on-sunday-celtic-transfer-rumour/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s recent link to Mathias Kvistgaarden seems to suggest that the club are in the market to add a new striker to the ranks. 67...
The post Brendan Rodgers comments cast doubt on Sunday Celtic transfer rumour appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers gets rough media treatment in Sunday morning paper]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171468</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-gets-rough-media-treatment-in-sunday-morning-paper/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Far be it from me to deny someone else an opinion, but when analysis of Celtic and the Celtic manager feels particularly harsh and mean-spirited,...
The post Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers gets rough media treatment in Sunday morning paper appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Celtic's excellent record vs Kilmarnock won't matter to Brendan Rodgers today]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171474</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/why-celtics-excellent-record-vs-kilmarnock-wont-matter-to-brendan-rodgers-today/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T10:12:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks the day where Celtic get the second part of their defence of the treble underway. Brendan Rodgers will be keen to get his...
The post Why Celtic's excellent record vs Kilmarnock won't matter to Brendan Rodgers today appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jurgen Klinsmann is already 'really impressed' with new Celtic summer signing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171465</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/jurgen-klinsmann-is-already-really-impressed-with-new-celtic-summer-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s foray into the Asian transfer market continued this summer with the additions of Hyunjun Yang and Hyeokkyu Kwon. Both players have had cameo appearances...
The post Jurgen Klinsmann is already 'really impressed' with new Celtic summer signing appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Celtic would be a great move for him"; Danish football expert's verdict on linked striker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171452</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-would-be-a-great-move-for-him-danish-football-experts-verdict-on-linked-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s need to bring in a striker was highlighted this summer when Hyeongyu Oh was ruled out for a number of weeks due to injury....
The post "Celtic would be a great move for him"; Danish football expert's verdict on linked striker appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In-form Sunderland player linked with return to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43529</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/20/sunderland-player-linked-return-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T09:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to bring in some reinforcements before the summer transfer window slams shut. The club have already brought in six new faces but their opening two performances of the league campaign seemed to lack a certain spark that was their last season. Maybe some established and experienced players are required in this youthful squad. […]
In-form Sunderland player linked with return to Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VIAPLAY CUP DRAW TONIGHT: FIVE DOWN, THREE TO GO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111207</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/viaplay-cup-draw-tonight-five-down-three-to-go/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T08:50:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC will discover their Viaplay League Cup quarter-final opponents after this afternoon’s tie against Kilmarnock – providing the holders are not involved in a calamity at Rugby Park. The last-eight draw will be broadcast live on Viaplay immediately after the satellite broadcasters’ coverage of Brendan Rodgers’ team’s meeting with Derek McInnes’ side in Ayrshire. Already [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Holm's big chance, another Sunday debut; Celtic team news and Predicted XI vs Kilmarnock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171444</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/holms-big-chance-another-sunday-debut-celtic-team-news-and-predicted-xi-vs-kilmarnock/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T08:40:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic begin the defence of another trophy in Ayrshire this afternoon, taking on Derek McInnes’ Kilmarnock side in the Scottish League Cup. As last season’s...
The post Holm's big chance, another Sunday debut; Celtic team news and Predicted XI vs Kilmarnock appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hyunjun Yang names teammate who motivates him to be a success at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171439</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/hyunjun-yang-tells-which-club-legend-motivates-him-to-be-a-success-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyunjun Yang has opened up on the Celtic legend who is inspiring him to be a success at Celtic. The South Korean winger joined the...
The post Hyunjun Yang names teammate who motivates him to be a success at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers breaks silence on Celtic's Ibrox ticket allocation stance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171422</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-breaks-silence-on-celtics-ibrox-ticket-allocation-stance/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T07:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The news headlines towards the end of this week were all dominated by the Glasgow Derby ticket allocation story. We all know the reasons why...
The post Brendan Rodgers breaks silence on Celtic's Ibrox ticket allocation stance appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS HINTS AT HART FUTURE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111203</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-hints-at-hart-future/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T07:29:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has offered a hint about the future of veteran keeper Joe Hart. The 36-year-old 75 times-capped England international is out of contract at the end of the season after his £1million switch from Spurs in August 2021. Hart has featured in every major success since his arrival, but there have been persistent reports since [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The verdict as transfer journalist inevitably links Celtic with Patrick Roberts return]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171420</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/the-verdict-as-transfer-journalist-inevitably-links-celtic-with-patrick-roberts-return-despite-injury/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T07:17:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer journalist Alan Nixon believes Celtic are one of the teams interested in Sunderland winger Patrick Roberts this summer. Nixon, who first reported Ben McPherson’s...
The post The verdict as transfer journalist inevitably links Celtic with Patrick Roberts return appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘A REAL SHAME,’ RODGERS WOE FOR McCARTHY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111201</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/a-real-shame-rodgers-woe-for-mccarthy/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T07:04:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORGOTTEN MAN James McCarthy is on his way out at Celtic. The former Republic of Ireland midfielder was signed as a free agent from Crystal Palace in August 2021 and still has two years to run on his contract. However, the 32-year-old Glasgow-born anchorman didn’t start a single game for the champions last season. McCarthy [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Sunday August 20: We Haven’t Started The Fire]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18457</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18457"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T06:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the magic of the League Cup today with Celtic in Kilmarnock to begin their defence of a trophy that’s always nice to have in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Malph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dominik Livakovic at centre of wild Saturday night drama that banks Celtic extra UEFA cash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171415</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/dominik-livakovic-at-centre-of-wild-saturday-night-drama-that-banks-celtic-extra-uefa-cash/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T06:48:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AEK Athens and Dinamo Zagreb played out one of the matches of the season so far on Saturday night for a place in the playoff...
The post Dominik Livakovic at centre of wild Saturday night drama that banks Celtic extra UEFA cash appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wolves boss provides Daniel Podence latest; Celtic target deletes tweet, is omitted from squad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171410</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/wolves-boss-provides-daniel-podence-latest-celtic-target-deletes-tweet-and-is-omitted-from-squad/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T06:27:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wolves boss Gary O’Neil sounds as if he is completely moving on from Celtic transfer target Daniel Podence as an option after omitting him from...
The post Wolves boss provides Daniel Podence latest; Celtic target deletes tweet, is omitted from squad appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC TARGET DANISH STRIKER]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111196</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-target-danish-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T06:25:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is poised to add more firepower to his Celtic attack with a swoop for Danish wonderkid Mathias Kvistgaarden. The Under-21 international striker is on the Hoops manager’s wanted list and he hopes to get the deal done before the August 31 midnight deadline, according to a report in The Scottish Sun. Rodgers acknowledges [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>