<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-08-17T08:12:19.385Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I REALLY BELIEVE WE CAN BEAT ANYBODY,’ O’RILEY EURO BOAST]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111109</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-really-believe-we-can-beat-anybody-oriley-euro-boast/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T08:10:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE nearest Matt O’Riley got to Champions League action two years ago was to switch on his television. Now the gifted playmaker, who was signed for a modest £1.5million from English third-tier outfit MK Dons in January 2022, insists Celtic can make an impact among Europe’s elite this season. London-born O’Riley is looking forward to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers backroom reshuffle ongoing at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171207</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-backroom-reshuffle-ongoing-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic coach, Scott Breddy, leaves the club this week after nine years of service. Breddy was the first-team Strength and Conditioning coach. Breddy made the...
The post Brendan Rodgers backroom reshuffle ongoing at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC IN DOUBLE DEAL BID]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111105</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-in-double-deal-bid/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T07:17:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC are preparing to thrash out new deals with Reo Hatate and Liel Abada. The Japanese midfielder and the Israeli winger, both under contract until June 2026, will be offered lucrative extensions, according to a report in the Daily Record. Hatate and Abada have been been involved in transfer speculation this summer and Brendan Rodgers [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing set to make very quick debut after strong preparation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171202</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/new-celtic-signing-declares-himself-ready-for-quick-debut-after-strong-preparation/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T07:15:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing Gustaf Lagerbielke has declared himself ready to compete for the Bhoys immediately after a summer of strong preparation in Sweden. The Swedish...
The post New Celtic signing set to make very quick debut after strong preparation appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic board make exciting moves to secure future of top talents]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171197</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/big-contract-moves-on-the-way-from-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T05:49:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will open contract talks with two of the club’s most important and exciting players in Reo Hatate and Liel Abada before the end of...
The post The Celtic board make exciting moves to secure future of top talents appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I LOOKED DOWN, MY ANKLE WAS TWICE THE SIZE IT WAS AT KICK-OFF,’ BOBBY MURDOCH, MAN OF THE MATCH IN LISBON]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=35538</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-looked-down-my-ankle-was-twice-the-size-it-was-at-kick-off-bobby-murdoch-man-of-the-match-in-lisbon/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T04:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BOBBY MURDOCH went through all sorts of agonies as Celtic gatecrashed the European big-time in Lisbon. The painful experience was highlighted in author Alex Gordon’s tribute book, ‘The Lisbon Lions: The 40th Anniversary Celebration’, which was published in 2007. The club legend, who would have been 79 today, was a thoughtful midfielder with a delightful touch [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Belgian club want to sign highly-rated Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43464</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/16/belgian-club-want-sign-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T22:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have lost a couple of key players this summer in the form of Carl Starfelt and Jota. Both of them were starters for the past two seasons and played a major part in winning five trophies during that period of time. Thus, their exits have certainly weakened the squad. It is not just established […]
Belgian club want to sign highly-rated Celtic player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano offers important Celtic transfer update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43460</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/16/fabrizio-offers-celtic-transfer-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T21:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have had a mixed summer transfer window till now. Nobody can deny that the club have brought in some very talented youngsters to Parkhead, who have a ton of potential. Gustaf Lagerbielke recently became the sixth signing of the second Brendan Rodgers era, with the Swedish centre-back being signed from IF Elfsborg. The likes […]
Fabrizio Romano offers important Celtic transfer update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic ready to open contract talks with two players]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43457</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/16/celtic-ready-open-contract-talks-two/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T19:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many Celtic fans are dissatisfied with how the summer transfer window has gone for the club. There were rumours about them making headling-grabbing additions to the squad. That has not happened at all. Instead, they have stuck to bringing in highly-rated youngsters and let’s see if they develop into key players in the future or […]
Celtic ready to open contract talks with two players - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gustaf Lagerbielke shares his reaction when he first heard of Celtic's interest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171192</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/gustaf-lagerbielke-shares-his-reaction-when-he-first-heard-of-celtics-interest/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing, Gustaf Lagerbielke has revealed the timeline of when he first heard about his new club’s interest in him. The Swedish defender joined...
The post Gustaf Lagerbielke shares his reaction when he first heard of Celtic's interest appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic finally make long-awaited transfer announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43452</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/16/celtic-make-long-awaited-announcement-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T18:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic might not have made any headline-grabbing signings in the ongoing summer transfer window, but that does not mean that the club have not been active in terms of incomings. They had already brought in five fresh faces in the form of Odin Thiago Holm, Marco Tilio, Yang Hyun-jun, Kwon Hyeok-kyu and Maik Nawrocki. And […]
Celtic finally make long-awaited transfer announcement - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REVEALED: ‘I WAS PUSHING FOR IT TO HAPPEN,’ NEW BHOY GUSTAF]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111096</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/revealed-i-was-pushing-for-it-to-happen-new-bhoy-gustaf/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:42:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEW Bhoy Gustaf Lagerbielke revealed he was “pushing for it to happen” as soon as he heard Celtic were interested in signing him. The Swedish international centre-back saw his efforts rewarded today when he signed a five-year deal with the treble winners in a move from Elfsborg estimated to be in the £3million bracket. Ironically, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers speaks as Celtic announce Gustaf Lagerbielke]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171186</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-speaks-as-celtic-announce-gustaf-lagerbielke/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:13:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have announced the signing of Swedish defender, Gustaf Lagerbielke, as the club’s sixth summer signing for Brendan Rodgers. The 23-year-old joins the club on...
The post Brendan Rodgers speaks as Celtic announce Gustaf Lagerbielke appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three reasons why Eric Dier would be a great signing for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171181</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/three-reasons-why-eric-dier-would-be-a-great-signing-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With transfer rumours ramping up for Celtic over the past few days, the Hoops support will be all be discussing whether the names mentioned so...
The post Three reasons why Eric Dier would be a great signing for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O'Riley explains what he has done off the pitch to help improve his Celtic performances]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171175</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/matt-oriley-explains-what-he-has-done-off-the-pitch-to-help-improve-his-celtic-performances/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder, Matt O’Riley has spoken about the techniques he has used to help improve his mindset and how they are helping to improve his...
The post Matt O'Riley explains what he has done off the pitch to help improve his Celtic performances appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Belgian side named as 'long-term admirers' of highly-rated Celtic prospect]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171153</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/belgian-side-named-as-long-term-admirers-of-young-celtic-prospect-rocco-vata/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T13:31:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Club Brugge are said to be interested in young Celtic prospect, Rocco Vata, according to a report by the Daily Record. The report claims that...
The post Report: Belgian side named as 'long-term admirers' of highly-rated Celtic prospect appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CCV AND THE KILLIE CONUNDRUM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111093</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ccv-and-the-killie-conundrum/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T12:18:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CAMERON CARTER-VICKERS is fighting to be fit to take his place in the heart of the Celtic defence against Kilmarnock at Rugby Park on Sunday. The £6million recruit from Spurs missed the entire second-half of the 3-1 success over Aberdeen at Pittodrie at the weekend with a hamstring injury. Now Brendan Rodgers could have a [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player could miss Glasgow Derby due to injury]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43448</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/16/celtic-player-glasgow-derby-injury/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T12:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have won both their league games till now and sit at the top of the Premiership table. But it has not been all smooth sailing for Brendan Rodgers’ side. Their performances have left a lot to be desired and at the moment they do not look like the well-oiled winning machine that they were […]
Celtic player could miss Glasgow Derby due to injury - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton's amusing tale of the Celtic legend who was the club's 'biggest moaner']]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171149</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-suttons-amusing-tale-of-the-celtic-legend-who-was-the-clubs-biggest-moaner/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic supporters have seen a variety of different players and managers who have graced the Parkhead corridors over the decades. From the supremely talented...
The post Chris Sutton's amusing tale of the Celtic legend who was the club's 'biggest moaner' appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qualifiers, cash, mitigating fitness]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111081</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/qualifiers-cash-mitigating-fitness/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T11:09:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lots to consider after last night’s Champions League qualifiers.  Top surprise of the night was Marseille being eliminated by Panathinaikos on penalties.  The Greek side equalised in the 10th minute of added time at the Velodrome in what must have been a horrible way to lose for the home fans. Should Panathinaikos reach the group [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIRTHDAY BHOY FALLON AND THE MISSING LISBON MEDAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=62740</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/birthday-bhoy-fallon-and-the-missing-lisbon-medal/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T11:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic keeper John Fallon celebrates his 83rd birthday today. Hopefully, the Hoops legend will be showered with gifts, but none will be as precious as the one he received in April 2019. Fallon, who had been the faithful understudy to Ronnie Simpson all the way through the historic European Cup campaign in season 1966/67, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pundit thinks coming to Celtic would be 'a very wise move' for Premier League player]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171142</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/john-hartson-believes-coming-to-celtic-would-be-a-very-wise-move-for-premier-league-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reports this week claiming that Celtic are preparing to make a move for Newcastle United’s Ryan Fraser came as a bit of a surprise to...
The post Pundit thinks coming to Celtic would be 'a very wise move' for Premier League player appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano drops double Celtic transfer update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43441</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/16/fabrizio-romano-double-celtic-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T09:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have brought in a number of highly-rated youngsters this summer already. Odin Thiago Holm, Marco Tilio, Yang Hyun-jun, Kwon Hyeok-kyu and Maik Nawrocki, are all believed to have the potential to become important players for the club someday. But more reinforcements are needed if the Hoops are to defend their domestic treble and also […]
Fabrizio Romano drops double Celtic transfer update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two obstacles Celtic must overcome to make Daniel Podence deal happen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171137</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/two-obstacles-celtic-must-overcome-to-make-daniel-podence-deal-happen/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With less than two weeks of the transfer window to go, the Celtic transfer rumours seem to be ramping up over the last couple of...
The post Two obstacles Celtic must overcome to make Daniel Podence deal happen appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James McPake explains Celtic's stance when he tried to sign Ben Summers on loan last season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171130</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/james-mcpake-explains-celtics-stance-when-he-tried-to-sign-ben-summers-on-loan-last-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Young Ben Summers is a player that has been in and around the Celtic first team over the course of this season and last. The...
The post James McPake explains Celtic's stance when he tried to sign Ben Summers on loan last season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I could see him come in"; Pundit believes Celtic's latest transfer rumour could be a goer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171122</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-could-see-him-come-in-john-hartson-thinks-celtics-latest-transfer-rumour-could-be-a-goer/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s latest transfer rumour sees the club linked to Wolverhampton Wanderers’ Portuguese winger, Daniel Podence. Tom Collomosse of The Daily Mail tweeted yesterday that the...
The post "I could see him come in"; Pundit believes Celtic's latest transfer rumour could be a goer appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HATATE DERBY SCARE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111077</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hatate-derby-scare/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T07:39:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE is facing a month on the sidelines and could miss three games, including the first derby of the season at Ibrox. The influential Japanese midfielder suffered a calf tear only 25 minutes after coming on as a second-half substitute in the 3-1 win over Aberdeen at Pittodrie at the weekend, according to a report [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC EYE WINGER – THREE YEARS AFTER FIRST LINK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111072</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-eye-winger-three-years-after-first-link/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T07:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS may be poised to reignite Celtic’s interest in Wolves winger Daniel Podence – a target for Neil Lennon more than THREE years ago, as CQN reported at the time. The Portuguese ace first came to the notice of the Hoops’ former boss back in July 2020 when it looked as though the flanker’s [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC TAKE £1.85m HIT ON MISFIT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111071</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-take-1-85m-hit-on-misfit/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T06:27:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC will take a massive £1.85million loss to remove midfield misfit Ismaila Soro from the club. The Ivorian anchorman, who cost £2million when Neil Lennon bought him from Israeli outfit Bnei Yehuda in January 2020, is finally poised to seal a move to French side Valenciennes, a move CQN reported 11 days ago. Soro still [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[International coach excited by Celtic 20-year-old's potential under Brendan Rodgers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171115</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/international-coach-excited-by-odin-thiago-holms-celtic-potential-under-brendan-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T06:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Odin Thiago Holm could soon be getting a call-up to the Norway U21s side with coach Jan Peder Jalland keeping a watchful eye on his...
The post International coach excited by Celtic 20-year-old's potential under Brendan Rodgers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Key Celtic star set to miss up to a month; major doubt for Ibrox trip]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171110</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/reo-hatate-celtic-injury-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder Reo Hatate is expected to be out of action for up to a month after limping off against Aberdeen in the Scottish Premiership...
The post Report: Key Celtic star set to miss up to a month; major doubt for Ibrox trip appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports man confirms Celtic interest in £12m player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43437</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/15/sky-sports-celtic-12-million-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T22:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already brought in five new players this summer and are believed to be closing in on a move for Gustaf Lagerbielke of IF Elfsborg as well. The club are expected to make further additions to their squad before the ongoing transfer window slams shut in a little over a couple of weeks. And […]
Sky Sports man confirms Celtic interest in £12m player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic announce new initiative in Australia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171102</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-soccer-academy-lay-new-foundations-in-australia-with-latest-partnership-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T21:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past two seasons, Celtic have been hard at work setting up football camps in Japan and America in a bid to boost their...
The post Celtic announce new initiative in Australia appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gustaf Lagerbielke's appraisal by Elfsborg captain bode well for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171099</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/gustaf-lagerbielkes-appraisal-by-elfsborg-captain-bode-well-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T20:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s pursuit of Gustaf Lagerbielke has been well-publicised over the last week or so. The Swedish defender looks set to become part of Brendan Rodgers’...
The post Gustaf Lagerbielke's appraisal by Elfsborg captain bode well for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer move for £7 million left-back ruled out]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43434</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/15/celtic-transfer-move-left-back-ruled/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T20:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic could do with another left-back right now. Greg Taylor might have done a tremendous job under the management of Ange Postecoglou but there are serious doubts over whether he is best suited to Brendan Rodgers’ style of football. And his recent performances have done nothing to prove the doubters wrong. On the other hand, […]
Celtic transfer move for £7 million left-back ruled out - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Away Days – Aberdeen]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58257</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-away-days-aberdeen/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T19:10:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s was an early start on Sunday morning for our away adventure to Aberdeen. Tickets are always the talking point for these games or should I say lack of tickets. Once again at kick off time there were plenty of empty seats in the home stands. The away end was packed with Celtic fans […]
The post Celtic Away Days – Aberdeen appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic linked with ambitious move for Wolves player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43431</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/15/celtic-linked-move-wolves-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T19:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jota left Celtic earlier in the summer in order to join Al-Ittihad in a £25 million move. Things have not quite gone the Portuguese winger’s way since then and there is already talk of him being sent out on loan. On the other hand, the Hoops have not brought in a proper replacement for him […]
Celtic linked with ambitious move for Wolves player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic finally manage to agree transfer deal for midfielder]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43428</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/15/celtic-agree-transfer-deal-midfielder/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T17:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been very active in the summer transfer window. They have brought in five fresh faces to the club and it remains to be seen how things turn out for them at Parkhead. On the other hand, there have been quite a few who have headed in the opposite direction as well, including starters […]
Celtic finally manage to agree transfer deal for midfielder - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yosuke Ideguchi recognised in Japan as Celtic midfielder voted onto on-loan club's God 7 list]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171088</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/yosuke-ideguchi-recognised-in-japan-as-celtic-midfielder-voted-onto-on-loan-clubs-god-7-list/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forgotten Celtic midfielder, Yosuke Ideguchi, has been given some recognition in Japan from his on-loan club, Avispa Fukuoka’s, fans. The Japanese midfielder has been at...
The post Yosuke Ideguchi recognised in Japan as Celtic midfielder voted onto on-loan club's God 7 list appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Doak explains how what he experienced at Celtic has benefitted him at Liverpool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171082</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ben-doak-explains-how-his-experience-at-celtic-has-benefitted-him-at-liverpool/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T16:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is absolutely no denying that Celtic lost a major talent the day Ben Doak left Glasgow for Liverpool. The 17-year-old winger was tipped as...
The post Ben Doak explains how what he experienced at Celtic has benefitted him at Liverpool appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic 'agree' to sell fringe player; fee reported as club set to take a financial hit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171093</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-agree-to-sell-ismaila-soro-fee-reported-as-club-set-to-take-a-financial-hit/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T15:50:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have agreed to sell fringe player, Ismaila Soro, according to a report from Footmercato. The club are set to take a big financial loss...
The post Report: Celtic 'agree' to sell fringe player; fee reported as club set to take a financial hit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MUIR IN CHARGE OF CELTIC CUP DEFENCE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111063</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/muir-in-charge-of-celtic-cup-defence/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T15:19:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ALAN MUIR will be in charge of Celtic’s first defence of their Viaplay League Cup against Kilmarnock at Rugby Park on Sunday. The match official will be seen as something of a lucky omen for the champions. Remarkably, he has been the man in the middle in 39 previous Hoops games – and the Parkhead [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confirmed: SFA announce match officials for Celtic's league cup tie vs Kilmarnock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171075</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/confirmed-sfa-announce-match-officials-for-celtics-league-cup-tie-vs-kilmarnock/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SFA has announced the officials that will undertake Celtic’s first attempt at defending the league cup against Kilmarnock at Rugby Park on Sunday afternoon....
The post Confirmed: SFA announce match officials for Celtic's league cup tie vs Kilmarnock appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The reason why ex-Celtic star Jota's future at Al-Ittihad could be in the balance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171069</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-reason-why-ex-celtic-star-jotas-future-at-al-ittihad-could-be-in-the-balance/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic star, Jota, could see his move to Al Ittihad cut short this season as his new boss Nuno Espirito Santo confirms that a...
The post The reason why ex-Celtic star Jota's future at Al-Ittihad could be in the balance appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur player linked with move to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43423</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/15/tottenham-hotspur-player-move-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T12:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were handed a major blow earlier in the summer when Ange Postecoglou left the club to join Tottenham Hotspur just days after winning the treble. The Australian had done a fantastic job at Parkhead over the past couple of seasons, winning five trophies. Thus, his leaving was not ideal. The Hoops have replaced him […]
Tottenham Hotspur player linked with move to Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spending big money in France]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111062</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/spending-big-money-in-france/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T11:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Christopher Jullien was 26 years old when Celtic paid Toulouse €8m for him four years ago.  We paid PSG even more a year earlier for Odsonne Edouard, then 20.  It is France, not England or Japan, that Celtic feel confident enough to spend their highest transfer fees. Compared to England, Germany, Italy and Spain, Celtic [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic are 'admirers' of Premier League defender]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171062</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/new-name-enters-the-fray-as-celtic-said-to-be-admirers-of-spurs-defender/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T10:25:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are said to be ‘admirers’ of Tottenham Hotspur defender Eric Dier according to a report in 90min. The experienced England international (49 caps) is...
The post Report: Celtic are 'admirers' of Premier League defender appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch: ex-Celtic striker Moussa Dembele scores debut winner for Al-Ettifaq]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171054</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/watch-ex-celtic-striker-moussa-dembele-scores-debut-winner-for-al-ettifaq/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T09:13:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic striker, Moussa Dembele, has gotten his Al-Ettifaq career off to a great start after the Frenchman made his goalscoring debut for his new club....
The post Watch: ex-Celtic striker Moussa Dembele scores debut winner for Al-Ettifaq appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic considering move for £7 million-plus left-back]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43419</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/15/celtic-7-million-plus-left-back/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T09:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic could be in need of a new left-back. They have plenty of options there already. Greg Taylor has been a consistent performer over the past couple of seasons. On the other hand, Alexandro Bernabei was brought in for a significant transfer fee last summer and has now had a year to settle into Scottish […]
Celtic considering move for £7 million-plus left-back - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic boss delivers assessment on Kieran Tierney's return to Paradise rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171049</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/neil-lennon-delivers-his-assessment-on-kieran-tierney-to-celtic-rumours/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The return of Kieran Tierney to Celtic has been a rumour that has been circulating in the media for the duration of this summer. The...
The post Former Celtic boss delivers assessment on Kieran Tierney's return to Paradise rumours appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STRIKING OUT: RODGERS ADVICE FOR O’RILEY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111058</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/striking-out-rodgers-advice-for-oriley/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T07:42:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY knew the score following an early chat with new manager Brendan Rodgers. The smooth playmaker was told his figures just didn’t stack up after the Irishman had scrutinised his personal statistics in his 18 months at the Hoops after his bargain £1.5million arrival from third-tier MK Dons. O’Riley provided more goal assists than any [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Motherwell's Mika Biereth tells how Celtic star's touch of class helped him settle in Scotland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171044</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/motherwells-mika-biereth-tells-how-celtic-stars-touch-of-class-helped-him-settle-in-scotland/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O’Riley has certainly been grabbing the headlines over the last few weeks. His goalscoring performances for Celtic have earned him praise from all quarters...
The post Motherwell's Mika Biereth tells how Celtic star's touch of class helped him settle in Scotland appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's latest transfer target featured on 2023 UEFA 'players to watch out for' list]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171040</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtics-latest-transfer-target-featured-on-2023-uefa-players-to-watch-out-for-list/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s transfer interest in Quentin Merlin is one of the most promising rumours of the summer window, with the young Frenchman already attracting plenty of...
The post Celtic's latest transfer target featured on 2023 UEFA 'players to watch out for' list appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£3m GUSTAF JETS IN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111056</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/3m-gustaf-jets-in/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T06:46:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GUSTAF LAGERBIELKE is jetting into Glasgow today and his £3million move from Elfsborg is likely to be sealed within 24 hours. The Swedish international centre-back is poised for a medical at Lennoxtown after the champions and the player’s club agreed on the financial package, according to The Scottish Sun. Lagerbielke arrives just a few days [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC IN FRENCH LINK – BUT NOT AT £7m]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111049</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-in-french-link-but-not-at-7m/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T06:18:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have been linked with Nantes left-back Quentin Merlin – but the champions will baulk at the £7million asking fee. Brendan Rodgers will continue his search of the market place as he strengthens his squad before the August 31 midnight deadline. Twenty-one-year-old Merlin, who has represented France through the youth ranks up to Under-21 level, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Brendan Rodgers told "intelligent" 2022 Celtic arrival about taking his game to next level]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171035</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-brendan-rodgers-has-said-to-matt-oriley-about-taking-his-celtic-game-to-next-level/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T05:46:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has given midfielder Matt O’Riley express instructions to add more goals to his game after reviewing the numbers of his first...
The post What Brendan Rodgers told "intelligent" 2022 Celtic arrival about taking his game to next level appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Euro club aware of serious Celtic interest in £7m deal after multiple scouting missions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171030</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/strong-celtic-interest-in-7m-deal-after-multiple-scouting-missions/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T05:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are showing ‘strong interest’ in Nantes defender Quentin Merlin this summer after multiple scouting trips to watch him in action. The Scottish Daily Mail...
The post Report: Euro club aware of serious Celtic interest in £7m deal after multiple scouting missions appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic already handed €12m Quentin Merlin problem]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43413</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/14/celtic-already-quentin-merlin-problem/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T22:35:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is no secret that Celtic could do with another left-back right now. Greg Taylor did a tremendous job in Ange Postecoglou’s system but he might not be best suited to Brendan Rodgers’ style of football and how full-backs feature in it. On the other hand, Alexandro Bernabei has major defensive shortcomings and does not […]
Celtic already handed €12m Quentin Merlin problem - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major update on Ryan Fraser to Celtic transfer situation]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43409</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/14/update-ryan-fraser-celtic-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T21:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans have been calling out for some experienced players to be brought in this summer but they might not be entirely happy with the rumours linking the club with one such player. That is none other than Newcastle United winger, Ryan Fraser, who is expected to depart St James’ Park this summer. Fraser was […]
Major update on Ryan Fraser to Celtic transfer situation - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic interest in French Ligue 1 left-back confirmed]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43405</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/14/celtic-french-left-back-confirmed/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T19:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are expected to remain active in the transfer window over the next few weeks. The club have both their league games this season till now but their performances have left a lot to be desired. This does not look or feel like the well-oiled engine that Ange Postecoglou’s team was. And there are certain […]
Celtic interest in French Ligue 1 left-back confirmed - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic considering multiple winger options; potential Ryan Fraser arrival hurdle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171025</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-considering-multiple-winger-options-potential-ryan-fraser-arrival-hurdle/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T19:26:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ryan Fraser isn’t the only wide option Celtic are considering in the final weeks of the transfer window, as Brendan Rodgers makes a new attacker...
The post Report: Celtic considering multiple winger options; potential Ryan Fraser arrival hurdle appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["He's a good technician"; Pat Bonner's verdict is forming on Celtic summer signing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171016</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/hes-a-good-technician-pat-bonners-verdict-is-forming-on-celtic-summer-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have added five new faces to the squad since the arrival of Brendan Rodgers seven weeks ago. There will be more, but for now,...
The post "He's a good technician"; Pat Bonner's verdict is forming on Celtic summer signing appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic ready to make move for Newcastle United player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43396</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/14/celtic-ready-newcastle-united-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T18:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a couple of weeks left in the summer transfer window, it appears that Celtic are about to make a move for a Newcastle United player. Losing Jota to Al-Ittihad was a major blow, but the early switch at least gave time for a quality replacement to be brought in. There is some cover available, […]
Celtic ready to make move for Newcastle United player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon says Celtic must reinforce two key areas for the upcoming Champions League campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171018</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/neil-lennon-says-celtic-must-reinforce-two-key-areas-for-the-upcoming-champions-league-campaign/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are certainly going to add more new faces in the transfer window this summer. Brendan Rodgers has already stated that he intends to have...
The post Neil Lennon says Celtic must reinforce two key areas for the upcoming Champions League campaign appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fend off Brighton and other English clubs to tie down two highly-rated young talents]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171009</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/celtic-fend-off-brighton-and-other-english-clubs-to-tie-down-two-highly-rated-young-talents/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic made the announcement today that 13 players have put pen to paper on their first professional contracts at the club, and there were two...
The post Celtic fend off Brighton and other English clubs to tie down two highly-rated young talents appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic star that has found a new spring in his step under Brendan Rodgers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171000</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/brendan-rodgers-effect-in-full-view-as-celtic-star-finds-a-new-lease-of-life-under-new-boss/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager, Brendan Rodgers, swept into Paradise this summer in a blaze of publicity this summer. Whilst many fans were unsure of the move, there...
The post The Celtic star that has found a new spring in his step under Brendan Rodgers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reported Celtic transfer target makes UEFA Super Cup squad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170996</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/reported-celtic-transfer-target-makes-uefa-super-cup-squad/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reported Celtic transfer target James McAtee is clearly highly thought of at Manchester City, with Pep Guardiola including him in first-team activities this week. McAtee...
The post Reported Celtic transfer target makes UEFA Super Cup squad appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UNIQUE ANGLE: KYOGO – 56 AND COUNTING]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111041</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/unique-angle-kyogo-56-and-counting/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T14:12:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CRACKSHOT Kyogo Furuhashi took his Celtic goal tally to 56 in just over two years with his whiplash right-foot effort in the 3-1 win over Aberdeen at Pittodrie yesterday, The Japanese international striker seized on a misdirected header from the unfortunate Nicky Devlin to drive a blistering shot wide of the helpless Kelle Roos to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's next 9 fixtures and the big test ahead for Brendan Rodgers' squad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170991</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-next-nine-domestic-fixtures-are-set-to-test-brendan-rodgers-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already negotiated a tough away fixture this season. The away trip to Pittodrie is about as tough a challenge as you can get....
The post Celtic's next 9 fixtures and the big test ahead for Brendan Rodgers' squad appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[POLISH UP YOU ACT, MAIK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111038</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/polish-up-you-act-maik/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T12:48:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IF new Bhoy Maik Nawrocki had any doubts about what is required to perform in the Celtic defence before the weekend, he certainly knows now! The £4.3million recruit from Legia Warsaw played his first competitive 90 minutes for the champions in the hard-fought 3-1 win over Aberdeen at Pittodrie yesterday. Nawrocki, 22, was rushed into [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic ready to make their move for Premier League player and it could be a bargain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170971</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-ready-to-make-their-move-for-premier-league-player-and-it-could-be-a-bargain/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T12:06:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are preparing a move for Newcastle and Scotland winger Ryan Fraser, The Northern Echo has reported this afternoon. Fraser is surplus to requirements on...
The post Celtic ready to make their move for Premier League player and it could be a bargain appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dominik Livakovic final decision amid Celtic rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43393</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/14/dominik-livakovic-final-celtic-rumours/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T12:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of Celtic fans have not been impressed by the performances of Joe Hart in recent times and have called for the club to add to their ranks between the posts. The Englishman has been the club’s number one for the past two seasons but seems to be struggling at the moment, as it […]
Dominik Livakovic final decision amid Celtic rumours - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Brendan Rodgers' assessment of Celtic's weekend win bodes well for this season - Opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170965</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-season-ahead-looks-exciting-after-brendan-rodgers-assessment-of-celtics-weekend-win/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T11:13:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now, before I start, I realise that there were aspects of our performance yesterday against Aberdeen that didn’t look pleasing on the eye. I’m well...
The post How Brendan Rodgers' assessment of Celtic's weekend win bodes well for this season - Opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yang delivered after control slipped]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111029</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/yang-delivered-after-control-slipped/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T11:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many roles a winger has to fulfil in the modern game, but the most important part is to beat your man, get a cross in and find a teammate.  Yang delivered this yesterday.  With Celtic under pressure, defending a one-goal lead late in the game, he collected the ball on the left – [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GUSTAF IN LINE FOR QUICKFIRE DEBUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111030</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/gustaf-in-line-for-quickfire-debut/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T10:56:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GUSTAF LAGERBIEKLE is on his way to Celtic – and could be in Brendan Rodgers’ squad for the start of Celtic’s defence of the Viaplay League Cup on Sunday. The £3million-rated Swedish international centre-back looks to have said farewell to Elfsborg in his team’s 1-0 loss to Hamaraby at the weekend. And the 23-year-old stopper [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dominic Livakovic's future finally decided after summer long links to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170961</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/dominic-livakovics-future-finally-decided-after-summer-long-links-to-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dominic Livakovic’s future has now been decided after a summer-long transfer saga. The Croatian goalkeeper had been linked with a summer move to Celtic. Reports...
The post Dominic Livakovic's future finally decided after summer long links to Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["He was really, really good"; Pat Bonner hails Celtic star's cameo performance vs Aberdeen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170957</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/he-was-really-really-good-pat-bonner-hails-celtic-stars-cameo-performance-vs-aberdeen/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pat Bonner has hailed Reo Hatate’s performance against Aberdeen as Celtic’s win took the three points back down to Glasgow yesterday afternoon. The former Celtic...
The post "He was really, really good"; Pat Bonner hails Celtic star's cameo performance vs Aberdeen appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Journalist makes Kieran Tierney Celtic return claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43390</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/14/journalist-kieran-tierney-celtic-return/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T09:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kieran Tierney was one of the faces of Celtic before leaving in the summer of 2019, to join Premier League giants Arsenal. He has had an inconsistent time in London. Not too long ago, the Scot was considered a future captain of the club. But now, he cannot even get into Mikel Arteta’s matchday squads. […]
Journalist makes Kieran Tierney Celtic return claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Monday August 14: We Feel Fine ?]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18455</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18455"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T08:50:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s no pleasing some people.     A difficult game against a much improved Aberdeen at Pittodrie ended in a 3-1 win for the hoops,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Malph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stan Petrov delivers a transfer message that Celtic must heed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170945</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/stan-petrov-delivers-a-transfer-message-that-celtic-must-heed/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s hard-fought win over Aberdeen came at a cost to Brendan Rodgers. Injuries to Cameron Carter-Vickers and Reo Hatate will be a cause for concern...
The post Stan Petrov delivers a transfer message that Celtic must heed appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["It is a very big club"; Gustaf Lagerbiekle speaks as Celtic speculation ramps up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170947</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/gustaf-lagerbiekle-speaks-as-celtic-speculation-ramps-up/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s reported pursuit of Gustaf Lagerbiekle appears to be coming to an end after the player spoke out prior to Elfsborg’s defeat against Hammarby yesterday....
The post "It is a very big club"; Gustaf Lagerbiekle speaks as Celtic speculation ramps up appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers clears up player discipline issue after Sutton was left fuming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170944</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-clears-up-alexandro-bernabei-situation/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has no ongoing concerns regarding Alexandro Bernabei, but did confirm that he was omitted from the squad last week after the...
The post Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers clears up player discipline issue after Sutton was left fuming appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIG TWO’S VERDICT ON NEW BHOYS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110982</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/big-twos-verdict-on-new-bhoys/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T06:27:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS and his skipper Callum McGregor were singing from the same hymn sheet after Celtic’s 3-1 win over Abereen at Pittodrie yesterday. The champions had to remain resolute to overcome a committed and determined Dons side who proved right from the start they had no intention of being bit-part players in the continuing Hoops [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers brushes off Spurs Celtic transfer query after Harry Kane sale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170938</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-brushes-off-spurs-celtic-transfer-concerns-after-harry-kane-sale/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T06:19:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers isn’t concerned in the slightest about Tottenham Hotspur coming in for any of Celtic’s big assets in the wake of selling Harry Kane...
The post Brendan Rodgers brushes off Spurs Celtic transfer query after Harry Kane sale appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing earns glowing review from Bhoys teammate; personality and mentality praised]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170935</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-captain-callum-mcgregor-lauds-outstanding-new-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T05:43:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic captain Callum McGregor was delighted with the performance of new signing Maik Nawrocki on Sunday afternoon, in difficult circumstances at Pittodrie. Nawrocki was playing...
The post New Celtic signing earns glowing review from Bhoys teammate; personality and mentality praised appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gustaf Lagerbielke appears to hint at Celtic transfer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43387</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/13/gustaf-lagerbielke-hint-celtic-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T22:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans were understandably left surprised to see Gustaf Lagerbielke line up for IF Elfsborg in their Allsvenskan game against Hammarby. Rumours have suggested that a deal has been agreed with the Hoops and a medical is set to take place next week. Under those circumstances, players do not feature in order to avoid any […]
Gustaf Lagerbielke appears to hint at Celtic transfer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player’s future takes twist due to Brendan Rodgers]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43385</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/13/celtic-player-future-brendan-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T21:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have not looked at their best over the first two matchdays in the Premiership. They have gotten the job done on both occasions though, winning 4-2 against Ross County on Flag Day and then 3-1 away at Pittodrie Stadium against Aberdeen. Fans will be hoping that the performances improve over the coming weeks as […]
Celtic player’s future takes twist due to Brendan Rodgers - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Honesty from the Celtic camp as player lays out reality despite win over Aberdeen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170928</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/honesty-from-the-celtic-camp-as-joe-hart-lays-out-reality-despite-win-over-aberdeen/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T20:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart didn’t pull his punches in the wake of today’s Celtic win over Aberdeen. While noting the strength of character in this Bhoys team...
The post Honesty from the Celtic camp as player lays out reality despite win over Aberdeen appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers calls for more Celtic signings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170922</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-calls-for-more-celtic-signings/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T19:40:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers isn’t putting a number on the amount of players we can expect to sign for Celtic before the end of the transfer window...
The post Brendan Rodgers calls for more Celtic signings appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms next Celtic signing very close]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43382</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/13/brendan-rodgers-next-celtic-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T19:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already made five signings this summer, bringing Odin Thiago Holm, Marco Tilio, Yang Hyun-jun, Kwon Hyeok-kyu and Maik Nawrocki to the club in the ongoing transfer window. The Hoops are expected to make more additions to their ranks though, and it looks like the next one is very close. Celtic recently saw Carl […]
Brendan Rodgers confirms next Celtic signing very close - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O'Riley shares how Brendan Rodgers has helped him contribute more at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170909</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/matt-oriley-shares-how-brendan-rodgers-has-impacted-a-major-part-of-his-game-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s wins over Ross County and Aberdeen showed us two sides of this team so far under Brendan Rodgers. There is the side that is...
The post Matt O'Riley shares how Brendan Rodgers has helped him contribute more at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gustaf Lagerbielke makes surprise appearance ahead of proposed Celtic move]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170913</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/gustaf-lagerbielke-plays-90-minutes-for-elfsborg-ahead-of-proposed-celtic-move/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T18:11:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Incoming Celtic signing Gustaf Lagerbielke played a full match for Elfsborg this evening, potentially his last for the club before making the switch to Glasgow....
The post Gustaf Lagerbielke makes surprise appearance ahead of proposed Celtic move appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player makes U-turn after controversial caption]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43380</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/13/celtic-player-turn-controversial-caption/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T18:05:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Odin Thiago Holm has made a bright start to life at Celtic. The Norwegian midfielder has been signed from Valerenga this summer and while he might not be a starter yet, he is certainly showing the potential to develop into one in the future. He came off the bench in the recent game against Aberdeen. […]
Celtic player makes U-turn after controversial caption - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers pays Kyogo the ultimate compliment after the Celtic striker's Pittodrie goal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170902</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-pays-kyogo-the-ultimate-compliment-after-the-celtic-strikers-pittodrie-goal/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T17:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Furuhashi has undoubtedly been one of Celtic’s most consistent performers over the last two seasons. The Japanese striker has been a vital component in...
The post Brendan Rodgers pays Kyogo the ultimate compliment after the Celtic striker's Pittodrie goal appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["A fantastic footballer"; Brendan Rodgers already likes what he sees from new Celtic signing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170888</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/a-fantastic-footballer-brendan-rodgers-already-likes-what-he-sees-from-new-celtic-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T17:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Odin Thiago Holm doesn’t have many competitive minutes under his belt at Celtic but he is already making a positive impression on manager Brendan Rodgers....
The post "A fantastic footballer"; Brendan Rodgers already likes what he sees from new Celtic signing appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton highlights Celtic's transfer need after win vs Aberdeen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170889</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/chris-sutton-highlights-celtics-transfer-need-after-win-vs-aberdeen/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A win over Aberdeen at Pittodrie is always a great result. But when it comes at the start of a new season, with a new...
The post Chris Sutton highlights Celtic's transfer need after win vs Aberdeen appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic deliver enormous 9-0 Sunday SWPL win; one star scores four]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170892</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/celtic-deliver-enormous-9-0-sunday-swpl-win/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T15:58:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have started the SWPL season with real intent, delivering an enormous 9-0 opening-day win away to Montrose this afternoon. Having so narrowly lost out...
The post Celtic deliver enormous 9-0 Sunday SWPL win; one star scores four appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS HAILS HOOPS’ ‘ELITE PLAYER’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110977</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-hails-hoops-elite-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T15:40:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS went 68 games without defeat against Scottish opposition during his first stint as Celtic manager. Now, after the 3-1 win over Aberdeen at Pittodrie this afternoon, it’s a case of two down and 66 to go if he hopes to equal that phenomenal record. Goals from Liel Abada, Kyogo Furuhashi and Matt O’Riley [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers delivers timeline for Celtic to replace Carl Starfelt]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170868</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-delivers-timeline-for-celtic-to-replace-carl-starfelt/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If ever there was a day when the replacing Carl Starfelt was needing to be addressed, today is that day. Especially after Cameron Carter-Vickers was...
The post Brendan Rodgers delivers timeline for Celtic to replace Carl Starfelt appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic star quotes Kendrick Lamar with spicy Instagram post aimed at Aberdeen opponent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170867</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/new-celtic-star-quotes-kendrick-lamar-with-spicy-instagram-post-aimed-at-aberdeen-opponent/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T14:44:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing Odin Thiago Holm is making his presence felt in the Scottish Premiership and clearly enjoyed today’s tussle with Aberdeen at Pittodrie, if...
The post New Celtic star quotes Kendrick Lamar with spicy Instagram post aimed at Aberdeen opponent appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart lauds Celtic duo for showing up when needed in tough win vs Aberdeen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170859</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/joe-hart-lauds-celtic-duo-for-showing-up-when-needed-in-tough-win-vs-aberdeen/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T14:17:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s 3-1 against Aberdeen at Pittodrie seems to have come at a cost to the first team after the injury scares to Cameron Carter-Vickers and...
The post Joe Hart lauds Celtic duo for showing up when needed in tough win vs Aberdeen appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers provides updates on Carter-Vickers and Hatate after Celtic injury scares]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170841</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-provides-updates-on-carter-vickers-and-hatate-after-celtic-injury-scares/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T13:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a hard-fought win, Celtic defeated Aberdeen 3-1 at Pittodrie to ensure all three points headed back to Glasgow this afternoon. Goals from Liel Abada,...
The post Brendan Rodgers provides updates on Carter-Vickers and Hatate after Celtic injury scares appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ABERDEEN 1 CELTIC 3: THREE CHEERS AS HOOPS DISPLAY TRUE GRIT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110968</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/aberdeen-1-celtic-3-three-cheers-as-hoops-display-true-grit/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T13:22:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ABERDEEN 1 CELTIC 3  THIS was an afternoon for Celtic to show what champions are made of in a gruelling, no-holds-barred confrontation at Pittodrie this afternoon. Brendan Rodgers’ Hoops claimed three vital points with goals from Liel Abada, Kyogo Furuhashi and Matt O’Riley, but that only tells you part of the story. The visitors had [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed double injury scare against Aberdeen]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43377</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/13/celtic-double-injury-scare-aberdeen/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T13:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just like matchday 1, Celtic did not perform anywhere near their best but were good enough to get the win and the three points. The Hoops got themselves a 3-1 victory against Aberdeen away at the Pittodrie Stadium with Liel Abada, Kyogo and Matt O’Riley getting on the scoresheet. It was not a positive display […]
Celtic handed double injury scare against Aberdeen - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carter-Vickers and Hatate concerns, Nawrocki's test; 3 things we learned as Celtic beat Aberdeen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170838</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/carter-vickers-and-hatate-concerns-nawrockis-test-3-things-we-learned-as-celtic-beat-aberdeen/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T12:56:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic came through a tough afternoon at Pittodrie to win 3-1 in the Scottish Premiership on Sunday, despite losing some key players to fitness and...
The post Carter-Vickers and Hatate concerns, Nawrocki's test; 3 things we learned as Celtic beat Aberdeen appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aberdeen v Celtic, GG Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110959</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/aberdeen-v-celtic-gg-live-updates/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T10:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 12:00.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: SAME AGAIN CELTS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110961</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-same-again-celts-10/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T09:56:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAVID TURNBULL, who sealed his first Celtic start in nine months with two goals in the 4-2 win over Ross County, continues in midfield for the match against Aberdeen at Pittodrie at noon today. Reo Hatate remains on the substitutes’ bench as Brendan Rodgers names an unchanged team from the one against the Highlanders that [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic XI confirmed: Rodgers makes big calls, global TV details, instant reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170832</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-vs-aberdeen-confirmed-rodgers-strong-options-global-tv-details-instant-reaction/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T09:51:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manager Brendan Rodgers has named his Celtic team vs Aberdeen for today’s big Scottish Premiership lunchtime kick-off. The full match squad is as follows: Starting...
The post Celtic XI confirmed: Rodgers makes big calls, global TV details, instant reaction appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I think it’s an interesting role"; Ex-Celtic boss sets ambitious career target]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170824</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-manager-neil-lennon-is-planning-an-ambitious-future-career-move/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic manager, Neil Lennon, has set himself an ambitious career target as he ponders his next move in football. 67 Hail Hail told this...
The post "I think it’s an interesting role"; Ex-Celtic boss sets ambitious career target appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Possible twist in Gustaf Lagerbielke to Celtic transfer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43374</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/13/twist-gustaf-lagerbielke-celtic-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T09:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Carl Starfelt leaving in order to join Celta Vigo, Celtic needed to bring in a centre-back to replace him. And it looks like they set their eyes on another Swedish international in the form of Gustaf Lagerbielke. The 23-year-old defender currently plays Allsvenskan table toppers, IF Elsborg. Rumours coming out of Sweden suggested that […]
Possible twist in Gustaf Lagerbielke to Celtic transfer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton delivers his verdict on Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers' Bernabei stance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170816</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-delivers-his-verdict-on-celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-bernabei-stance/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alexandro Bernabei has had a varied start to his Celtic career. Having spent most of his time playing second fiddle to Greg Taylor, the arrival...
The post Chris Sutton delivers his verdict on Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers' Bernabei stance appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STOPPAGE-TIME WOE FOR ON-LOAN CELT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110955</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/stoppage-time-woe-for-on-loan-celt/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T08:10:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ON-LOAN teenage Celts Ben Summers and Ben McPherson made their debuts for new clubs Dunfermline and Queen’s Park yesterday. The midfielder and defender, both highly rated at Parkhead, agreed season-long switches to the Championship sides during the week, as CQN reported. In front of a crowd of 8,892 at Tannadice, Summers came on as a [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Stewart spells out why Brendan Rodgers' return to Celtic is bad news for Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170812</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/michael-stewart-spells-out-why-brendan-rodgers-return-to-celtic-is-bad-news-for-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers’ return to Celtic has lifted the Parkhead club to another level. That’s according to BBC pundit, Michael Stewart. Stewart was asked how big...
The post Michael Stewart spells out why Brendan Rodgers' return to Celtic is bad news for Rangers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aberdeen star sets out gameplan vs Celtic; it could play into Brendan Rodgers' hands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170799</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/aberdeen-star-sets-out-gameplan-vs-celtic-it-could-play-into-brendan-rodgers-hands/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks a real test for Celtic in the defence of the title. A trip to Pittodrie to face Aberdeen beckons and the Hoops will...
The post Aberdeen star sets out gameplan vs Celtic; it could play into Brendan Rodgers' hands appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big midfield call, dangerous attack: Celtic team news and Predicted XI vs Aberdeen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170805</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/big-midfield-call-dangerous-attack-celtic-team-news-and-predicted-xi-vs-aberdeen/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T07:10:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic don’t have it easy in their first away trip of the Scottish Premiership season, facing last year’s third-placed side Aberdeen in front of a...
The post Big midfield call, dangerous attack: Celtic team news and Predicted XI vs Aberdeen appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Criticised Celtic star "fighting every day" to impress Rodgers behind-the-scenes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170795</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/anthony-ralston-fighting-every-day-to-impress-brendan-rodgers-in-celtic-training/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T06:40:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Ralston has had a difficult start to the Celtic season but is determined to impress manager Brendan Rodgers and compete for the right-back spot...
The post Criticised Celtic star "fighting every day" to impress Rodgers behind-the-scenes appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers' inside track on money-spinning summer transfers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170792</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-inside-track-on-money-spinning-summer-transfers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T06:16:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems there are few managers better placed to understand what is going on with Saudi Arabia and their mega-money push in football than Celtic...
The post Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers' inside track on money-spinning summer transfers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REVEALED: RODGERS TRANSFER FEARS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110950</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/revealed-rodgers-transfer-fears/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T06:04:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has revealed his concerns of a transfer raid on Celtic – AFTER the UK deadline has passed at midnight on August 31. The Hoops boss mirrored the fears of Celtic book author Alex Gordon in his EXCLUSIVE CQN column yesterday. Rodgers admitted it would not be easy for the champions to reject a similar [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers set to keep Aberdeen waiting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170789</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-set-to-keep-aberdeen-waiting/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T05:41:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers isn’t yet ready to make a decision on Liam Scales’ future as the Bhoys put a squad together in the final...
The post Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers set to keep Aberdeen waiting appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BOXING DAY BEDLAM, ROPEY REF, DODGY PENS, SEVEN GOALS, HAT-TRICK HERO: THE LAST TIME RODGERS FACED DONS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110908</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/boxing-day-bedlam-ropey-ref-dodgy-pens-seven-goals-hat-trick-hero-the-last-time-rodgers-faced-dons/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T05:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS takes his squad to Pittodrie today for the High Noon shoot-out – and the returning Celtic boss is unlikely to have forgotten his last encounter with Aberdeen at the same venue. It was a chaotic Boxing Day 2018 confrontation in the north east when ropey ref Willie Collum adopted Santa Claus-like generosity in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ABERDEEN v CELTIC: 5-MINUTE QUIZ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110902</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/aberdeen-v-celtic-5-minute-quiz-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-13T04:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC faced Aberdeen four times in the Premiership last season and won them all without conceding a solitary goal. The champions embarked upon a new campaign last time around with a 2-0 victory over the Dons on Premiership Flag Day on July 31 at Parkhead. One of the highlights of a colourful afternoon was the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers gives update on Aberdeen-linked Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43371</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/12/brendan-rodgers-aberdeen-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T22:32:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic started their campaign with a win over Ross County. Now, they are set to face a tougher test. Brendan Rodgers’ side will travel to Pittodrie Stadium for the second game of their league season. With the Rangers winning this weekend, the pressure is on the Hoops to come home with the three points in […]
Brendan Rodgers gives update on Aberdeen-linked Celtic player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou signing wants to leave Celtic this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43368</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/12/ange-postecoglou-signing-leave-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-12T21:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a stacked squad at this point in time. Yet, there are some positions where they could do with strengthening. One of them is certainly between the posts, where Joe Hart is the number one right now. The Englishman has played his part in the five trophies the club have won over the previous […]
Ange Postecoglou signing wants to leave Celtic this summer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>