<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-10-06T20:10:26.497Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two returns, potential first league start; Celtic team news ahead of Kilmarnock test]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176714</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/two-returns-potential-first-league-start-celtic-team-news-ahead-of-kilmarnock-test/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T20:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s squad is getting stronger as the weeks pass and Brendan Rodgers is able to call upon a number of players that he couldn’t last...
The post Two returns, potential first league start; Celtic team news ahead of Kilmarnock test appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The uncomfortable Celtic reality for Rangers that doesn't change whoever replaces Michael Beale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176711</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-uncomfortable-celtic-reality-for-rangers-that-doesnt-change-whoever-replaces-michael-beale/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T19:36:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers may have made a managerial change earlier in the season than they did last year, but it doesn’t change the fact that only a...
The post The uncomfortable Celtic reality for Rangers that doesn't change whoever replaces Michael Beale appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers sent Celtic message amid Frank Lampard talk]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44742</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/06/rangers-celtic-message-frank-lampard/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T19:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It remains to be seen who the next manager of the Rangers will be. The Ibrox club recently decided to part ways with Michael Beale after a bad start to the campaign that left them seven points behind Celtic in the league after just the first seven games. As a result, they now begin their […]
Rangers sent Celtic message amid Frank Lampard talk - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic youths lauded after impressing at elite Euro level]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176706</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/celtic-youths-lauded-after-impressing-at-elite-euro-level/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T19:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic B coach Darren O’Dea was left very impressed with his young Hoops team following their match against Lazio U19s on Wednesday. A late Mackenzie...
The post Celtic youths lauded after impressing at elite Euro level appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hollywood star spotted at Celtic Park as he shares picture]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44738</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/06/hollywood-star-celtic-park-picture/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T18:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is musicians who have grabbed most of the headlines in recent times when it comes to supporting Celtic. Of course, Rod Stewart is arguably the most famous fan that the Hoops have these days. Lewis Capaldi is well known for his support of the club as well. Recently, even Macklemore was seen performing on […]
Hollywood star spotted at Celtic Park as he shares picture - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Superb Celtic efforts recognised by FIFA and time is running out to get involved]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176701</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/superb-celtic-efforts-recognised-by-fifa-and-time-is-running-out-to-get-involved/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T17:12:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s treble success in 2022/23 is the basis for Ange Postecoglou’s nomination as the Best FIFA Men’s Coach Of The Year at their annual awards...
The post Superb Celtic efforts recognised by FIFA and time is running out to get involved appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton delivers grim Celtic Champions League verdict]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176697</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-delivers-grim-celtic-champions-league-verdict/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:17:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker Chris Sutton reckons the Bhoys will struggle to even make third position in Group E of the UEFA Champions League after losing...
The post Chris Sutton delivers grim Celtic Champions League verdict appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hearts explanation for shockingly low Celtic Tynecastle ticket allocation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176692</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-hearts-explanation-for-shockingly-low-celtic-tynecastle-ticket-allocation/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T15:21:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There will be just 576 Celtic supporters at Tynecastle for the upcoming Scottish Premiership match against Hearts, it was confirmed by the club today. The...
The post The Hearts explanation for shockingly low Celtic Tynecastle ticket allocation appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No surprises as Derek McInnes calls for 'aggressive' Kilmarnock at Celtic Park on Saturday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176688</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/no-surprises-as-derek-mcinnes-calls-for-aggressive-kilmarnock-at-celtic-park-on-saturday/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T14:55:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kilmarnock boss Derek McInnes reckons his team can pull off another shock victory against Celtic this weekend, after dumping the Bhoys out of the Scottish...
The post No surprises as Derek McInnes calls for 'aggressive' Kilmarnock at Celtic Park on Saturday appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO CRACKERJACK ACCOLADE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112875</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kyogo-crackerjack-accolade/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T13:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO FURUHASHI’S spectacular volley at Ibrox has won the Premiership Goal of the Month for September. The Japanese hitman was favourite for the accolade following his winner in Govan when he lashed a first-time drive away from the groping fingers of Jack Butland for the points-clincher just before the interval. It was Kyogo’s sixth goal against [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[International mention shows how far midfielder has come at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176680</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/international-mention-shows-how-far-matt-oriley-has-come-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder Matt O’Riley won’t be featuring for Denmark during the upcoming international break. The former MK Dons man has arguably been our best player...
The post International mention shows how far midfielder has come at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon confirms Leeds United’s interest in Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44735</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/06/neil-lennon-confirms-leeds-united-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T13:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a number of very talented players in their squad right now who have been linked with moves away from the club. It remains to be seen what the future holds for them. The Hoops did lose two regular starters over the summer in the form of Jota and Carl Starfelt. But other than […]
Neil Lennon confirms Leeds United’s interest in Celtic player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scotland's precarious UEFA coefficient position; a concern for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176668</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/scotlands-precarious-uefa-coefficient-position-a-concern-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scotland and Celtic find themselves in a precarious place in the UEFA coefficient standings after another disappointing week. The Hoops played their second European fixture...
The post Scotland's precarious UEFA coefficient position; a concern for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Much-loved Celtic stars set to face-off in tasty international clash next week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176653</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/much-loved-celtic-stars-set-to-face-off-in-tasty-international-clash-next-week/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a tasty-looking international clash next week that is set to have some current Celtic stars facing each other. The fixture between Japan and...
The post Much-loved Celtic stars set to face-off in tasty international clash next week appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Containing consequences]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112866</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/containing-consequences/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T11:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It still stings, but we need to park the pain of defeat and get back on the horse tomorrow.  Reversals can become infectious, they can drive confidence into a spiral. For my money, this phenomenon in part formed Brendan’s reaction after the game on Wednesday. He was relatively upbeat, containing the consequences by saying whatever [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio vlogger shares cool Celtic Park footage from the night that could have been]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176674</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/lazio-vlogger-shares-cool-celtic-park-footage-from-the-night-that-could-have-been/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seeing 58,000 Celtic fans going wild from the away end is a pretty cool sight. Okay, there’s a fair chance you don’t want to hear...
The post Lazio vlogger shares cool Celtic Park footage from the night that could have been appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston's referee theory that is making things difficult for Celtic in Europe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176644</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alistair-johnstons-referee-theory-that-is-making-things-difficult-for-celtic-in-europe/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston and Celtic are experiencing many difficulties when moving from domestic to European football. The Canadian is part of a Hoops side that have...
The post Alistair Johnston's referee theory that is making things difficult for Celtic in Europe appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss explains questionable decision vs Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44727</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/06/celtic-boss-explains-decision-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T10:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was the same old story for Celtic in Europe once again, as they lost 2-1 to Lazio at Parkhead despite being the better side in almost all departments for the majority of the game. The Hoops went ahead early through Kyogo Furuhashi, who ended his goal drought in the Champions League. But then, they […]
Celtic boss explains questionable decision vs Lazio - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PEDRO GOAL EXPLAINED: VAR TOO LATE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112856</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/pedro-goal-explained-var-too-late/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T09:36:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE questions over the legality of Pedro’s stoppage-time winner at Parkhead in midweek raged long after the final whistle and Celtic’s agonising 2-1 Champions League loss to Lazio. The header in the sixth minute of added-on time looked like a decidedly close call, but, curiously, there was no intervention from VAR. Live TV pictures were [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Friday October 6: Cheer Up Stevie D]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18515</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18515"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T08:35:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The disappointment in the result against Lazio might take a while to go away, and with a double header against group favourites Atletico Madrid ahead,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Malph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GREAT EXPECTATIONS: ‘I EXPECT HIM TO GET BETTER AND BETTER,’ BOSS VERDICT ON PALMA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112852</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/great-expectations-i-expect-him-to-get-better-and-better-boss-verdict-on-palma/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T07:35:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LUIS PALMA is standing by for his first start at Parkhead when Celtic take on Kilmarnock tomorrow afternoon. The 23-year-old winger is still settling in at the champions following his £3.5million switch from Greek outfit Aris Thessaloniki just before the September 1 transfer deadline. Brendan Rodgers predicts big things from the exciting raider who was [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers thinks the Celtic support showed something at the end of Lazio loss]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176630</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-thinks-the-celtic-support-showed-something-at-the-end-of-lazio-loss/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers thinks the Celtic support gave him a good indication of the team’s performance against Lazio. It was a tough midweek defeat for the...
The post Brendan Rodgers thinks the Celtic support showed something at the end of Lazio loss appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘WE’LL RECOVER,’ VOWS RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112847</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/well-recover-vows-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T06:44:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS insists Celtic have moved on from their Viaplay League Cup exit against Kilmarnock at Rugby Park in August. The Hoops boss saw the holders crash out of the competition in only the third game of his return to the club. Rodgers’ remarkable sequence of 24 successive knock-out wins during his seven consecutive trophy [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star shares the dressing room feeling after late Lazio sickener]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176637</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alistair-johnston-shares-the-celtic-dressing-room-feeling-after-late-lazio-sickener/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston has shared the feeling inside the Celtic dressing room after our late sickener against Lazio. The Canadian was one of the players closest...
The post Celtic star shares the dressing room feeling after late Lazio sickener appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC TRIO CALL-UP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112844</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-trio-call-up/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T05:51:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A TRIO of Celtic kids have been called into the Republic of Ireland squad for the European Under-21 Championship qualifier against Latvia a week today. Top prospects winger Rocco Vata, central defender Bosun Lawal and sriker Johnny Kenny will be involved in the 1pm kick-off as the Irish travel to Riga following back-to-back wins over [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers explains why Celtic supporters haven't seen more of summer signing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176621</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-explains-why-celtic-supporters-havent-seen-more-of-luis-palma-so-far/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has been speaking about Luis Palma since our UEFA Champions League loss to Lazio. The Honduran winger, signed from Aris Thessaloniki at the...
The post Brendan Rodgers explains why Celtic supporters haven't seen more of summer signing appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The media go down a very obvious route with Rodgers ahead of weekend Celtic clash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176659</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/the-media-go-down-a-very-obvious-route-with-brendan-rodgers-ahead-of-celtic-vs-kilmarnock/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T05:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers won’t speak to the media on Friday ahead of Celtic vs Kilmarnock this weekend. Due to the short turnaround between the midweek loss...
The post The media go down a very obvious route with Rodgers ahead of weekend Celtic clash appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS’ UNWANTED HAT-TRICK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112837</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-unwanted-hat-trick/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T04:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS completed an unwanted hat-trick in the Champions League Group E loss to Lazio in midweek. The 2-1 reverse against the Italians was the Celtic’s manager’s third consecutive defeat in European competition at Parkhead. The latest setback follows the 2-1 flop in front of the Hoops fans against RB Salzburg in the Europa League [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic called far better than Rangers as Graham Potter talk rubbished]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44724</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/05/celtic-rangers-graham-potter-talk/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T22:35:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic sit seven points clear at the top of the league table while the Rangers find themselves in need of a fourth manager within the space of two years. It remains to be seen who the Ibrox club are able to appoint next after Michael Beale was shown the exit door following a bad start […]
Celtic called far better than Rangers as Graham Potter talk rubbished - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Chelsea manager wants Rangers job despite Celtic lead]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44720</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/05/former-chelsea-rangers-job-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T21:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another manager departed the Rangers recently, unable to overcome the challenge posed by Celtic during his time in the Ibrox hot seat. Michael Beale was not able to win a single trophy during his 10-month stint in Glasgow. In comparison, the Hoops won the treble in the previous campaign and already have a 7-point lead […]
Former Chelsea manager wants Rangers job despite Celtic lead - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Derby Delight: Celtic secure dramatic Thursday win over rivals to go top of SWPL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176616</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/derby-delight-celtic-secure-dramatic-thursday-win-over-rivals-to-go-top-of-swpl/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T20:27:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic FC Women have maintained their perfect record in the SWPL after a 2-1 win over rivals Glasgow City this evening, ensuring they go top...
The post Derby Delight: Celtic secure dramatic Thursday win over rivals to go top of SWPL appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I would be embarrassed"; Chris Sutton uses Celtic and Rangers example to slate Liverpool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176609</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-would-be-embarrassed-chris-sutton-uses-celtic-and-rangers-example-to-slate-liverpool/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T19:50:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker Chris Sutton has been left perplexed by the reaction of Liverpool and Jurgen Klopp to the VAR controversy in England over the...
The post "I would be embarrassed"; Chris Sutton uses Celtic and Rangers example to slate Liverpool appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic target now wanted by Real Madrid in €20m move]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44716</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/05/former-celtic-target-wanted-real-madrid/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T19:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the biggest reasons Celtic were so successful during Ange Postecoglou’s time at the club was their ability to identify top talents. Of course, they went on to bring in players like Kyogo, Jota, Josip Juranovic, Giorgos Giakoumakis, Cameron Carter-Vickers, Matt O’Riley, Reo Hatate, Daizen Maeda and several others over those two years. But […]
Former Celtic target now wanted by Real Madrid in €20m move - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manchester United icon defends Celtic player in loss to Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44712</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/05/manchester-united-icon-celtic-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T18:04:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hearts were left broken again as they conceded late on to lose at the hands of Lazio at Parkhead, a game that they should have won comfortably considering the performances of the two teams. But unfortunately, that has been the story of the Hoops in the Champions League in recent years. It was an […]
Manchester United icon defends Celtic player in loss to Lazio - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Far better club’: Simon Jordan shuts down pundit's Celtic claim amid Rangers-Potter talk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176584</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/far-better-club-simon-jordan-shuts-down-pundits-celtic-claim-amid-rangers-graham-potter-talk/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T17:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Simon Jordan has made it clear that Celtic are a ‘far better club’ on the pitch than Rangers amid talk of Graham Potter replacing Michael...
The post 'Far better club’: Simon Jordan shuts down pundit's Celtic claim amid Rangers-Potter talk appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero unhappy with Brendan Rodgers’ comments]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44709</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/05/celtic-hero-brendan-rodgers-comments/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T15:30:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic can’t find a way to win in the Champions League. Whether they play well or badly, the Hoops always seem to find a way to lose in Europe’s elite competition. The recent game against Lazio at Parkhead was the perfect example of that. Maurizio Sarri’s side came into the contest on a bad run […]
Celtic hero unhappy with Brendan Rodgers’ comments - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I would never': Peter Schmeichel defends Celtic player after crushing defeat to Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176561</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/peter-schmeichel-defends-celtic-player-after-crushing-champions-league-defeat-to-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Schmeichel has defended Celtic goalkeeper Joe Hart for the role he played in Lazio’s stoppage-time winner in the Champions League on Wednesday night. The...
The post 'I would never': Peter Schmeichel defends Celtic player after crushing defeat to Lazio appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SCALES’ EURO 24 REWARD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112833</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/scales-euro-24-reward/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T13:05:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIAM SCALES has been rewarded for his superb form for Celtic this season with a call-up to the Republic of Ireland Euro 24 squad. The Hoops defender has accepted a pivotal role in the champions’ rearguard after answering an SOS following injuries to Cameron Carter-Vickers, Maik Nawrocki and Stephen Welsh. Scales, who has yet to win [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston knows what Celtic must do to succeed in Europe; honest Atletico admission]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176512</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alistair-johnston-knows-what-celtic-must-do-to-succeed-in-europe-honest-atletico-admission/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Alistair Johnston reckons he knows what the team needs to do to succeed in Europe. The Canadian was part of the Hoops side...
The post Alistair Johnston knows what Celtic must do to succeed in Europe; honest Atletico admission appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Micah Richards points out Celtic mistake Michael Beale made]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44705</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/05/micah-richards-celtic-michael-beale/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T12:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Michael Beale’s run as the manager of the Rangers proved to be a failure. He came in with a lot of expectations surrounding him and the tag of ‘the mastermind’ who had helped the Ibrox club to their Premiership triumph a couple of years back. Celtic won the […]
Micah Richards points out Celtic mistake Michael Beale made - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Up there’: Paul Merson makes Celtic Park claim after Newcastle's 'amazing' win in UCL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176539</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/up-there-paul-merson-makes-celtic-park-claim-after-newcastles-amazing-win-in-ucl/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T11:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Merson says Newcastle United’s 4-1 win over PSG in the Champions League is ‘up there with the European nights at Celtic Park’. Whilst Eddie...
The post ‘Up there’: Paul Merson makes Celtic Park claim after Newcastle's 'amazing' win in UCL appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beale Ciao – Etims Podcast]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18511</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18511"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T11:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NB  This was recorded  before the Lazio game…..booooooooooooooooooooooohhhhhhhhhhh Monty and Desi get together to discuss a wonderfully entertaining September. From various wins, a Euro defeat,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Desi Mond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hyunjun Yang, Luis Palma and the unavoidable Jota feeling at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176458</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/hyunjun-yang-luis-palma-and-the-unavoidable-jota-feeling-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a sense amongst the Celtic support that, with a few additions in key areas, we could be a force to be reckoned with in...
The post Hyunjun Yang, Luis Palma and the unavoidable Jota feeling at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PEDRO WINNER: EXPLAIN THIS, VAR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112832</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/pedro-winner-explain-this-var/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T11:03:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ARE we alone in thinking Pedro’s stoppage-time winner at Parkhead last night looked suspiciously offside? Okay, CQN accepts we may be a tad biased – and desperate – but surely VAR could have cleared up the dubiety with all their new-fangled technology? They were quick enough to put up images of Luis Palma being inches [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic potential and softness on show]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112801</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-potential-and-softness-on-show/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T11:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic looked nervy during the opening exchanges in their Champions League clash with Lazio last night, as Lazio imposed a high press.  A 12th minute  turn and drive inside from Daizen Maeda changed things. Daizen found Matt O’Riley who played a truly great one-touch pass behind the defence into the box.  This is Kyogo Territory [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss makes feelings known about referee in his own unique way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176451</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-makes-feelings-clear-about-referee-in-his-own-unique-way/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers wasn’t happy with the standard of officiating during Celtic’s defeat to Lazio on Wednesday. It was a frustrating evening to be a Celtic...
The post Celtic boss makes feelings known about referee in his own unique way appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Thursday October 5: Same Old Feeling Every Time]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18507</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18507"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T09:05:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I guess now we all know how Motherwell fans felt at the weekend.     I don’t want to say “that’s fucked it ” but…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Malph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NO PAIN, NO GAIN: McGREGOR SEARCHES FOR POSITIVES]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112799</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/no-pain-no-gain-mcgregor-searches-for-positives/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T08:51:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC went from heroes to zeroes in the space of 15 dramatic minutes at Parkhead last night. In the 81st minute, Luis Palma looked as though he had claimed a sensational winner when he flashed in a low angled drive against Lazio to make the scoreline 2-1 to the hosts. Alas, the ‘goal’ was wiped [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Wrong': Micah Richards highlights Michael Beale's huge Celtic mistake after Rangers sacking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176515</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/wrong-micah-richards-highlights-huge-celtic-mistake-from-michael-beale-after-rangers-sacking/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Micah Richards says sacked Rangers manager Michael Beale picked the ‘wrong battle’ by deciding to have a war of words with Celtic hero, Chris Sutton....
The post 'Wrong': Micah Richards highlights Michael Beale's huge Celtic mistake after Rangers sacking appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘COULDN’T FAULT THEM,’ BUT RODGERS PINPOINTS CELTIC FLAW]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112792</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/couldnt-fault-them-but-rodgers-pinpoints-celtic-flaw/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T07:56:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS admitted he couldn’t fault his players in the aftermath of another sickening Champions League failure in the 2-1 loss to Lazio. However, the Celtic boss also insisted his team have to be more “ruthless” to have any hope of success at this elite level in the European game. Following the disappointing setback in Rotterdam [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Liam Scales about to get big reward for impressive Celtic form]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176505</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/liam-scales-is-about-to-get-a-big-reward-for-impressive-celtic-form/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liam Scales is about to get a big reward for his impressive recent form at Celtic. The Irish Sun say that the Hoops defender will...
The post Report: Liam Scales about to get big reward for impressive Celtic form appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["They wear out quickly"; What the Italian media are saying about Celtic vs Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176473</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/they-wear-out-quickly-what-the-italian-media-are-saying-about-celtic-vs-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was defeat again for Celtic in the UEFA Champions League despite an encouraging display against Lazio. Brendan Rodgers‘ team looked composed at the top...
The post "They wear out quickly"; What the Italian media are saying about Celtic vs Lazio appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['He was superb': Trevor Sinclair praises standout Celtic player after 'harsh' Lazio defeat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176475</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/he-was-superb-trevor-sinclair-praises-standout-celtic-player-after-harsh-lazio-defeat/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trevor Sinclair praised Liam Scales as a standout performer for Brendan Rodgers’ Celtic during a gut-wrenching 2-1 defeat to Lazio in the Champions League. At...
The post 'He was superb': Trevor Sinclair praises standout Celtic player after 'harsh' Lazio defeat appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rodgers explains exactly where Celtic went wrong for Lazio winner; Carter-Vickers backing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176442</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-explains-exactly-where-celtic-went-wrong-for-lazio-winner-carter-vickers-backing/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has explained exactly where he feels his Celtic side went wrong for Lazio’s late winner. It was the cruelest of endings for the...
The post Rodgers explains exactly where Celtic went wrong for Lazio winner; Carter-Vickers backing appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kind words from Maurizio Sarri but the Celtic support are waking up to a cold hard reality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176465</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/kind-words-from-maurizio-sarri-but-the-celtic-support-are-waking-up-to-a-cold-hard-reality/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T05:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, it’s the morning after the night before and we’re all still coming to terms with Celtic’s loss to Lazio. Just how did we manage...
The post Kind words from Maurizio Sarri but the Celtic support are waking up to a cold hard reality appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JOCK STEIN THE PR MAN: A PERSONAL MEMORY FROM AUTHOR ALEX GORDON]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=97520</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/jock-stein-the-pr-man-a-personal-memory-from-author-alex-gordon/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T04:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOCK STEIN was born on this day in Burnbank, South Lanarkshire – exactly 101 years ago. CQN have been paying tribute to Celtic’s legendary manager on a special day. In another EXCLUSIVE, author Alex Gordon, who has written twenty-four books and fifteen on Celtic, travels back in time to his early days on the Daily [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JOCK STEIN: FOUR LIONS HAVE THEIR SAY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=97519</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/jock-stein-four-lions-have-their-say/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T04:32:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Jock Stein was born on this day in Burnbank, South Lanarksire – exactly 101 years ago. CQN has been celebrating the birth of a Hoops great who transformed the entire football club when he arrived as manager in March 1965. Jim Craig, John Clark, Willie Wallace and Bobby Lennox, four of the existing [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JOCK STEIN v RANGERS AND THE SWEETEST TITLE TRIUMPH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=97522</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/jock-stein-v-rangers-and-the-sweetest-title-triumph/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T04:31:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOCK STEIN was born on this date in Burnbank, South Lanarkshire, in 1922 – exactly 101 years ago. CQN is paying tribute today to the legendary Celtic manager with Alex Gordon, author of fifteen Celtic publications, opening his book files to reflect on the life and times of a genuine club great. Here is an EXCLUSIVE [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JOCK STEIN: THE BIRTH OF A LEGEND 101 YEARS AGO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=97516</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/jock-stein-the-birth-of-a-legend-101-years-ago/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T04:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOCK STEIN was born on this date in Burnbank, South Lanarkshire, in 1922 – exactly 101 years ago. Ironically, the Celtic legend played his first senior game as a trialist centre-half AGAINST the Parkhead club on November 14 1942. He witnessed his future team score four goals. Mind you, Rovers were good enough to score [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player criticised for performance against Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44701</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/04/celtic-player-criticised-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T22:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was an evening that promised so much and provided so little, as Celtic lost 2-1 at Parkhead against Lazio. Maurizio Sarri’s side were not great by any stretch of the imagination and the Hoops were undone by their own mistakes at the back. Going forward, they perhaps could have done more and had a […]
Celtic player criticised for performance against Lazio - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers reacts to the cruelest of nights for Celtic in the Champions League]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176434</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-reacts-to-the-cruelest-of-nights-for-celtic-in-the-champions-league/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T22:16:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has been giving his thoughts in the aftermath of Celtic’s Champions League loss to Lazio. It proved to be the cruelest of nights...
The post Brendan Rodgers reacts to the cruelest of nights for Celtic in the Champions League appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC 1 LAZIO 2: HOOPS’ MISERY PILE-UP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112787</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-1-lazio-2-hoops-misery-pile-up/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T21:18:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC 1  LAZIO 2 DAME FORTUNE positively snarled in the direction of Celtic as they lost in heartbreaking fashion to the Italians at Parkhead tonight. In the 81st minute, Luis Palma had what he – and most of the rocking stadium – thought was a superb second goal for Brendan Rodgers’ men. The celebrations were [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VAR costs Celtic again by missing potential Lazio red card]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44696</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/04/var-costs-celtic-red-card-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T21:15:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Celtic have not had the best of luck when it comes to VAR. There have been numerous times in the past when they have come at the wrong end of things because of the technology and that run continued in their 2-1 defeat to Lazio in the Champions […]
VAR costs Celtic again by missing potential Lazio red card - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Absolute gutter, Kyogo's moment; 3 things we learned as Celtic lose to Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176425</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/absolute-gutter-kyogos-moment-3-things-we-learned-as-celtic-lose-to-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T21:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a gutting night for Celtic in the UEFA Champions League as we fell to a horrible 2-1 loss to Lazio. The Hoops were...
The post Absolute gutter, Kyogo's moment; 3 things we learned as Celtic lose to Lazio appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo finally ends Champions League curse at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44692</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/04/kyogo-ends-champions-league-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T19:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo has been nothing short of fantastic since he joined Celtic in the summer of 2021 from Vissel Kobe. Of course, he arrived amidst a lot of doubts. Many questioned whether he could deal with the physicality of Scottish football. Well, it has been the other clubs who have had a tough time dealing with […]
Kyogo finally ends Champions League curse at Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MORATA DOUBLE DUMPS DUTCH AND SEALS WIN FOR ATLETICO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112789</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/morata-double-dumps-dutch-and-seals-win-for-atletico/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T18:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TWO goals from Alvaro Morata sealed a spirited fightback by Atletico Madrid to overcome Feyenoord 3-2 in Champions League Group E in the Spanish capital tonight. The Dutch, 2-0 conquerors over Celtic in Rotterdam a fortnight ago, led 2-1 just after the half-hour mark before they collapsed to defeat. The visitors took the lead in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic v Lazio, ‘GG Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112784</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-lazio-gg-live-updates/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T18:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 20:00.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: PHILLIPS, YANG GET NOD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112769</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-phillips-yang-get-nod/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T17:54:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIVERPOOL loanee Nat Phillips will start alongside Liam Scales in the middle of the Celtic rearguard in the Champions League Group E encounter against Lazio at Parkhead tonight. Cameron Carter-Vickers, who has missed the last seven games through injury, will take his place among the stand-by squad. Yang Hyun-jun, who was taken off at half-time [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur want to sign Celtic-linked player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44688</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/04/tottenham-hotspur-celtic-linked-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T17:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans were left somewhat disappointed by how the club’s summer transfer window turned out. They did bring in nine players to Parkhead but the general feeling was that enough experience was not signed, as the Hoops instead focused on making ‘project’ signings. On the other hand, key players like Jota and Carl Starfelt had […]
Tottenham Hotspur want to sign Celtic-linked player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Barry Ferguson needs reality check after Celtic & Rangers title claim following Beale's exit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176406</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/barry-ferguson-needs-a-reality-check-after-celtic-rangers-title-claim-following-michael-beales-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Beale is out of the door at Rangers after being outclassed by a Brendan Rodgers and Celtic side that’s not even at full strength...
The post Barry Ferguson needs reality check after Celtic & Rangers title claim following Beale's exit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three changes, big attacking switch; Celtic Predicted XI vs Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176294</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/three-changes-big-attacking-switch-celtic-predicted-xi-vs-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Park will be rocking on Wednesday night when the Hoops welcome the might of Lazio to Glasgow. It’s matchday two of the UEFA Champions...
The post Three changes, big attacking switch; Celtic Predicted XI vs Lazio appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic player tipped for vacant Rangers job]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44686</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/04/former-celtic-player-rangers-job/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T14:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is safe to say that the Rangers have struggled to find the right manager for a long time now. Many view Steven Gerrard’s run at Ibrox as a success but the fact of the matter is that he only won one trophy in nine attempts. Giovanni van Bronckhorst showed early promise but lasted just […]
Former Celtic player tipped for vacant Rangers job - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maurizio Sarri makes fantastic comments about Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44681</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/04/maurizio-sarri-fantastic-comments-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T12:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are set to continue their UEFA Champions League campaign by welcoming Lazio to Parkhead. The Hoops made a losing start in the competition, losing 2-0 away against Feyenoord in their opening game and will be looking to put some points up on the board when they take on Maurizio Sarri’s side. A lot has […]
Maurizio Sarri makes fantastic comments about Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic Park fightback could begin tonight]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176351</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-celtic-park-fightback-could-begin-tonight/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor says it is up to him and his team-mates to make Celtic Park a fortress in Europe again. For the first 11 or...
The post The Celtic Park fightback could begin tonight appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TIERNEY OUT, TAYLOR IN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112781</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/tierney-out-taylor-in/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T11:48:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GREG TAYLOR has been named in Steve Clarke’s Scotland squad while former Celtic fans’ favourite Kieran Tierney drops out through injury. The champions’ left-back gets the nod for the crucial Euro 24 qualifier against Spain in Seville a week tomorrow and the glamour friendly against France in Lille the following Tuesday. Taylor has been in fine [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EX-CELT PILES WOE ON HAKSA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112776</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ex-celt-piles-woe-on-haksa/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T11:26:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic midfielder Stuart Armstrong piled the misery on Sead Haksabanovic and his Stoke City team-mates with a sublime free-kick winner for Southampton last night. The one-time Hoops fans’ favourite claimed the game’s only goal four minutes from the interval to seal three Championship points for the south-coast side who sit in tenth place, seven [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic star shares social media post after recent visit to Lennoxtown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176287</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/charlie-mulgrew-shares-social-media-post-after-recent-visit-to-celtic-training/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic star Charlie Mulgrew was back at Lennoxtown this week as he begins his coaching journey. The ex-Scotland international announced his retirement from football...
The post Former Celtic star shares social media post after recent visit to Lennoxtown appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The games we aspire to]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112774</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-games-we-aspire-to/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T11:03:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As fans, we all like to think we know what we are talking about.  Then, now and again, we’re happy to leave decisions up to the man paid the big money to take them.  Brendan Rodgers told the media yesterday that Cameron Carter-Vickers could be in the squad for tonight’s game against Lazio.  What a [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ciro Immobile continues Lazio theme of knowledgeable comments about Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176319</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/ciro-immobile-continues-lazio-theme-of-knowledgeable-comments-about-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio captain Ciro Immobile has continued the theme of knowledgable comments in the lead-up to his side’s clash against Celtic. It’s going to be a...
The post Ciro Immobile continues Lazio theme of knowledgeable comments about Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC v LAZIO: 5-MINUTE QUIZ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112765</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-lazio-5-minute-quiz/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T09:16:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC beat Lazio home and away in the Europa League in the space of a fortnight in season 2019/20. On both occasions, Neil Lennon’s side had to come from behind to win 2-1 to secure famous victories over the Italian aces, the first at Parkhead on October 24 2019 and the second in Rome two [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['The ultimate': Moussa Dembele reacts to Celtic's official Twitter post about 30-year-old]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176372</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/moussa-dembele-reacts-to-celtics-tribute-to-tom-rogic-after-he-announces-retirement/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moussa Dembele has told Tom Rogic to ‘have fun’ after the Celtic hero announced his retirement from football at the age of 30. The midfielder’s...
The post 'The ultimate': Moussa Dembele reacts to Celtic's official Twitter post about 30-year-old appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE NAT AND MATT SHOW]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112760</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-nat-and-matt-show/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T08:35:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NAT PHILLIPS is preparing for his Celtic Champions League debut in the Group E encounter against Lazio at Parkhead tonight. The on-loan Liverpool defender failed to make Brendan Rodgers’ matchday squad for the 2-0 loss against Feyenoord in the section opener in Rotterdam a fortnight ago. Phillips, who joined on a temporary transfer until January [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Wednesday October 4: Now We See It]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18503</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18503"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T08:20:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The dramatic events at Fir Park on Saturday, which at times seemed almost scripted for the Motherwell pay tv audience, showed that the message from…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Malph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maurizio Sarri has done his homework on Celtic; impressive comments that go against the norm]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176303</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/maurizio-sarri-has-done-his-homework-on-celtic-impressive-comments-that-go-against-the-norm/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maurizio Sarri has clearly done his homework on Celtic ahead of Wednesday’s UEFA Champions League clash. It’s matchday two of the group stage and Sarri’s...
The post Maurizio Sarri has done his homework on Celtic; impressive comments that go against the norm appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Not from a Celtic': Neil Lennon jibes at Rangers after Michael Beale's sacking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176271</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/not-from-a-celtic-neil-lennon-jibes-at-rangers-after-michael-beales-sacking/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon has made it clear that Rangers’ squad doesn’t put fear into Celtic after the sacking of Michael Beale. In the summer, Rangers, led...
The post 'Not from a Celtic': Neil Lennon jibes at Rangers after Michael Beale's sacking appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOME SWEET HOME? RODGERS’ EURO RECORD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112750</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/home-sweet-home-rodgers-euro-record/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T06:54:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS will take charge of Celtic against Lazio tonight for his 22nd European game at Parkhead. The sequence kicked off with a 3-0 win in a Champions League qualifier against Lincoln Red Imps on July 20 2016 after the shock 1-0 first leg setback in Gibraltar the previous week. Swedish defender Mikael Lustig got the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Young manager"; Rodgers offers some advice to Beale that Celtic fans will enjoy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176312</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/rodgers-has-some-advice-for-young-manager-beale-after-he-came-up-short-against-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers had some advice for recently departed Rangers boss Michael Beale. The Englishman certainly did his fair share of talking during his...
The post "Young manager"; Rodgers offers some advice to Beale that Celtic fans will enjoy appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The pretty disappointing Lazio support expected at Celtic Park tonight]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176362</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/the-pretty-disappointing-lazio-support-expected-at-celtic-park-tonight/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Park will be packed to the rafters when the Hoops take on Lazio on Wednesday evening. It may only be matchday two of the...
The post  The pretty disappointing Lazio support expected at Celtic Park tonight appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The full Cameron Carter-Vickers story from Brendan Rodgers; surprising Celtic vs Lazio status]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176265</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-full-cameron-carter-vickers-story-from-brendan-rodgers-could-make-celtic-return-vs-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cameron Carter-Vickers definitely won’t start for Celtic against Lazio on Wednesday night. However, the Hoops defender could make his long-awaited return from injury off the...
The post The full Cameron Carter-Vickers story from Brendan Rodgers; surprising Celtic vs Lazio status appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EVERGREEN CELT’S EURO POSER FOR BOSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112740</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/evergreen-celts-euro-poser-for-boss/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T05:27:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JAMES FORREST is on stand-by for his FORTY-SEVENTH Champions League appearance for Celtic against Lazio tonight. The 32-year-old evergreen winger made his debut in Europe’s most prestigious competition in 2014/15 and he has been involved in the tourney every year since. Forrest got the nod from Ronny Deila to face Legia Warsaw as a 70th-minute substitute [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Embarrassing’: Chris Sutton makes Celtic comment after Manchester United lose in UCL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176321</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/chris-sutton-makes-celtic-comment-after-manchester-united-arsenal-lose-in-champions-league/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton has come to the defence of Celtic after both Manchester United and Arsenal were beaten in the Champions League on Tuesday night. The...
The post ‘Embarrassing’: Chris Sutton makes Celtic comment after Manchester United lose in UCL appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO: HIT OR MYTH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112735</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kyogo-hit-or-myth-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T04:32:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO FURUHASHI will be a man on a mission when he lines up against Lazio at Parkhead tonight. Amazingly, Celtic’s prolific striker, who has claimed 58 goals in just over two years at the Hoops, has yet to open his account in the Champions League. Kyogo fired blanks in successive outings in Europe’s elite competition [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE FIVE WORDS WE DON’T WANT TO HEAR FROM BRENDAN RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112719</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-five-words-we-dont-want-to-hear-from-brendan-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-04T04:15:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“THEY were better than us.” Those were the five words used by Brendan Rodgers to sum up a defeat in his previous Champions League group game at Parkhead almost six years ago. The Celtic manager had just seen his team beaten 1-0 by Anderlecht in front of a stunned home crowd on December 5 2017 [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manchester United icon and Celtic fan linked with Rangers job]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44677</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/03/manchester-united-celtic-fan-rangers-job/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T22:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers find themselves without a manager once again after showing Michael Beale the exit door following a bad start to the season that has left them trailing Celtic by seven points just seven games into the league campaign. This is the fourth time within the space of two years that they are looking for someone […]
Manchester United icon and Celtic fan linked with Rangers job - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend takes final dig at Michael Beale on air]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44644</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/03/celtic-legend-michael-beale-air/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T21:05:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Beale seemed to have a habit of creating controversy with his comments during his less than a-year-long run as the manager of the Rangers. Much like too many of his results in the Glasgow Derby, he appears to have come out on the wrong end when it comes to his back-and-forth comments with one […]
Celtic legend takes final dig at Michael Beale on air - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Journalist tips Celtic to sign £20 million goalkeeper]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44670</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/03/journalist-celtic-20-million-goalkeeper/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T19:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will need to sign a new goalkeeper in the near future. In fact, they were expected to bring in someone to challenge Joe Hart for the first-team gloves this summer and there were links with Croatian number one Dominik Livakovic. Ultimately, it led nowhere though and the Hoops did not strengthen their ranks between […]
Journalist tips Celtic to sign £20 million goalkeeper - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Had it tougher': Chris Sutton makes Celtic claim after Postecoglou's flying start at Spurs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176248</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-highlights-celtics-might-after-ange-postecoglous-unbeaten-start-at-tottenham/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T19:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton says Ange Postecoglou had it ‘tougher’ at Celtic following his unbeaten start at Tottenham Hotspur. On Saturday, Tottenham beat nine-man Liverpool in a...
The post 'Had it tougher': Chris Sutton makes Celtic claim after Postecoglou's flying start at Spurs appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss makes Michael Beale claim after Rangers sack]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44666</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/03/celtic-boss-michael-beale-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T18:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is safe to say that there has been very little stability in the Rangers managerial office over the past couple of years as Celtic have continued to dominate Scottish football. Steven Gerrard left to take the Aston Villa job. Giovanni van Bronckhorst impressed early on, guiding them to a Scottish Cup triumph and an […]
Celtic boss makes Michael Beale claim after Rangers sack - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Too much': Stuart Pearce delivers truth bombs to Rangers about Celtic after Beale's sacking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176232</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/stuart-pearce-delivers-truth-bombs-to-rangers-about-celtic-after-michael-beales-sacking/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stuart Pearce has suggested that sought-after Rangers managers might look at the situation in Scotland and think the gap is ‘too much’ to bridge between...
The post 'Too much': Stuart Pearce delivers truth bombs to Rangers about Celtic after Beale's sacking appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CCV COMEBACK HINT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112717</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ccv-comeback-hint/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T16:51:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has hinted crocked centre-back Cameron Carter-Vickers could make a surprise comeback to his Champions League squad tomorrow night. The defender hasn’t figured since coming off at the interval of the 3-1 Premiership win over Aberdeen at Pittodrie on August 13 after suffering a muscular injury. The rock in the heart of the Hoops’ rearguard [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic drop possible hint about Cameron Carter-Vickers return]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44662</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/03/celtic-drop-cameron-carter-vickers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T16:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cameron Carter-Vickers is widely recognised as the best centre-back that Celtic have in their ranks at this point in time. But he has played very little football lately. The American international underwent surgery towards the end of last season and only returned earlier in the ongoing campaign. But soon he found himself back on the […]
Celtic drop possible hint about Cameron Carter-Vickers return - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic join Europe's elite after impressive start under Brendan Rodgers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176225</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-join-europes-elite-after-impressive-start-under-brendan-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may not realise it, but it’s been a hugely impressive start to the Premiership season from Celtic. It’s been far from easy at times...
The post Celtic join Europe's elite after impressive start under Brendan Rodgers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[O’RILEY SNUB MYSTERY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112714</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/oriley-snub-mystery/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T13:40:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S on-fire midfielder Matt O’Riley has been snubbed by Denmark for their forthcoming Euro 24 qualifiers this month. The Hoops star had been tipped to step up to the senior squad of his adopted nation for the first time after turning out six times for their Under-21 side. However, manager Kasper Hjulmand has overlooked the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switched-on Celtic star already making great noises about move to Scotland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176141</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/switched-on-hyunjun-yang-already-making-great-noises-about-move-to-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic winger Hyunjun Yang seems to be settling in well to life in Scotland. The South Korean winger made the switch from Gangwon in late...
The post Switched-on Celtic star already making great noises about move to Scotland appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["So proud of you"; Brown, Cahill, Duffy and more react to Celtic great's very personal message]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176219</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/so-proud-of-you-brown-cahill-duffy-and-more-react-to-celtic-great-tom-rogics-big-message/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T11:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic hero Tom Rogic has announced his retirement from football at the age of 30. Rogic spent nine years on our books, joining as...
The post "So proud of you"; Brown, Cahill, Duffy and more react to Celtic great's very personal message appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Barcelona star returns to Celtic Park after playing in famous 2012 night]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176134</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/former-barcelona-star-returns-to-celtic-park-after-playing-in-famous-2012-night/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A number of Lazio personnel will arrive at Celtic Park with previous experience on their side. The likes of Ciro Immobile and Danilo Cataldi were...
The post Former Barcelona star returns to Celtic Park after playing in famous 2012 night appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CL hopes, Tom, Mick hustling for his job]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112712</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/cl-hopes-tom-mick-hustling-for-his-job/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T11:03:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been so long since Celtic progressed into the knockout rounds of the Champions League we dare not allow expectations to take root in our heads.  For now, at least, the prospect is a live one.  The result against Lazio at Celtic Park tomorrow night will give us a real insight into where our [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic vs Lazio referee has already been involved in Ibrox controversy this season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176114</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-vs-lazio-referee-has-already-been-involved-in-ibrox-controversy-this-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donatas Rumšas will be the man in charge when Celtic face Lazio this Wednesday. It’s set to be a huge evening in Glasgow as we...
The post Celtic vs Lazio referee has already been involved in Ibrox controversy this season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano drops late-night news that will affect Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44658</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/03/fabrizio-romano-late-night-news-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T10:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Celtic’s transfer business over the recent years has been a bit inconsistent. They were incredible during the summer of 2021 and the winter of 2022, building the core of the team by signing many players who would go on to be first-team starters. But other than that, it […]
Fabrizio Romano drops late-night news that will affect Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[’Laughing’: Celtic icon Neil Lennon slams Rangers-Postecoglou claim after Beale's sacking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176195</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-icon-neil-lennon-slams-rangers-ange-postecoglou-claim-after-michael-beales-sacking/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T09:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon has fired back at a Rangers fan who suggested that his supporters were ‘jealous’ when Celtic first appointed Ange Postecoglou as their manager...
The post ’Laughing’: Celtic icon Neil Lennon slams Rangers-Postecoglou claim after Beale's sacking appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WILL THE REAL REO HATATE PLEASE STAND UP?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112710</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/will-the-real-reo-hatate-please-stand-up-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T08:37:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE, a dynamic performer last season, has yet to complete 90 minutes in a Celtic game this time around. Admittedly hampered by injury, the 25-year-old Japanese midfielder has yet to get into his stride with the team now facing their tenth game of the campaign in the Champions League Group E encounter against Lazio [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INVINCIBLE RETIRES: THANKS FOR THE MEMORIES, TOM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112706</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/invincible-retires-thanks-for-the-memories-tom/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T07:56:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC Invincible Tom Rogic has quit football – at the age of 30. The Wizard of Oz, a Hoops fans’ favourite, has hung up his boots after leaving West Brom at the end of the season. Rogic had been out of football for four months before Steve Bruce took him to the Championship club on [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Fair play': Barry Ferguson can't deny Celtic truth after Rangers sack Michael Beale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176156</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/barry-ferguson-cant-deny-celtic-truth-after-rangers-sack-michael-beale/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Barry Ferguson couldn’t deny that there is a ‘spirit building’ at Celtic after Rangers sacked Michael Beale. As Celtic produced a stunning win at Motherwell...
The post 'Fair play': Barry Ferguson can't deny Celtic truth after Rangers sack Michael Beale appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic unveil well-intentioned Champions League merch but they're unlikely to be big sellers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176121</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-unveil-well-intentioned-champions-league-merch-but-theyre-unlikely-to-be-big-sellers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have unveiled some new merchandise that is unlikely to be a big seller. The Hoops are back in the UEFA Champions League for the...
The post Celtic unveil well-intentioned Champions League merch but they're unlikely to be big sellers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liverpool fume at VAR shambles but they got a better explanation than Celtic last season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176154</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/liverpool-fume-at-var-shambles-but-they-got-a-better-explanation-than-celtic-last-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some Celtic fans may have been scratching their heads a little bit during the Tottenham Hotspur vs Liverpool game on Saturday. As you’ll no doubt...
The post Liverpool fume at VAR shambles but they got a better explanation than Celtic last season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano's big Jeremie Frimpong report should play right into Celtic's hands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176127</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/fabrizio-romanos-big-jeremie-frimpong-report-should-play-right-into-celtics-hands/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic defender Jeremie Frimpong is set to sign a new deal with Bayer Leverkusen. That’s according to well-known transfer guru Fabrizio Romano who offered...
The post Fabrizio Romano's big Jeremie Frimpong report should play right into Celtic's hands appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Charlton under-14s"; former Celtic hero's brutal trolling of Michael Beale continues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176148</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/charlton-under-14s-celtic-hero-chris-suttons-brutal-trolling-of-michael-beale-continues/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T05:17:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic hero Chris Sutton’s brutal trolling of Michael Beale has continued. The Englishman was dismissed as Rangers manager at the weekend after his side...
The post "Charlton under-14s"; former Celtic hero's brutal trolling of Michael Beale continues appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIRTHDAY BHOY ABADA’S EURO HOPE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=83303</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/birthday-bhoy-abadas-euro-hope/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T04:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIEL ABADA is hoping for a belated birthday celebration when Celtic take on Lazio in the Champions League Group E encounter at Parkhead tomorrow night. The exciting Israel international winger turns 22 today, but, alas, the nearest he will get to the action against the Serie A cracks will be a seat in the stand when [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans react as Arsene Wenger claim goes viral]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44654</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/02/celtic-fans-arsene-wenger-claim/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T22:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers find themselves without a manager once again. This has not been an uncommon situation for them in recent years, to be honest. Whoever arrives next will be their fourth head coach in less than two years. During that period of time, they have won one trophy compared to Celtic’s five. Of course, there will […]
Celtic fans react as Arsene Wenger claim goes viral - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Favourite named for Rangers job as Celtic race ahead]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44652</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/02/favourite-named-rangers-job-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T21:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a four-point lead in the Premiership over second-placed St Mirren and seven points ahead of the Rangers. The Hoops seem to be showing no signs of slowing down both on and off the pitch though. The situation is very different when it comes to Ibrox. They find themselves without a manager for the […]
Favourite named for Rangers job as Celtic race ahead - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James McFadden highlights Celtic star who has been ‘sensational’ this season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176092</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/james-mcfadden-highlights-celtic-star-who-has-been-sensational-this-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The game of Matt O’Riley is just going from strength to strength at Celtic. After impressing under Ange Postecoglou, it feels as though the 22-year-old...
The post James McFadden highlights Celtic star who has been ‘sensational’ this season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero makes superb tweet after Michael Beale sack]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44649</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/02/celtic-hero-tweet-michael-beale/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T19:34:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is safe to say that Michael Beale’s time at Ibrox did not turn out as he would have envisioned. The manager had come in amidst a lot of expectations and hype but failed to deliver. He was not able to win a single trophy during his time with the Rangers and did not even […]
Celtic hero makes superb tweet after Michael Beale sack - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As rivals fracture Brendan Rodgers shows unity with Celtic hierarchy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176089</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/as-rivals-fracture-brendan-rodgers-shows-unity-with-celtic-hierarchy/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T18:52:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers demonstrated the unity at Celtic with comments in the wake of Saturday’s thrilling win over Motherwell. Luis Palma and Matt O’Riley scored late...
The post As rivals fracture Brendan Rodgers shows unity with Celtic hierarchy appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Michael Beale comments on Celtic that look even more foolish now after Rangers sacking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176084</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-michael-beale-comments-on-celtic-that-look-even-more-foolish-now-after-rangers-sacking/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T18:20:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Beale was far from a shy and retiring character during his spell as a manager in Scottish football, but in truth, the controversial comments...
The post The Michael Beale comments on Celtic that look even more foolish now after Rangers sacking appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bayern Munich player does not regret leaving Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44646</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/02/bayern-munich-regret-leaving-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T18:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have continued to enjoy success on the pitch for a long time now. They have won 11 of the last 12 league campaigns and if something unexpected does not happen, they should be able to clinch this one as well. But that does not mean that the Hoops have been successful in all aspects […]
Bayern Munich player does not regret leaving Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Lazio and Man City star left impressed by Celtic ahead of Champions League showdown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176079</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-lazio-and-man-city-star-left-impressed-by-celtic-ahead-of-champions-league-showdown/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T17:55:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Lazio and Man City attacker Rolando Bianchi reckons Celtic will be competitive against the Italians on Wednesday night – and the rest of their...
The post Former Lazio and Man City star left impressed by Celtic ahead of Champions League showdown appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Motherwell publish sensational new footage of Celtic heartbreaker and celebration drama]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176076</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/motherwell-publish-sensational-new-footage-of-celtic-heartbreaker-and-celebration-drama/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T17:20:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘Football can be so cruel’ is the verdict of Motherwell Football Club this Monday evening as they reflect on a weekend of so close, yet...
The post Motherwell publish sensational new footage of Celtic heartbreaker and celebration drama appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['That’s where Celtic’: Kris Boyd makes Celtic claim on Sky after Rangers sack Michael Beale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176058</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/thats-where-celtic-kris-boyd-makes-celtic-claim-on-sky-after-rangers-sack-michael-beale/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T16:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kris Boyd has praised Celtic for getting the job done on the domestic stage and winning the trophies after Rangers sacked Michael Beale. The former...
The post 'That’s where Celtic’: Kris Boyd makes Celtic claim on Sky after Rangers sack Michael Beale appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic concern after shocker of a Motherwell challenge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175970</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-addresses-greg-taylor-celtic-concern-after-heavy-motherwell-tackle-nat-phillips-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T16:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers is hoping that Greg Taylor won’t be suffering from any ill effects resulting from a heavy Motherwell challenge on him late on in...
The post Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic concern after shocker of a Motherwell challenge appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have golden chance to put immediate pressure on Steven Davis, Alex Rae and Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176053</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/celtic-have-golden-chance-to-put-immediate-pressure-on-steven-davis-alex-rae-and-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T14:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that Celtic’s rivals Rangers have sacked their manager, attention is turning to the upcoming list of fixtures for both Glasgow teams and what the...
The post Celtic have golden chance to put immediate pressure on Steven Davis, Alex Rae and Rangers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Lineker makes fantastic claim about Celtic on air]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44640</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/02/gary-lineker-makes-claim-celtic-air/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T13:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are coming off quite the week. They got themselves a dramatic 2-1 win over Motherwell at Fir Park. The Hoops went ahead in the 87th minute through Luis Palma, as the Honduran international scored his first goal for the club. Most fans thought that was the winner before the home team equalised in the […]
Gary Lineker makes fantastic claim about Celtic on air - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIG DEAL: CELTIC TARGET TWO MORE STARS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112702</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/big-deal-celtic-target-two-more-stars/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T11:38:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CAMERON CARTER-VICKERS and Greg Taylor are in line to become the next Celtic players to be offered extended contracts. The Hoops hierarchy want the defenders to follow the recent trend of EIGHT stars who have signed enhanced terms at the champions. Matt O’Riley became the latest star to pledge his immediate future to the Parkhead men [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sisyphus FC’s endless struggle to catch Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112701</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/sisyphus-fcs-endless-struggle-to-catch-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T11:06:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That late winner by Matt O’Riley was the start of a great weekend for Celtic, as later, main challengers St Mirren could only manage a draw at Kilmarnock.  The fact that this result is better than Celtic managed there in the League Cup is no comfort to the Paisley side’s title aspirations. St Mirren are [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic look ready to hold talks with two more players]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44636</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/02/celtic-ready-talks-two-players/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T10:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been very active in recent times and taking a number of steps in the positive direction. Yes, the club’s signings in the summer came under a lot of criticism and understandably so. They decided to go for only highly-rated youngsters and no real experience was brought to the club. The shortcoming of that […]
Celtic look ready to hold talks with two more players - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>