<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2024-01-15T12:20:26.166Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anatomy of transfer negotiations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116442</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/anatomy-of-transfer-negotiations/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T12:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting your top targets in is usually difficult to do in the middle of a transfer window, even more so in January.  The selling club is incentivised to make you wait until the last few days, while they work on attracting a competitive bid.  Whatever your opening bid is, it’s not enough.  Why would it [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOOPS DUO’S CUP TARGET]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116440</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hoops-duos-cup-target/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T09:47:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC attacking double-act Oh Hyeon-gyu and Yang Hyun-jun are hoping to get the nod to play in South Korea’s opening Asian Cup encounter against Bahrain in Qatar this morning. So far, Japan’s Reo Hatate and Daizen Maeda and Australia’s Marco Tilio have been left frustrated as they have been snubbed for their nations’ first game [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£3m KUHN’S QUICKFIRE DEBUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116433</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/3m-kuhns-quickfire-debut/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T09:02:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NICOLAS KUHN is poised for a quickfire Celtic debut against Buckie Thistle in the Scottish Cup at Parkhead on Sunday afternoon. The 24-year-old winger is poised to finalise his £3million move to the champions from Rapid Vienna tomorrow. Kuhn, who will be in London today to undergo a medical, is set to pen a deal [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC KID HEADS FOR LOAN No.4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116431</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-kid-heads-for-loan-no-4/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T07:48:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC defender Adam Montgomery is heading for his FOURTH loan deal in three years. The 21-year-old left-back was recalled early from an original season-long temporary switch at English third-tier Fleetwood Town at the weekend, as CQN reported. Montgomery has already had spells at Aberdeen and St Johnstone in his efforts to gain much-needed game-time. Brendan [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…YOUSSOUF MULUMBU?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109033</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-youssouf-mulumbu/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T05:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TENACIOUS midfielder Youssouf Mulumbu was signed by Brendan Rodgers on a free transfer from Kilmarnock in August 2018. The 31-year-old anchorman arrived to bolster the squad, but he was heading for the exit only five months later as he returned to the Ayrshire club on loan for the remainder of the season. Mulumbu, after making [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The big stumbling block in any Celtic move for Caoimhin Kelleher]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=186145</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/the-big-stumbling-block-in-any-celtic-move-for-caoimhin-kelleher/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T20:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reports have again surfaced that Celtic have Liverpool goalkeeper Caoimhin Kelleher in their sights as a long-term replacement for Joe Hart. It was reported back...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Invincible's surprising route to retirement before the age of 30]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=186111</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/jozo-simunovics-surprising-route-to-potential-retirement-before-the-age-of-30-following-celtic-exit/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jozo Simunovic had his fair share of injury issues during five years at Celtic, but not many would have predicted he’d be effectively retired as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The latest on Celtic's transfer interest in Romeo Amane]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=186140</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/the-latest-on-celtics-transfer-interest-in-romeo-amane/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have midfielder Romeo Amane on a transfer ‘shortlist’ but it doesn’t look like he’ll be making a switch to the Bhoys this month. Amane...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Right to the top': Celtic sent a clear Liel Abada message amid latest transfer news]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=186113</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-sent-a-clear-liel-abada-message-amid-the-latest-transfer-news/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic might be bringing in another winger this January in the form of Nicolas Kuhn, but the possible new capture from Rapid Wien will have...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Brown on Philippe Clement's reality check up against Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=186084</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/scott-brown-on-philippe-clements-reality-check-up-against-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The vast majority of the fallout from Celtic’s recent win over Rangers focused on a phantom penalty that was never going to be given. Nobody...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[With Nicolas Kuhn's transfer imminent, the chances of signing 21-year-old could also be increasing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=186086</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/with-nicolas-kuhns-transfer-imminent-the-chances-of-signing-21-year-old-could-also-be-increasing/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With talk around Nicolas Kuhn’s arrival from Rapid Wien, one other name that has popped up on Celtic’s transfer radar has been Leeds United’s, Joe...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nicolas Kuhn opponent in Austria shares lightning traits that could make him a big hit at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=186079</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/nicolas-kuhn-opponent-in-austria-shares-lightning-traits-that-could-make-him-a-big-hit-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T16:46:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Motherwell defender Max Johnston reckons incoming Celtic signing Nicolas Kuhn has the attributes to be a success in the Scottish Premiership. Kuhn is reported...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exciting talent arrives in the UK as Celtic make transfer breakthrough; fee, contract details]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=186075</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/nicolas-kuhn-arrives-in-the-uk-as-celtic-make-transfer-breakthrough-fee-contract-details/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T15:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will put Nicolas Kuhn through a medical in London on Monday before confirming his signing early in the week, according to the latest Sunday...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['On their way out': Mark Wilson thinks Nicolas Kuhn's arrival spells bad news for Celtic duo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=186053</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/mark-wilson-thinks-nicolas-kuhns-arrival-spells-bad-news-for-celtic-duo/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic seem to be closing in on the first piece of January transfer business with the expected arrival of Rapid Wien star, Nicolas Kuhn. If...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC RIVAL BAN FEAR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116424</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-rival-ban-fear/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T09:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BOSS Graeme Stewart could be BANNED from Buckie Thistle’s Scottish Cup-tie against Celtic at Parkhead a week today. The gaffer could miss the biggest game in the club’s history after seeing red in his side’s 3-2 Highland League win over Huntly yesterday. Stewart was banished by referee Harry Bruce after a 55th-minute flashpoint with opposition midfielder [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S £2m ACE SNUBBED]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116419</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtics-2m-ace-snubbed/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T08:38:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MARCO TILIO’S hopes of making a huge impression in the Asian Cup were dealt a blow when he was snubbed by Australia in their opening 2-0 Group B  win over India in Al Rayyan in Qatar. The Celtic winger, who has figured for only 28 minutes in Brendan Rodgers’ first team since his £2million arrival [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…EBOUE KOUASSI?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=108962</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-eboue-kouassi/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-14T05:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘IF I play more then you will see the lion. I will fight for the team, do anything for the team. I will go to war for the team and win for the team. I just want to play.’ The stirring words belonged to Ivory Coast international midfielder Eboue Kouassi shortly after he arrived at [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nicolas Kuhn gets 'project' verdict but he will have priority over at least 3 used players at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=186044</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/nicolas-kuhn-gets-project-verdict-from-sutton-but-he-will-have-priority-over-at-least-3-used-players-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T21:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker Chris Sutton reckons incoming signing Nicolas Kuhn looks like a project player, but he’s at least likely to be a regular performer...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Celtic do their January transfer business as fans wait for new faces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=186039</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/when-celtic-do-their-january-transfer-business-as-fans-wait-for-new-faces/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T20:46:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s been a fair amount of discussion out there about whether or not Celtic fans should be worried at the club’s lack of business in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Brown chooses game that utterly broke Rangers as his greatest ever at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=186032</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/scott-brown-chooses-game-that-utterly-broke-rangers-as-his-greatest-ever-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T20:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Brown enjoyed some incredible occasions in a Celtic shirt and is one of the club’s most decorated players as a result. That provides him...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Henrik Larsson opens up on Seville, 'indescribable' Celtic moment and destroying Rangers streak]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=186025</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/henrik-larsson-opens-up-on-seville-indescribable-celtic-moment-and-destroying-rangers-streak-in-new-interview/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T18:37:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For seven years at Celtic, Henrik Larsson was king. The king of kings, in fact. His incredible finishing style, penchant for goals on the big...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton names his 'absolute priorities' for Lawwell and Rodgers at Celtic this month]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=186020</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/chris-sutton-names-his-absolute-priorities-for-mark-lawwell-and-brendan-rodgers-at-celtic-this-month/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T17:42:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are 13 days into Celtic’s January transfer window and it’s fair to say it’s been a quiet month so far. There has been a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: KENNY DALGLISH AND THE PERILS OF A QUICK FIX]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116417</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-kenny-dalglish-and-the-perils-of-a-quick-fix/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T09:04:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MY LONG-SUFFERING missus would most assuredly endorse the fact I have not been blessed with a superabundance of tolerance. Alas, I am from the school of: “God give me patience…and give me it right NOW!” There are occasions, though, when I realise you have to take a deep breath and calm your jets. Brendan Rodgers [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC RECALL LOAN BHOY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116413</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-recall-loan-bhoy/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T07:23:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ADAM MONTGOMERY’S season-long loan deal to Fleetwood Town has been cut short. The 21-year-old left-back has returned to Celtic following an injury-stricken spell at the English third-tier club. Montgomery, who has also previous temporary spells at St Johnstone and Aberdeen, signed a 12-month contract in July last year to be reunited with Hoops legend Scott [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘DILEMMA FACING CELTIC,’ SUTTON’S BLUNT WARNING]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116411</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/dilemma-facing-celtic-suttons-blunt-warning/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T06:46:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic goal hero Chris Sutton has highlighted the dilemma facing Brendan Rodgers in this month’s transfer market. The one-time England international frontman was Martin O’Neill’s first signing for the club in the summer of 2000 when he arrived in a £6million switch from Chelsea. The incoming Hoops boss urgently required firepower with Mark Viduka already [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GOING, GOING, KWON: WHO’S NEXT?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116407</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/going-going-kwon-whos-next/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T05:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KWON HYEON-KYU has joined Yosuke Ideguchi through the Celtic exit. The midfielder has yet to kick a ball in competitive action for the champions since his £850,000 arrival from South Korea in the summer. Now Kwon, 22, who signed a five-year contract at the Hoops, has agreed a loan deal with St Mirren until the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…MARK VIDUKA?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=87598</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-mark-viduka/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-13T05:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EVEN the persuasive tongue of Martin O’Neill could not convince Mark Viduka to hang around Celtic and play a part in his revolution in the summer of 2000. The Irishman had just arrived to take charge of the Hoops a year after the introduction of the so-called ‘Dream Team’ of Kenny Dalglish and John Barnes [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend Scott Brown's next steps as a manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=186006</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-legend-scott-browns-next-steps-as-a-manager/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T19:59:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic icon Scott Brown is casting the net far and wide to find a new opportunity to test himself as a manager after leaving Fleetwood...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summer signing gets Scottish Premiership loan chance after slow Celtic start]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=186008</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/hyeokkyu-kwon-gets-scottish-premiership-loan-chance-after-slow-celtic-start/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T18:22:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder Hyeokkyu Kwon has joined St Mirren on loan until the end of the season, it was announced this evening. Kwon arrived at the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic appoint Everton coach to replace Fran Alonso]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=186001</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/celtic-appoint-everton-coach-elena-sadiku-to-replace-fran-alonso/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T17:11:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everton WSL Academy coach Elena Sadiku has won the race to succeed Fran Alonso as manager of Celtic FC Women, it was announced today. Alonso...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smiles, new introductions and beep tests as Celtic make Friday return to training]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185996</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/smiles-new-introductions-and-beep-tests-as-celtic-make-friday-return-to-training/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T16:46:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic players looked happy to get back to work despite a cold and grey Lennoxtown on Friday, as the squad started their preparations for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Italian newspaper raises Sydney van Hooijdonk Celtic hypothesis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185988</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/italian-newspaper-raises-sydney-van-hooijdonk-celtic-hypothesis/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T16:16:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been intermittently linked with a move for Sydney van Hooijdonk since the summer window and the prospect of a transfer switch to Glasgow...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liel Abada Celtic rumour mill put to rest with new report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185983</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/liel-abada-celtic-rumour-mill-put-to-rest-with-new-report/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T15:26:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite significant speculation and opinion that Liel Abada could make a Celtic exit this month, the club are said to be expecting him to contribute...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attacker has heart set on Celtic move despite German and Italian interest; Rodgers influence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185978</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/nicolas-kuhn-has-heart-set-on-celtic-move-despite-german-and-italian-interest-arrival-timeline/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T14:12:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will fend off interest from German and Italian clubs over the coming days to deliver Nicolas Kuhn as their latest transfer signing. The Bhoys...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seeking game time in Qatar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116402</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/seeking-game-time-in-qatar/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T12:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marco Tilio made a late substitute appearance in Australia’s final Asian Cup warm-up game against Bharain on Saturday.  The player is clearly valued higher in his home country than around Lennoxtown.  With little prospect of a promotion to the Celtic starting line-up ahead, any chance the player has to shine would be useful for him [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GREEN LIGHT FOR KUHN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116385</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/green-light-for-kuhn/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T09:23:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC are closing in on a £2.5million deal for Rapid Vienna winger Nicolas Kuhn. The German winger is poised to become the champions’ first signing of the 2024 window with the clubs now negotiating the final details of the contract, as reported in the Scottish Sun. Left-footed Kuhn, who has been playing on the right [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTS AT THE ASIAN CUP: WHEN TILIO AND CO ARE IN ACTION]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116382</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celts-at-the-asian-cup-when-tilio-and-co-are-in-action/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T08:56:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FIVE Celtic stars will be involved in the Asian Cup which kicks off this evening when hosts Qatar play Lebanon. Winger Marco Tilio will be the first Hoops star to go into action when Australia take on India tomorrow morning. Next up, midfielder Reo Hatate and forward Daizen Maeda could be involved when Japan face [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's next transfer priorities after Nicolas Kuhn is in the door with "lots of players" offered]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185972</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtics-next-transfer-priorities-after-nicolas-kuhn-is-in-the-door-with-lots-of-players-offered/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T08:12:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are closing in on a transfer move for winger Nicolas Kuhn but the Bhoys are expected to add more talent to Brendan Rodgers’ squad...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's first January transfer window signing now looks imminent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185966</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtics-first-january-transfer-window-signing-now-looks-imminent/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T07:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s quest to make an addition to Brendan Rodgers’ first-team squad is moving closer as the team prepares to regroup at Lennoxtown. It’s well known...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…JEREMY TOLJAN?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=108911</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-jeremy-toljan/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T05:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JEREMY TOLJAN was heralded as an “inspired” loan signing by Brendan Rodgers on the last day of the January 2019 transfer window. The Borussia Dortmund right-back agreed a short-term deal until the end of the season as the Celtic boss searched for an alternative for Mikael Lustig with teenage Anthony Ralston deemed too young after [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marvin Bartley baffled and 'shocked' by transfer claim about Celtic star Kyogo Furuhashi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185950</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/marvin-bartley-baffled-and-shocked-by-transfer-claim-about-celtic-star-kyogo-furuhashi/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Furuhashi is a cult hero at Celtic and a player you can trust when you go into the biggest of games. Even though the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Lambert says Celtic star going ‘under the radar’ & without him team would be in 'difficulty']]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185929</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/paul-lambert-tells-callum-mcgregor-what-he-needs-to-go-to-the-next-level-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor doesn’t just continue to be Mr. Consistent for Celtic, but a player who steps up when it matters most. Donning the Celtic armband...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thursday Celtic transfer bulletin: Kuhn, Lagerbielke & Araujo latest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185923</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-transfer-news-nicolas-kuhn-gustaf-lagerbielke-tiago-araujo/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T16:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your Thursday Celtic January transfer bulletin, as 67 Hail Hail provides the latest January transfer updates and rumours. Finally, what appears to be a tangible...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Brown names the three advantages Celtic have over Rangers in title race]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185917</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/scott-brown-has-named-the-three-advantages-celtic-have-over-rangers-in-title-race/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Brown has explained the three reasons why Celtic will have the upper hand over Rangers in this season’s Scottish Premiership title race. Celtic have...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How many trebles have Celtic won? (1967 to 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185903</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/feature/how-many-trebles-have-celtic-won/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How many trebles have Celtic won in their history? Here, 67 Hail Hail go through each and every one secured by the Hoops since their...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kuhn and the 60 game threshold]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116380</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kuhn-and-the-60-game-threshold/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T12:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are looking for a (football) gem, you need to do some (data) mining.  Jota was unearthed after a spell on the Valladolid bench.  For 18 months, Nicolas Kuhn (24) has ploughed a furrow on the Rapid Vienna right wing.  Just as Kuhn left Munich for Vienna, Rapid were deducted points for various financial [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's all-time biggest wins over Rangers ranked]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185892</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/feature/celtic-all-time-biggest-wins-over-rangers-in-history/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T11:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here, 67 Hail Hail rank Celtic’s biggest wins over Rangers in the history of the Old Firm and Glasgow derby. Celtic and Rangers are undoubtedly...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Brown gives unexpected answer regarding best thing Brendan Rodgers has ever done for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185888</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/scott-brown-on-the-best-thing-brendan-rodgers-has-ever-done-for-celtic-not-what-you-think/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T09:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Brown doesn’t think the countless number of trophies or the ‘Invincible Treble’ success is the best thing Brendan Rodgers has brought to Celtic. With...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marco Tilio has now issued a plea amid Celtic loan exit speculation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185881</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/marco-tilio-has-now-issued-a-plea-amid-celtic-loan-exit-speculation/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T09:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marco Tilio admits he is desperate for game time as the Celtic outcast looks for solutions this January transfer window. The Aussie winger was signed...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Kirkpatrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Top-tier side now looking for replacements after Celtic table bid for versatile star]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=185860</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/report-delivers-significant-transfer-update-in-celtics-push-for-rapid-vienna-star-nicolas-kuhn/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T07:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have started to make significant moves to sign the first player of the 2024 January transfer window. Rapid Vienna winger Nicolas Kuhn seems to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC LINE UP KUHN TALKS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116375</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-line-up-kuhn-talks/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T07:46:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS will step up his interest in Rapid Vienna winger Nicolas Kuhn. The left-sided touchline ace is on the Celtic manager’s January hit-list, as CQN reported earlier this month. Rodgers is keen to add the 24-year-old German to his squad and it is believed the champions have already had talks with the Austrian club about [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MARCO TILIO’S SURPRISE CELTIC ADMISSION]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116373</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/marco-tilios-surprise-celtic-admission/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T07:08:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MARCO TILIO has played a mere 28 minutes since his £2million June arrival at Celtic. However, the rarely-seen Australian winger insists he has IMPROVED since joining the champions from Melbourne City, despite his lack of game-time. Tilio, who is currently with the Socceroos international squad in Qatar for the Asian Cup, was put into cold [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CALAMITY RED ALERT: ACT IN HASTE, REPENT AT LEISURE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=116363</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/calamity-red-alert-act-in-haste-repent-at-leisure/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T06:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC fans are clamouring for new recruits in this January transfer window as the clock ticks down towards the end of the month. The Hoops have plundered this market in recent windows and come up trumps with the likes of Reo Hatate, Daizen Maeda and Matt O’Riley in 2022. Alistair Johnston, fresh from his impressive [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…MUBARAK WAKASO?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=69525</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-mubarak-wakaso/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-11T05:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC loan flop Mubarak Wakaso has played for TWELVE clubs in eight years following his return to Rubin Kazan after just one hardly-memorable campaign at Parkhead. The 70 times-capped Ghanian winger is now in China with Shenzehen FC after joining them from Jiangsu Suning in April 2021. Wakaso was one of Ronny Deila’s first signings for the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic want to sign £4 million-rated player in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45945</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-4-million-player-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T23:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The defeat at the hands of Lazio was further proof of Celtic’s need to strengthen in the January transfer window. The club might have brought in nine new faces in the summer but a lot of people feel that the team has taken a step back since last season, when they breezed past the competition […]
Celtic want to sign £4 million-rated player in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers sends clear message Celtic board must not ignore]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45941</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/brendan-rodgers-message-celtic-board/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T21:35:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s fate in Europe for this season is sealed after their 2-0 defeat at the hands of Lazio. The result means that the Hoops are guaranteed to finish bottom of their group in the UEFA Champions League. That also means that they will not be dropping down to the Europa League, something that should have […]
Brendan Rodgers sends clear message Celtic board must not ignore - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton publicly criticises Celtic after loss to Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45938</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/chris-sutton-celtic-loss-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T20:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic lost 2-0 away in Rome to Lazio. The Hoops were in the match for a long time before Ciro Immobile came off the bench to score a brace and put the game to bed. The result means that not only are Brendan Rodgers’ side out of the Champions League following the group stages but […]
Chris Sutton publicly criticises Celtic after loss to Lazio - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed £7 million Jeremie Frimpong windfall news]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45933</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-jeremie-frimpong-windfall-news/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremie Frimpong’s rise at Bayer Leverkusen has been fascinating, to say the least. The Dutchman had shown a lot of quality going forward at Celtic as well but not many could have foreseen him becoming one of the most prolific wingbacks in Europe just a few years later. That is exactly what has happened under […]
Celtic handed £7 million Jeremie Frimpong windfall news - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic told 29-goal striker is good enough amid links]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45930</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-told-29-goal-striker-good-enough/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T13:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to add to their options up top this January. Kyogo has done well once again but he is not scoring as frequently as he was last season. On the other hand, Oh Hyeon-gyu has been inconsistent as well and is not at the level required to start for the Hoops right now. There […]
Celtic told 29-goal striker is good enough amid links - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anderlecht consider making offer for Celtic standout in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45927</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/anderlecht-offer-celtic-standout-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T11:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have not had the greatest campaign till now. They were eliminated early from the Scottish League Cup and while they do lead the Premiership, their performances and results have been somewhat inconsistent. Almost half a season on, it feels like the Hoops are still finding their feet under the management of Brendan Rodgers and […]
Anderlecht consider making offer for Celtic standout in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serie A club want to sign Celtic player amid contract worry]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45907</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/serie-club-want-celtic-player-contract/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T22:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic fans hope for more quality players arriving there could be a problem with others heading for the exit door. It seems pretty clear that Brendan Rodgers wants to make the size of the squad more manageable over the next couple of transfer windows and departures are expected. But there is a risk of […]
Serie A club want to sign Celtic player amid contract worry - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur step up bid to sign Celtic-linked player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45918</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/tottenham-hotspur-bid-sign-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur made a fantastic start to the season under the management of Ange Postecoglou. With Harry Kane leaving the club in the summer for Bayern Munich, most expected them to struggle. Instead, they appeared to be putting up an unlikely title challenge and were sitting atop the Premier League table not too long ago. […]
Tottenham Hotspur step up bid to sign Celtic-linked player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boost in race to sign £11 million Real Madrid player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45914</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/celtic-boost-real-madrid-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to sign a goalkeeper in the near future. It is quite clear that Joe Hart is not the long-term solution between the posts. The Englishman’s performances have been criticised lately. Also, he is set to turn 37 years of age before this season comes to an end. So, while he has done a […]
Celtic boost in race to sign £11 million Real Madrid player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio boss Maurizio Sarri makes fantastic Celtic claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45910</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/lazio-boss-maurizio-sarri-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T18:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By now, Celtic fans have accepted that Brendan Rodgers’ side are most probably not going through or even finishing third in their group in the UEFA Champions League. It would be a positive step to get a win in the competition though. It has been quite some time since the Hoops won at this level. […]
Lazio boss Maurizio Sarri makes fantastic Celtic claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic tipped to go for 28-year-old Premiership striker]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45904</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/celtic-tipped-go-premiership-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T12:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans breathed a sigh of relief as the Rangers dropped points at the weekend against Aberdeen. In fact, it took a late penalty for them to even come out with a draw from the game. That means that the Hoops will maintain their strong position at the top of the Scottish Premiership table. That […]
Celtic tipped to go for 28-year-old Premiership striker - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£7.5 million Mathias Kvistgaarden to Celtic transfer update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45900</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/mathias-kvistgaarden-celtic-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T10:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to sign a striker in January. On one hand, we have seen the club struggle for goals in some games this season. When the opposition puts up a resolute defence, the Hoops do not appear to have a lot of answers other than Kyogo, Matt O’Riley or Luis Palma. On the other hand, […]
£7.5 million Mathias Kvistgaarden to Celtic transfer update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur have been eyeing Celtic superstar]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45896</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/tottenham-hotspur-eyeing-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T23:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou made the move to Tottenham Hotspur in the summer and it was only a matter of time before the Australian was linked with a reunion with some Celtic players. The manager enjoyed a lot of success at Parkhead, even though he was at the club for just two seasons, and won five trophies […]
Tottenham Hotspur have been eyeing Celtic superstar - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John McGinn claims he spoke to Celtic players about manager]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45890</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/john-mcginn-spoke-celtic-players/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T21:35:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most Celtic fans will remember how the club missed out on the opportunity to sign John McGinn some years back. The Scot grew up supporting the Hoops but a move to Parkhead failed to materialise even though it had looked close and he ended up moving down south to join Aston Villa. McGinn has risen […]
John McGinn claims he spoke to Celtic players about manager - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic must consider signing striker from Premiership rivals]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45886</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-signing-striker-premiership-rivals/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T20:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there is one position where Celtic need to strengthen during the upcoming January transfer window, it is striker. The Hoops have been pretty inconsistent in front of goal this season so far. Of course, there are games when they can go out and score six times. But then, on days they are having a […]
Celtic must consider signing striker from Premiership rivals - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend takes dig at Rangers player for diving]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45884</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-legend-rangers-player-diving/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T18:35:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Celtic drew 1-1 against Motherwell, the Rangers were handed a major chance to get back into the title race. All they needed to do was win their games in hand and they would be just three points behind the Hoops in the league table. We have seen the Ibrox side not perform at their […]
Celtic legend takes dig at Rangers player for diving - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player criticised after draw against Motherwell]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45881</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-player-criticised-draw-motherwell/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T12:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Titles are not decided this early in the season. That has been proven once again. Not too long ago, Celtic were sitting seven points clear at the top of the Premiership table and most fans felt that the league was pretty much in the bag with the Rangers struggling for any kind of form.  It […]
Celtic player criticised after draw against Motherwell - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgio Chiellini makes superb claim about Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45874</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/giorgio-chiellini-claim-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T10:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Giorgio Chiellini is one of the best defenders of all time and he had some pretty positive comments about Celtic Park recently. The 39-year-old spent the majority of his career playing for Juventus and won more silverware there than one should try to count. Overall, he made more […]
Giorgio Chiellini makes superb claim about Celtic Park - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s problem is very clear and needs solving quick]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45870</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/celtic-problem-needs-solving-quick/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T19:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two more dropped points mean that Celtic have well and truly allowed the Rangers to get back into the title race. A lead which once stood at seven points, could be reduced to three if Philippe Clement’s side are able to win their games in hand. And the sad thing is that the Hoops have […]
Celtic’s problem is very clear and needs solving quick - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic problem after draw]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45866</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/brendan-rodgers-celtic-problem-draw/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T18:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was not the result Celtic were looking for, as they dropped two valuable points against Motherwell. David Turnbull’s goal appeared to have won it for the Hoops but the visitors equalised in the 90th minute and it ended 1-1. That means that if the Rangers win their games in hand, the gap will be […]
Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic problem after draw - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hollywood superstar pictured wearing Celtic jersey]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45861</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/hollywood-pictured-wearing-celtic-jersey/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T12:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Celtic have their fair share of famous fans. Rod Stewart is the first name that comes to most people’s minds, one of the best-selling music artists in history. Lewis Capaldi is another popular musician known to support the Hoops. And several A-list celebrities like Gerard Butler, Snoop Dogg, […]
Hollywood superstar pictured wearing Celtic jersey - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic pushing for priority signing in January window]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45859</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/celtic-priority-signing-january-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T09:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s January transfer window is expected to be a busy one. The club might have made nine signings in the summer, seven arriving on a permanent basis and two on loan, but there are still holes in Brendan Rodgers’ squad that need to be filled. On the other hand, there are way too many players […]
Celtic pushing for priority signing in January window - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable source offers Sydney van Hooijdonk to Celtic update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45854</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/reliable-sydney-van-hooijdonk-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T22:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are believed to be on the lookout for a striker in the January transfer window. There might be a few reasons behind that. Firstly, both Kyogo and Oh Hyeon-gyu might be unavailable for a considerable length of time early next year due to the AFC Asian Cup. They are the club’s two options to […]
Reliable source offers Sydney van Hooijdonk to Celtic update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou claims Celtic success gets dismissed]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45852</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/ange-postecoglou-claims-celtic-success/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T21:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has proven to be a major success in the Premier League since swapping Celtic for Tottenham Hotspur. Of course, a lot of fans were not happy to see him depart after just two years at Parkhead. But he has been very respectful about the club even after leaving. And it is hard not […]
Ange Postecoglou claims Celtic success gets dismissed - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>