<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-10-21T16:11:33.434Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic now have a chance to send out a big statement to Rangers and the rest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178504</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-now-have-a-chance-to-send-out-a-big-statement-to-rangers-and-the-rest/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T16:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There was a limited Scottish Premiership card on Saturday due to complications resulting from Storm Babet, but Celtic’s league lead was reduced to four points...
The post Celtic now have a chance to send out a big statement to Rangers and the rest appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic open unexpected contract talks with another player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45042</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/21/celtic-contract-talks-another-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T13:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic find themselves in a very interesting position right now. The club have a young core but there are some areas of the pitch which is in clear need of reinforcements. It remains to be seen if the required additions are made in upcoming transfer windows. News of contract talks being opened with a veteran […]
Celtic open unexpected contract talks with another player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A bright future ahead as Celtic enter a period to be savoured]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178495</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/a-bright-future-ahead-as-celtic-enter-a-period-to-be-savoured/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Things are ticking along nicely for Brendan Rodgers and Celtic, even if we are still waiting on that major euphoric moment. It’s been a bizarre...
The post A bright future ahead as Celtic enter a period to be savoured appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unsung Hoops hero comes in for credit from both Hearts and Celtic sides]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178478</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/unsung-hoops-hero-comes-in-for-credit-from-both-hearts-and-celtic-sides/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When reading some of the press conference quotes ahead of Hearts vs Celtic this weekend, it was interesting to come across an unsung Hoops hero...
The post Unsung Hoops hero comes in for credit from both Hearts and Celtic sides appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss keen to make rotation point after praising defensive surprise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178463</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-keen-to-make-rotation-point-after-more-liam-scales-praise/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers was keen to point out that he would be making use of his Celtic squad over the next three weeks, after praising Liam...
The post Celtic boss keen to make rotation point after praising defensive surprise appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summer Hearts signing shares what he knows about Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178471</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/summer-hearts-signing-shares-what-he-knows-about-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hearts defender Frankie Kent has shared what he knows about Celtic ahead of this weekend’s clash. It’s a tasty visit to Tynecastle for the Hoops...
The post Summer Hearts signing shares what he knows about Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STORM BABET UPDATE: THREE PREMIERSHIP GAMES OFF]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113269</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-championship-game-between-arbroath-and-raith-rovers-in-the-worst-hit-area-of-angus-has-been-called-off-cove-rangers-against-montrose-has-been-postponed-along-with-two-games-in-league-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T08:15:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THREE Premiership games have been scrapped as Storm Babet continues to create chaos and havoc in Scotland. Ross County v St Mirren in Dingwall was called off this morning to join the matches at Pittodrie, with Aberdeen due to face Dundee, and Perth, with St Johnstone scheduled to host Motherwell, which were postponed yesterday. Also [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers is seeing improvement in Celtic as he references "a wee bit of drama"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178443</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-is-seeing-improvement-in-celtic-as-he-references-a-wee-bit-of-drama/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers is seeing improvement in his Celtic side and thinks there is more to come as we move forward. The Hoops seemed to really...
The post Brendan Rodgers is seeing improvement in Celtic as he references "a wee bit of drama" appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TWO CELTS ON TRIAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113268</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/two-celts-on-trial/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T07:59:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MIKEY JOHNSTON and Yuki Kobayashi will have to convince Brendan Rodgers they are good enough for first-team places at Celtic. Neither the Republic of Ireland international winger nor the Japanese centre-back have figured in the champions’ top side this season. Johnston returned to Parkhead in the summer after a season-long loan at Portuguese top-flight club Vitoria [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star's "random" international call-up; less glamorous family image]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178485</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-star-matt-orileys-random-denmark-call-up-less-glamorous-family-image/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star Matt O’Riley got his first proper call-up for the Denmark senior side during the international break. The in-form Hoops midfielder was called up...
The post Celtic star's "random" international call-up; less glamorous family image appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘BEST I’VE FELT,’ INSISTS O’RILEY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113266</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/best-ive-felt-insists-oriley/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T07:32:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY reckons he is improving with every game after his eye-catching performances from day one of the campaign. The stylish midfielder put in a polished display against stubborn Ross County in the Premiership opener on August 5 when he scored a thumping goal and set up another for David Turnbull with some mesmerising skills on [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O'Riley explains how his role at Celtic has changed under Brendan Rodgers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178434</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/matt-oriley-explains-how-his-role-at-celtic-has-changed-under-brendan-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star Matt O’Riley has explained how his role has changed under Brendan Rodgers. The Danish midfielder has been one of our best performers so...
The post Matt O'Riley explains how his role at Celtic has changed under Brendan Rodgers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘CRUNCH TIME’: SUTTON SPELLS OUT RODGERS’ TREBLE TEST]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113263</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/crunch-time-sutton-spells-out-rodgers-treble-test/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T06:38:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC cannot afford a slip when they face a double crunch in the capital with the game against Hearts at Tynecastle tomorrow and Hibs at Easter Road a week today. The champions are now seven points ahead after eight games as they remain focused on winning their twelfth title in 13 years and they are determined [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers talks honestly about legacies and his relationship with the Celtic support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178453</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-talks-honestly-about-legacies-and-his-relationship-with-the-celtic-support/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has opened up on his return to Celtic and his relationship with the Hoops support. It’s fair to say the Celtic manager is...
The post Brendan Rodgers talks honestly about legacies and his relationship with the Celtic support appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: HEARD THE ONE ABOUT THE DUTCHMAN, THE ENGLISHMAN AND THE BELGIAN?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113250</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-heard-the-one-about-the-dutchman-the-englishman-and-the-belgian/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T04:45:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I AM working off memory here, but I seem to recall honeymoon periods tend to last just a shade longer than 48 hours. And, yet, that is the unpleasant prospect facing Philippe Clement as he begins his new job this weekend. As you would expect, the Belgian has been talking the talk since his appointment [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WAR GAMES: PART FOUR: ‘WE WERE SICKENED, BATTERED, BRUISED AND BEATEN’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=84117</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/war-games-part-four-we-were-sickened-battered-bruised-and-beaten/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-21T04:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FIFTY-SIX YEARS ago, Celtic were involved in three of the most infamous games in the club’s proud history. Billy McNeill scored the only goal of a thuggish encounter on October 18 1967 at Hampden in the Parkhead club’s quest to conquer the world and win the first leg of the Intercontinental Cup Final against Argentina’s [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou explains Pep Guardiola Celtic rumour]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45033</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/20/ange-postecoglou-pep-guardiola-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T22:05:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou is not an overnight success by any means even though it might feel so to many football fans. The Australian had been managing for decades before he had gotten his well-earned worldwide recognition. Of course, the beginning of his meteoric rise was at Celtic, who appointed him in the summer of 2021. At […]
Ange Postecoglou explains Pep Guardiola Celtic rumour - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bonus for Celtic as Brendan Rodgers clears up injury mystery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178430</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-clears-up-daizen-maeda-celtic-concern/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T20:46:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda is fit and available for this weekend’s Celtic match away to Hearts despite dropping out of international duty with Japan due to injury....
The post Bonus for Celtic as Brendan Rodgers clears up injury mystery appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic linked with bringing back former player from Premier League]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45029</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/20/celtic-bringing-back-former-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T20:34:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been pretty active in the transfer market in recent times even though all of their signings have not been able to impress. Out of the nine additions that the Hoops made in the summer, Luis Palma is the one who has shown the most promise till now. It is still very early days […]
Celtic linked with bringing back former player from Premier League - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: EPL star's camp indicates Celtic interest with contract up for renewal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178426</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ryan-christies-camp-indicates-celtic-interest-to-outlet-contract-up-for-renewal/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T20:08:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People close to Ryan Christie have indicated there is interest from Celtic and Brendan Rodgers in making a move to re-sign the Scotland international, TEAMtalk...
The post Report: EPL star's camp indicates Celtic interest with contract up for renewal appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou asked about Pep Guardiola rumour, Dermot Desmond & Celtic fans in new interview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178421</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-asked-about-pep-guardiola-rumour-dermot-desmond-and-celtic-fans-in-new-interview/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T19:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has given a wide-ranging interview to FourFourTwo for their latest edition of the magazine and naturally Celtic was a big topic. Postecoglou enjoyed...
The post Ange Postecoglou asked about Pep Guardiola rumour, Dermot Desmond & Celtic fans in new interview appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers finally clears up Celtic injury mystery]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45025</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/20/brendan-rodgers-finally-celtic-injury/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T19:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have had their fair share of injury problems already this season. The Scottish champions stumbled out of the gates as a result, in Brendan Rodgers’ second stint as manager of the club, with fitness issues, the change in the managerial hot seat and the arrival of several new players over the summer creating a […]
Brendan Rodgers finally clears up Celtic injury mystery - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["That's the reality of it"; Brendan Rodgers delivers honest verdict on unused player at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178418</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/thats-the-reality-of-it-brendan-rodgers-on-yuki-kobayashis-lack-of-celtic-game-time/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T17:34:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers says Yuki Kobayashi isn’t putting a foot wrong at Celtic, there are simply other players ahead of him when selecting match squads on...
The post "That's the reality of it"; Brendan Rodgers delivers honest verdict on unused player at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager opens door to unlikely first-team return]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45022</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/20/celtic-opens-door-first-team-return/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T17:30:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have undergone quite a bit of change in recent times. The biggest one was of course the departure of Ange Postecoglou and the return of Brendan Rodgers as his replacement. With the arrival of the Northern Irishman, the team’s playing style has changed a bit and so has the status of some players. The […]
Celtic manager opens door to unlikely first-team return - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers says one summer signing has found it "really, really hard" so far at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178413</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-provides-an-update-on-marco-tilios-hard-situation-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T16:52:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has provided Celtic supporters with an update on summer signing Marco Tilio, who is yet to make his debut for the Bhoys. Tilio...
The post Brendan Rodgers says one summer signing has found it "really, really hard" so far at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[St. Margaret’s CSC celebrate in style with MON, Tommo & Fallon]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58438</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/st-margarets-csc-celebrate-in-style-with-mon-tommo-fallon/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T15:03:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The dust has now settled on St. Margaret’s Celtic Supporters 25 Anniversary Gala Charity Dinner Dance and what a night it was as 390 members and friends celebrated 25 years on the road following Celtic. The club was set up for 3 reasons. 1. To travel to Glasgow and beyond to see the famous Celtic […]
The post St. Margaret’s CSC celebrate in style with MON, Tommo & Fallon appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NO EXCUSES: RODGERS’ RALLYING CALL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113247</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/no-excuses-rodgers-rallying-call/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T14:47:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS insists Celtic will not be looking for excuses when they face Hearts at Tynecastle on Sunday. The champions will go into enemy territory with the meagre total of 571 fans to back them in their quest for three more points as the Irishman bids to win his third title at the Parkhead club. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The date and referee quirk that could leave Celtic fans with deja vu this weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178353</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/the-date-and-referee-quirk-that-could-leave-celtic-fans-with-deja-vu-this-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic return to action after a long international break this Sunday against Hearts. The Tynecastle clash takes place on October 22. Amusingly, that’s exactly one...
The post The date and referee quirk that could leave Celtic fans with deja vu this weekend appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWARD-WINNING CELT: MATT’S THE WAY TO DO IT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113245</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/award-winning-celt-matts-the-way-to-do-it/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T12:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY completed a Celtic double when he was named the Premiership Player of the Month for September. The classy midfielder was a certainty for the prize following his excellent start to the new season under the guidance of second time-around Hoops boss Brendan Rodgers who also lifted the manager award, as CQN reported earlier [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic should be worried by manager’s recent comments]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45015</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/20/celtic-worried-manager-recent-comments/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T12:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have signed plenty of players in recent times. Some moves have worked out for the club, others have not. But overall, they have remained successful on the pitch. So, there is very little incentive for the Hoops to steer away from their transfer strategy unless they are planning to make a serious impact in […]
Celtic should be worried by manager’s recent comments - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The changing perception of Hyeongyu Oh at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178387</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-changing-perception-of-hyeongyu-oh-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Hyeongyu Oh netted Celtic’s final two goals of the 2022/23 Premiership season, he was on a real high. It had been a pretty good...
The post The changing perception of Hyeongyu Oh at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic heading for rare TV blackout; not even pay-per-view can save the day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178404</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-fans-heading-for-rare-tv-blackout-not-even-pay-per-view-can-save-the-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic return to action this weekend when they take on Hearts in a tasty-looking clash. The Tynecastle clash is a 2:15pm kick-off and will be...
The post Celtic heading for rare TV blackout; not even pay-per-view can save the day appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hearts biggest hurdle is the Celtic jersey]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113228</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hearts-biggest-hurdle-is-the-celtic-jersey/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T11:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[69 games undefeated in domestic football, setting a new Scottish record, but eventually, Things Fall Apart and Celtic lost 4-0 at Tynecastle.  It was Brendan Rodgers’ first defeat to a Scottish club, 18 months after taking over as manager.  Celtic were not even bad that day; when Hearts went three ahead shortly after halftime, the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disappointing scenes as Mark Wilson gets it all wrong about Celtic and Rangers allocation drama]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178369</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/disappointing-scenes-as-mark-wilson-gets-it-all-wrong-about-celtic-and-rangers-allocation-drama/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Given what we know about the Celtic and Rangers derby allocation furore, it was disappointing to see Mark Wilson get it all wrong this week....
The post Disappointing scenes as Mark Wilson gets it all wrong about Celtic and Rangers allocation drama appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘DELIGHTED,’ PRIZE GUY BRENDAN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113226</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/delighted-prize-guy-brendan/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T07:54:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS won seven successive domestic honours in his four-and-a-half year first stint as Celtic manager. It has taken the returning Hoops gaffer just two months to pick up his first award this time around. Rodgers has just been named Premiership Manager of the Month for September after guiding the champions to four back-to-back league [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers' classy move after being named Premiership Manager of the Month]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178390</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-classy-move-after-being-named-premiership-manager-of-the-month/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T07:21:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers has been named Premiership Manager of the Month for September. It was a terrific month for the Hoops as we won...
The post Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers' classy move after being named Premiership Manager of the Month appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IBROX BOSS THANKS ‘CELTIC BABYSITTER’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113222</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ibrox-boss-thanks-celtic-babysitter/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T07:08:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PHILIPPE CLEMENT has thanked Gordon Strachan for volunteering his babysitting services during their time together at Coventry City. The new Ibrox gaffer, who has taken over from axed Michael Beale who didn’t last a year in the job, has recalled his days in the Midlands and his debt to the former Celtic manager and his wife [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steven Naismith actually makes a good point about Hearts vs Celtic ticket outcry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178344</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/steven-naismith-actually-makes-a-good-point-amid-hearts-vs-celtic-ticket-outcry/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steven Naismith has offered his thoughts on the Hearts vs Celtic ticket situation. The Jambos boss will lead his side into battle this weekend at...
The post Steven Naismith actually makes a good point about Hearts vs Celtic ticket outcry appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Bang-average"; former Celtic hero Chris Sutton just obliterated Ibrox star]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178378</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/bang-average-former-celtic-hero-chris-sutton-just-obliterated-ibrox-star/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic hero Chris Sutton has had the latest say in his spat with Todd Cantwell. The Rangers man has been embroiled in the off-field...
The post "Bang-average"; former Celtic hero Chris Sutton just obliterated Ibrox star appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["They were calling him Maldini"; the Liam Scales hype continues after brilliant Celtic rise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178360</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/they-were-calling-him-maldini-the-liam-scales-hype-continues-after-brilliant-celtic-rise/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Footballer Daire O’Connor — a close friend of Liam Scales — has been speaking about the Celtic defender’s remarkable rise. The Irish centre-back was totally...
The post "They were calling him Maldini"; the Liam Scales hype continues after brilliant Celtic rise appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WAR GAMES: PART THREE: THE SECOND BATTLE OF THE RIVER PLATE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=84050</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/war-games-part-three-the-second-battle-of-the-river-plate/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T04:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FIFTY-SIX YEARS ago Celtic were involved in three of the most infamous games in the club’s proud history. The first encounter at Hampden on October 18 1967 had seen a header from Billy McNeill give Jock Stein’s men a 1-0 win over Racing Club of Buenos Aires in the Parkhead side’s historic quest to conquer [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I just can’t see it’: Andy Walker delivers Celtic reality check to new Rangers boss]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178318</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-just-cant-see-it-andy-walker-delivers-celtic-reality-check-to-new-rangers-boss/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T20:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andy Walker has made it clear that he just simply ‘can’t see’ new Rangers boss Philippe Clement overtaking Brendan Rodgers’ Celtic. The Bhoys hold a...
The post ‘I just can’t see it’: Andy Walker delivers Celtic reality check to new Rangers boss appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘He has got a lot of criticism’: Peter Grant reacts to claim Celtic player could be replaced]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178298</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/he-has-got-a-lot-of-criticism-peter-grant-reacts-to-rumours-involving-celtics-joe-hart/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T20:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant has defended Joe Hart amid rumours that Brendan Rodgers’ Celtic could be bringing in a new goalkeeper.  Joe Hart’s contract at Celtic expires...
The post ‘He has got a lot of criticism’: Peter Grant reacts to claim Celtic player could be replaced appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real Madrid hand Andriy Lunin transfer problem to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45008</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/19/real-madrid-lunin-problem-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T19:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with quite a few players in recent times although we are still months away from the opening of the January transfer window. The club have done their business early in recent years though and could we see them continue on that same path even though Ange Postecoglou is no longer the […]
Real Madrid hand Andriy Lunin transfer problem to Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic injuries latest as Brendan Rodgers plans for Hearts and Atletico Madrid]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178229</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-injury-latest-as-brendan-rodgers-faces-selection-dilemma/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The international break is over and Celtic have some big games coming up, including a Champions League tie against Atletico Madrid. Here are the latest...
The post Celtic injuries latest as Brendan Rodgers plans for Hearts and Atletico Madrid appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Weaser-Seychell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I spoke to him': Celtic legend says 45-year-old would have been 'success' had he become manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178267</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/no-doubt-celtic-pundits-say-45-year-old-would-have-a-success-had-he-become-manager/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant and Andy Walker are certain that now-Newcastle United boss Eddie Howe would have been a ‘success’ at Celtic. Before Celtic could appoint Ange...
The post 'I spoke to him': Celtic legend says 45-year-old would have been 'success' had he become manager appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero gives superb reply to Todd Cantwell’s dig]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45006</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/19/celtic-hero-gives-reply-todd-cantwell/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T18:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton and Todd Cantwell have had their fair share of exchanges since the midfielder’s arrival at Ibrox earlier this year. Of course, the former Celtic striker is renowned for his wit and sharp takes, which have made him a popular pundit after retiring from the game. And it is safe to say that the […]
Celtic hero gives superb reply to Todd Cantwell’s dig - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['It is good news': Club legend delighted with what he is hearing from Celtic training now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178240</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/it-is-good-news-john-hartson-reacts-to-what-hes-hearing-from-celtic-training/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Hartson is delighted to hear that summer signing Maik Nawrocki is back in training with Brendan Rodgers’ Celtic after his injury. It wasn’t so...
The post 'It is good news': Club legend delighted with what he is hearing from Celtic training now appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's own 'Super Sunday' live on Sky Sports this weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178166</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-own-super-sunday-live-on-sky-sports-this-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic support will be treated to their own ‘Super Sunday’ on Sky Sports this weekend. The broadcaster’s flagship football offering graces many living rooms...
The post Celtic's own 'Super Sunday' live on Sky Sports this weekend appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic decision confirmed amid Green Brigade controversy]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44999</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/19/celtic-decision-confirmed-green-brigade/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T13:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Green Brigade are no stranger to controversy and there has been quite a bit of it in recent weeks, especially considering the global situation at this point in time. Of course, the Celtic fan group have never hesitated to let their opinions be known in public, even though they might not always represent the views […]
Celtic decision confirmed amid Green Brigade controversy - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carl Starfelt may have a part to play in Celtic preparation for upcoming clash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178174</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/carl-starfelt-may-have-a-part-to-play-in-celtic-preparation-for-upcoming-clash/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re less than a week away from arguably the most appetising fixture of Celtic’s UEFA Champions League group stage campaign: Atletico Madrid at home. Okay,...
The post Carl Starfelt may have a part to play in Celtic preparation for upcoming clash appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic must follow after Aston Villa’s announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44995</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/19/celtic-follow-aston-villa-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T11:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s transfer strategy shifted significantly following the arrival of Ange Postecoglou as the manager of the club in the summer of 2021. They started to spread their scouting net further and wider. and found a lot of success as a result. One of the biggest reasons they were able to recover from the 20/21 campaign […]
Celtic must follow after Aston Villa’s announcement - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Brendan Rodgers told Liam Scales before big Celtic breakthrough]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178129</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-brendan-rodgers-told-liam-scales-before-big-celtic-breakthrough/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has been speaking about Liam Scales as the Celtic defender’s brilliant rise continues. Scales is now a Republic of Ireland international, having started...
The post What Brendan Rodgers told Liam Scales before big Celtic breakthrough appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recency matters in partnerships]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113220</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/recency-matters-in-partnerships/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T11:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirmed yesterday that Maik Nawrocki has recovered from his hamstring injury, sustained in the League Cup defeat at Kilmarnock two months ago.  Since then, Celtic have been through a crisis in central defence.  Cameron Carter-Vickers and Stephen Welsh were already absent, Nat Phillips came in on loan, then immediately picked up an injury, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has an interesting theory on early-season Celtic struggles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178159</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-has-an-interesting-theory-on-early-season-celtic-struggles/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are in the midst of a good domestic run under Brendan Rodgers. It’s five Premiership wins in a row for the team, going back...
The post Brendan Rodgers has an interesting theory on early-season Celtic struggles appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE RETURN OF REO: ‘I DON’T INTEND TO BE SATISFIED’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113218</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-return-of-reo-i-dont-intend-to-be-satisfied/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T09:25:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE has come roaring back to blistering form following a lacklustre start to the season. The Celtic playmaker was puzzlingly off the pace in the first two months after the second coming of Brendan Rodgers. David Turnbull got the not from the Irishman to start the Premiership opener and scored a double in the 4-2 [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin Bridges meets Hoops hero and there may be more Celtic loving to come on world tour]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178153</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kevin-bridges-meets-hoops-hero-and-there-may-be-more-celtic-loving-to-come-on-world-tour/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin Bridges bumped into Celtic hero Mikael Lustig on Wednesday night. The Hoops-mad comedian has just finished the Scandinavian leg of his world tour. ‘The...
The post Kevin Bridges meets Hoops hero and there may be more Celtic loving to come on world tour appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘We heard the same’: Celtic legend John Hartson shuts down what he's hearing out of Rangers now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178198</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-legend-john-hartson-delivers-reality-check-to-rangers-ceo-james-bisgrove/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend John Hartson has told Rangers CEO James Bisgrove ‘we have heard the same’ from the Ibrox club before following their appointment of Philippe...
The post ‘We heard the same’: Celtic legend John Hartson shuts down what he's hearing out of Rangers now appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NO FEARS FOR JAPANESE TRIO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113215</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/no-fears-for-japanese-trio/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T07:59:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC will dispel fears they could be without star trio Kyogo Furuhashi, Reo Hatate and Daizen Maeda for the second Glasgow derby on December 30. Reports indicate Japan will call up all three players as they prepare for the Asian Cup with a friendly on January 1 2024, just two days after Philippe Clement’s Ibrox [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['What a find': Barry Ferguson can't hide Celtic envy as he is blown away by two players]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178181</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-a-find-barry-ferguson-cant-hide-celtic-envy-as-he-is-blown-away-by-two-players/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Barry Ferguson admitted that he has been ‘hugely impressed’ by Celtic duo Kyogo Furuhashi and Reo Hatate. Signed by Ange Postecoglou, the duo came to...
The post 'What a find': Barry Ferguson can't hide Celtic envy as he is blown away by two players appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers can't resist a comment on dire Celtic ticket situation for upcoming clash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178120</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-cant-resist-making-a-comment-on-dire-celtic-allocation-for-tynecastle/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers was keen to bring up the measly Celtic allocation at Tynecastle this weekend as he looked ahead to the match. In an interview...
The post Brendan Rodgers can't resist a comment on dire Celtic ticket situation for upcoming clash appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The positive Celtic injury news that may have gone unnoticed on Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178136</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-positive-celtic-injury-news-that-may-have-gone-unnoticed-on-wednesday/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There was a welcome injury update delivered by Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers on Wednesday. Rodgers spoke to Celtic TV in a lengthy interview ahead of...
The post The positive Celtic injury news that may have gone unnoticed on Wednesday appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The weekend experience that took Brendan Rodgers back to his early days following Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178143</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-weekend-experience-that-took-brendan-rodgers-back-to-his-early-days-following-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers says he was taken back to his early days following the club last weekend. On Sunday, Rodgers made a surprise appearance...
The post The weekend experience that took Brendan Rodgers back to his early days following Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘OH HAMPDEN IN THE SUN: CELTIC 7 RANGERS 1’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=55438</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/oh-hampden-in-the-sun-celtic-7-rangers-1/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T04:45:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC were the holders when they took on Rangers in the League Cup Final at Hampden on October 19 1957. The Hoops, managed by the club’s goalscoring legend Jimmy McGrory, had beaten Partick Thistle 3-0 after a goalless draw the previous year. A crowd of 31,000 watched a double from John McPhail and another from [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WAR GAMES: PART TWO: THE BRAWL IN BUENOS AIRES: ‘THE RIOT POLICE WERE OUT IN FORCE’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=84018</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/war-games-part-two-the-brawl-in-buenos-aires-the-riot-police-were-out-in-force/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T04:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FIFTY-SIX YEARS ago, Celtic were involved in three of the most infamous games in the club’s proud history. Yesterday was the anniversary of the first vicious encounter in the Parkhead club’s quest to conquer the world and win the first leg of the Intercontinental Cup Final against Argentina’s Racing Club of Buenos Aires. The confrontation [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have announced three-year contract for midfielder]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44992</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/18/celtic-announced-three-year-contract/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T22:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been very active in recent months when it comes to agreeing contracts with players. The likes of Matt O’Riley, Reo Hatate, Kyogo, Daizen Maeda, Callum McGregor and a few others have put pen to paper on new deals. And the Hoops are not focusing on just the senior team either. One complaint that […]
Celtic have announced three-year contract for midfielder - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic offered bad news about £12 million goalkeeper]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44989</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/18/celtic-offered-12-million-goalkeeper/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T21:04:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with quite a few high-profile names in recent times although the club have not ended up signing any of them since the arrival of Brendan Rodgers as manager in the summer. The latest such name rumoured to be on the Hoops’ radar is none other than Real Madrid goalkeeper, Andriy Lunin. […]
Celtic offered bad news about £12 million goalkeeper - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic problem as five players could be out for a month]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44986</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/18/celtic-problem-five-players-month/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T19:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic currently find themselves in a pretty good spot but at the same time, it is way too early to take anything for granted. The seven-point lead is a significant one but with so much of the season left to be played, it is not one that cannot be overturned. Of course, Brendan Rodgers will […]
Celtic problem as five players could be out for a month - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['It's been a while': Lee McCulloch can't hide Celtic envy as he makes Rangers academy plea]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178087</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/its-been-a-while-lee-mcculloch-cant-hide-celtic-envy-as-he-makes-rangers-academy-plea/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lee McCulloch couldn’t hide his Celtic envy when talking about the club’s ability to bring players through their academy in comparison to Rangers. From Kieran...
The post 'It's been a while': Lee McCulloch can't hide Celtic envy as he makes Rangers academy plea appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rumoured target told he is not good enough for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44983</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/18/rumoured-target-good-enough-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T18:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been pretty active when it comes to signing players in recent times although the additions that they have made have not pleased all the supporters. Most had hoped for some high-profile signings over the summer in order to make a mark in the Champions League and early rumours had suggested so as well. […]
Rumoured target told he is not good enough for Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['His passing, strength & composure': Andy Walker says rival coach impressed by Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178023</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/it-impressed-andy-walker-shares-aberdeen-coach-barry-robsons-admiration-for-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been a season to remember for Celtic star Liam Scales, as he continues to go from strength to strength. After turning himself into...
The post 'His passing, strength & composure': Andy Walker says rival coach impressed by Celtic player appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Credit where it's due; new Celtic podcast has been a breath of fresh air]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178011</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/credit-where-its-due-new-celtic-podcast-has-been-a-breath-of-fresh-air/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a Celtic supporter angling for any Hoops content over the international break, the club’s new-look podcast has been a welcome sight. I will happily...
The post Credit where it's due; new Celtic podcast has been a breath of fresh air appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player hailed as ‘positional wizard’ by Japanese fans]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44957</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/18/celtic-player-wizard-japanese-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With several Celtic stars away on international duty, the main concern for the fans is usually hoping to avoid bad news regarding potential injuries. So far there have been no new issues reported, which is great. Brendan Rodgers will of course be delighted to have seen Reo Hatate and Kyogo Furuashi on top form for […]
Celtic player hailed as ‘positional wizard’ by Japanese fans - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The pressure is firmly on Premiership side to sell tickets for Celtic clash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177994</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/with-many-celtic-fans-locked-out-of-tynecastle-this-weekend-the-pressure-is-firmly-on-hearts/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic return to action this weekend when we take on Hearts at their Tynecastle home. It’s probably the second tastiest away day we face during...
The post The pressure is firmly on Premiership side to sell tickets for Celtic clash appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Celtic can keep the heat on Rangers under Philippe Clement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178017</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-ten-point-challenge-how-celtic-can-keep-the-heat-on-rangers-under-philippe-clement/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The international break is almost over and Celtic will soon be with us again. The Hoops return to action on Sunday afternoon against Hearts. The...
The post How Celtic can keep the heat on Rangers under Philippe Clement appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boost confirmed with return of €5 million player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44975</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/18/celtic-confirmed-return-5-million-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T12:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Things are starting to look up for Celtic. The club did stumble out of the gates and many had even started questioning the decision to bring back Brendan Rodgers. That seems to have been an overreaction though as the Hoops have gotten things back on track. Yes, getting knocked out of the Scottish League Cup […]
Celtic boost confirmed with return of €5 million player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GREEN LIGHT FOR CELTIC DUO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113210</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/green-light-for-celtic-duo/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T11:49:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GREG TAYLOR came through unscathed as his Scotland international comeback ended in a 4-1 friendly defeat against France in Lille. Skipper Callum McGregor was afforded a rare night off as he remained on the substitutes’ bench while Steve Clarke’s side lost for the third consecutive game. The Scots, who sealed their place in next summer’s Euro [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["A draw is a disaster"; class quotes show Carter-Vickers was born to play for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177943</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/a-draw-is-a-disaster-class-quotes-show-carter-vickers-was-born-to-play-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cameron Carter-Vickers has been speaking about Celtic while away on international duty. The USA international featured in both of his country’s matches during this FIFA...
The post "A draw is a disaster"; class quotes show Carter-Vickers was born to play for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Relief for one of the world’s busiest players]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113204</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/relief-for-one-of-the-worlds-busiest-players/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T11:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of us considered Cameron Carter-Vickers unfortunate not to be more involved in last year’s World Cup in Qatar.  The US international featured in only one match.  This international break, Cameron came off the bench in both US games; against Germany and Ghana – reward for his form since December, as Celtic collected a treble. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CROCKED CELT UPDATE: ‘HE’S DOING VERY WELL,’ RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113201</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/crocked-celt-update-hes-doing-very-well-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T10:54:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has revealed £4.3million summer recruit Maik Nawrocki is on his way back. The towering centre-back, who arrived from Legia Warsaw in August around the same time Carl Starfelt was heading for Celta Vigo, made his debut in the 4-2 Premiership opening-day win over Ross County at Parkhead on August 5. Nawrocki was in place [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Kennedy explains the benefits of the international break that Celtic fans could soon see]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177946</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/john-kennedy-explains-the-benefits-of-the-international-break-that-celtic-fans-could-soon-see/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Kennedy has been speaking about the benefits of this international break on the Celtic squad. The Hoops assistant manager is one of those left...
The post John Kennedy explains the benefits of the international break that Celtic fans could soon see appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['MVP': Portuguese top-flight star hails Celtic player after performance on national duty]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178069</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/mvp-portuguese-top-flight-star-hails-celtic-player-after-performances-on-national-duty/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T09:40:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mikey Johnston put his name up in lights this week after the Celtic star scored his first goal for the Republic of Ireland. The 24-year-old...
The post 'MVP': Portuguese top-flight star hails Celtic player after performance on national duty appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC LEGEND: THE YEAR-LONG MYSTERY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113197</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-legend-the-year-long-mystery/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T09:27:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEIL LENNON has been out of work since being sacked by Cypriot outfit Omonia Nicosia EXACTLY a year ago today. Astonishingly, the Celtic legend has not been offered a suitable pathway back into management, despite an indisputably impressive track record. The 52-year-old Northern Irishman is the solitary individual in the Hoops’ proud history to play [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Celtic star Kyogo Furuhashi has posted this morning on Instagram to fans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=178050</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-celtic-star-kyogo-furuhashi-has-posted-this-morning-on-instagram-to-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T08:50:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scoring for fun at Celtic. And scoring for fun in the colours of Japan. Some things just don’t change for Kyogo Furuhashi. The 28-year-old was...
The post What Celtic star Kyogo Furuhashi has posted this morning on Instagram to fans appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE JOY OF SIXTY: KYOGO’S AIM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113195</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-joy-of-sixty-kyogos-aim/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T08:03:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CRACKSHOT Kyogo Furuhashi has Hearts in his sights as he aims for goal No.60 since joining Celtic in late July 2021. The speedy Japanese raider cost a bargain £4.6million from J-League outfit Vissel Kobe and has repaid the Hoops with a prolific striking return. Despite being sidelined for four months with two separate injuries in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I DON’T THINK THE CELTIC FANS ALLOW THAT,’ ADMITS HOOPS ACE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113192</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-dont-think-the-celtic-fans-allow-that-admits-hoops-ace/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T07:24:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CAMERON CARTER-VICKERS prepared for Celtic’s visit to Tynecastle on Sunday with an 18-minute work-out as the USA eased to a 4-0 win over Ghana in Nashville today. The Hoops centre-back made his first Premiership start in the 3-1 success over Kilmarnock at Parkhead 11 days ago after being sidelined with a muscular injury sustained in the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The rarest of evenings for Celtic captain Callum McGregor in Lille]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177960</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-rarest-of-evenings-for-celtic-captain-callum-mcgregor-in-lille/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic captain Callum McGregor was an unused substitute for Scotland on Tuesday evening. Steve Clarke’s men were 4-1 losers away to France, as the likes...
The post The rarest of evenings for Celtic captain Callum McGregor in Lille appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star Kyogo explains why latest Japan goal was extra special]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177936</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-star-kyogo-furuhashi-explains-why-latest-japan-goal-was-extra-special/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star Kyogo Furuhashi was back amongst the goals for Japan on Tuesday. Hajime Moriyasu’s side are one of the form teams in international football...
The post Celtic star Kyogo explains why latest Japan goal was extra special appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant urges Celtic 24-year-old to 'step up', suggests teammate could be 'moving on']]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177975</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-have-been-impressed-peter-grant-worried-celtic-star-could-be-moving-on/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wide positions at Celtic became a bit of a talking point this week after Mikey Johnston scored for the Republic of Ireland. The 24-year-old...
The post Peter Grant urges Celtic 24-year-old to 'step up', suggests teammate could be 'moving on' appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic international round-up: Carter-Vickers relief, promising Bernardo, Oh struggles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177953</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-international-round-up-carter-vickers-relief-promising-bernardo-ohs-struggles/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The international action is now over with Celtic’s global stars jetting back to Scotland. We’re still a good few days away from the Hoops returning...
The post Celtic international round-up: Carter-Vickers relief, promising Bernardo, Oh struggles appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WAR GAMES: PART ONE: ‘MORE X-CERTIFICATE THAN EXHIBITION’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=83969</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/war-games-part-one-more-x-certificate-than-exhibition/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T04:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TODAY is the 56th anniversary of one of the most infamous games in Celtic’s proud history – the first leg of three vicious encounters in the Intercontinental Cup Final against Argentina’s Racing Club of Buenos Aires. It was the evening at a packed Hampden where “football went oot the windae,” according to Wee Jimmy Johnstone, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alex McLeish offers blunt Celtic truth to Philippe Clement]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44971</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/17/alex-mcleish-celtic-philippe-clement/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T21:04:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers have finally appointed a new manager. Philippe Clement is the man replacing Michael Beale in the Ibrox hot seat and it is safe to say that he has a lot of work to do. As things stand, they find themselves seven points behind Celtic in the Scottish Premiership table. That is a significant gap […]
Alex McLeish offers blunt Celtic truth to Philippe Clement - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cameron Carter-Vickers makes potential Celtic exit claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44968</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/17/cameron-carter-vickers-celtic-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T19:34:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cameron Carter-Vickers has been one of Celtic’s best players since joining the club back in 2021. We have not seen the best of him this season till now and understandably so. He had undergone surgery towards the end of the previous campaign and returned early in this one only to be injured after a few […]
Cameron Carter-Vickers makes potential Celtic exit claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic eyeing move for £12 million player in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44964</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/17/celtic-eyeing-move-12-million-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T18:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have stuck to signing youngsters in recent times and while the strategy has not gone down too well with a large section of the fanbase, one cannot argue with the success that they have had. The likes of Matt O’Riley, Reo Hatate, Jota, Cameron Carter-Vickers and several others would have been considered as ‘project’ […]
Celtic eyeing move for £12 million player in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘A shame’: Alex McLeish delivers Celtic reality to new Rangers boss Philippe Clement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177922</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/a-shame-alex-mcleish-delivers-celtic-reality-to-new-rangers-boss-philippe-clement/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alex McLeish thinks new Rangers boss Philippe Clement faces a ‘difficult task’ in trying to overcome Brendan Rodgers’ Celtic this season. Those at Ibrox turned...
The post ‘A shame’: Alex McLeish delivers Celtic reality to new Rangers boss Philippe Clement appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two season debuts that must surely be in the offing for Celtic over the coming weeks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177915</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/two-season-debuts-that-must-surely-be-in-the-offing-for-celtic-over-the-coming-weeks/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The season is over three months old, yet the Celtic support are still waiting to see a couple of attackers play their first minutes. It’s...
The post Two season debuts that must surely be in the offing for Celtic over the coming weeks appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou makes emotional admission about Celtic fans]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44955</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/17/ange-postecoglou-admission-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T15:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is safe to say that Ange Postecoglou was beloved during his time as manager of Celtic. He arrived as a bit of an unknown to the European football fan and with very few expectations surrounding him. There were many Rangers supporters who felt that he would be gone by Christmas. Postecoglou exceeded the expectations […]
Ange Postecoglou makes emotional admission about Celtic fans - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Luis Palma rise continues and now Celtic are about to benefit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177843</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-luis-palma-rise-continues-and-now-celtic-are-about-to-benefit/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic attacker Luis Palma had another good performance as his rise in the game continues. It’s been a hectic few months for the 23-year-old as...
The post The Luis Palma rise continues and now Celtic are about to benefit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALL SYSTEMS GO FOR KYOGO AND CO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113180</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/all-systems-go-for-kyogo-and-co/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T13:25:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO FURUHASHI swept in the opening goal in Japan’s 2-0 win over Tunisia in the Kirin Cup in Kobe today. The prolific Celtic hitman combined composure with a killer touch as he raced between the rival centre-backs onto a through pass before slotting the ball away with his usual expertise, leaving the outrushing keeper helpless. Kyogo’s [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic man set for an unlikely elite-level international outing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177869</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-man-looks-set-for-an-unlikely-elite-level-international-outing-on-tuesday/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some Celtic stars look set to feature as Scotland face their latest elite-level test on Tuesday. Fresh from their qualification for UEFA Euro 2024 being...
The post Celtic man set for an unlikely elite-level international outing appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The surprising position Celtic star Reo Hatate is set to play for Japan on Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177877</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-surprising-position-celtic-star-reo-hatate-is-set-to-play-for-japan-on-tuesday/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star Reo Hatate will get his big Japan opportunity on Tuesday, but it is set to come in a surprising position. The former Kawasaki...
The post The surprising position Celtic star Reo Hatate is set to play for Japan on Tuesday appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Benefit of Celtic players becoming full internationals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113179</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/benefit-of-celtic-players-becoming-full-internationals/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T11:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A place in the Denmark national team would be an appropriate reward for Matt O’Riley’s early season form at Celtic.  The midfielder is with the squad for the first time for tonight’s away game to San Marino.  Denmark are not yet guaranteed qualification for Euro 2024, so are likely to start with a tried and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This weekend's unusual Celtic kick-off explained as complex Sky Sports issue arises]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177862</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/this-weekends-unusual-celtic-kick-off-explained-as-complex-sky-sports-issue-arises/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are back in action this weekend and we are involved in a pretty tasty clash. On Sunday, Brendan Rodgers‘ side will try to continue...
The post This weekend's unusual Celtic kick-off explained as complex Sky Sports issue arises appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic want to sign Real Madrid player set for free agency]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44951</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/17/celtic-want-real-madrid-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T10:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were pretty active in the recent summer transfer window, signing nine players in total. The additions did not leave many of the supporters impressed though. With Champions League football guaranteed, the hope was that experienced and established players would be brought in. Instead, the Hoops stuck to bringing in youngsters with high potential for […]
Celtic want to sign Real Madrid player set for free agency - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S No.1 PUZZLE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113175</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtics-no-1-puzzle/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T08:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART’S future at Celtic has once again been thrown into doubt with the champions linked with a January move for Real Madrid back-up keeper Andriy Lunin. The 36-year-old 75 times-capped England international shotstopper is out of contract at the end of the season following his £1million switch from Spurs in August 2021. Hart is the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘A LOT OF PEOPLE COULD HAVE GONE UNDER,’ BROONY’S PRAISE FOR CELT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113171</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/a-lot-of-people-could-have-gone-under-broonys-praise-for-celt/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T07:33:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC hero Scott Brown insists his successor Callum McGregor is relishing the responsibility of being the captain at the champions. The old warhorse quit Parkhead at the end of season 2020/21 when the team limped home without silverware for the first time in 11 years. At the age of 35, Brown took the opportunity go [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic attacker fully explains his most recent injury; pre-match text from Rodgers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177900</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/mikey-johnston-fully-explains-his-most-recent-celtic-injury-pre-match-text-from-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic winger Mikey Johnston has been in the Irish media after netting his second goal for his country. Johnston scored the Republic of Ireland’s second...
The post Celtic attacker fully explains his most recent injury; pre-match text from Rodgers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘BUZZING,’ FORGOTTEN CELT’S STRIKING REMINDER]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113162</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/buzzing-forgotten-celts-striking-reminder/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T06:23:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MIKEY JOHNSTON has yet to kick a first-team ball for Celtic since his summer return from Portugal. The 24-year-old winger spent the previous campaign on loan at top-fight Vitoria Guimaraes and his hopes of impressing Brendan Rodgers suffered a setback when he was injured in pre-season training. However, the forgotten Celt sent a reminder to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Brown is loving what Callum McGregor is achieving as Celtic captain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177884</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/scott-brown-is-loving-what-callum-mcgregor-is-achieving-as-celtic-captain/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic great Scott Brown has been speaking about what Callum McGregor is achieving at both club and international level. McGregor is an integral part of...
The post Scott Brown is loving what Callum McGregor is achieving as Celtic captain appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I love watching him play’: Shay Given wowed by Celtic player after he stars on national duty]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177845</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/i-love-watching-him-play-pundit-wowed-by-celtic-player-after-he-stars-on-international-duty/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shay Given has lauded Mikey Johnston after the Celtic star shone brightly for the Republic of Ireland last night.  Life might be difficult, in terms...
The post ‘I love watching him play’: Shay Given wowed by Celtic player after he stars on national duty appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real Madrid goalkeeper just one of "several" exciting options for Celtic; January possibility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177892</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/real-madrid-goalkeeper-just-one-of-several-exciting-options-for-celtic-with-january-possibility/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T05:20:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic supporters are going to hear a fair bit about the signing of a new goalkeeper between now and next summer. Current Celtic number one...
The post Real Madrid goalkeeper just one of "several" exciting options for Celtic; January possibility appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>