<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-11-02T18:13:03.413Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic made mistake letting €2.5 million player leave]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45309</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/02/celtic-made-mistake-player-leave/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T18:04:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans would have been delighted to see the ball find the back of the net as Oh Hyeon-gyu scored the winner against St Mirren. It was a tough game but three points is all that matters and the supporters would have come out of Parkhead feeling great. But that does not take away from […]
Celtic made mistake letting €2.5 million player leave - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker wins annual MLS award ahead of Lionel Messi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179452</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-striker-wins-annual-mls-award-ahead-of-lionel-messi/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T17:53:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker Giorgos Giakoumakis has won the Major League Soccer Newcomer Of The Year Award for 2023 after a vote by players, coaches and...
The post Former Celtic striker wins annual MLS award ahead of Lionel Messi appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers praises Celtic player after heroics vs St Mirren]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45302</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/02/brendan-rodgers-praises-celtic-st-mirren/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T16:02:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s 2-1 win over St Mirren was another tough match. The Hoops dominated possession and had plenty of chances in the game. But it took a late goal to secure the win and the three points. The match as it unfolded gave more opportunities to players to show what they could do. David Turnbull seemed […]
Brendan Rodgers praises Celtic player after heroics vs St Mirren - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Man of the Match': Gustaf Lagerbielke hails Celtic 22-year-old after win over St Mirren]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179427</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/man-of-the-match-gustaf-lagerbielke-hails-celtic-22-year-old-after-win-over-st-mirren/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T13:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gustaf Lagerbielke thinks Hyeongyu Oh was ‘Man of the Match’ as Celtic came from a goal down to beat St Mirren 2-1 at Parkhead on...
The post 'Man of the Match': Gustaf Lagerbielke hails Celtic 22-year-old after win over St Mirren appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IMAGES: KYOG-OH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113758</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/images-kyog-oh/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T13:32:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO FURUHASHI has scored 61 goals for Celtic since arriving on a £4.6million transfer from J-League outfit Vissel Kobe in late July 2021. Hoops fans are still wondering why the prolific Japanese ace hasn’t claimed 62! In the fading moments of last night’s 2-1 win over St Mirren at Parkhead, an opportunity was presented to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Holm, Yang, Maeda determined outcome]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113717</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/holm-yang-maeda-determined-outcome/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T12:02:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For reasons that are not clear to me, St Mirren are a proper football team.  They benefited from a central defensive lapse to take an early lead and limited Celtic large spells of unproductive possession.  Then, after going behind, finished the game playing some of the best football we have seen from a Scottish opponent [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘It’s actually his fault’: Celtic told Greg Taylor ‘wasn’t happy’ with teammate v St Mirren]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179407</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/its-actually-his-fault-celtic-told-greg-taylor-wasnt-happy-with-teammate-v-st-mirren/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Stewart says Greg Taylor ‘wasn’t happy’ with Liam Scales for failing to stop St Mirren from opening the scoring against Celtic on Wednesday night....
The post ‘It’s actually his fault’: Celtic told Greg Taylor ‘wasn’t happy’ with teammate v St Mirren appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic urged to make double deal involving Joe Hart]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45299</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/02/celtic-urged-double-deal-joe-hart/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T10:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are some areas most Celtic fans agree that the club need to improve in. One of them is goalkeeper. Joe Hart has been the number one since arriving in the summer of 2021. There was talk in the previous transfer window that the Hoops could bring in a new first-choice between the posts and […]
Celtic urged to make double deal involving Joe Hart - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CCV PUZZLE SOLVED]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113714</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ccv-puzzle-solved/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T08:49:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS explained the absence of Cameron Carter-Vickers from his starting line-up for last night’s 2-1 win over St Mirren at Parkhead. The team list sparked fears among fans the rock-solid USA World Cup centre-back had suffered a recurrence of the hamstring problem that sidelined him for seven games earlier this season. However, Rodgers was [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Thursday November 2: Help Me If You Can]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18531</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18531"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T08:45:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, John Beaton gets to referee a Celtic game.   That’s handy, because based on last nights evidence, where despite his best efforts, Celtic dug…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Malph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers clears up Wednesday night Celtic concern]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179402</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-clears-up-wednesday-night-celtic-selection-concern/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T08:25:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cameron Carter-Vickers’ omission from the Celtic squad was a big worry for supporters when the team news was announced last night. The USA international wasn’t...
The post Brendan Rodgers clears up Wednesday night Celtic concern appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘SO HAPPY FOR BIG OH,’ RODGERS REVEALS HERO’S ‘SECRET’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113706</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/so-happy-for-big-oh-rodgers-reveals-heros-secret/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T08:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS hailed matchwinner Oh Hyeon-gyu after Celtic’s dramatic 2-1 triumph over St Mirren at Parkhead that keeps the champions five points ahead at the Premiership pinnacle. The encounter was deadlocked at 1-1 with only seven minutes to go before the South Korean thumped in the second to relieve the tension around the east end of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hyeongyu Oh's thrilling Celtic winner quickly became even more important on Wednesday night]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179399</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/hyeongyu-ohs-thrilling-celtic-winner-quickly-became-even-more-important-on-wednesday-night/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T07:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic could have seen their Scottish Premiership lead being reduced to just three points on Wednesday night before Hyeongyu Oh’s thrilling winner over St Mirren....
The post Hyeongyu Oh's thrilling Celtic winner quickly became even more important on Wednesday night appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton hails Celtic hero he recently raised doubts about after win over St Mirren]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179394</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/chris-sutton-hails-celtic-hero-he-recently-raised-doubts-about-after-win-over-st-mirren/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T07:28:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyeongyu Oh’s winner at Celtic Park on Wednesday was a thrilling moment and one much-needed not just for the team but for the South Korean’s...
The post Chris Sutton hails Celtic hero he recently raised doubts about after win over St Mirren appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers makes a big point about his players after dramatic Celtic win vs St Mirren]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179388</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-makes-a-big-point-about-his-players-after-dramatic-celtic-win-vs-st-mirren/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-02T06:55:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has hailed his players for not panicking at the 80-minute mark in their quest for a winner over St Mirren on...
The post Brendan Rodgers makes a big point about his players after dramatic Celtic win vs St Mirren appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic finally show something they had not since Ange Postecoglou left]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45294</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/01/celtic-finally-ange-postecoglou-left/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T22:35:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The performance would not have pleased a lot of Celtic fans. But they will surely be delighted to get all three points from a game which had looked headed for a draw for quite some time. St Mirren had actually taken the lead, going against all expectations. David Turnbull brought the two teams level but […]
Celtic finally show something they had not since Ange Postecoglou left - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC 2 ST MIRREN 1: OH YES: STRIKER IS LATE-GOAL HERO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113704</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-2-st-mirren-1-oh-yes-striker-is-late-goal-hero/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T21:42:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC 2 ST MIRREN  1 POWERHOUSE Oh Hyeon-gyu blasted in a dramatic late winner for Celtic in a tension-laden encounter at Parkhead this evening. The game was balanced at 1-1 with seven minutes of regulation time to go when the South Korean struck to claim three crucial points. Oh, who hadn’t scored this season, proved [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss explains Cameron Carter-Vickers absence amid concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45291</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/01/celtic-cameron-carter-vickers-absence/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T21:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cameron Carter-Vickers has already dealt with his fair share of injury problems lately. The American is widely considered as Celtic’s best defender and leader at the back. Naturally, fans were left worried when they saw that he was missing from the matchday squad against St Mirren. There had been no reports of any injuries ahead […]
Celtic boss explains Cameron Carter-Vickers absence amid concerns - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers refuses to give up on Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45254</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/01/brendan-rodgers-refuses-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T19:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers recently came out in defence of one of his players and confirmed that he still has a part to play in the team’s story this season. It is widely expected that the Hoops will look to part ways with a player or two in January due to the size of the […]
Brendan Rodgers refuses to give up on Celtic player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Wyatt-Hupton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic v St Mirren, GG Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113702</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-st-mirren-gg-live-updates/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T18:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 19:45.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: CCV OUT, PHILLIPS IN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113656</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-ccv-out-phillips-in/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T18:38:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CAMERON CARTER-VICKERS misses out as Celtic prepare to get back to winning ways in the Premiership against St Mirren at Parkhead tonight after firing blanks in the stalemate against Hibs at Easter Road at the weekend. The USA World Cup centre-back didn’t even make the squad, presumably after sustaining an injury in Edinburgh. Livrpool loanee [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paulo Bernardo reveals what Jota told him about Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45285</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/01/paulo-bernardo-jota-told-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T18:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paulo Bernardo joined Celtic in the summer on a season-long loan from Benfica. He was one of the most highly-rated youngsters at the Portuguese club but never really found his feet in the senior team. Does that story sound familiar? Well, that was pretty much exactly Jota’s situation before he arrived at Parkhead. Jota would […]
Paulo Bernardo reveals what Jota told him about Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I hope the Celtic board aren’t listening’: Barry Ferguson expresses 'worry' after what he's told]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179367</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-hope-the-celtic-board-arent-listening-barry-ferguson-expresses-worry-after-what-hes-told/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T18:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Barry Ferguson wasn’t too keen to hear that Celtic are being pushed to break their club-record transfer in January in order to boost Brendan Rodgers’...
The post ‘I hope the Celtic board aren’t listening’: Barry Ferguson expresses 'worry' after what he's told appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers flags up new Celtic fixture concern]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179354</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-flags-up-new-celtic-fixture-concern/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T17:39:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers believes league officials can do more to assist teams facing potential fixture congestion. For instance, Celtic's Champions League group stage opponents, Atletico Madrid, have only one game scheduled on Friday against Las Palmas between next week's Group E tie. In comparison Celtic face St Mirren tonight at Celtic Park and Ross County away in Dingwall on Saturday ahead of next Tuesday's clash against Atletico. 
The post Brendan Rodgers flags up new Celtic fixture concern appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Jota told Paulo Bernardo before Benfica to Celtic move; prediction comes true]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179323</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-jota-told-paulo-bernardo-before-benfica-to-celtic-move-prediction-comes-true/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T16:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder Paulo Bernardo is aiming to stay at Celtic for the long-term despite no assurances over his future at the club. 
The post What Jota told Paulo Bernardo before Benfica to Celtic move; prediction comes true appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Nobody had heard of him’: Neil Lennon says Celtic 22-year-old now the ‘best player’ in Scotland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179333</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/nobody-had-heard-of-him-neil-lennon-says-celtic-22-year-old-now-the-best-player-in-scotland/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T16:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon has waxed lyrical about Matt O’Riley and the performances he is putting in for Celtic. Like many Celtic transfers, Matt O’Riley arrived as...
The post ‘Nobody had heard of him’: Neil Lennon says Celtic 22-year-old now the ‘best player’ in Scotland appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Record Celtic valuation isn't putting off suitors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179269</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/record-celtic-transfer-valuation-is-only-increasing-demand/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T15:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou is targeting a surprise move for Matt O'Riley. 
O'Riley who has undeniably been Celtic's star player this season has been linked with the move to Tottenham Hotspur who currently sit top of the English Premier League. 
The post Record Celtic valuation isn't putting off suitors appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[West Ham United eyeing move for £25 million Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45282</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/01/west-ham-united-eyeing-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T15:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is nothing new for Celtic players to be linked with a move to the Premier League. Several have made the jump over the years. It has worked out for some and not so much for others. As the financial divide continues to grow between the English top flight and the other European leagues, one […]
West Ham United eyeing move for £25 million Celtic player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Bhoys striker calls for resolution over Celtic Park Green Brigade ban]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179252</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-bhoys-striker-calls-for-resolution-over-celtic-park-green-brigade-ban/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Green Brigade was informed yesterday by Celtic that they will not be able to attend any home or away games until further notice, including tonight's Scottish Premiership match at Celtic Park against St Mirren.
The post Former Bhoys striker calls for resolution over Celtic Park Green Brigade ban appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['No chance': Barry Ferguson needs to be put right over recent comments about Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179292</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/no-chance-barry-ferguson-needs-to-be-put-right-over-recent-comments-about-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Barry Ferguson has stated that there is ‘no chance’ the title race is over between Celtic and Rangers, with Brendan Rodgers’ side holding a five-point...
The post 'No chance': Barry Ferguson needs to be put right over recent comments about Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defensive call, potential rotation; Celtic team news and Predicted XI vs St Mirren]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179259</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/defensive-call-potential-rotation-celtic-team-news-and-predicted-xi-vs-st-mirren/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T14:12:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will look to get back to winning ways after a disappointing 0-0 draw against Hibernian on Saturday at Easter Road. 
The post Defensive call, potential rotation; Celtic team news and Predicted XI vs St Mirren appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero eyeing unexpected return from retirement]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45279</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/01/celtic-hero-eyeing-return-retirement/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T13:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is also sad to see Celtic legends retire from the game but at the end of the day, that is just the nature of football and life. Nobody can continue playing forever, no matter how good they were in their prime. The good thing is that many make a move into management and remain […]
Celtic hero eyeing unexpected return from retirement - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bans and rocking Saints]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113701</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/bans-and-rocking-saints/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T12:22:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s email to those who had their season tickets suspended yesterday, in the Green Brigade section, alleges a series of incidents, including “intimidating and threatening behaviour towards staff” on multiple occasions, “forcing open fire exits to permit access to individuals without tickets” at Fir Park, a list of pyrotechnic and banner violations and several other [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘COULD I STAY?’ LOAN BHOY REVEALS TARGET]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113694</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/could-i-stay-loan-bhoy-reveals-target/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T10:23:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PAULO BERNARDO has made one start in his six appearances for Celtic since arriving on a season-long loan from Benfica just before the transfer deadline. The Portuguese playmaker has already experienced the highs and lows of football at the champions. Remarkably, he has been involved in two wins, two draws and two defeats in his [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['It wouldn't surprise': Celtic told 32-year-old could earn first start of season v St Mirren]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179236</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/it-wouldnt-surprise-celtic-told-32-year-old-could-earn-his-first-start-this-season-v-st-mirren/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T08:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Hartson has backed James Forrest to start for Celtic against St Mirren in the Scottish Premiership on Wednesday night. After dropping points against Hibernian...
The post 'It wouldn't surprise': Celtic told 32-year-old could earn first start of season v St Mirren appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OUR TEAM CELTIC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113685</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/our-team-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T07:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AUTHOR Alex Gordon presented a personal thought on Celtic in his fifteenth tribute to the club, ‘Fifty Flags Plus One‘. The former Sports Editor of Scotland’s biggest-selling newspaper the Sunday Mail is a lifelong Celtic supporter. Alex wrote of his pride of being among those followers of a special sporting institution. Here is the Author’s Note in full. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘He can come in’: John Hartson backs Celtic to sign Scotland international for ‘£2m’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179213</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/he-can-come-in-john-hartson-backs-celtic-to-sign-scotland-international-for-2m/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T07:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Hartson has backed Brendan Rodgers’ Celtic to secure the transfer of in-demand Hearts striker Lawrence Shankland in January.  The 28-year-old has got the attention...
The post ‘He can come in’: John Hartson backs Celtic to sign Scotland international for ‘£2m’ appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘NO FAVOURS,’ RODGERS WARNS RIVAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113675</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/no-favours-rodgers-warns-rival/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T06:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS admits he is an admirer of fellow-Northern Irishman Stephen Robinson. However, the Celtic boss has warned the St Mirren manager “there will be no favours” when the dug-out rivals lock horns at Parkhead tonight. The Paisley side arrive in the east end of Glasgow in fine form after Saturday’s home 4-0 hammering of St [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THANKS, SAINTS, FOR THE WAKE-UP CALL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113670</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/thanks-saints-for-the-wake-up-call/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T06:30:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC embarked upon a stunning TWENTY-EIGHT game unbeaten league run after being given a wake-up call by St Mirren last season. Ange Postecoglou’s men delivered their worst performance of the campaign as they nosedived to a shocking 2-0 defeat against Stephen Robinson’s team in Paisley on September 18 2022. It was the Greek-Australian gaffer’s first Premiership [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S 14-GAME MAKE-OR-BREAK SCHEDULE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113660</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtics-14-game-make-or-break-schedule/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T06:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC kick off a hectic schedule of FOURTEEN games in TWO months when they take on St Mirren at Parkhead this evening. Brendan Rodgers’ side will face three crucially important Champions League Group E encounters – two away from home – before they reach the turn of the year. The Hoops, with just one point after [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE LAST HORROR SHOW]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113632</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-last-horror-show/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T05:45:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ST MIRREN have the rare distinction of being the last team to inflict a domestic defeat on Celtic at Parkhead. The Paisley side achieved the feat on January 30 2021 at a Covid-enforced deserted stadium when they piled the misery on the struggling champions as the bid for a historic tenth successive title bid collapsed [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC v ST MIRREN: 5-MINUTE QUIZ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113629</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-st-mirren-5-minute-quiz-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T05:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC played St Mirren three times at Parkhead last season and thumped 11 goals into their net. The Hoops walloped their Paisley rivals 4-0 in the league in January and followed up with a rousing 5-1 triumph to end the Saints’ Scottish Cup hopes one month later. There was a hiccup when Stephen Robinson’s side [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton delivers bleak reflection on Celtic performance]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45233</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/31/chris-sutton-delivers-celtic-performance/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T22:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It wasn’t the result we all wanted when Celtic could only manage a goalless draw against Hibernian at Easter Road at the weekend. It was not the level of performance we had hoped to see either. Chris Sutton has since added his own simple but bleak reflection on the match and the result. The draw […]
Chris Sutton delivers bleak reflection on Celtic performance - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic told 22-year-old is not capable and urged to make signing]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45271</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/31/celtic-22-year-old-capable-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T21:05:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic made additions in a number of positions over the course of the summer. Maybe even in some where they did not need to. On the other hand, there were other areas of the squad which were confusingly overlooked. And after the first few months of the season, striker has to be considered as one […]
Celtic told 22-year-old is not capable and urged to make signing - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms what Celtic fans have been waiting for]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45266</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/31/brendan-rodgers-celtic-fans-waiting/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T19:34:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were very active during the summer transfer window, bringing in nine new players. But till now, only one of them has been successful in making a genuine impact, in the form of Luis Palma. Gustaf Lagerbielke and Maik Nawrocki have looked decent when on the pitch but might struggle to get ahead of Cameron […]
Brendan Rodgers confirms what Celtic fans have been waiting for - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['In January': Chris Sutton has a clear message for Celtic and Brendan Rodgers after dropped points]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179199</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/in-january-chris-sutton-has-clear-message-for-celtic-and-brendan-rodgers-after-dropped-points/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T19:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton feels Celtic and Brendan Rodgers will need to dip into the January transfer market to improve the club’s squad depth. Celtic dropped points...
The post 'In January': Chris Sutton has a clear message for Celtic and Brendan Rodgers after dropped points appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chelsea transfer update means bad news for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45261</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/31/chelsea-transfer-update-news-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T18:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are in a decent position right now but at the same time, it is evident that they need to improve in certain areas. There has been a lot of talk about the squad depth in recent days, as it is clear that Brendan Rodgers does not have a lot of players who can come […]
Chelsea transfer update means bad news for Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player returns to training in major injury boost]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45256</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/31/celtic-player-returns-training-injury/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T15:30:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is no secret that Celtic have already dealt with a number of injury problems this season and continue to do so. The latest one was a problem suffered by Reo Hatate in the game against Atletico Madrid, which looks set to have ruled him out for the rest of the year. That is a […]
Celtic player returns to training in major injury boost - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GREEN LIGHT FOR CELTIC CROCK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113678</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/green-light-for-celtic-crock-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T14:33:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[STEPHEN WELSH has been given the green light to re-join training with the Celtic first team. The centre-back has been crocked since a freak training ground accident in mid-August just hours after penning a four-year extension to his contract. At the start of the season, Welsh answered an SOS from the champions when Brendan Rodgers [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic tipped to make move for Aberdeen’s best player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45251</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/31/celtic-tipped-move-aberdeen-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T12:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s transfer policy underwent quite some change following the appointment of Ange Postecoglou as the manager of the club in the summer of 2021. They spread their scouting network further and wider than ever before, bringing in players from all over the globe. It translated to success on the pitch, with the Australian guiding them […]
Celtic tipped to make move for Aberdeen’s best player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zombie EBT tales, Medicine for Reo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113669</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/zombie-ebt-tales-medicine-for-reo/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T12:02:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I see there is a bit of sensitivity across the city today, on the 11th anniversary of Rangers liquidation.  Fair enough.  We are all entitled to our own backstory and if the shoe was on the other foot, we would be clinging to dear life to whatever comforts we could.  As the years go by, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REVEALED: WHAT RODGERS SAID TO KEEP STAR AT CELTIC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113649</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/revealed-what-rodgers-said-to-keep-star-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T09:31:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has revealed he convinced Mikey Johnston to stay at Celtic in the summer and fight for a first-team place. The Republic of Ireland international returned to the champions after a season-long loan at Portuguese top-flight outfit Vitoria Guimaraes. Johnston was suffering from back injury problems in the summer and has remained out of the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS HAILS HOOPS SPEED MERCHANT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113644</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-hails-hoops-speed-merchant/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T09:06:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JAMES FORREST has a speedy response to his critics who insist his Celtic days are over. The evergreen winger, who has won a phenomenal 22 honours and scored over 100 goals after his first appearance against Motherwell 13 years ago, has been on the periphery in recent seasons. However, Brendan Rodgers has no intention of throwing [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['He can go': Celtic tipped to sign 'really talented' Aberdeen superstar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179177</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/he-can-go-celtic-tipped-to-sign-really-talented-aberdeen-superstar/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tam McManus has tipped Brendan Rodgers’ Celtic to sign Aberdeen striker, Bojan Miovski. The 24-year-old has been a consistent performer for Aberdeen since his transfer...
The post 'He can go': Celtic tipped to sign 'really talented' Aberdeen superstar appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Tuesday October 31: The Suspicion Of Bias]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18529</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18529"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T08:07:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regular readers of this irregular page will be well aware of previous mentions of a perception of bias towards one or two officials in the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Malph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REO ‘SHAME’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113640</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/reo-shame/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T08:05:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S worst fears were confirmed with the admission from Brendan Rodgers that Reo Hatate will be OUT for the remainder of the year. There was conjecture over the extent of the hamstring damage sustained by the influential midfielder after he pulled up inside a minute of the 2-2 Champions League Group E draw with Atletico Madrid at Parkhead [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC CLEAR-OUT: RODGERS PLANS SECOND EXODUS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113636</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-clear-out-rodgers-plans-second-exodus/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T07:48:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is planning a massive Celtic clear-out in January. The Hoops boss oversaw an exodus of players in the summer with the club taking a hit of over £10million to get rid of expensive flops Albian Ajeti, Vasilis Barkas and Ismaila Soro. The trio of duds – who cost £11.5million in transfer fees – [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC CLEAR=OUT: RODGERS PLANS SECOND EXODUS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113636</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-clearout-rodgers-plans-second-exodus/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T07:48:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is planning a massive Celtic clear-out in January. The Hoops boss oversaw an exodus of players in the summer with the club taking a hit of over £10million to get rid of expensive flops Albian Ajeti, Vasilis Barkas and Ismaila Soro. The trio of duds – who cost £11.5million in transfer fees – [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘He is wasted there’: Neil Lennon thinks Rodgers is using Celtic 30-year-old in the wrong way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179158</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/he-is-wasted-there-neil-lennon-thinks-brendan-rodgers-is-using-celtic-30-year-old-in-the-wrong-way/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon feels Brendan Rodgers needs to use Celtic captain, Callum McGregor, ‘further forward’. Celtic were dealt a major blow when Reo Hatate went down...
The post ‘He is wasted there’: Neil Lennon thinks Rodgers is using Celtic 30-year-old in the wrong way appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS v POSTECOGLOU: STARTER FOR TEN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113633</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-v-postecoglou-starter-for-ten/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T05:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has steered Celtic safely through an unbeaten trail in the first 10 games of the season to sit at the Premiership pinnacle. The champions, bidding for their twelfth title in 13 years, have amassed 26 points, five ahead of their nearest challengers. This time last year after the same number of league outings, his [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Loaned out Celtic players: Sead Haksabanovic update as six-game winning run ended]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179137</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/loaned-out-celtic-players-sead-haksabanovic-update-as-six-game-winning-run-ended/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T21:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sead Haksabanovic left Celtic this summer under a dark cloud after his cryptic Instagram message where he expressed his frustration at a lack of game...
The post Loaned out Celtic players: Sead Haksabanovic update as six-game winning run ended appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carl Starfelt seems to have made major mistake leaving Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45248</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/30/carl-starfelt-mistake-leaving-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T21:35:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There were two high-profile exits from Celtic over the course of the summer. Jota left in a Scottish record move in order to join Al-Ittihad. We all know how that one has turned out for him. He seems to be completely out of the first-team picture at the club already and it seems to be […]
Carl Starfelt seems to have made major mistake leaving Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic should sign prolific striker for free next summer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45243</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/30/celtic-prolific-striker-free-next-summer/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T20:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there is one thing that has become clear over the first few months of this season, it is that Celtic need another consistent goalscorer. Kyogo has continued to deliver the goods, even if at a slightly lower rate than the previous campaign. And Matt O’Riley has added goals to his game as well. Other […]
Celtic should sign prolific striker for free next summer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton tells Celtic what to do in January window]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45240</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/30/chris-sutton-tells-celtic-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T18:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is difficult to make a judgement on Celtic’s squad till now. There are many who arrived in the summer and must be given some time to settle down. But so far, Luis Palma seems to be the only one who could potentially be a part of the club’s best starting XI. With Reo Hatate […]
Chris Sutton tells Celtic what to do in January window - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Atletico like that sort of player': Celtic told how 26-year-old star could be worth '£100m']]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179124</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/atletico-madrid-like-that-sort-of-player-celtic-told-how-26-year-old-star-could-be-worth-100m/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T17:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant thinks Celtic winger Daizen Maeda would be worth ‘£100 million’ if he had better end product to his game and how he is...
The post 'Atletico like that sort of player': Celtic told how 26-year-old star could be worth '£100m' appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[’Celtic aren’t the same’: Chris Sutton makes feelings clear about 25-year-old after Hibs draw]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179103</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-arent-the-same-chris-sutton-makes-feelings-clear-about-25-year-old-after-hibs-draw/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton has expressed the importance of Reo Hatate after he was absent as Celtic dropped points away at Hibernian on Saturday.  During the early...
The post ’Celtic aren’t the same’: Chris Sutton makes feelings clear about 25-year-old after Hibs draw appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic blow confirmed by Brendan Rodgers as fear comes true]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45236</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/30/celtic-confirmed-brendan-rodgers-true/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T15:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whenever it looks like Celtic’s season is picking up momentum, they are handed another hurdle to overcome. The club had been in good form lately and the 2-2 draw against Atletico Madrid in midweek was a result that must have boosted their confidence. Instead, they drew 0-0 against Hibernian at Easter Road to allow the […]
Celtic blow confirmed by Brendan Rodgers as fear comes true - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blame it on Reo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113635</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/blame-it-on-reo/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T12:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate missed three games through injury early this season.  During that period, we scored only one goal, went out the League Cup and dropped our only points of the season before Saturday.  Reo returned as a second half substitute at home to Dundee, with only a penalty goal separating the teams, but within seven [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player ruled out for rest of the year with injury]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45227</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/30/celtic-player-ruled-rest-year-injury/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T10:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This has not been a good few days for Celtic. First, they dropped a couple of points away at Easter Road even though Hibernian did not put in a great performance themselves. Then they saw the Rangers score two late goals to grab victory from the jaws of defeat to cut the lead at the […]
Celtic player ruled out for rest of the year with injury - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HATATE: WHAT’S THE SCORE, CELTIC?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113626</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hatate-whats-the-score-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T08:33:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE pulled up after only 35 seconds of Celtic’s 2-2 draw with Atletico Madrid at Parkhead last Wednesday. The influential Japanese midfielder attempted to continue, but it was clear he had a hamstring problem and he was replaced by on-loan Benfica playmaker Paulo Bernardo in the seventh minute. Forty-eight hours after the Euro deadlock, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘WE STRIVE TO BE PERFECT,’ INSISTS CELT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113622</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/we-strive-to-be-perfect-insists-celt/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T07:45:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC saw their lead at the Premiership pinnacle cut to five points following a see-saw weekend. The champions shed two points in the disappointing goalless draw with Hibs at Easter Road while, 24 hours later at Ibrox, Philippe Clement’s side were heading for defeat against Hearts. An early headed goal from Lawrence Shankland looked like [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers criticises Celtic player for giving ball away]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45224</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/29/brendan-rodgers-criticises-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-29T22:05:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic came into the game against Hibernian on the back of a confidence-boosting performance against Atletico Madrid in the Champions League. That was not on display at Easter Road though, as the Hoops put in an uninspiring display and could only manage a goalless draw against Hibernian. The result allowed the Rangers to cut the […]
Brendan Rodgers criticises Celtic player for giving ball away - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic tipped to sign two players in January window]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45219</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/29/celtic-tipped-sign-two-players-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-29T19:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have had an interesting season so far. They got knocked out of the Scottish League Cup early and are winless in their first three games in the Champions League group stage despite putting in impressive performances. On the other hand, the Hoops do have a commanding lead at the top of the Premiership table […]
Celtic tipped to sign two players in January window - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton raises constructive concerns about Celtic attack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179092</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-raises-constructive-concerns-about-celtic-attack/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-29T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker Chris Sutton thinks the Bhoys need a different kind of attacking approach in high-intensity games that could leave Brendan Rodgers’ starters flagging...
The post Chris Sutton raises constructive concerns about Celtic attack appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic-linked player now wanted by PSG and Napoli]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45216</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/29/celtic-linked-player-wanted-psg-napoli/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-29T18:05:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have done a pretty good job in recent times when it comes to identifying top talents. It is not just the players that they have been able to sign like Kyogo, Matt O’Riley, Reo Hatate, Cameron Carter-Vickers and more but also those who they have missed out on. Names like Ivan Toney, Kaoru Mitoma […]
Celtic-linked player now wanted by PSG and Napoli - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Celtic are really very interested"; Euro sporting director keen to progress talks with Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179082</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-are-very-interested-euro-sporting-director-keen-to-strengthen-link-with-bhoys/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-29T17:52:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A delegation from the Austrian side Admira Wacker was in Glasgow during the week to hold discussions with Celtic about a formal link between the...
The post "Celtic are really very interested"; Euro sporting director keen to progress talks with Bhoys appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brighton & Hove Albion eye move for Celtic superstar]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45212</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/29/brighton-hove-albion-eye-move-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-29T16:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brighton & Hove Albion have arguably the best scouting network in world football right now. It is remarkable how they have been able to identify one potential superstar after another, move them on for big transfer fees and replace them with new players without their performance levels going down. It looks like they have a […]
Brighton & Hove Albion eye move for Celtic superstar - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£7m Celtic target now wanted by 3 Champions League clubs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179072</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-summer-transfer-target-now-wanted-by-3-champions-league-clubs-including-psg/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-29T13:35:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic summer transfer target Quentin Merlin is now attracting the attention of some of European football’s biggest clubs, according to a new report coming out...
The post £7m Celtic target now wanted by 3 Champions League clubs appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In-form £1 million midfielder unsure about Celtic return]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45208</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/29/form-midfielder-unsure-celtic-return/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-29T13:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a lot of players on their books at the moment and yet, it does not feel like they have genuine quality when it comes to squad depth. That has been clear for all to see in the previous two matches, against Atletico Madrid and Hibernian. Brendan Rodgers’ substitutions faced a lot of criticism […]
In-form £1 million midfielder unsure about Celtic return - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JOHNSTON KO BLOW]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113614</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/johnston-ko-blow/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-29T10:33:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC will almost certainly be without Alistair Johnston for the Premiership match against St Mirren at Parkhead on Wednesday. The Canadian World Cup right-back had to be removed from the action in the 26th minute with suspected concussion during the goalless draw with Hibs at Easter Road yesterday. Johnston was in direct line of a [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Be careful what you wish for]]></title>
        <id>https://celticunderground.net/?p=6685</id>
        <link href="http://celticunderground.net/be-careful-what-you-wish-for-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-29T10:11:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scottish football is ripe for English Elite Club acquisition. The issue for us is, would the added competition here be a detriment or a benefit, and would the long-term benefits of us being allowed multi-cloud ownership overseas outweigh any challenge we may face by having a greater competition to a domestic dominance here?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harry Brady</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Lennoxtown chats that have helped bring Celtic player back from the brink]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179066</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-lennoxtown-chats-that-have-helped-bring-liam-scales-back-from-the-celtic-brink/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-29T09:56:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liam Scales’ rise at Celtic this season has been fantastic to watch for all sorts of reasons. Firstly, it’s just heartwarming to see a player...
The post The Lennoxtown chats that have helped bring Celtic player back from the brink appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["No ceiling"; Diego Simeone's former assistant blown away by Celtic summer signing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179058</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/no-ceiling-luis-palmas-former-boss-thinks-he-has-already-been-improved-by-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-29T08:59:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A former manager of Luis Palma, German Burgos, believes the sky is the limit for him at Celtic. Like everyone else, Burgos has been impressed...
The post "No ceiling"; Diego Simeone's former assistant blown away by Celtic summer signing appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘A GOOD POINT,’ McGREGOR’S POSITIVE SPIN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113590</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/a-good-point-mcgregors-positive-spin/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-29T08:53:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CALLUM McGREGOR reckons the disappointing scoreless stalemate against Hibs could be a point WON and not two dropped when the prizes are being handed out at the end of the campaign. Celtic have been to Pittodrie, Ibrox and Tynecastle already this term and emerged victorious in all three encounters on dangerous territory. That impressive sequence [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Dalglish labels £1.5m Celtic deal 'an absolute steal'; urges 18-month transfer plan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179053</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kenny-dalglish-labels-1-5m-celtic-deal-an-absolute-steal-as-he-urges-18-month-transfer-plan/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-29T08:28:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Dalglish is hoping that Celtic can retain the core of their team and best players for the next 18 months, suggesting it could lead...
The post Kenny Dalglish labels £1.5m Celtic deal 'an absolute steal'; urges 18-month transfer plan appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘TOO SLOW,’ RODGERS AIMS TO HIT FAST FORWARD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113574</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/too-slow-rodgers-aims-to-hit-fast-forward/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-29T07:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS will make sure Celtic are up to speed when they take on St Mirren at Parkhead on Wednesday evening. The Hoops boss watched a second blankety-blank performance from the champions as they struggled through a drab scoreless stalemate against Hibs at Easter Road yesterday. It was the identical scoreline as the outcome of another [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic squad depth issue after Hibs draw]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=179046</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-addresses-celtic-squad-depth-issue-after-hibs-draw/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-29T07:51:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has reiterated that, like any manager, he wants his squad to be stronger but has refused to point the finger at the bench...
The post Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic squad depth issue after Hibs draw appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>