<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2022-07-18T18:26:41.237Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Turkish Side Want Celtic Outcast – Report]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/turkish-side-want-celtic-outcast-report/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/turkish-side-want-celtic-outcast-report/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T17:56:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Turkish side Trabzonspor is being credited with a major interest in Celtic outcast Christopher Jullien ahead of the new season. Record Sport claim the Turkish side is looking into a move for the French defender who looks set to make his Parkhead exit sooner rather than later. Chris looked all set to move out to […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic&#039;s global outlook now paying off for the rest of Scottish football]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-global-outlook-now-paying-off-for-the-rest-of-scottish-football/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-global-outlook-now-paying-off-for-the-rest-of-scottish-football/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SPFL have signed a new TV deal with Japanese streaming company SPOTV Japan for the coming season, which plans to emphasise Celtic matches, it was announced over the weekend. SPOTV also hold Japanese rights to the English Premier League and Major League Baseball, with the Scottish Premiership now added to an increasingly robust portfolio. ...
The post Celtic&#039;s global outlook now paying off for the rest of Scottish football appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo: North Curve Concourse Given A Brilliant New Paint Job]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/photo-north-curve-concourse-given-a-brilliant-new-paint-job/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/photo-north-curve-concourse-given-a-brilliant-new-paint-job/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T17:39:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The North Curve standing section at Celtic Park has been given more than a lick of paint this summer as the Green Brigade have been busy decorating the area ahead of the new season. An artistic nod was given to refugees, amid the ongoing Rwanda scandal at present and the arrival of many displaced from Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keevin’s Goram Piece Reeked Of Attitudes Scotland Should Have Left Behind.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/keevins-goram-piece-reeked-of-attitudes-scotland-should-have-left-behind/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/keevins-goram-piece-reeked-of-attitudes-scotland-should-have-left-behind/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T16:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This time last year, Hugh Keevins was forced to make a grovelling apology for utterly idiotic remarks he uttered in the aftermath of Kyogo being racially abused by Ibrox fans. His comment was that things are worse on that front than they were 60 years ago when the issue was “virtually non-existent.” He was slammed […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nohan Kenneh in Hibs transfer admission as Easter Road recruit eyes up Rangers and Celtic in European dream - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEFguFf0FVnGjZCmguUZnUDYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/nohan-kenneh-hibs-transfer-admission-27512864"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T16:14:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nohan Kenneh in Hibs transfer admission as Easter Road recruit eyes up Rangers and Celtic in European dream  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Pirie’s Piece On Ange And Mooy Is Pathetic Anti-Celtic Stirring For The Sake Of It.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/mark-piries-piece-on-ange-and-mooy-is-pathetic-anti-celtic-stirring-for-the-sake-of-it/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/mark-piries-piece-on-ange-and-mooy-is-pathetic-anti-celtic-stirring-for-the-sake-of-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T15:33:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What a dire writer is Mark Pirie of The Daily Record. His article today, dredging up a five year old story, about how Aaron Mooy and Ange fell out over the latter subbing the former whilst manager of Australia is barrel scrapped gunk. It is gossip not news. “Aaron Mooy’s Celtic transfer olive branch as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic Hero Admits He Turned Down Arsenal to Stay at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/former-celtic-hero-admits-he-turned-down-arsenal-to-stay-at-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/former-celtic-hero-admits-he-turned-down-arsenal-to-stay-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T15:32:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC are heading to Poland on Wednesday to play in Artur Boruc’s farewell match against Legia Warsaw. Once upon a time, the hoops signed Artur from the Polish club. Under Gordon Strachan, Artur was a stalwart of the Celtic team. The goalkeeper was fantastic and his eccentric personality also endeared him to supporters. As he […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linfield boss David Healy makes "front foot" vow ahead of daunting date with Celtic's conquerors - Belfast Live]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEPizJLtjSotyuOEgnFrKNMcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowpM37CjCKx_QCMJXO0wU</id>
        <link href="https://www.belfastlive.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/linfield-boss-david-healy-makes-24521974"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T15:22:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linfield boss David Healy makes "front foot" vow ahead of daunting date with Celtic's conquerors  Belfast Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James Forrest praises "under the radar" Celtic teammate who is set to shine this season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/match/james-forrest-praises-under-the-radar-celtic-teammate-who-is-set-to-shine-this-season/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/james-forrest-praises-under-the-radar-celtic-teammate-who-is-set-to-shine-this-season/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T15:10:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Forrest was on media duties at Celtic Park today after the squad’s open training session in front of supporters. Season ticket holders got the opportunity to see Ange Postecoglou and his staff put the players through their pre-season paces ahead of a trip to Legia Warsaw. Forrest was asked about competition for places and ...
The post James Forrest praises "under the radar" Celtic teammate who is set to shine this season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James Forrest praises “under the radar” Celtic teammate who is set to shine this season - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEAUxEBGWWFxNHsl_aiJsxuMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMI7NpgY</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/james-forrest-praises-under-the-radar-celtic-teammate-who-is-set-to-shine-this-season/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T15:10:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Forrest praises “under the radar” Celtic teammate who is set to shine this season  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James Forrest hails Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou's high expectations as winger 'buzzing' for Champions League - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEOzKC7dCis383YPyOmO-NQ8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/james-forrest-hails-celtic-boss-27512084"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T15:08:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Forrest hails Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou's high expectations as winger 'buzzing' for Champions League  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fausto Vera drops Celtic transfer clue as in demand star erases his socials amid Argentinos Juniors absence - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>1496351407</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/fausto-vera-drops-celtic-transfer-27511612"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T14:33:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fausto Vera drops Celtic transfer clue as in demand star erases his socials amid Argentinos Juniors absence  Daily Record
Celtic have chance to sign Barcelona midfield maestro  The Celtic Bhoys
The next candidate for Celtic departure after pleasing Tuesday announcement  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News
Postecoglou Plays It Coy On The Rumoured Celtic Target: Why The Manager Must Make The Call  The 4th Official
View Full coverage on Google News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The second signing – Chelsea’s Levi Colwill could be our man]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/the-second-signing-chelseas-levi-colwill-could-be-our-man/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/the-second-signing-chelseas-levi-colwill-could-be-our-man/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T14:19:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With excitement building up surrounding the possible signing of Australian international Aaron Mooy, it is also worth remembering Ange Postecoglou hinted heavily that two signings may arrive at the club this week, as Paul Gillespie informed us in The Celtic Star just yesterday. With Mooy looking like the midfielder Postecoglou was looking to target, and Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free agent Aaron Mooy edges out PSG youngster Edouard Michut for now]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/free-agent-aaron-mooy-edges-out-psg-youngster-edouard-michut-for-now/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/free-agent-aaron-mooy-edges-out-psg-youngster-edouard-michut-for-now/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T14:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It may seem a strange decision to choose between the 31-year-old in the twilight of their career and the up-and-coming PSG starlet, but according to Scottish Sun Football editor Derek McGregor that was the choice Ange Postecoglou made when picking Aaron Mooy over Edouard Michut.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time For Celtic’s CEO TO Step Up And Stop Being The Invisible Man.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/time-for-celtics-ceo-to-step-up-and-stop-being-the-invisible-man/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/time-for-celtics-ceo-to-step-up-and-stop-being-the-invisible-man/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T13:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The news today that Michael Nicholson has been “voted” onto the SPFL board is interesting, but not surprising. There was no real election here. Due to a grubby, scandalous backstage deal our club and the one at Ibrox swap places on that board every couple of years, a seedy practice the rest of the game […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The clubs Aaron Mooy is turning down to sign for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/the-clubs-aaron-mooy-is-turning-down-to-sign-for-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/the-clubs-aaron-mooy-is-turning-down-to-sign-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy is widely expected to sign for Celtic this week, with a deal even potentially being announced as early as today. Multiple outlets and journalists, including Mike McGrath at The Telegraph, Derek McGregor at The Scottish Sun, Mark Hendry at Football Scotland and Fabrizio Romano, are all reporting that the move is likely following ...
The post The clubs Aaron Mooy is turning down to sign for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SPFL roles for Celtic and Hibs chief executives in league boardroom re-shuffle]]></title>
        <id>3772391</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/spfl-roles-for-celtic-and-hibs-chief-executives-in-league-boardroom-re-shuffle-3772391"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T12:47:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Hibs chief executives will sit on the new-look board of the SPFL following the recent re-shuffle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Oliver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calvin Bassey is kicking off Rangers megabucks transfer era that will leave Celtic reeling - Hotline - Sports Hotline - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEMBZ4FF4AQLgV-yyA2DTeM0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/calvin-bassey-kicking-rangers-megabucks-27510068"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T12:43:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Calvin Bassey is kicking off Rangers megabucks transfer era that will leave Celtic reeling - Hotline - Sports Hotline  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Nicholson Replaces Ibrox Chief on SPFL Board]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/michael-nicholson-replaces-ibrox-chief-on-spfl-board/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/michael-nicholson-replaces-ibrox-chief-on-spfl-board/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T12:39:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S CHIEF EXECUTIVE Michael Nicholson has been appointed to the SPFL board this afternoon, replacing Ibrox chief Stewart Robertson. The SPFL board for the new season has been appointed this afternoon and here is the full run down: Michael Nicholson, Ron Gordon, James MacDonald, Les Gray, Graeme Mathie, Alastair Donald and Paul Hetherington The board […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Nicholson replaces Rangers MD Stewart Robertson on SPFL board as Celtic chief leads shake up - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEMIAGhs3g1qUSY0E54_iDYgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/michael-nicholson-replaces-rangers-md-27510136"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T12:21:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Nicholson replaces Rangers MD Stewart Robertson on SPFL board as Celtic chief leads shake up  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Chief Executive Michael Nicholson appointed to SPFL board]]></title>
        <id>990bf6e65c312dd2bba10c06c742377d</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20286639.celtic-chief-executive-michael-nicholson-appointed-spfl-board/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T12:16:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE 42 member clubs of the Scottish Professional Football League have today elected the seven club representatives who will serve on the SPFL Board for the forthcoming season at the league’s Annual General Meeting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Injury Boost]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-injury-boost/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-injury-boost/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T11:39:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC got their open training day underway at Celtic Park on a very hot Monday afternoon in Glasgow. The club had promised season tickets holders over a yer ago the even would take place as an extra thank you for loyalty during the pandemic season. They came good on the promise on Monday as a […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic inspired Union Bhoys nickname as Rangers prepare for red-hot welcome from Saint-Gilloise ultras - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEANNI263-mh4zw0VqghR848qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPLfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/celtic-inspired-union-bhoys-nickname-24518841"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T11:17:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic inspired Union Bhoys nickname as Rangers prepare for red-hot welcome from Saint-Gilloise ultras  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Joseph drops Celtic transfer claim as Hoops eye up move for &#039;top class&#039; 53-cap stalwart]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-transfer-talks-aaron-mooy-over-summer-move-transfer-ange-rogic-spl/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-transfer-talks-aaron-mooy-over-summer-move-transfer-ange-rogic-spl/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T11:10:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are ‘in talks’ with free agent Aaron Mooy over a move to Parkhead in the summer transfer window, according to reliable journalist Anthony Joseph. The Lowdown: Mooy without a club The 31-year-old made a name for himself at Huddersfield Town, helping them to reach the Premier League, before moving to Shanghai Port in 2020 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saint Gilloise Celtic link explained as Union Bhoys gear up for Rangers Champions League clash - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEDgv5bdKzWq6y1X9V4PqABEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/saint-galloise-celtic-link-explained-27508995"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T11:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Saint Gilloise Celtic link explained as Union Bhoys gear up for Rangers Champions League clash  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mooy feels like a pivotal decision for season ahead]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/mooy-feels-like-a-pivotal-decision-for-season-ahead/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/mooy-feels-like-a-pivotal-decision-for-season-ahead/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T11:04:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My knowledge of Chinese football since 1979 is limited, and I don’t watch a lot of Brighton or Huddersfield, so I’ll need to bow to Ange Postecoglou’s judgement when it comes to Australian international midfielder, Aaron Mooy. Mooy was a mainstay in the Huddersfield team that won promotion to the English Premier League, stayed there, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Waiter – a new nickname for Josip Juranovic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/the-waiter-a-new-nickname-for-josip-juranovic/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/the-waiter-a-new-nickname-for-josip-juranovic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T11:02:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who Knows – perhaps the Daily Record is trying to make amends for playing fast and loose with a previous interpretation of Josip Juranovic’s words as was highlighted over the weekend by Joe McHugh at Video Celts, but whatever the reason today has seen the Record produce an article altogether more positive when it comes Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stoke City take on Celtic in double header - Stoke-on-Trent Live]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEOB64RUAoEoszNy37Po1McAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow6L2hCTDb05YCMNzZkAM</id>
        <link href="https://www.stokesentinel.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/stoke-city-celtic-pre-season-7345766"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T10:58:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stoke City take on Celtic in double header  Stoke-on-Trent Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy for Celtic could well be two players for the price of one]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/aaron-mooy-for-celtic-could-well-be-two-players-for-the-price-of-one/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/aaron-mooy-for-celtic-could-well-be-two-players-for-the-price-of-one/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T10:35:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is there really anyone out there with any doubts regarding Celtic signing Aaron Mooy? If there is, there is little to worry about and much more to delight in. Okay let’s get the limited negatives out the way. He doesn’t have pace over distance, and probably lacks that burst of acceleration, but when you can Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Josip Juranovic Talks Family, Football and Celtic Fans]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/josip-juranovic-talks-family-football-and-celtic-fans/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/josip-juranovic-talks-family-football-and-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T09:31:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOSIP JURANOVIC has been talking about Celtic’s potential and their inclusion in the Champions League this season. The Croatian revealed he knew all about Celtic and their European exploits before joining the club and he wants to make his own lasting memories on those crazy nights at Celtic Park. Josip told SunSport: “We all know […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy Might Not Be The Universal Choice, But For Celtic He’s The Right One.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/blogs/aaron-mooy-might-not-be-the-universal-choice-but-for-celtic-hes-the-right-one/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/blogs/aaron-mooy-might-not-be-the-universal-choice-but-for-celtic-hes-the-right-one/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T09:30:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[About a fortnight ago, I wrote about the prospect of this club moving for Jordan Larsson and Aaron Mooy. I thought Mooy was the more likely of the two and that there was probably a deal to be done. I wasn’t in the least bit surprised last night when it was his name who emerged […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Rogic’s Aaron Mooy Comments Come to Light]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/tom-rogics-aaron-mooy-comments-come-to-light/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/tom-rogics-aaron-mooy-comments-come-to-light/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T09:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic’s pursuit of Aaron Mooy looks set to end in success, a quote from ex-Celtic midfielder Tom Rogic has come to light. The Hoops Icon left the club this summer after ten years of brilliant service where he helped the bhoys make history. Tom has played with a lot of great footballers in his […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maeda running on empty and the reason he doesn’t watch football on TV]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/maeda-running-on-empty-and-the-reason-he-doesnt-watch-football-on-tv/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/maeda-running-on-empty-and-the-reason-he-doesnt-watch-football-on-tv/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T08:47:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gradually Daizen Maeda is building up towards full fitness after just two weeks break after a season and a half of football in the J-League then immediately after it’s conclusion in the Scottish Premiership for the second half of last season. That was then followed by an international call-up for Japan so his long run Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic learning lessons as Aaron Mooy contract factor sweetens the deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-learning-lessons-as-aaron-mooy-contract-details-sweeten-the-deal/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-learning-lessons-as-aaron-mooy-contract-details-sweeten-the-deal/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ll have heard by now that Aaron Mooy is on the brink of joining Celtic and reuniting with his former national team boss Ange Postecoglou. As reported by multiple outlets, Mooy will become the Bhoys’ latest summer signing as early as today after talks progressed between the two parties over the weekend. A further update ...
The post Celtic learning lessons as Aaron Mooy contract factor sweetens the deal appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou’s Major Transfer Decision]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/ange-postecoglous-major-transfer-decision/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/ange-postecoglous-major-transfer-decision/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T08:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECGOLOU has been given a lot more rope than many other Celtic managers when it comes to player recruitment. The Hoops gaffer’s involvement in the recruitment last season resulted in a double winning season. He has earned the right to be trusted when it comes to deals. Twitter can give you a gauge of […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I’M WORKING WITH MY TEMPO,’ BHOY RACER MAEDA’S WARNING]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/im-working-with-my-tempo-bhoy-racer-maedas-warning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/im-working-with-my-tempo-bhoy-racer-maedas-warning/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T08:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAIZEN MAEDA certainly hit the ground running in his Celtic career. The Japan international striker scored within four minutes of his Hoops debut as Ange Postecoglou’s side beat Hibs 2-0 at Parkhead on January 17. Maeda had arrived on Hogmanay as part of the ambitious triple swoop on the J-League with midfielders Reo Hatate and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic set to sign ex-St Mirren star - one-time £8million recruit could be Tom Rogic replacement]]></title>
        <id>3771681</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-set-to-sign-ex-st-mirren-star-one-time-ps8million-recruit-could-be-tom-rogic-replacement-3771681"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T08:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are understood to be closing in on a deal for former St Mirren midfielder Aaron Mooy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy closing in on Celtic move after turning down English Championship interest]]></title>
        <id>2ace477e5e82104c516b28d14c617436</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20285664.aaron-mooy-closing-celtic-move-turning-english-championship-interest/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T07:34:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AARON MOOY is closing in on a move to Celtic after turning down options in the English Championship.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Aaron Mooy. Ange Postecoglou. Harry Kewell. Massive,’ Optus Sport]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/aaron-mooy-ange-postecoglou-harry-kewell-massive-optus-sport/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/aaron-mooy-ange-postecoglou-harry-kewell-massive-optus-sport/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T07:25:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The news that Ange Postecoglou is about to sign Australian international midfielder Aaron Mooy on a free transfer after his departure from Chinese club Shanghai Port – where he was on huge money incidentally – will deliver on half of the promise that the Celtic manager made on Saturday afternoon after the 2-2 draw with Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: BIG JOCK v THE DOC: EVAN WILLIAMS REVEALS ALL (Part Four)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-big-jock-v-the-doc-evan-williams-reveals-all-part-four/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-big-jock-v-the-doc-evan-williams-reveals-all-part-four/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T07:14:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EVAN WILLIAMS was a worthy successor to the legendary Ronnie Simpson at Celtic after signing for his boyhood favourites in October 1969. However, the keeper, who celebrated his 79th birthday last week, did not emulate the achievements of the veteran shotsopper with the Scotland international team. Simpson made his debut at the highest level at [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda Makes Unusual Champions League Admission]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/daizen-maeda-makes-unusual-champions-league-admission/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/daizen-maeda-makes-unusual-champions-league-admission/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T07:13:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda has revealed he has never watched a Champions League game as he gets prepared to take the plunge in the competition. Celtic won the league last season, earning the right to be in the elite European competition. Daizen came into the club in January and made a big difference to Celtic’s title tilt. […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch ex-Celtic star Karamoko Dembele score first goal and last minute winner for Stade Brestois 29 - Glasgow Live]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEL1vyo5msNzlugfshW2dLRwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow96D9CjDOy_QCMPvp0wU</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowlive.co.uk/sport/watch-ex-celtic-star-karamoko-24516039"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T07:08:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Watch ex-Celtic star Karamoko Dembele score first goal and last minute winner for Stade Brestois 29  Glasgow Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: NEW-LOOK CELTIC – AND MISSING OUT ON LENNY: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Seven)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-new-look-celtic-and-missing-out-on-lenny-the-tommy-burns-story-part-seven/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-new-look-celtic-and-missing-out-on-lenny-the-tommy-burns-story-part-seven/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T06:12:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS celebrated his return to Celtic as manager on July 12 1994 by winning the Scottish Cup with the club’s 1-0 win over Airdrie. The league title, though, was the iconic Celt’s main target as he prepared for his second term in charge of the team that was always closest to his heart. In [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEW BHOY MOOY SEALS DEAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/new-bhoy-mooy-seals-deal/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/new-bhoy-mooy-seals-deal/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T05:28:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AARON MOOY will seal a dream move to Celtic this week. The Australian midfielder will join his former international manager Ange Postecoglou at the champions after being released from his contract at Shanghai Port. The 31-year-old former Huddersfield and Brighton star, who had a two-year spell in Scotland with St Mirren after joining in 2012, and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer news LIVE as Celtic and Rangers plus Aberdeen, Hearts and Hibs eye signings - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CBMibmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLXRyYW5zZmVyLW5ld3MvdHJhbnNmZXItbmV3cy1saXZlLWNlbHRpYy1yYW5nZXJzLTI3NTA1NzE20gFyaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZGFpbHlyZWNvcmQuY28udWsvc3BvcnQvZm9vdGJhbGwvZm9vdGJhbGwtdHJhbnNmZXItbmV3cy90cmFuc2Zlci1uZXdzLWxpdmUtY2VsdGljLXJhbmdlcnMtMjc1MDU3MTYuYW1w</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-transfer-news/transfer-news-live-celtic-rangers-27505716"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T05:25:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer news LIVE as Celtic and Rangers plus Aberdeen, Hearts and Hibs eye signings  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy’s Celtic Contract; Transfer Latest]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/aaron-mooys-celtic-contract-transfer-latest/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/aaron-mooys-celtic-contract-transfer-latest/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Sunday evening, Celtic transfer talk burst into life with the news the club were closing in on a deal for Australian midfielder Aaron Mooy. The former Premier League midfielder ripped up his contract with Shanghai Port earlier this year and has been mulling over his options for quite some time. Mooy and the current […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda sets Celtic Champions League targets as he reveals he swerved showpiece final for baseball - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEPZnvTixEhwveEpNNTcyo-0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/daizen-maeda-sets-celtic-champions-27503973"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda sets Celtic Champions League targets as he reveals he swerved showpiece final for baseball  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Calvin Bassey transfer cash give Rangers boss Gio van Bronckhorst greater spending power? Monday Jury - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEANr7W9Q3VkXHw_kDWF_AAcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/calvin-bassey-cash-give-rangers-27502474"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will Calvin Bassey transfer cash give Rangers boss Gio van Bronckhorst greater spending power? Monday Jury  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mooy set for Celtic // Blackburn reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.jerseydoesntshrink.com/2022/7/17/23266911/mooy-set-for-celtic-blackburn-reaction</id>
        <link href="https://www.jerseydoesntshrink.com/2022/7/17/23266911/mooy-set-for-celtic-blackburn-reaction"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T22:57:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Matthew Ashton - AMA/Getty Images
  

 Many have said it should happen, and probably would have at some point, now it’s practically confirmed - Aaron Mooy is all but set to sign for Celtic. 


Celtic are set to sign Aaron Mooy on free transfer. Full agreement in place, been told contract will be valid until June 2023 with an option to extend for further season. ⚪️  #CelticFC Deal will be completed this week after he left Shanghai. pic.twitter.com/9FqfQpkIrK— Fabrizio Romano (@FabrizioRomano) July 17, 2022



The tap in merchant of confirmed transfers has tweeted it, and we should expect to see Mooy confirmed by the club in the next few days.
We’ll have more of an opinion on Mooy on the podcast as well and discuss it thoroughly rather than shooting at this time on a Sunday night when rational emotions are nowhere to be seen!
We’re sure 67HailHail will have one of the Aussie pundits on to chat about him too.
And speaking of 67HailHail, there was a reaction to the 2-2 draw with Blackburn at the weekend: 

And if you missed the game on Saturday, here’s the highlights:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On This Day: Wins over Sarajevo, Cliftonville and QPR]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/on-this-day-wins-over-sarajevo-cliftonville-and-qpr/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/on-this-day-wins-over-sarajevo-cliftonville-and-qpr/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T22:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On This Day, Celtic have recorded two Champions League Qualifier wins as well as a pre-season friendly victory over London side QPR. In 2019, Neil Lennon, having been appointed Celtic manager for a second time, saw out the second leg of the Champions League First Round Qualifying against FK Sarajevo at Parkhead. Ryan Christie opened Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano’s Mooy update, contract until 2023 with one year option]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/fabrizio-romanos-mooy-update-contract-until-2023-with-one-year-option/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/fabrizio-romanos-mooy-update-contract-until-2023-with-one-year-option/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T22:38:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano has updated Celtic supporters in relation to the club’s pursuit of Aaron Mooy. The 31-year-old midfielder is a free agent following his departure from Shanghai Port earlier this summer. The Italian journalist and transfer specialist has taken to Twitter to state that the Scottish Champions are set to seal a deal to sign Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy Closing in on ‘Dream Move’ to Celtic – Report]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/aaron-mooy-closing-in-on-dream-move-to-celtic-report/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/aaron-mooy-closing-in-on-dream-move-to-celtic-report/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T21:38:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SKY SPORTS is claiming tonight Celtic are now in talks with Australian midfielder Aaron Mooy over a deal to bring him to the Scottish Champions. Anthony Joseph has wrote on Sunday evening the Hoops are in talks with the former English Premier League star after he ripped up his contract with Shanghai Port. Joseph wrote: […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy to 'secure' Celtic transfer as Ange Postecoglou talks progress with in demand free agent - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEPm1TxrnR00fXrwyko8zafQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/aaron-mooy-secure-celtic-transfer-27505215"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T21:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy to 'secure' Celtic transfer as Ange Postecoglou talks progress with in demand free agent  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer breakthrough as Aaron Mooy set to sign for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/transfer-breakthrough-as-aaron-mooy-set-to-sign-for-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/transfer-breakthrough-as-aaron-mooy-set-to-sign-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T21:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic look set to seal the signing of Aaron Mooy as Ange Postecoglou beefs up his options in the centre of the park. According to Mike McGrath, Daily Telegraph’s Football reporter, Mooy will disappoint a number of Championship teams to become Celtic’s fifth signing of the summer. The 31-year-old is a free agent after leaving Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon target set to seal move to Rangers, Celtic have moved on]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/neil-lennon-target-set-to-seal-move-to-rangers-celtic-have-moved-on/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/neil-lennon-target-set-to-seal-move-to-rangers-celtic-have-moved-on/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T20:48:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic target Ben Davies looks set to seal a move to Rangers from Liverpool. The Merseyside club signed Davies in January 2021 for £2m and have struck an impressive £3m deal, with another £1m in add-ons. The Englishman was a target for Neil Lennon as his second spell in charge as manager came to Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fausto Vera to Celtic transfer sticking point as agent breaks next move silence - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEIVrcATbUyUSm5G2N8t_F-IqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/fausto-vera-celtic-transfer-sticking-27504893"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T20:08:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fausto Vera to Celtic transfer sticking point as agent breaks next move silence  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A year of Celtic brilliance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/a-year-of-kyogo-furuhashi-his-top-5-celtic-moments/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/a-year-of-kyogo-furuhashi-his-top-5-celtic-moments/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans awoke to a pleasant surprise on the morning of July 16th 2021, with news that the club had signed the J-League’s then top-scorer Kyogo Furuhashi from Vissel Kobe. Though initially unknown to most if not all Celtic fans, 20 goals in 33 appearances marked a stellar return from an injury-plagued first season. Fans ...
The post A year of Celtic brilliance appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player completed exit after honest Ange Postecoglou chat - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>CAIiELEB6qf22Ci-UwnVUM4dMkIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4KKJCzCv9JoDMICkoAY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2022/07/17/celtic-player-ange-postecoglou-chat/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T18:03:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player completed exit after honest Ange Postecoglou chat  The Celtic Bhoys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic&#039;s current strongest Day 1 starting XI with new signings imminent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/celtics-current-strongest-day-1-starting-xi-with-new-signings-imminent/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/celtics-current-strongest-day-1-starting-xi-with-new-signings-imminent/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T17:40:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s transfer window thus far has been about reinforcing, rather than improving last season league title-winning starting XI. With the permanent signings of Cameron Carter-Vickers, Alexandro Bernabei, Benjamin Siegrist and Jota, Celtic have secured two of last season’s stars on long-term deals and recruited badly-needed backups in two key positions, but manager Ange Postecoglou expects ...
The post Celtic&#039;s current strongest Day 1 starting XI with new signings imminent appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero Chris Sutton relishing "frightening prospect" in store for Scottish football]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-hero-chris-sutton-relishing-frightening-prospect-in-store-for-scottish-football/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-hero-chris-sutton-relishing-frightening-prospect-in-store-for-scottish-football/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic hero Chris Sutton knows a thing or two about the striking position, becoming an icon for supporters as a forward during the Martin O’Neill era. Sutton struck up a famous partnership with Henrik Larsson during that time, often providing the physical presence and applying the finishing touch that dovetailed perfectly with the Swedish ...
The post Celtic hero Chris Sutton relishing "frightening prospect" in store for Scottish football appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I’m excited"; Pundit&#039;s all out Ange Celtic prediction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/pundit-predicts-uncompromising-celtic-in-champions-league/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/pundit-predicts-uncompromising-celtic-in-champions-league/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic star Mark Wilson has backed manager Ange Postecoglou to stick to his philosophy for the forthcoming Champions League group stage campaign. Wilson played in the Champions League under Gordon Strachan, including the last time the club started the season without European qualifiers in 2008-09. Speaking to The Scotsman, Wilson said: “They are all ...
The post "I’m excited"; Pundit&#039;s all out Ange Celtic prediction appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What channel is Legia Warsaw vs Celtic? Live stream, TV and kick off details for Artur Boruc farewell friendly - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEPaAtnRt-byMHw6K2D8Hrl0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/what-channel-legia-warsaw-vs-27503550"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T15:45:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What channel is Legia Warsaw vs Celtic? Live stream, TV and kick off details for Artur Boruc farewell friendly  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Much improved star is the big winner of Celtic’s pre-season so far]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-big-winner-of-celtics-pre-season-so-far/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-big-winner-of-celtics-pre-season-so-far/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T15:41:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For many football players, the pre-season represents the chance for a reset, a the chance to wipe the slate clean for the coming season. Doubtlessly, there are some in Celtic’s team who likely have no future with the club, but one who has used this break to his advantage is David Turnbull. The 23-year-old missed ...
The post Much improved star is the big winner of Celtic’s pre-season so far appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic, The SPFL-Japanese TV Deal And The Dangers Posed By The Cinch Surrender.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/blogs/celtic-the-spfl-japanese-tv-deal-and-the-dangers-posed-by-the-cinch-surrender/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/blogs/celtic-the-spfl-japanese-tv-deal-and-the-dangers-posed-by-the-cinch-surrender/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T15:15:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is always great to get affirmation of that which every Celtic supporter knows; our club is the last remaining superpower in the game here. The club across the city might have stumbled on the “brilliant” transfer strategy of selling its best players (most other clubs in Europe figured this out ages ago, but they […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Sunday July 17: Lazing On A Sunday Afternoon]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=17832</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=17832"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T14:45:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s hot.   Damn hot.   In fact, it would be fair to say I’m sweating like an Ibrox director with the accounts open in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Rangers 5 Champions League opponents are faring in pre season as Union Saint-Gilloise make some noise - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEFz8GtYbWt8IZQqbA9yGehsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/how-rangers-5-champions-league-27502992"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T14:12:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Rangers 5 Champions League opponents are faring in pre season as Union Saint-Gilloise make some noise  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scots cops release pic of man linked to 'pyro' incident at Celtic Europa League game - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEAuG3HwxubWNCB6zLpSMAuUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/news/scottish-news/scots-cops-release-pic-man-27502964"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T14:06:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scots cops release pic of man linked to 'pyro' incident at Celtic Europa League game  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Loan move now needed for one of yesterday&#039;s Celtic performers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/bosun-lawals-celtic-future-and-the-next-steps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/bosun-lawals-celtic-future-and-the-next-steps/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T13:49:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s always difficult for young players to make a breakthrough at any club, but at Celtic, it can be especially troublesome. With the pressures of title races, trophy hunts and European ambitions always prioritised, the environment is harsh when getting the minutes needed to earn the trust of the coaching staff and supporters. Ultimately, it ...
The post Loan move now needed for one of yesterday&#039;s Celtic performers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Park police probe after pyro device thrown from stands onto pitch - Glasgow Live]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEPl09VstCmZRQZksa7yRW0MqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow96D9CjDOy_QCMPvp0wU</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowlive.co.uk/news/celtic-park-police-probe-after-24513561"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T13:47:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Park police probe after pyro device thrown from stands onto pitch  Glasgow Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O&#039;Riley addresses Celtic pre-season mistakes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/matt-oriley-addresses-celtic-pre-season-mistakes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/matt-oriley-addresses-celtic-pre-season-mistakes/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder Matt O’Riley isn’t shying away from some of the on-pitch errors being made by the team in pre-season but insists it’s all part of the process at this stage of the summer. Some slack Celtic play directly led to Blackburn Rovers’ opening goal in yesterday’s 2-2 draw at Paradise, following other mistakes made ...
The post Matt O&#039;Riley addresses Celtic pre-season mistakes appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[&#039;Update...&#039; - Anthony Joseph shares news on Celtic&#039;s move for Edouard Michut after info from PSG]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-anthony-joseph-edouard-michut-transfer-update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-anthony-joseph-edouard-michut-transfer-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T13:05:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports journalist Anthony Joseph has provided an update on reported Celtic transfer target Edouard Michut. The Lowdown: Celtic linked with Michut The Hoops have been busy this summer and have already made five permanent signings at a cost of just over £18m. Loan moves for Jota, Cameron Carter-Vickers and Daizen Maeda have been made […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why The Bassey Deal Won’t Fix Ibrox’s Long Term Financial Problems.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/why-the-bassey-deal-wont-fix-ibroxs-long-term-financial-problems/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/why-the-bassey-deal-wont-fix-ibroxs-long-term-financial-problems/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T12:33:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Dalglish thinks the powers-that-be at Ibrox are “heartbroken” at losing Calvin Bassey. I don’t know what planet he lives on at times, but it isn’t this one. Not only are the club across the city overjoyed at getting this deal done, but they’ve been pushing it since they lost the Europa League Final. That […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three games this week plus a few new signings says Natalie Ross]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/three-games-this-week-plus-a-few-new-signings-says-natalie-ross/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/three-games-this-week-plus-a-few-new-signings-says-natalie-ross/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T12:08:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Natalie Ross started her first match in 18 yesterday at a behind closed doors match against Southampton at Barrowfield, played ahead of Celtic’s pre-season friendly against Blackburn Rovers, nearby at Celtic Park. Ross, like Lisa Robertson who has returned to the club after a season on loan at Birmingham City, adds much needed experience and Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Games this week plus a few new signings says Natalie Ross - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CBMiWmh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vdGhyZWUtZ2FtZXMtdGhpcy13ZWVrLXBsdXMtYS1mZXctbmV3LXNpZ25pbmdzLXNheXMtbmF0YWxpZS1yb3NzL9IBXmh0dHBzOi8vdGhlY2VsdGljc3Rhci5jb20vdGhyZWUtZ2FtZXMtdGhpcy13ZWVrLXBsdXMtYS1mZXctbmV3LXNpZ25pbmdzLXNheXMtbmF0YWxpZS1yb3NzL2FtcC8</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/three-games-this-week-plus-a-few-new-signings-says-natalie-ross/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T12:08:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three Games this week plus a few new signings says Natalie Ross  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O’Riley Perfectly Sums Up Blackburn’s Embarrassing Display]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/matt-oriley-perfectly-sums-up-blackburns-embarrassing-display/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/matt-oriley-perfectly-sums-up-blackburns-embarrassing-display/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T11:48:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY echoed the sentiments of a lot of Celtic fans on Saturday, branding Blackburn a bit ‘nasty’ as the bhoys played out a 2-2 draw with the Championship side. Blackburn scored with their first attack, but it became very clear after that Celtic were the superior footballing side. Blackburn knew it and went about […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic 'at centre' of lucrative Asian TV deal as Scottish Premiership cash in on Japanese interest - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEMZEWag9msC0LHlyLe2F8lQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/celtic-at-centre-lucrative-asian-27502254"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T11:31:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic 'at centre' of lucrative Asian TV deal as Scottish Premiership cash in on Japanese interest  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HOW CELTIC MISSED OUT ON £50m MAN UTD TARGET]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/how-celtic-missed-out-on-50m-man-utd-target/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/how-celtic-missed-out-on-50m-man-utd-target/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T11:14:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic target Ivan Toney has been linked with a dramatic £50million move to Manchester United. Former Hoops boss Neil Lennon wanted the striker during his summer 2020 rebuild as the Parkhead club prepared for their assault on a historic tenth successive title. Toney had attracted attention of the club’s scouts with his goalscoring expolits [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calvin Bassey exit sparks Rangers fan belief as they warn Celtic to savour the Sydney Super Cup - Hotline - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEIU6bZGhQyN_BviS_s9U9q4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/calvin-bassey-exit-sparks-rangers-27501964"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T11:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Calvin Bassey exit sparks Rangers fan belief as they warn Celtic to savour the Sydney Super Cup - Hotline  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Deep down knew I wasn’t going to get a chance,” Ross Doohan on his Celtic exit]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/deep-down-knew-i-wasnt-going-to-get-a-chance-ross-doohan-on-his-celtic-exit/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/deep-down-knew-i-wasnt-going-to-get-a-chance-ross-doohan-on-his-celtic-exit/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T10:41:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Ross Doohan finally left Celtic earlier this month to sign a permanent deal with Tranmere Rovers, it brought to an end a long-term futile attempt for the 24 year old to finally break into the Celtic first team set-up. A Celtic Academy graduate, Doohan has been sent out on loan by the club on Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Park prices under the spotlight after support&#039;s Saturday return]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-park-prices-under-the-spotlight-after-supports-saturday-return/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-park-prices-under-the-spotlight-after-supports-saturday-return/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of food and drink available at Celtic Park has come under fresh scrutiny upon fans’ return to Paradise for the 2-2 draw against Blackburn Rovers yesterday. Celtic’s catering is provided by Sodexo Live who offer services to a number of events and stadia worldwide. As pointed out by Twitter user @dmmcluskey94, their updated ...
The post Celtic Park prices under the spotlight after support&#039;s Saturday return appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Park prices under the spotlight after support’s Saturday return - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEIHHhkurlG-z8Nm0UBloanAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMLbFpgY</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-park-prices-under-the-spotlight-after-supports-saturday-return/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Park prices under the spotlight after support’s Saturday return  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If Celtic Gets Ange Those Extra Players In, What Happens Elsewhere Won’t Matter.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/if-celtic-gets-ange-those-extra-players-in-what-happens-elsewhere-wont-matter/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/if-celtic-gets-ange-those-extra-players-in-what-happens-elsewhere-wont-matter/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T10:38:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the boss man, at the end of yesterday’s game, the next seven days will see tell the tale of the coming campaign. He expects to further signings this week. If Celtic delivers on that, then the final shape of this year’s team will have become clear to us, and there are good reasons […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers want defender who almost joined Celtic to replace Calvin Bassey at Ibrox]]></title>
        <id>3771319</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/rangers/rangers-want-defender-who-almost-joined-celtic-to-replace-calvin-bassey-at-ibrox-3771319"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T10:34:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liverpool's Ben Davies has emerged as a potential replacement for Calvin Bassey at Rangers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Elder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steven Gerrard salutes Ange Postecoglou's Celtic glory as ex Rangers boss sidesteps rivalry to praise rebuild - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEFZCFQzrr3r-A5thIJFLKqAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/steven-gerrard-salutes-ange-postecoglous-27501898"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T10:17:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steven Gerrard salutes Ange Postecoglou's Celtic glory as ex Rangers boss sidesteps rivalry to praise rebuild  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[24-year-old discusses the Postecoglou chat that sealed his Celtic exit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-academy-talent-on-the-ange-postecoglou-chat-that-sealed-his-celtic-exit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-academy-talent-on-the-ange-postecoglou-chat-that-sealed-his-celtic-exit/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A former Celtic youth academy product has spoken about the chat with Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou that ended his time at the club. 24-year-old Ross Doohan never made an appearance for Celtic’s first team, going out on seven loans to six different clubs since 2015, including Tranmere Rovers, with whom he signed permanently this month. ...
The post 24-year-old discusses the Postecoglou chat that sealed his Celtic exit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steven Gerrard shares Ange Postecoglou respect as former Rangers boss hails work of Celtic manager]]></title>
        <id>6b4a3a5167d5d15b410f007a563f9ec9</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20284848.steven-gerrard-shares-ange-postecoglou-respect-former-rangers-boss-hails-work-celtic-manager/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T09:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[STEVEN GERRARD has shared his classy respect for Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou after the pair went head to head in the Scottish Premiership.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou rebuffs specific Celtic midfield criticism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-rebuffs-specific-celtic-midfield-criticism/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-rebuffs-specific-celtic-midfield-criticism/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou has denied suggestions that the Scottish Champions are specifically looking to add physicality in midfield. He spoke after the Bhoys continued their pre-season preparations with 2-2 draw against Blackburn Rovers at Celtic Park yesterday, in which Sam Gallagher scored for the visitors scored after just 21 seconds. As reported by The ...
The post Ange Postecoglou rebuffs specific Celtic midfield criticism appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fausto Vera in transfer admission amid Celtic link as in-demand midfielder has trophies on his mind - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiELuAOblpBOwr8PYMWDy8BQ8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/fausto-vera-transfer-admission-amid-27501630"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T09:18:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fausto Vera in transfer admission amid Celtic link as in-demand midfielder has trophies on his mind  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Tony&#039;s boot was split in half"; Celtic hero doesn&#039;t miss with Blackburn comments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/tonys-boot-was-split-in-half-celtic-heros-brutal-blackburn-rovers-verdict/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/tonys-boot-was-split-in-half-celtic-heros-brutal-blackburn-rovers-verdict/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Football returned to Celtic Park yesterday as the Scottish Champions played out an often frenetic 2-2 draw with Blackburn Rovers. One Celtic player who was critical of Jon Dahl Tomasson’s side was Matt O’Riley, who played 73 minutes of Celtic’s first pre-season game, with teammates Liel Abada and Anthony Ralston in particular on the receiving ...
The post "Tony&#039;s boot was split in half"; Celtic hero doesn&#039;t miss with Blackburn comments appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Celtic star tipped for 'next level' is already primed for player of the season]]></title>
        <id>3771259</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/why-celtic-star-tipped-for-next-level-is-already-primed-for-player-of-the-season-3771259"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T08:59:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There was a slight lull at Celtic Park during the friendly with Blackburn Rovers. Then there wasn’t. In its place a roar of approval, of celebration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven days, two new signings, straight from the horses mouth]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/seven-days-two-new-signings-straight-from-the-horses-mouth/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/seven-days-two-new-signings-straight-from-the-horses-mouth/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T08:28:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amongst the post-match thoughts of the Celtic manager yesterday, one item of interest went slightly unnoticed in regards to recruitment plans whilst he was chewing the fat with the media . That is namely, that Ange is looking to bring in two more players within a seven day timescale as he put it to the Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘AMAZING,’ JOTA HAPPY TO BE BACK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/amazing-jota-happy-to-be-back/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/amazing-jota-happy-to-be-back/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T08:27:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FILIPE JOTA paraded his flashing skills in his first game at Parkhead as a permanent Celtic player in the 2-2 draw with Blackburn Rovers yesterday. The Portuguese flyer, who moved to the champions in a £6.5million switch from Benfica after last season’s impressive season-long loan, was outstanding in a competitive encounter against opponents who proved [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[O’RILEY SIDESWIPE AT ‘FIESTY’ AND ‘NASTY’ RIVALS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/oriley-sideswipe-at-fiesty-and-nasty-rivals/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/oriley-sideswipe-at-fiesty-and-nasty-rivals/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T07:58:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC midfielder Matt O’Riley picked up where he left off last season by sauntering through the 2-2 draw against Blackburn Rovers at Parkhead yesterday. The elegant playmaker performed for 72 minutes before being replaced by James McCarthy as manager Ange Postecoglou utilised his player pool in preparation for the competitive action kicking off a fortnight [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forfar decide against Leigh Griffiths move as ex-Celtic striker struggles]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/forfar-decide-against-leigh-griffiths-move-as-ex-celtic-striker-struggles/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/forfar-decide-against-leigh-griffiths-move-as-ex-celtic-striker-struggles/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T07:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker Leigh Griffiths is struggling to find a new club following his release from Falkirk back in May. The former Scotland Internationalist had been released by Celtic in January before sealing a deal until the end of the season with The Bairns. Unfortunately, he could not find the form to be rewarded with Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forfar decide against Leigh Griffiths move as ex-Celtic striker struggles - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEJmuUh9l6VQlRxvfmbhFycgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/forfar-decide-against-leigh-griffiths-move-as-ex-celtic-striker-struggles/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T07:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forfar decide against Leigh Griffiths move as ex-Celtic striker struggles  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic v Blackburn Rovers – Ange’s thoughts plus reaction from supporters]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-v-blackburn-rovers-anges-thoughts-plus-reaction-from-supporters/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-v-blackburn-rovers-anges-thoughts-plus-reaction-from-supporters/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T07:17:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what Ange Postecoglou had to say to Celtic TV after the 2-2 draw against Blackburn Rovers at Celtic Park yesterday afternoon. And we’ve included some supporter feedback to this interview to gauge the thoughts of the Celtic fans after the latest pre-season fixture and the first back at Paradise… Q: For a pre-season friendly Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: FACING THE IBROX FOES: EVAN WILLIAMS LOOKS BACK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-facing-the-ibrox-foes-evan-williams-looks-back/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-facing-the-ibrox-foes-evan-williams-looks-back/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T07:14:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EVAN WILLIAMS, who celebrated his 79th birthday on Friday, may have had his run-ins with Jock Stein, but Celtic’s legendary manager never hesitated in giving the keeper the nod to play in Old Firm encounters. The games against the club’s fiercest foes brought out the best in the netminder who recalled: “I played against Rangers [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steven Gerrard admits admiration for Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/steven-gerrard-admits-admiration-for-celtic-boss-ange-postecoglou/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/steven-gerrard-admits-admiration-for-celtic-boss-ange-postecoglou/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Rangers manager Steven Gerrard has expressed his admiration and respect for Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou. Gerrard left Ibrox for Villa in November last year, leaving Postecoglou’s juggernaut to kick on and win the League and League Cup, blowing Rangers away in the process. Speaking to Fox Sport as his Villa side tour Australia as Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: ‘UNBELIEVABLE’ CUP TRIUMPH: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Six)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-unbelievable-cup-triumph-the-tommy-burns-story-part-six/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-unbelievable-cup-triumph-the-tommy-burns-story-part-six/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T06:50:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS was just 90 minutes away from his first silverware in his debut season as Celtic manager after returning to the club on July 12 1994. The League Cup had been lost in a sensational penalty-kick shoot-out to Raith Rovers in November, the league was blown, but the Scottish Cup was tantalisingly close. In [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Johnston told to quit Celtic by McAvennie after new twist - Football Insider]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEFcFh0y1WKQAut3y6m2jukgqMwgEKioIACIQnJ4k3aT29tENAyPF0QESjSoUCAoiEJyeJN2k9vbRDQMjxdEBEo0w4IzKBg</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballinsider247.com/johnston-told-to-quit-celtic-by-mcavennie-after-new-twist/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T06:35:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Johnston told to quit Celtic by McAvennie after new twist  Football Insider]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[O’Riley on Blackburn: “They were feisty, a bit nasty and left a few on a few of us”]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/oriley-on-blackburn-they-were-feisty-a-bit-nasty-and-left-a-few-on-a-few-of-us/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/oriley-on-blackburn-they-were-feisty-a-bit-nasty-and-left-a-few-on-a-few-of-us/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T06:11:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After yesterday’s 2-2 draw with Blackburn Rovers Ange Postecoglou confirmed that he plans to sign two players probably this coming week as he gears his squad up for an intense fixture list of around 60 games starting with the Scottish Premiership opener against Aberdeen at the end of the month. “We’re definitely going to add Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Left a few on us' - Celtic star reckons 'feisty, nasty' friendly ideal preparation for Premiership return]]></title>
        <id>3771127</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/left-a-few-on-us-celtic-star-reckons-feisty-nasty-friendly-ideal-preparation-for-premiership-return-3771127"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Referee Kevin Clancy was likely not expecting to be so busy when appointed to oversee Celtic’s friendly with Blackburn Rovers. In the end, he had to reach for his yellow card on six occasions, while also having a quiet word with a few players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Karamoko Dembele Scores Last Gasp Winner for New Side]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/video-karamoko-dembele-scores-last-gasp-winner-for-new-side/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/video-karamoko-dembele-scores-last-gasp-winner-for-new-side/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T21:39:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KARAMOKO DEMBELE has endeared himself to his new side by bagging a last minute winner in a friendly on Saturday evening against FC Lorient. The former Celtic prodigy left Parkhead in the summer in pursuit of first team football. French side Brest signed the winger to a long term deal. Coming on as a second […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Karamoko Dembele Scores Last Gasp Winner for New Side - CeltsAreHere]]></title>
        <id>CBMiVWh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS92aWRlby1rYXJhbW9rby1kZW1iZWxlLXNjb3Jlcy1sYXN0LWdhc3Atd2lubmVyLWZvci1uZXctc2lkZS_SAVlodHRwczovL2NlbHRzYXJlaGVyZS5jb20vdmlkZW8ta2FyYW1va28tZGVtYmVsZS1zY29yZXMtbGFzdC1nYXNwLXdpbm5lci1mb3ItbmV3LXNpZGUvYW1wLw</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/video-karamoko-dembele-scores-last-gasp-winner-for-new-side/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T21:39:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Karamoko Dembele Scores Last Gasp Winner for New Side  CeltsAreHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic supporters outdo themselves with class support of new initiative]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/organisers-of-new-charitable-initiative-blown-away-by-celtic-supporters/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/organisers-of-new-charitable-initiative-blown-away-by-celtic-supporters/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T20:53:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organisers of a new foodbank donation initiative have been left “blown away” by the response of Celtic supporters today. Fans Supporting Foodbanks Scotland put out word earlier this week that they’d be taking donations opposite Celtic Park ahead of the Blackburn Rovers friendly. Co-founder Robert Foster was taken aback by the response, telling The Daily ...
The post Celtic supporters outdo themselves with class support of new initiative appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Organisers of new charitable initiative “blown away” by Celtic supporters - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CBMiaGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL25ld3Mvb3JnYW5pc2Vycy1vZi1uZXctY2hhcml0YWJsZS1pbml0aWF0aXZlLWJsb3duLWF3YXktYnktY2VsdGljLXN1cHBvcnRlcnMv0gFsaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuNjdoYWlsaGFpbC5jb20vbmV3cy9vcmdhbmlzZXJzLW9mLW5ldy1jaGFyaXRhYmxlLWluaXRpYXRpdmUtYmxvd24tYXdheS1ieS1jZWx0aWMtc3VwcG9ydGVycy8_YW1w</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/organisers-of-new-charitable-initiative-blown-away-by-celtic-supporters/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T20:53:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organisers of new charitable initiative “blown away” by Celtic supporters  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange could form “special” duo with Celtic bid for £2.1kp/w target, imagine him & CCV - opinion - msnNOW]]></title>
        <id>CBMipgFodHRwczovL3d3dy5tc24uY29tL2VuLWdiL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2FuZ2UtY291bGQtZm9ybS0lRTIlODAlOUNzcGVjaWFsJUUyJTgwJTlELWR1by13aXRoLWNlbHRpYy1iaWQtZm9yLSVDMiVBMzIxay1wLXctdGFyZ2V0LWltYWdpbmUtaGltLWFuZC1jY3Ytb3Bpbmlvbi9hci1BQVpFdUR10gEA</id>
        <link href="https://www.msn.com/en-gb/sport/football/ange-could-form-%E2%80%9Cspecial%E2%80%9D-duo-with-celtic-bid-for-%C2%A321k-p-w-target-imagine-him-and-ccv-opinion/ar-AAZEuDu"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T20:10:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange could form “special” duo with Celtic bid for £2.1kp/w target, imagine him & CCV - opinion  msnNOW]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange provides update on Celtic star who limped off vs Blackburn; 2 more concerns cleared up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-ange-postecoglou-clears-up-hatate-and-giakoumakis-situations-update-on-ralston-limp-off/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-ange-postecoglou-clears-up-hatate-and-giakoumakis-situations-update-on-ralston-limp-off/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T20:04:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has cleared up the status of Anthony Ralston, Reo Hatate and Giorgos Giakoumakis after Celtic’s 2-2 draw against Blackburn Rovers. Both Hatate and Giakoumakis were missing from the matchday squad, while Ralston limped off towards the end of the fixture. However, there’s nothing to worry about with any of them, with no long-term ...
The post Ange provides update on Celtic star who limped off vs Blackburn; 2 more concerns cleared up appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[&#039;Have had conversations...&#039; - Celtic could snap up &#039;excellent&#039; starlet as comments emerge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-hoops-have-had-conversations-with-dylan-reid/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-hoops-have-had-conversations-with-dylan-reid/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T18:15:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic ‘have had conversations’ with St Mirren midfielder Dylan Reid over a summer move to Parkhead, according to manager Stephen Robinson. The Lowdown: Reid linked with move The 17-year-old is considered an exciting young prospect in Scotland, having already made a name for himself at St Mirren, making three appearances in the Scottish Premiership last […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Celtic new boys Benjamin Siegrist and Alexandro Bernabei performed on home debuts]]></title>
        <id>3771123</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/how-celtic-new-boys-benjamin-siegrist-and-alexandro-bernabei-performed-on-home-debuts-3771123"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T18:13:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed non-competitive home debuts to summer signings Benjamin Siegrist and Alexandro Bernabei for the second half of the 2-2 friendly draw with Blackburn Rovers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steven Gerrard Breaks Silence on Ange Postecoglou’s Celtic Double Winning Season]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/steven-gerrard-breaks-silence-on-ange-postecoglous-celtic-double-winning-season/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/steven-gerrard-breaks-silence-on-ange-postecoglous-celtic-double-winning-season/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T18:10:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[STEVEN GERRARD is free to talk more openly since leaving the Ibrox bubble, so when asked about the Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou, he had nothing but praise for the Australian. The manager was speaking as Villa are in Australia for pre-season. It took Gerrard three seasons, a pandemic and football fans being locked out of […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic confirmed to be closing in on double signing - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEKFftxNa9oitrhyFIssH3XQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4KKJCzCv9JoDMICkoAY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2022/07/16/celtic-confirmed-closing-double-signing/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T18:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic confirmed to be closing in on double signing  The Celtic Bhoys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Of The Day: Celtic Fans In Belgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/photo-of-the-day-celtic-fans-in-belgrade/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/photo-of-the-day-celtic-fans-in-belgrade/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T18:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today’s photo of the day rewinds to September 1989 when Celtic fans travelled in good numbers to Mostar for the European Cup Winner’s Cup clash against Partizan Belgrade. 1,000 Celts made the trip to the neutral Bosnia & Herzegovina based venue (Gradski Stadium), where the match was held on the instruction of UEFA due to Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Of The Day: Celtic Fans In Belgrade - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEGWUm7GO6ImAYjj3SozZylEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/photo-of-the-day-celtic-fans-in-belgrade/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T18:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Of The Day: Celtic Fans In Belgrade  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou: &#039;We&#039;re set to sign two new players next week&#039;]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sportsmole.co.uk/football/celtic/transfer-talk/news/postecoglou-were-set-to-sign-two-new-players-next-week_490232.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.sportsmole.co.uk/football/celtic/transfer-talk/news/postecoglou-were-set-to-sign-two-new-players-next-week_490232.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T18:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou reveals that he will "definitely" add a couple more players to his squad this summer and expects new signings to be made some time next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Athletic’s Story On Celtic’s “Transfer Kitty Ceiling” Is Lurid Speculation With A Fishy Smell.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/the-athletics-story-on-celtics-transfer-kitty-ceiling-is-lurid-speculation-with-a-fishy-smell/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/the-athletics-story-on-celtics-transfer-kitty-ceiling-is-lurid-speculation-with-a-fishy-smell/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T17:31:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before I start, let me state that I’ve not read The Athletic’s article on Celtic’s transfer plans, only what part of them Joe McHugh at VideoCelts put in his excellent article on this earlier today. That boy does amazing work. I cannot praise him enough. But the article he’s talking about is simply not something […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Another Level; Ange Makes Exciting Celtic Decleration]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/another-level-ange-makes-exciting-celtic-decleration/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/another-level-ange-makes-exciting-celtic-decleration/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou didn’t hold back in his praise of Jota, his now full time winger. The Portuguese born player signed a long term deal with the club this summer after a successful loan spell where he helped the bhoys to a famous title win. During the Celtic vs Blackburn pre-season game at Celtic Park, the […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Dahl Tomasson’s Celtic Praise As He Talks Champions League]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/john-dahl-tomassons-celtic-praise-as-he-talks-champions-league/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/john-dahl-tomassons-celtic-praise-as-he-talks-champions-league/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T17:15:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blackburn boss John Dahl Tomasson is a famous name in football, mostly due to his impressive playing career at Feyenoord, AC Milan and the Danish national team. However, he is also well known for his credible spell as manager of Malmo between 2020 and 2021, where he won back to back Swedish titles and qualified Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Dahl Tomasson’s Celtic Praise As He Talks Champions League - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEKOMnB2jM3KXN7n5FBGPqu4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/john-dahl-tomassons-celtic-praise-as-he-talks-champions-league/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T17:15:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Dahl Tomasson’s Celtic Praise As He Talks Champions League  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debut for Green Brigade’s Celtic Park Makeover]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/debut-for-green-brigades-celtic-park-makeover/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/debut-for-green-brigades-celtic-park-makeover/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC fans were back at Parkhead on Saturday to take in a friendly between the Scottish Champions and Blackburn. The game ended 2-2 and it was just good to get back into the stadium after a long summer away. If you enter the stadium around the green brigade end, you will have noticed some marked […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Fantastic! It’s an amazing feeling to be back,” Jota’s shines back in Paradise]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/fantastic-its-an-amazing-feeling-to-be-back-jotas-shines-back-in-paradise/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/fantastic-its-an-amazing-feeling-to-be-back-jotas-shines-back-in-paradise/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T16:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jota managed to nab himself a man-of-the-match award for his goal and general performance this afternoon against Jon Dahl Tomasson’s Balckburn Rovers side. Post-match he revealed his delight at being back home – this time pemannently – and playing in front of that famous Parkhead crowd. The winger looked to be enjoying the occasion in Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premier Sports Cup: St Johnstone in peril, ten-man Livingston strike late, Aberdeen off top spot]]></title>
        <id>3771099</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/premier-sports-cup-st-johnstone-in-peril-ten-man-livingston-strike-late-aberdeen-off-top-spot-3771099"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T16:53:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[St Johnstone are facing early Premier Sports Cup elimination after losing another penalty shoot-out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angus Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steven Gerrard dishes out praise for Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou away from the Ibrox bubble]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/steven-gerrard-dishes-out-praise-for-celtic-boss-ange-postecoglou-away-from-the-glasgow-bubble/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/steven-gerrard-dishes-out-praise-for-celtic-boss-ange-postecoglou-away-from-the-glasgow-bubble/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T16:43:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Rangers manager Steven Gerrard believes Ange Postecoglou has done “fantastically well” at Celtic and has stated that he has nothing but “respect and admiration” for the Australian. Gerrard started last season as Postecoglou’s main managerial rival, in charge of the Ibrox club, but quickly scarpered down south to join Aston Villa with the rest ...
The post Steven Gerrard dishes out praise for Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou away from the Ibrox bubble appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Ex-Celt Mulgrew Scores Embarrassing Own Goal]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/video-ex-celt-mulgrew-scores-embarrassing-own-goal/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/video-ex-celt-mulgrew-scores-embarrassing-own-goal/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T16:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic star Charlie Mulgrew had a nightmare for Dundee Utd on Saturday afternoon as they took on Sunderland in a pre-season friendly. The former Celtic captain has done well for the Tannadice club since signing last season, however, he won’t want to watch this one back again. The gare finished 2-0 to Sunderland at […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Jota Raises The Roof With Outrageous Skill Against Blackburn At Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/video-jota-raises-the-roof-with-outrageous-skill-against-blackburn-at-celtic-park/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-jota-raises-the-roof-with-outrageous-skill-against-blackburn-at-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T16:34:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have recently made the permanent signing of Jota and fans were thrilled to discover that news. The dazzling Portuguese winger has excited the faithful for nigh on 12 months now, and this afternoon was no different as he raised the roof at Celtic Park with a sublime piece of skill against Blackburn Rovers. Jota, Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charlie Mulgrew scores bizarre Dundee United own goal as Sunderland howler leaves defender red faced - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEARrUFVobo__iEEPRvPRn_cqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/charlie-mulgrew-scores-bizarre-dundee-27498972"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T16:23:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Charlie Mulgrew scores bizarre Dundee United own goal as Sunderland howler leaves defender red faced  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Whole Bassey Business Is Like A Confidence Trick. Has Someone Really Fallen For It?]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/this-whole-bassey-business-is-like-a-confidence-trick-has-someone-really-fallen-for-it/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/this-whole-bassey-business-is-like-a-confidence-trick-has-someone-really-fallen-for-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T16:10:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s deal with it, with the ridiculous stories doing the rounds that Ibrox has found not just one mug but two willing to pay big money for a guy who’s had six good months in the game. If this deal goes through and the numbers are in eight figures, then football really has gone mad. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange refutes standing still chatter]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/ange-refutes-standing-still-chatter/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/ange-refutes-standing-still-chatter/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T16:01:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I think we’ve signed two better players than we had last year. That’s why we brought them in”, Ange refutes standing still chatter… Throughout the match today our Portuguese superstar Jota showcased just why we decided to shell out £6 million or so to secure him on a permanent transfer from Benfica. Ever the menace, Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘NO CEILING TO JOTA’S POTENTIAL,’ HAILS POSTECOGLOU]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/no-ceiling-to-jotas-potential-hails-postecoglou/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/no-ceiling-to-jotas-potential-hails-postecoglou/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T15:59:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU insists Filipe Jota is ready to take his game to a new level at Celtic. The Celtic manager was impressed by the Portuguese flyer’s stunning 59-minute performance in a competitive 2-2 draw with Blackburn Rovers in the friendly at Parkhead this afternoon. Jota, who signed a permanent £6.5million deal in the summer after [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate Update]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/reo-hatate-celtic-injury-update/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/reo-hatate-celtic-injury-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T15:48:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate was missing on Wednesday night for the Hoops after picking up a knock in training. Reo wasn’t seen with the rest of the Celtic squad on Friday’s training. He was being put through his paces alone. However, Ange revealed while the man from Japan had recovered from the knock, Reo fell ill on […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch Charlie Mulgrew score extraordinary own goal in Dundee United v Sunderland friendly as ex-Celtic defender left with egg on face]]></title>
        <id>3771064</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/watch-charlie-mulgrew-score-extraordinary-own-goal-in-dundee-united-v-sunderland-friendly-as-ex-celtic-defender-left-with-egg-on-face-3771064"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T15:48:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pre-season friendlies carry an often unwarranted tag of being meaningless and boring. This match between Dundee United and Sunderland at Tannadice certainly gave those in attendance a moment of sheer comedy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“We have two more weeks to get ready,” Ange Postecoglou]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/we-have-two-more-weeks-to-get-ready-ange-postecoglou/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/we-have-two-more-weeks-to-get-ready-ange-postecoglou/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T15:40:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou watched from the sidelines as we welcomed Blackburn Rovers to Paradise after our foreign adventures over the past few weeks or so. Anticipation was high for this one with a good day weather-wise adding to the excitement ahead of kick-off. The game didn’t fail to deliver either as there was a real hunger Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Clears Up Giakoumakis Absence]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/ange-clears-up-giakoumakis-absence/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/ange-clears-up-giakoumakis-absence/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T15:35:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GIAKOUMAKIS played for Celtic on Wednesday night and there were no reports of the striker sustaining an injury. That’s why it was surprising not to see the big man in the squad for the 2-2 draw against Blackburn on Saturday. The Greek scored a cracking goal for Celtic in the Czech Republic and the Hoops […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou signals exciting Celtic transfer intent over next 7 days; players to sign]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-boss-ange-postecoglou-looking-to-sign-2-players-over-next-7-days/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-boss-ange-postecoglou-looking-to-sign-2-players-over-next-7-days/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T15:25:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou is looking to add a couple of players to his Celtic squad and they could arrive within the next week. The Celtic boss has already signed up Jota, Cameron Carter-Vickers, Alexandro Bernabei and Ben Siegrist this summer. Now it looks like we’re approaching the next phase of his transfer work. Speaking after today’s ...
The post Ange Postecoglou signals exciting Celtic transfer intent over next 7 days; players to sign appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Antonio Colak tipped for Rangers goal glut as Jon Dahl Tomasson gives Celtic Champions League advice - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEPa88gcD2M61S1LuSF6noeMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/antonio-colak-tipped-rangers-goal-27498662"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T15:16:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Antonio Colak tipped for Rangers goal glut as Jon Dahl Tomasson gives Celtic Champions League advice  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blackpool 0 Rangers 0 LIVE score as Scott Arfield among triple change to spark a goal rush - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CBMiY2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvYmxhY2twb29sLXZzLXJhbmdlcnMtbGl2ZS1zY29yZS0yNzQ5Njc4NNIBZ2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvYmxhY2twb29sLXZzLXJhbmdlcnMtbGl2ZS1zY29yZS0yNzQ5Njc4NC5hbXA</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/blackpool-vs-rangers-live-score-27496784"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T15:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blackpool 0 Rangers 0 LIVE score as Scott Arfield among triple change to spark a goal rush  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou expects two new Celtic arrivals within a week]]></title>
        <id>ff237801e77e3e1316fcacde87b4de5f</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20284348.ange-postecoglou-expects-two-new-celtic-arrivals-within-week/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T15:06:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU says that he expects two more players to be added to his Celtic squad within the next week as he looks to land his major targets before the start of the season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky’s the limit for Jota as Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou and teammate Matt O’Riley wax lyrical about winger]]></title>
        <id>e94527c7ced84f9e80842b36ebb9bc4c</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20284339.skys-limit-jota-celtic-manager-ange-postecoglou-teammate-matt-oriley-wax-lyrical-winger/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T14:59:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THERE was a moment in the second-half of Celtic’s draw against Blackburn Rovers that had the entire home support on their feet, as some magic from Jota lit up Celtic Park and reminded everyone just why the fans were so excited when he was finally confirmed on a permanent contract earlier this summer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Centric Japanese Deal Announced]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-centric-japanese-deal-announced/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-centric-japanese-deal-announced/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T14:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic is making waves in Japan and they’re taking the SPFL along for the ride. It’s been announced the SPFL has been picked up by Japanese streaming service SpotNowTV. The broadcaster has paid for the rights to air the Scottish Premiership. They’re coverage will be Celtic centric according to Japanese based journalist Dan Orlowitz for […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou gives honest assessment of Celtic draw vs Blackburn Rovers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/match/ange-postecoglou-gives-honest-assessment-of-celtic-draw-vs-blackburn-rovers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/ange-postecoglou-gives-honest-assessment-of-celtic-draw-vs-blackburn-rovers/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T14:24:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has reacted to today’s Celtic draw at home vs Blackburn Rovers, admitting that after positive signs in the first half, the second half became less of a productive contest. Celtic were ahead at the interval after goals from Jota and David Turnbull cancelled out a shock early Rovers opener. The Bhoys were in ...
The post Ange Postecoglou gives honest assessment of Celtic draw vs Blackburn Rovers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Close to end point' - Celtic signings expected this week as Ange Postecoglou delivers injury update]]></title>
        <id>3771019</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/close-to-end-point-celtic-signings-expected-this-week-as-ange-postecoglou-delivers-injury-update-3771019"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T14:16:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou wants to go into the season with a more robust squad with added quality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC 2 BLACKBURN ROVERS 2: JOTA, TURNBULL ON MARK IN TOUGH TEST]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-2-blackburn-rovers-2-jota-turnbull-on-mark-in-tough-test/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-2-blackburn-rovers-2-jota-turnbull-on-mark-in-tough-test/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T13:49:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC 2 BLACKBURN ROVERS 2 IF Ange Postecoglou was looking for a stiff work-out for his players at Parkhead this afternoon he certainly got it in the shape of the Championship side. It was abundantly clear they were not appearing in the east end of Glasgow simply to make up the numbers and they went [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attacking verve and defensive sloppiness on show from Celtic once more in draw with Blackburn]]></title>
        <id>feec9746301d2fec21f6f0b593361a5e</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20284270.attacking-verve-defensive-sloppiness-show-celtic-draw-blackburn/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T13:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MANAGERS will often say that there is little to be taken from friendly games other than the improvement of fitness and match sharpness. But if there is one thing to be deduced from Celtic’s four warm-up encounters to date this summer, it’s that it is unlikely to be a dull season once again under Ange Postecoglou. There were just the four goals this time as they played out a 2-2 draw with English Championship side Blackburn Rovers, first-half strikes from Jota and David Turnbull turning round an early deficit after Sam Gallagher had scored for the visitors in the opening couple of minutes. Ben Brereton-Diaz scored the leveller with 15 minutes left from a free-kick after some slack play from Yosuke Ideguchi, a slightly worrying common theme of Celtic’s games to date. Yes, it’s pre-season of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 talking points as Celtic and Blackburn serve up breathless friendly amid Jota wreaking havoc - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>1501901899</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/3-talking-points-celtic-blackburn-27497792"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T13:27:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[3 talking points as Celtic and Blackburn serve up breathless friendly amid Jota wreaking havoc  Daily Record
Celtic announce pleasing triple sell out but club need to take action on last season’s trend  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News
Celtic team news confirmed as Blackburn Rovers visit Parkhead for pre-season clash  Football Scotland
Celtic vs Blackburn Rovers pre-season: How to watch, team news, head-to-head, odds, prediction and everything you need to know  GIVEMESPORT
Celtic starting XI v Blackburn confirmed as duo spark absence mystery  Glasgow Live
View Full coverage on Google News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange signing dazzles, passing puzzles; 3 talking points as Celtic draw vs Blackburn Rovers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/match/jota-dazzles-passing-puzzles-3-talking-points-as-celtic-draw-vs-blackburn-rovers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/jota-dazzles-passing-puzzles-3-talking-points-as-celtic-draw-vs-blackburn-rovers/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T13:26:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic continued with their pre-season work on Saturday afternoon, drawing 2-2 with Blackburn Rovers at home. Jon Dahl Tomasson’s side actually took the lead at Paradise, scoring within a minute after some loose play between Matt O’Riley and Callum McGregor in the middle of the park. However, from that point on, Celtic controlled proceedings – ...
The post Ange signing dazzles, passing puzzles; 3 talking points as Celtic draw vs Blackburn Rovers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's intoxicating quality on show against Blackburn Rovers - and the Champions League identity fascination]]></title>
        <id>3770990</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtics-intoxicating-quality-on-show-against-blackburn-rovers-and-the-champions-league-identity-fascination-3770990"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T13:22:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There cannot be many more intoxicating teams in world football than Celtic. Ange Postecoglou's men have a seldom seen quality in the game, the ability to make the mundanity and routine of pre-season friendlies a thrilling joy-ride.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Match Report: Celtic FC Women 1-1 Southampton - Yardbarker]]></title>
        <id>CBMiaWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnlhcmRiYXJrZXIuY29tL3NvY2Nlci9hcnRpY2xlcy9tYXRjaF9yZXBvcnRfY2VsdGljX2ZjX3dvbWVuXzFfMV9zb3V0aGFtcHRvbi9zMV8xNTk3NF8zNzY4NDcxNNIBAA</id>
        <link href="https://www.yardbarker.com/soccer/articles/match_report_celtic_fc_women_1_1_southampton/s1_15974_37684714"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T13:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Match Report: Celtic FC Women 1-1 Southampton  Yardbarker]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Celtic things we learned as champions draw with Blackburn]]></title>
        <id>5b2c294817c7fdc6749a49da5aaff2f6</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20284260.3-celtic-things-learned-champions-draw-blackburn/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T13:20:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unusual slow start It took just 22-seconds for the visitors to take the lead in the match. Some poor mis control in midfield by allowed Blackburn’s attackers to latch onto the ball. A lovely reverse through-ball from Jack Vale slipped in Sam Gallagher. The big striker made no mistake inside the box as he slammed home past Joe Hart. Without doubt, the sloppiness was highly unlike Celtic’s midfield and defensive players. With it being a friendly, of course it doesn’t matter in the grand scheme of things. However, there’s no denying that Postecoglou will not want to a repeat of those mistakes when the league season starts in two weeks. Celtic are always a threat going forward, but it’s also clear at they’re far too open at the back still and are therefore susceptible to losing goals against decent opposition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Match Report: Celtic FC Women 1-1 Southampton]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/match-report-celtic-fc-women-1-1-southampton/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/match-report-celtic-fc-women-1-1-southampton/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fran Alonso took his Celtic FC Women side into their first pre-season friendly of the season today, as the Hoops took on Southampton in a behind closed doors match at Barrowfield. Celtic returned this week from a pre-season training camp to Gran Canaria, however, were unable to arrange a match over there, so it was Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Match Report: Celtic FC Women 1-1 Southampton - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEEIYUTUtTWj9i0U4xWLWRBsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/match-report-celtic-fc-women-1-1-southampton/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Match Report: Celtic FC Women 1-1 Southampton  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic held by Blackburn Rovers in first pre-season game at Celtic Park - Official Celtic Football Club Website]]></title>
        <id>1501901899</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticfc.com/news/2022/july/16/celtic-held-by-blackburn-rovers-in-first-pre-season-game-at-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T13:16:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic held by Blackburn Rovers in first pre-season game at Celtic Park  Official Celtic Football Club Website
Celtic 2 Blackburn Rovers 2 RECAP: Parkhead treated to friendly thriller  Daily Record
Ange Postecoglou gives honest assessment of Celtic draw vs Blackburn Rovers  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News
Celtic star’s mystery absence vs Blackburn Rovers explained  The Celtic Bhoys
Video: Jota Raises The Roof With Outrageous Skill Against Blackburn At Celtic Park  The Celtic Star
View Full coverage on Google News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Outstanding Jota Moment; Rinses Blackburn star]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/video-outstanding-jota-moment-rinses-blackburn-star/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/video-outstanding-jota-moment-rinses-blackburn-star/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T13:09:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic took on Blackburn in a pre-season friendly at Celtic Park. It was the first chance for fans to get back to see the champions play after a summer off. The game was very competitive, Blackburn lucky not to have a man sent off in the game for the amount of fouling. Ange Postecoglou fielded […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Half-time: Celtic 2 Blackburn Rovers 1 – Early setback but Hoops roar back]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/half-time-celtic-2-blackburn-rovers-1-early-setback-but-hoops-roar-back/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/half-time-celtic-2-blackburn-rovers-1-early-setback-but-hoops-roar-back/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T12:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic suffered an early shot inside the first twenty seconds of the match against Blackburn Rovers this afternoon after an uncharacteristic loss of possession by the Celtic captain Callum McGregor just inside the Celtic half. Sam Gallagher’s low shot went under Joe Hart to give the English side the lead. However after that it was Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Watch Jota Magic]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/video-watch-jota-magic/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/video-watch-jota-magic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T12:23:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bhoys are back from a successful European trip where they scored 14 goals in three games. Blackburn Rovers are the opponents today. Match sharpness and fitness is obviously top priority at this stage of the game but beating any English team is always a good thing considering how the Scottish game is viewed down […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Southampton FC kick off pre-season with strong draw at Celtic - Southern Daily Echo]]></title>
        <id>CBMiYWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5ZWNoby5jby51ay9zcG9ydC8yMDI4NDIwOC5zb3V0aGFtcHRvbi1mYy1raWNrLW9mZi1wcmUtc2Vhc29uLXN0cm9uZy1kcmF3LWNlbHRpYy_SAS9odHRwczovL3d3dy5kYWlseWVjaG8uY28udWsvc3BvcnQvMjAyODQyMDguYW1wLw</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyecho.co.uk/sport/20284208.southampton-fc-kick-off-pre-season-strong-draw-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T12:15:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Southampton FC kick off pre-season with strong draw at Celtic  Southern Daily Echo]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic 2 Blackburn Rovers 1 LIVE score as Ange loves it as his stars Never Stop in dominant display - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>1501901899</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/celtic-vs-blackburn-rovers-live-27496646"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T12:11:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic 2 Blackburn Rovers 1 LIVE score as Ange loves it as his stars Never Stop in dominant display  Daily Record
Celtic announce pleasing triple sell out but club need to take action on last season’s trend  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News
Celtic team news confirmed as Blackburn Rovers visit Parkhead for pre-season clash  Football Scotland
Celtic vs Blackburn Rovers pre-season: How to watch, team news, head-to-head, odds, prediction and everything you need to know  GIVEMESPORT
Celtic 2-1 Blackburn Rovers LIVE: Ross Turnbull defected free-kick puts Hoops ahead  Lancs Live
View Full coverage on Google News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic v Blackburn Rovers, Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-blackburn-rovers-live-updates/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-blackburn-rovers-live-updates/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T11:23:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 12:30.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hoops star dismisses any notion of a direct comparison with Celtic legend]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/hoops-star-dismisses-any-notion-of-a-direct-comparison-with-celtic-legend/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/hoops-star-dismisses-any-notion-of-a-direct-comparison-with-celtic-legend/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T11:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Ralston has dismissed any notion of a direct comparison between himself and Celtic’s legendary right-back Danny McGrain. The most improved Celtic player in recent memory at Parkhead has eclipsed the former captain’s goalscoring record and jokingly said he would take great pleasure in bringing it up in conversation the next time they bump into Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: ABADA RETURNS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-abada-returns/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-abada-returns/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T10:48:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIEL ABADA returns to Ange Postecoglou’s starting line-up for the friendly against Blackburn Rovers at Parkhead this afternoon. The Israeli winger came on a substitute and scored the final goal in the 4-2 win over Banik Ostrava in the Czech Republic and keeps his place with James Forrest among the substitutes. Celtic go into the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Step Up Backroom Recruitment; New Role]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-step-up-backroom-recruitment-new-role/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-step-up-backroom-recruitment-new-role/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T10:43:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC has been making changes behind the scenes and recruiting a plethora of talent to help the club gain any sort of edge they can whether it be sports science or data. The club is now looking at bringing in a data analyst for the B team, showing their commitment to the B team project. […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Step Up Backroom Recruitment; New Role - CeltsAreHere]]></title>
        <id>CBMiRmh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMtc3RlcC11cC1iYWNrcm9vbS1yZWNydWl0bWVudC1uZXctcm9sZS_SAUpodHRwczovL2NlbHRzYXJlaGVyZS5jb20vY2VsdGljLXN0ZXAtdXAtYmFja3Jvb20tcmVjcnVpdG1lbnQtbmV3LXJvbGUvYW1wLw</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-step-up-backroom-recruitment-new-role/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T10:43:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Step Up Backroom Recruitment; New Role  CeltsAreHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Team’s Up – Abada on the wing, Kyogo doing his thing]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/teams-up-abada-on-the-wing-kyogo-doing-his-thing/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/teams-up-abada-on-the-wing-kyogo-doing-his-thing/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T10:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s the Celtic side to play Blackburn Rovers at Paradise this lunchtime. Joe Hart is the sweeper/keeper while Josip Juranovic gets the nod at right-back ahead of Anthony Ralston. Same situation at left-back with Greg Taylor starting and new signing Bernabei on the bench. With Carl Starfelt still sidelined, Stephen Welsh is starting alongside Cameron Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Great team Ange: Celtic XI confirmed, exciting attack, TV details, instant reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-vs-blackburn-rovers-confirmed-ange-goes-strong-tv-details-instant-reaction/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-vs-blackburn-rovers-confirmed-ange-goes-strong-tv-details-instant-reaction/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T10:24:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has named his Celtic team vs Blackburn Rovers in today’s lunchtime kick-off. The full match squad is as follows: Starting XI – Hart, Juranovic, Carter-Vickers, Welsh, Taylor, McGregor, O’Riley, Turnbull, Abada, Jota, Kyogo. Substitutes – Bain, Siegrist, Oluwayemi, Jullien, McCarthy, Johnston, Ideguchi, Kenny, Bernabei, Urhoghide, Maeda, Lawal, Forrest, Ralston, Vata. It’s set to ...
The post Great team Ange: Celtic XI confirmed, exciting attack, TV details, instant reaction appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic team news for Blackburn Rovers friendly revealed]]></title>
        <id>a3abee9dcc5be20aee1ed84a96ea2c8f</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20283793.celtic-team-news-blackburn-rovers-friendly-revealed/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T10:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU has named his Celtic starting line-up to take on Blackburn Rovers this afternoon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confirmed Celtic Team For Home Return V Blackburn]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/confirmed-celtic-team-for-home-return-v-blackburn/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/confirmed-celtic-team-for-home-return-v-blackburn/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T10:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the official Celtic channels, today’s friendly game against Blackburn is a sold-out gig as fans flock to see the champions return to Paradise for a brand new season. The Bhoys are back from a successful European trip where they scored 14 goals in three games. Match sharpness and fitness is obviously top priority […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confirmed Celtic Team For Home Return V Blackburn - CeltsAreHere]]></title>
        <id>CBMiS2h0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jb25maXJtZWQtY2VsdGljLXRlYW0tZm9yLWhvbWUtcmV0dXJuLXYtYmxhY2tidXJuL9IBT2h0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9jb25maXJtZWQtY2VsdGljLXRlYW0tZm9yLWhvbWUtcmV0dXJuLXYtYmxhY2tidXJuL2FtcC8</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/confirmed-celtic-team-for-home-return-v-blackburn/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T10:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Confirmed Celtic Team For Home Return V Blackburn  CeltsAreHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video Celts assists Daily Record with their lost in translation Juranovic remarks]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/video-celts-assists-daily-record-with-their-lost-in-translation-juranovic-remarks/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-celts-assists-daily-record-with-their-lost-in-translation-juranovic-remarks/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T09:53:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Video Celts journalist Joe McHugh deserves plenty of praise for highlighting the discrepancies between the ‘translation’ of Josip Juranovic’s thoughts on the possibility of a move to Atletico Madrid highlighted in the Daily Record in comparison to those run in Spanish publication Mundio Sportivo this week. It’s an impressive questioning of the Daily Record journalist Mark Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Beale makes Rangers Champions League prediction and 'strongest squad' Celtic claim - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEB-gcpPW30FdRoPGT3fSr-AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPLfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/michael-beale-makes-rangers-champions-24508134"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T09:39:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Beale makes Rangers Champions League prediction and 'strongest squad' Celtic claim  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trip to Stadion Wojska Polskiego could be Champions League rehearsal for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/trip-to-stadion-wojska-polskiego-could-be-champions-league-rehearsal-for-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/trip-to-stadion-wojska-polskiego-could-be-champions-league-rehearsal-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T09:34:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic head to Warsaw on Wednesday night to face our old foe Legia, whilst at the same time joining the celebration of our former Holy Goalie Artur Boruc’s career. And there is a chance Celtic could be returning there in the Champions’ League Group stages later this year. Sky Sport’s Anthony Joseph has confirmed Ukrainian Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cedric Itten breaks Rangers exit silence as he reveals secret agony amid Ibrox struggles - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEJbrNKhsCpAknWekpbC-llIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/cedric-itten-breaks-rangers-exit-27497004"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T09:16:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cedric Itten breaks Rangers exit silence as he reveals secret agony amid Ibrox struggles  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUTTON POSER FOR POSTECOGLOU]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/sutton-poser-for-postecoglou/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/sutton-poser-for-postecoglou/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T09:16:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“WHO is Celtic’s main striker?” The question is posed by former Celtic goal hero Chris Sutton as he looks at the frontline options open to boss Ange Postecoglou. Just over a year ago in the pre-season friendly against West Ham at Parkhead, the recently-appointed Hoops gaffer played Odsonne Edouard in the first-half and Leigh Griffiths [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Frightening’ – Sutton Lays Down Mouth Watering Celtic Scenario]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/frightening-sutton-lays-down-mouth-watering-celtic-scenario/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/frightening-sutton-lays-down-mouth-watering-celtic-scenario/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T08:52:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CHRIS SUTTON has piled praise on two of Celtic’s biggest stars as we get ready for the new season. The former Celtic striker has been having his say on who will be the number one striker this season at Parkhead. Kyogo and Giakoumakis both showed last season they’re more than capable of taking on the […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dylan Reid and the worrying comparisons to Luca Connell and Jonathan Afolabi]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/dylan-reid-and-the-worrying-comparisons-to-luca-connell-and-jonathan-afolabi/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/dylan-reid-and-the-worrying-comparisons-to-luca-connell-and-jonathan-afolabi/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T08:35:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Celtic sign Dylan Reid from St Mirren it would in theory be a big move for the kid. The Scotland Under-17 international has broken through to the first team in Paisley and has clearly done enough to catch the eye of someone at Celtic as a result, but if and when he arrives here Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou’s Comments Not Directed at Scottish Media]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-ange-tom-australia/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-ange-tom-australia/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T08:21:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou’s comments on Tom Rogic were well publicised on Friday after the Celtic manager was quizzed on what was going on with Tom. The former Celtic midfielder has went off the grid since leaving Celtic – even ignoring his Socceroos boss Graham Arnold. When asked about Tom, Ange replied in typical Ange fashion: “I […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Ralston Celtic icon comparison draws laugh as Brendan Rodgers' claim revisited - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEB3ImqcwAVAFQAIFVG6erBcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPPfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/anthony-ralston-celtic-icon-comparison-24507882"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Ralston Celtic icon comparison draws laugh as Brendan Rodgers' claim revisited  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Could Celtic remove Betting and Boozer Brands from our kits permanently?]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/could-celtic-remove-betting-and-boozer-brands-from-our-kits-permanently/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/could-celtic-remove-betting-and-boozer-brands-from-our-kits-permanently/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T08:11:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the matches in Austria and Czech Republic in recent weeks the Celtic players have performed wearing shirts that did not display the club’s main sponsor’s branding due to advertising restrictions in these countries. And as such restrictions edge closer to home, with the English Premier League looking at following a similar path a Celtic Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Could Celtic remove Betting and Boozer Brands from our kits permanently? - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiECLKvXuc49ltHPi_mhvBL8QqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/could-celtic-remove-betting-and-boozer-brands-from-our-kits-permanently/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T08:11:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Could Celtic remove Betting and Boozer Brands from our kits permanently?  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[McGrain 9 Ralston 10 – “I hadn’t realised I’ve now scored more goals than Danny”]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/mcgrain-9-ralston-10-i-hadnt-realised-ive-now-scored-more-goals-than-danny/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/mcgrain-9-ralston-10-i-hadnt-realised-ive-now-scored-more-goals-than-danny/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T07:33:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Ralston has now scored more goals for Celtic than Danny McGrain who rather surprisingly scored nine times for the Hoops. Danny’s finishing was of course legendary and was a bit of a running joke throughout his illustrious career as a truly world class performer happy to remain at Celtic. Recently I had the pleasure Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ralston’s Brilliant Celtic Admission]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/ralstons-brilliant-celtic-admission/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/ralstons-brilliant-celtic-admission/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Ralston has been speaking to the media ahead of Celtic’s fourth pre-season friendly on Saturday. Parkhead is welcoming Championship side Blackburn as the team continue their preparations for their title defence season. Postecoglou won’t allow his team’s performance levels to drop as he looks to build on last season’s success. The gaffer will be […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Lundstram sends rousing Rangers message in rare social media outing - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEFeY6O8tSYh_PWWyzuSF3MgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPLfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/john-lundstram-sends-rousing-rangers-24507719"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T07:23:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Lundstram sends rousing Rangers message in rare social media outing  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I’LL NEED TO MENTION IT TO HIM,’ RALSTON IN McGRAIN ADMISSION]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ill-need-to-mention-it-to-him-ralston-in-mcgrain-admission/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ill-need-to-mention-it-to-him-ralston-in-mcgrain-admission/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T07:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANTHONY RALSTON laughs off comparisons with Celtic’s legendary right-back Danny McGrain. It was Brendan Rodgers who made the remarkable statement after being appointed Hoops boss in June 2016. Departing boss Ronny Deila introduced two eager teenagers to the full-back positions, Ralston on the right and Kieran Tierney on the left, as he wound down his [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leigh Griffiths Post Celtic Struggle]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/leigh-griffiths-post-celtic-struggle/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/leigh-griffiths-post-celtic-struggle/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic released Leigh Griffiths in January after Dundee sent him back to Parkhead early. He had a disappointing first half of the season, but was keen to redeem himself. For the latter part of the season, the once Scotland internationalist dropped down to League 1, penning a six-month contract with Falkirk. He failed to impress […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Dylan Reid brings to Celtic as St Mirren icon pays rising star the ultimate compliment - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEEHSDa9tylmEL3FT78niG9IqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-transfer-news/what-dylan-reid-brings-celtic-27496647"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T06:59:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What Dylan Reid brings to Celtic as St Mirren icon pays rising star the ultimate compliment  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Celtic don’t have one main striker now – they’ve got two,” Chris Sutton]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-dont-have-one-main-striker-now-theyve-got-two-chris-sutton/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-dont-have-one-main-striker-now-theyve-got-two-chris-sutton/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T06:44:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Chris Sutton played for Celtic, Martin O’Neill didn’t have one or even two top class strikers to choose from, he had three. The big Englishman was joined by Henrik Larsson, Celtic’s King of Kings and Big Bad John Hartson and sometimes all three were played together! Looking at the striking situation at his old Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: ‘BIG JOCK AND ME’: EVAN WILLIAMS REVEALS ALL (Part Two)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-big-jock-and-me-evan-williams-reveals-all-part-two/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-big-jock-and-me-evan-williams-reveals-all-part-two/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T06:07:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EVAN WILLIAMS, who celebrated his 79th birthday yesterday, was a goalkeeper decades ahead of his time. Ange Postecoglou encourages Joe Hart or whoever is in the Celtic goal to play their role in quickly turning defence into attack, as CQN reported yesterday. Williams, who joined the Hoops from Wolves in October 1969 as the club [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: ‘WE HAVE LEARNED FROM THE EXPERIENCE’: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Five)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-we-have-learned-from-the-experience-the-tommy-burns-story-part-five/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-we-have-learned-from-the-experience-the-tommy-burns-story-part-five/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T05:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS was determined to win silverware in his first season as Celtic manager after returning to the club on July 12 1994. The chance to achieve his goal after only four months was obliterated in a dramatic penalty-kick shoot-out to First Division Raith Rovers in the League Cup Final at Ibrox. With the league [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calvin Bassey will bank Rangers big bucks but there's a key to sparking a bidding war - Saturday Jury - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiECZZ4BCVbZWVnkWXlk1r6RgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/calvin-bassey-bank-rangers-big-27491924"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Calvin Bassey will bank Rangers big bucks but there's a key to sparking a bidding war - Saturday Jury  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Ralston admits Celtic comparison still sparks a chuckle as he revisits Brendan Rodgers claim - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEP2rEZNbglvq9T8ST7HbGEIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/anthony-ralston-admits-celtic-comparison-27494839"/>
        <updated>2022-07-16T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Ralston admits Celtic comparison still sparks a chuckle as he revisits Brendan Rodgers claim  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Ralston laughs off Brendan Rodgers’ Danny McGrain comparison after eclipsing Celtic hero’s goal haul]]></title>
        <id>0d944c3d543715195724a9e478120895</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20282731.anthony-ralston-laughs-off-brendan-rodgers-danny-mcgrain-comparison-eclipsing-celtic-heros-goal-haul/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS left behind some incredible memories for Celtic supporters after his tenure as manager, but he also left behind more than a few memorably far-fetched stories. From encounters with Rangers fans in the Clyde Tunnel to pipping Real Madrid to Charly Musonda, the Irishman had the gift of the gab to go with his undoubted coaching quality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have chance to sign Barcelona midfield maestro - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>CAIiELrvozgDjKuHheOszTdU16MqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4KKJCzCv9JoDMICkoAY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2022/07/15/celtic-sign-barcelona-midfield-maestro/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T21:04:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have chance to sign Barcelona midfield maestro  The Celtic Bhoys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic target told to stay put by St Mirren boss Stephen Robinson]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-target-told-to-stay-put-by-st-mirren-boss-stephen-robinson/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-target-told-to-stay-put-by-st-mirren-boss-stephen-robinson/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T21:02:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the summer recruitment drive and pre-season plans roll on as we build up ahead of steam in the run up to facing Aberdeen on 31 July at Celtic Park, one transfer story has flown slightly under the radar of late. Last week Celtic had a bid accepted for St Mirren youngster Dylan Reid, with Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Site Catches The Daily Record In A Filthy Lie Over Juranovic Interview.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/celtic-site-catches-the-daily-record-in-a-filthy-lie-over-juranovic-interview/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/celtic-site-catches-the-daily-record-in-a-filthy-lie-over-juranovic-interview/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T19:53:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congratulations to the ever-excellent Joe McHugh over on VideoCelts, who tonight has broken a story about how The Daily Record mistranslated – certainly deliberately – the interview Juranovic gave to the Croat media the other day. The Record did their own version of the translation. Because the story involved Atletico Madrid, the Spanish also did […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malik Tillman Rangers permanent transfer option revealed as Ross Wilson details lengthy chase - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiELNuyaCG1-exrBGiqgYrM_AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPTfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/malik-tillman-rangers-permanent-transfer-24506731"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T19:31:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malik Tillman Rangers permanent transfer option revealed as Ross Wilson details lengthy chase  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s 100 Goal Striker Should Be Worth More Than Rejection By Forfar.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/celtics-100-goal-striker-should-be-worth-more-than-rejection-by-forfar/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/celtics-100-goal-striker-should-be-worth-more-than-rejection-by-forfar/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T19:02:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If a rejection by Forfar isn’t Leigh Griffiths’ career low-light then you have to wonder if he’s wasting his time even playing further football. He’s 31 years old. He should have two or three more years at the top of his game. A player who did what he did? Leigh was the last guy to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic vs Blackburn Rovers: TV channel, live stream and kick-off time]]></title>
        <id>e7b01ce149e6531f9cae9feba968ac63</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20283704.celtic-vs-blackburn-rovers-tv-channel-live-stream-kick-off-time/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T18:34:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC are back at home this weekend for the first time since lifting the Premiership title in May.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ferguson’s Talk Of Bassey Being Worth A Tierney Fee Is Insulting To The Ex-Celtic Bhoy.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/fergusons-talk-of-bassey-being-worth-a-tierney-fee-is-insulting-to-the-ex-celtic-bhoy/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/fergusons-talk-of-bassey-being-worth-a-tierney-fee-is-insulting-to-the-ex-celtic-bhoy/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T18:02:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Barry Ferguson reckons Ibrox should hold out for £25 million for Bassey because that’s what Tierney left Celtic for. What a grotesque insult to our former footballer, and what a sterling example of the blindness and stupidity at the heart of this whole debate. I’ve written about this Bassey nonsense a bunch of times and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tillman nears Rangers transfer, Juranovic Celtic boost, Hearts target Anderson as Aberdeen sign Lopes - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEPSQnnjBfuU2RaH1VDPHwhYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPLfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/transfer-news/tillman-nears-rangers-transfer-juranovic-24505893"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T17:54:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tillman nears Rangers transfer, Juranovic Celtic boost, Hearts target Anderson as Aberdeen sign Lopes  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager comments on worrying Tom Rogic situation - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEFM6uKny7BUkSRUKcR81lxsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4KKJCzCv9JoDMICkoAY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2022/07/15/celtic-manager-tom-rogic-situation/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T17:44:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager comments on worrying Tom Rogic situation  The Celtic Bhoys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ange Factor &amp; the SOLD OUT signs]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/the-ange-factor-the-sold-out-signs/</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/the-ange-factor-the-sold-out-signs/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T17:28:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ange Factor this season has certainly added to the anticipation ahead of the new season. Last year we were entering unchartered waters but this pre-season we seem to be swimming with the Dolphins. https://celticfanzine.com/product-category/monthly-print-subscription/ When Martin O’Neill arrived on the steps of Celtic Park we all felt that change was coming and a treble […]
The post The Ange Factor & the SOLD OUT signs appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calvin Bassey gets Rangers transfer plea from Barry Ferguson as he draws cash comparison with Celtic hero - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CBMicGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLXRyYW5zZmVyLW5ld3MvY2FsdmluLWJhc3NleS1nZXRzLXJhbmdlcnMtdHJhbnNmZXItMjc0OTQ3NjXSAQA</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-transfer-news/calvin-bassey-gets-rangers-transfer-27494765"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T17:25:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Calvin Bassey gets Rangers transfer plea from Barry Ferguson as he draws cash comparison with Celtic hero  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Happens if Celtic Draw Shakhtar Donetsk]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/what-happens-if-celtic-draw-shakhtar-donetsk/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/what-happens-if-celtic-draw-shakhtar-donetsk/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T17:20:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the ongoing invasion of Ukraine, many Celtic fans have been wondering what would happen if the club was drawn a team from the country. After some uncertainty if Shakhtar Donetsk would compete in this year’s competition, they declared they would be participating, and the country’s league would start again. It’s too dangerous for an […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic star Leigh Griffiths won't be offered Forfar deal, reveals Gary Irvine]]></title>
        <id>9d5a02d3a5ffeafef25f22f8f5786413</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20283603.ex-celtic-star-leigh-griffiths-wont-offered-forfar-deal-reveals-gary-irvine/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T17:20:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORFAR ATHLETIC boss Gary Irvine has revealed that Leigh Griffiths won't be joining his side this summer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scotrail timetable boost for Celtic supporters ahead of season start]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/scotrail-timetable-boost-for-celtic-supporters-ahead-of-season-start/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/scotrail-timetable-boost-for-celtic-supporters-ahead-of-season-start/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T17:14:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scotrail have announced that full train services will resume from next week, providing a boost to travelling Celtic fans ahead of the new competitive season getting underway. Since May 23rd, rail services across the country have been reduced to an emergency timetable during a dispute with staff regarding pay and working conditions. An agreement was ...
The post Scotrail timetable boost for Celtic supporters ahead of season start appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ralston Impressed with Summer Recruit]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/ralston-impressed-with-summer-recruit/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/ralston-impressed-with-summer-recruit/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T17:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Ralston was talking to the media today after he captained the team on Wednesday night. The Hoops are preparing to face Blackburn Rovers on Saturday as the Hoops return to Glasgow to prepare for the upcoming season. Premier Sports are showing the game live, but it’s set to be a sell-out in the stadium […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hatate and Starfelt Injury Updates]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/hatate-and-starfelt-injury-updates/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/hatate-and-starfelt-injury-updates/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T16:59:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic return to Paradise as their pre-season preparations continue. After a ten-day training camp in Austria and the Czech Republic, the Bhoys will face Blackburn Rovers on Saturday. Postecoglou will likely start the match with a strong side before rotating the players as the match goes on. However, the match will be played with Carl […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Juranovic Statement Clarified after Poor Translation]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/juranovic-statement-clarified-after-poor-translation/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/juranovic-statement-clarified-after-poor-translation/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T16:43:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic signed Josip Juranovic a year ago from Legia Warsaw for a small fee of £2.5 million. He took the league by storm, becoming a vital player for Ange Postecoglou. The Croatian had become the target of some English sides and Athletico Madrid, with transfer guru Fabrizio Romano claiming he was expected to leave Celtic […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou provides positive assurances over departed Celtic star]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-provides-positive-assurances-over-departing-celtic-star-tom-rogic/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-provides-positive-assurances-over-departing-celtic-star-tom-rogic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou has stated he has no concerns over former Hoops midfielder Tom Rogic as he continues to decide his future. The 29-year-old received an emotional send-off on the final day of the 2021/22 season after announcing his departure from Parkhead. Rogic enjoyed an extremely successful nine-year stay in Glasgow, picking up a ...
The post Ange Postecoglou provides positive assurances over departed Celtic star appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tony Ralston admits Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou transformed him as he reveals daughter motivation - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEI2SYLLrhohMWO68Sz8NdUUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPPfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/tony-ralston-admits-celtic-boss-24505564"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T16:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tony Ralston admits Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou transformed him as he reveals daughter motivation  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHY IT’S NO-GO GRIFF FOR THE FOURTH TIER]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/why-its-no-go-griff-for-the-fourth-tier/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/why-its-no-go-griff-for-the-fourth-tier/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T16:38:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORFAR boss Gary Irvine has revealed he considered making an offer to Leigh Griffiths. The former Celtic and Scotland striker, who hit 123 goals for the Hoops, was in the thoughts of the fourth-tier outfit as he continues his search for a new club. Thirty-one-year-old Griffiths was released by the Parkhead side in January with [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Football fans across Scotland to hold collection at Celtic park tomorrow]]></title>
        <id>1e65c0dab23f17f9b2a22fdbdbd6531c</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20282020.football-fans-across-scotland-hold-collection-celtic-park-tomorrow/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T16:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Football fans across Scotland have united to tackle the country's food poverty crisis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Juranovic And Bassey Stories Sum Up The Difference Between Celtic Fans And Sevconuts.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/blogs/the-juranovic-and-bassey-stories-sum-up-the-difference-between-celtic-fans-and-sevconuts/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/blogs/the-juranovic-and-bassey-stories-sum-up-the-difference-between-celtic-fans-and-sevconuts/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T16:13:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the resurrection of the Juranovic story – or rather, the media’s failure to just let it die – on the same day as Bassey is again in the news, it is worth examining the reactions from both sets of fans to the way these two tales have developed over the window. On the night […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Once upon a time in Gosford: Celtic FC's history with the A-League - The Roar]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEF30d6-KC1Xp9XZvtvO2Va0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowq7qCCzDduf8CMLO_ggY</id>
        <link href="https://www.theroar.com.au/2022/07/16/once-upon-a-time-in-gosford-celtic-fcs-history-with-the-a-league/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T16:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once upon a time in Gosford: Celtic FC's history with the A-League  The Roar]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Celtic are reaping benefits of not following path tread by Rangers this season]]></title>
        <id>3770567</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/how-celtic-are-reaping-benefits-of-not-following-path-tread-by-rangers-this-season-3770567"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T15:58:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Ralston highlighted the “brilliant” benefits of automatic Champions League qualification amid Celtic’s stress-free pre-season preparations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ross McLeish</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender talks up squad&#039;s pre-season advantage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/anthony-ralston-insists-early-pre-season-advantage-has-celtic-squad-in-a-good-place/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/anthony-ralston-insists-early-pre-season-advantage-has-celtic-squad-in-a-good-place/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Anthony Ralston believes that the advantage of no Champions League qualifiers this summer has Ange Postecoglou’s squad in a good place. The Bhoys have returned to Lennoxtown to continue their preparations for the new season after a 10-day to Austria and the Czech Republic last week. During their time in Europe, the Celtic ...
The post Celtic defender talks up squad&#039;s pre-season advantage appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic vs Blackburn: How to Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-vs-blackburn-how-to-watch/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-vs-blackburn-how-to-watch/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T15:29:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will play their fourth pre-season friendly on Saturday afternoon and will be the first at Home. All season ticket holders will be able to access the first game in Celtic Park and the Blackburn Rovers fans will be given a relatively small amount of seats at the away end. After last season’s success, it […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Rather than playing the qualifiers, automatically qualifying is brilliant,” Ralston]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/rather-than-playing-the-qualifiers-automatically-qualifying-is-brilliant-ralston/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/rather-than-playing-the-qualifiers-automatically-qualifying-is-brilliant-ralston/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T15:26:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Ralston spoke at a Celtic Media Conference today ahead of Celtic’s return to our natural habitat at Parkhead. The Bhoys face-off against theRangers conqueror Jon Dahl Tomasson and his Balckburn Rovers side tomorrow afternoon in what promises to be an exciting occasion. The fans will be eager to see the group perform again after Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Ralston shares positive first impressions of new Celtic signing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/anthony-ralston-shares-positive-first-impressions-of-new-celtic-signing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/anthony-ralston-shares-positive-first-impressions-of-new-celtic-signing/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T15:16:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Ralston was the Celtic player on media duties today at Lennoxtown, ahead of this weekend’s match against Blackburn Rovers. Ange Postecoglou’s squad have returned to familiar territory after a ten-day trip to Austria and Czechia. The Bhoys are set to play in front of Celtic supporters for the first time this summer in a ...
The post Anthony Ralston shares positive first impressions of new Celtic signing appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Edouard Michut Latest; Midfielder’s Fee]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/edouard-michut-latest-midfielders-fee/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/edouard-michut-latest-midfielders-fee/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T15:12:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic was reportedly in advanced talks with PSG’s Edouard Michut during the week, but Ange played down the possible transfer, ruling a possible move out. It was obvious Ange Postecoglou was aware of the player. He commented on the midfielder, saying, “Good player, but no” [The National], indicating that he was an option for Celtic. […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo: Jota meeting Celtic’s King of Kings at Champions League Final]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/photo-jota-meeting-celtics-king-of-kings-at-champions-league-final/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/photo-jota-meeting-celtics-king-of-kings-at-champions-league-final/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T15:10:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the pantheon of Celtic legends, it would be fair to say that there is no greater name than that of Henrik Larsson. The Super Swede was the magnificent seven for seven whole years in the Hoops and managed to score a phenomenal 242 goals in 315 games for the club. Larsson didn’t just do Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange has not held discussions about Japan tour in summer 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/ange-has-not-held-discussions-about-japan-tour-in-summer-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/ange-has-not-held-discussions-about-japan-tour-in-summer-2023/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T14:57:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since signing from Yokohama F. Marinos in the J-League and then going on to sign four players from Japan too, Ange Postecoglou and Celtic have been widely tipped to go on a tour of the country at some point in an attempt to raise the club’s profile even more in Asia. Rumours have been circulating Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange has not held discussions about Japan tour in summer 2023 - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEN7uRREAxSSB-w7dUvqRGgQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/ange-has-not-held-discussions-about-japan-tour-in-summer-2023/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T14:57:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange has not held discussions about Japan tour in summer 2023  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What channel is the Celtic game against Blackburn on? TV details, live stream and kick-off time for pre-season friendly]]></title>
        <id>3770313</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/what-channel-is-the-celtic-game-against-blackburn-on-tv-details-live-stream-and-kick-off-time-for-pre-season-friendly-3770313"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T14:48:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic continue their pre-season campaign with their first home friendly of the season when Blackburn Rovers visit the east end of Glasgow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What channel is the Celtic game against Blackburn on? TV details, live stream and kick-off time for friendly]]></title>
        <id>3770313</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/what-channel-is-the-celtic-game-against-blackburn-on-tv-details-live-stream-and-kick-off-time-for-friendly-3770313"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T14:48:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic continue their pre-season campaign with their first home friendly of the season when Blackburn Rovers visit the east end of Glasgow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serie A scout insists Scottish Premiership is ‘incredibly, incredibly underrated’]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/serie-a-scout-insists-scottish-premiership-is-incredibly-incredibly-underrated/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/serie-a-scout-insists-scottish-premiership-is-incredibly-incredibly-underrated/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T14:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A former football scout in Serie A has revealed that Scottish football is a totally undervalued source of talent and potential. Francesco Struzzo – formerly of Bologna – and the man who took Aaron Hickey from Heart of Midlothian to Italy insists that the game in this country is awash with great footballers and it Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Scotsman’s Headline On Juranovic Is A Ridiculous Effort To Keep A Non-Story Going.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/the-scotsmans-headline-on-juranovic-is-a-ridiculous-effort-to-keep-a-non-story-going/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/the-scotsmans-headline-on-juranovic-is-a-ridiculous-effort-to-keep-a-non-story-going/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T14:08:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The media simply refuses to let their garbage Juranovic story die. No matter how many times this has been beaten around the head, it continues to live on. The big guy himself has stamped on it, but there’s no killing this one it seems. Today The Scotsman had a go. “Celtic transfers: Josip Juranovic boost […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Celtic is a really good team,” Hibs latest signing Marijan Cabraja]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-is-a-really-good-team-hibs-latest-signing-marijan-cabraja/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-is-a-really-good-team-hibs-latest-signing-marijan-cabraja/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T13:50:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hibs latest signing Marijan Cabraja has revealed he was sold on the move to Easter Road due to the prospect of playing the mighty Glasgow Celtic. Cabraja was an old foe in last year’s Europa League, having been on loan at Hungarian side Ferencvaros whom we beat home and away and were mightily unlucky in Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moussa Dembele plans to see out contract at Lyon, ending Celtic windfall hopes]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/moussa-dembele-plans-to-see-out-contract-at-lyon-ending-celtic-windfall-hopes/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/moussa-dembele-plans-to-see-out-contract-at-lyon-ending-celtic-windfall-hopes/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T13:28:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Football Scotland have reported that former Celtic striker Moussa Dembele is set to run down the final year of his contract and leave for free next summer. The news comes after a spate of interest in the powerful forward, particularly in the Premier League – with Erik Ten Haag and Antonio Conte supposedly keen. There Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfers: Josip Juranovic boost as La Liga interest cools - for now - as developments come in Spain]]></title>
        <id>3769926</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-transfers-josip-juranovic-boost-as-la-liga-interest-cools-for-now-as-developments-come-in-spain-3769926"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T13:22:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are unlikely to field a bid at this stage for their right-back Josip Juranovic from Atletico Madrid after the Spanish outfit moved closer to a deal for Nahuel Molina.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Large Blackburn Rovers away support expected at Celtic Park on Saturday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/large-blackburn-rovers-away-support-expected-at-celtic-park-on-saturday/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/large-blackburn-rovers-away-support-expected-at-celtic-park-on-saturday/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blackburn Rovers expect to be backed by around 1,500 away supporters at tomorrow’s pre-season friendly at Celtic Park. The club revealed the numbers on their official website last night, suggesting that ticket sales have been strong against the allocation given in the stadium’s southeast corner. Celtic have been charging Rovers fans between £7 and £16 ...
The post Large Blackburn Rovers away support expected at Celtic Park on Saturday appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou on the Tommy Burns Story, Bertie Auld &amp; Celtic Values]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/ange-postecoglou-on-the-tommy-burns-story-bertie-auld-celtic-values/</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/ange-postecoglou-on-the-tommy-burns-story-bertie-auld-celtic-values/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T12:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Glasgow Poet, Erin Boyle chats to Celtic FC Manager, Ange Postecoglou on the Tommy Burns Story, the late great Bertie Auld, his own values and beliefs and the culture at Celtic Football Club on Celtic Fanzine TV. For more Celtic Soul Shorts, interviews and podcasts visit https://www.youtube.com/c/CelticFanzineTV/videos and hit the subscribe button & alarm button so […]
The post Ange Postecoglou on the Tommy Burns Story, Bertie Auld & Celtic Values appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Return to Paradise – Watch Celtic v Blackburn]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/return-to-paradise-watch-celtic-v-blackburn/</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/return-to-paradise-watch-celtic-v-blackburn/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T12:08:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic return to action at Celtic Park for the first time since the SPFL trophy was lifted in the sunshine back in May.  Old Uefa Cup opponents Blackburn Rovers who now find themselves in the English Championship will be the first visitors to Paradise and it will give their fans a taste of a foreign […]
The post Return to Paradise – Watch Celtic v Blackburn appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: The Edouard Michut price tag that may have prompted public Celtic stance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/report-the-edouard-michut-price-tag-that-may-have-prompted-public-celtic-stance/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/report-the-edouard-michut-price-tag-that-may-have-prompted-public-celtic-stance/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T12:06:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this week, it was reported that Celtic were interested in bringing young PSG midfielder Edouard Michut to the club. The 19-year-old Frenchman is expected to leave his current side this summer after expressing his disappointment at the lack of game time. Michet is thought to be highly rated at the European giants, having already ...
The post Report: The Edouard Michut price tag that may have prompted public Celtic stance appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Jota Met Larsson; Brilliant Image Emerges]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/when-jota-met-larsson-brilliant-image-emerges/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/when-jota-met-larsson-brilliant-image-emerges/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T11:47:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We know Jota got around during his summer holidays, but we had no idea this image existed! Celtic posted an image of Jota and Celtic legend Henrik Larsson while they attended the Champions League final in Paris! There’s too much talent in one picture! Looking back at your holiday pictures before returning to Paradise 🏟️ […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Legia Take Action to Save Celtic Friendly]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/legia-take-action-to-save-celtic-friendly/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/legia-take-action-to-save-celtic-friendly/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T11:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legia Warsaw have been forced to cut the price of tickets for Artur Boruc’s farewell match with a poor turnout having been expected.  The club were charging supporters more money for this match than they were for Europa League matches last season which appeared to be one of the reasons why there was such anger […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HART ATTACK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hart-attack/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hart-attack/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T11:36:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART will be encouraged to add his ball-playing skills to Celtic’s attacking outlook. The 75 times-capped England international keeper, who joined the Hoops in a £1million three-year deal from Spurs in August last year, brought on a few moments of anxiety after straying out of his penalty area in the 4-2 win over Banik [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic announce pleasing triple sell out but club need to take action on last season&#039;s trend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-announce-pleasing-triple-sell-out-but-club-need-to-take-action-on-last-seasons-trend/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-announce-pleasing-triple-sell-out-but-club-need-to-take-action-on-last-seasons-trend/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T11:10:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have announced that Parkhead has sold out for the first three home fixtures of the 2022/23 season against Blackburn Rovers, Norwich City and Aberdeen. The Bhoys’ preparations for the new campaign were kicked start after a 10-day pre-season tour of Austria and the Czech Republic. Ange Postecoglou and his squad have been busy getting ...
The post Celtic announce pleasing triple sell out but club need to take action on last season&#039;s trend appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic announce pleasing triple sell out but club need to take action on last season’s trend - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEHgO1G2_L9rPIBQY63XUKKcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMLbFpgY</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-announce-pleasing-triple-sell-out-but-club-need-to-take-action-on-last-seasons-trend/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T11:10:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic announce pleasing triple sell out but club need to take action on last season’s trend  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Rangers are a Poundland double act fuelled by delusional diehards making things worse - Hotline - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEBItgDDXKto3Nx6BNhGA518qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-transfer-news/celtic-rangers-poundland-double-act-27490205"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T11:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Rangers are a Poundland double act fuelled by delusional diehards making things worse - Hotline  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THREE CHEERS: CELTIC SELL OUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/three-cheers-celtic-sell-out/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/three-cheers-celtic-sell-out/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T11:03:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU’S champions will be welcomed back to Celtic Park with three successive sold-out occasions. The Hoops will perform at a packed Parkhead in the friendlies against Blackburn Rovers tomorrow and Norwich City the following week. And the stadium will be rocking again during the Flag Day celebrations as the title-winners kick off the defence [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Men against boys: how did that turn out, Graeme?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/men-against-boys-how-did-that-turn-out-graeme/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/men-against-boys-how-did-that-turn-out-graeme/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T11:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have played Blackburn Rovers 19 times, 17 friendlies and two very memorable competitive games.  The English side travelled north for the first leg of a Uefa Cup tie, on Halloween 2002.  Manager, Graeme Souness waited until after kick-off before walking out of the tunnel, an indication that he expected a hostile reception.  His players [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou reacts to Celtic&#039;s reported plans for Japan pre-season tour]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-reacts-to-celtics-reported-plans-for-japan-pre-season-tour/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-reacts-to-celtics-reported-plans-for-japan-pre-season-tour/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou has responded to reports suggesting that the Hoops are heading for a pre-season tour of Japan in 2023. Of course, the Bhoys are well known across the globe. However, the club’s popularity in Asia has been on the rise in the last 12 months, thanks to the arrival of four Japanese ...
The post Ange Postecoglou reacts to Celtic&#039;s reported plans for Japan pre-season tour appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Has Ange Given The Celtic Board A Deadline For Getting His Remaining Deals Done?]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/has-ange-given-the-celtic-board-a-deadline-for-getting-his-remaining-deals-done/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/has-ange-given-the-celtic-board-a-deadline-for-getting-his-remaining-deals-done/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T10:38:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In spite of a lot of rumours, Celtic haven’t yet one critical piece of transfer business over the line; the signing of a defensive midfield player. The season kicks off in just over a fortnight. What I found interesting about this is that Ange seemed to suggest, the other night, that he expects to have […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Mols namechecks Celtic striker and Manchester United legend Rangers wanted to sign before him - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEGb5gw0fZLceyq_qycXBzQ8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPLfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/michael-mols-namechecks-celtic-striker-24498363"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T10:13:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Mols namechecks Celtic striker and Manchester United legend Rangers wanted to sign before him  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["We tried to impose our intensity" - Celtic star outlines Ange&#039;s pre-season friendly demands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/we-tried-to-impose-our-intensity-giakoumakis-outlines-ange-postecoglous-celtic-pre-season-friendly-demands/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/we-tried-to-impose-our-intensity-giakoumakis-outlines-ange-postecoglous-celtic-pre-season-friendly-demands/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic striker Giorgos Giakoumakis has outlined Hoops boss Ange Postecoglou’s demands of his squad during the pre-season friendly outings in Austria and the Czech Republic. Postecoglou’s squad have spent the last 10-days in Europe as preparation ramped up for the 2022/23 campaign. Alongside the hard work on the training ground, the Bhoys have also faced ...
The post "We tried to impose our intensity" - Celtic star outlines Ange&#039;s pre-season friendly demands appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artur Boruc sees Celtic ticket price slash as Legia Warsaw relent amid fan fury - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEKiMgcdVriJ93iMmvAGhBIEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/artur-boruc-sees-celtic-ticket-27488921"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T09:27:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artur Boruc sees Celtic ticket price slash as Legia Warsaw relent amid fan fury  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moussa Dembele plans Lyon contract expiry as Celtic fear cash windfall nightmare - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiECq18QO04Av_qL6AQtEp5pwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPPfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/moussa-dembele-post-celtic-transfer-24497381"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T09:16:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moussa Dembele plans Lyon contract expiry as Celtic fear cash windfall nightmare  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Postecoglou unaware of Rumoured Celtic Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/postecoglou-unaware-of-rumoured-celtic-plans/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/postecoglou-unaware-of-rumoured-celtic-plans/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T08:46:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou is not aware of any plans for the Hoops to compete in Japan next summer.  Rumours surfaced during the week that talks had been held for the Celtic squad to make the trip east but nothing appears to be concrete. Sides such as Yokohama F Marinos and Vissel Kobe were mentioned as potential […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic confirm that January signing has left the club]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-confirm-that-january-signing-has-left-the-club/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-confirm-that-january-signing-has-left-the-club/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T08:46:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yet another departure from the Celtic FC Women squad has been announced this morning with the news released by the club that Annie Timoney has returned to Glentoran after what turned out to be a short spell at the double cup winners. Annie only joined Celtic at the end of January this year but failed Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic confirm that January signing has left the club - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEP5sxaztarYfWV2C9OJTXo0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-confirm-that-january-signing-has-left-the-club/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T08:46:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic confirm that January signing has left the club  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou hints that interesting Celtic tactical change could be here to stay]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-hints-that-interesting-celtic-tactical-change-could-be-here-to-stay/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-hints-that-interesting-celtic-tactical-change-could-be-here-to-stay/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou has hinted that a tactical change integrated in pre-season could be here to stay. The Hoops have kicked off the summer with a 10-day trip to Austria and Czech Republic, spending plenty of time working on the training ground. The Celtic support have also been given their first look at the ...
The post Ange Postecoglou hints that interesting Celtic tactical change could be here to stay appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou hints that interesting Celtic tactical change could be here to stay - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEJ9dLNWqim--zQGYvcEpODsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMLbFpgY</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-hints-that-interesting-celtic-tactical-change-could-be-here-to-stay/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou hints that interesting Celtic tactical change could be here to stay  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘LEAVE HIM ALONE, HE’S FINE,’ ANGE IN ROGIC PLEA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/leave-him-alone-hes-fine-ange-in-rogic-plea/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/leave-him-alone-hes-fine-ange-in-rogic-plea/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T08:36:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU has moved to quell any anxiety concerning Tom Rogic. The Australian playmaker quit Celtic at the end of the season following an honour-laden nine-and-a-half year at the club. Rogic made a tearful exit following the 6-0 win over Motherwell on the final day of the Premiership-winning campaign at a rocking Parkhead on May [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Legia forced to reduce ticket prices for Celtic’s visit to Warsaw]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/legia-forced-to-reduce-ticket-prices-for-celtics-visit-to-warsaw/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/legia-forced-to-reduce-ticket-prices-for-celtics-visit-to-warsaw/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T08:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fears that Celtic could have ended up playing Legia Warsaw in the Artur Boruc farewell match on Wednesday in front of a tiny crowd appear to have been eased thanks to a major victory for Legia fan-power which has forced a pricing u-turn by the club in order to ensure that the match is played Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Legia forced to reduce ticket prices for Celtic’s visit to Warsaw - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEN7X9RywqB9gSiCAd_3vSH0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/legia-forced-to-reduce-ticket-prices-for-celtics-visit-to-warsaw/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T08:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legia forced to reduce ticket prices for Celtic’s visit to Warsaw  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[17-goal Celtic hero makes exciting vow insisting that his very best is still come]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-hero-giorgos-giakoumakis-makes-exciting-vow-insisting-that-his-very-best-is-still-come/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-hero-giorgos-giakoumakis-makes-exciting-vow-insisting-that-his-very-best-is-still-come/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic striker Giorgos Giakoumakis has insisted that his best is still to come at Parkhead after an impressive end to the 2021/22 campaign. The 27-year-old joined the club on transfer deadline day last summer from Dutch side VVV-Venlo, becoming part of Ange Postecoglou’s recruitment overdrive at Parkhead. There were high expectations of the Greek frontman, ...
The post 17-goal Celtic hero makes exciting vow insisting that his very best is still come appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC ACE AND THE MYSTERY OF THE MISSING TROPHY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-ace-and-the-mystery-of-the-missing-trophy/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-ace-and-the-mystery-of-the-missing-trophy/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T07:54:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GIORGOS GIAKOUMAKIS didn’t exactly hit the ground running in the first half of his debut season at Celtic. The Greek international striker was a £2.5million arrival from Dutch minnows VVV-Venlo in August last year and managed to score just one goal – in the 2-0 win over St Johnstone on October 23 – before the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blackburn Rovers boss expects ‘tough day at the office’ at Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/blackburn-rovers-boss-expects-tough-day-at-the-office-at-celtic-park/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/blackburn-rovers-boss-expects-tough-day-at-the-office-at-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T07:49:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The legend that is Jon Dahl Tomasson, takes his new Blackburn Rovers side to Celtic Park on Saturday to face up an Ange Postecoglou side who have negotiated three away friendly encounters without loss and now return to Paradise looking to put on a show for an expectant home crowd. And Tomasson, who famously arrived Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic managerial candidate expresses his admiration for Ange Postecoglou]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-managerial-candidate-jesse-marsch-expresses-his-admiration-for-ange-postecoglou/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-managerial-candidate-jesse-marsch-expresses-his-admiration-for-ange-postecoglou/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T07:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leeds United manager Jesse Marsch has expressed his admiration for Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou due to his work done around the globe. The American took charge at Elland Road towards the back end of last season and guided his side to safety in the English Premier League on the final day of the campaign. Marsch ...
The post Former Celtic managerial candidate expresses his admiration for Ange Postecoglou appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Leave Him Alone’ Ange’s Brilliant Response to Media Question]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/leave-him-alone-anges-brilliant-response-to-media-question/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/leave-him-alone-anges-brilliant-response-to-media-question/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T07:35:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou is confident that former Celtic midfielder Tom Rogic will find a new club and there is nothing to worry about.  Tom Rogic is still on the hunt for a new club after leaving Celtic at the end of the last campaign. It had been rumoured that he may have been seeking […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Where’s my trophy? Maybe they lost it,” Giorgos Giakoumakis]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/wheres-my-trophy-maybe-they-lost-it-giorgos-giakoumakis/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/wheres-my-trophy-maybe-they-lost-it-giorgos-giakoumakis/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T07:24:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a healthy but competitive rivalry emerging in the Celtic dressing room this season and it can only benefit Celtic as we look to defend our Scottish Premiership title and make a dent in the Champions League. After Kyogo recently went public on his goalscoring targets for the season, now Giorgos Giakoumakis, as reported Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Where’s my trophy? Maybe they lost it,” Giorgos Giakoumakis - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEJRTItB2vowGT5IqizXXfL8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/wheres-my-trophy-maybe-they-lost-it-giorgos-giakoumakis/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T07:24:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Where’s my trophy? Maybe they lost it,” Giorgos Giakoumakis  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Atletico Madrid closing in on right-back target amidst interest in Celtic star]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/report-atletico-madrid-closing-in-on-right-back-target-amidst-interest-in-celtics-josip-juranovic/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/report-atletico-madrid-closing-in-on-right-back-target-amidst-interest-in-celtics-josip-juranovic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T07:14:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Atletico Madrid are reportedly closing in on a move for Udinese right-back Nahuel Molina amidst interest in Celtic’s Josip Juranovic. The Spanish giants have been on the hunt for a full-back this summer, with a gap appearing in Diego Simone’s squad due to exits over the last six months. One of the targets high on ...
The post Report: Atletico Madrid closing in on right-back target amidst interest in Celtic star appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic no risk, no reward aggressive game plan Joe Hart and Co working on - Glasgow Live]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEFEciUBoqo0veKBRIpKXjGsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow96D9CjDOy_QCMPvp0wU</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowlive.co.uk/sport/celtic-no-risk-no-reward-24496102"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T07:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic no risk, no reward aggressive game plan Joe Hart and Co working on  Glasgow Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“There is no risk when you don’t give the ball away,” Ange on Hart playing like Beckenbauer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/there-is-no-risk-when-you-dont-give-the-ball-away-ange-on-hart-playing-like-beckenbauer/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/there-is-no-risk-when-you-dont-give-the-ball-away-ange-on-hart-playing-like-beckenbauer/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T07:01:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s been plenty of reaction on social media among Celtic fans regarding Joe Hart taking such an advanced position on the pitch as Celtic build the play. On at least a couple of occasions during the three match pre-season tour in Austria and Czech Republic, the former English international goalkeeper was lucky not to concede Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘JOCK DIDN’T LIKE GOALIES’: HAPPY 79th BIRTHDAY, EVAN WILLIAMS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/jock-didnt-like-goalies-happy-79th-birthday-evan-williams/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/jock-didnt-like-goalies-happy-79th-birthday-evan-williams/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T06:43:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EVAN WILLIAMS, who celebrates his 79th birthday today, was left in tears after the game of his life on May 6 1970. The goalkeeper, who had been brought to the club from Wolves the previous year, was probably the only Celtic player to emerge from the European Cup Final loss to Feyenoord at the San [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Provides Positive Rogic Update: “People I know say that he’s got no problems”]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/ange-provides-positive-rogic-update-people-i-know-say-that-hes-got-no-problems/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/ange-provides-positive-rogic-update-people-i-know-say-that-hes-got-no-problems/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T06:15:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou provides some very welcome re-assurance regarding former Celtic star Tom Rogic after concern levels regarding the Australian international playmaker were raised by Socceroos boss Graham Arnold who admitted that he had no idea why Rogic pulled out of the recent World Cup qualifier squads and that he had subsequently attempted to contact Rogic Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atletico Madrid closing in on right-back after Fabrizio Romano update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/atletico-madrid-closing-in-on-right-back-after-fabrizio-romano-update/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/atletico-madrid-closing-in-on-right-back-after-fabrizio-romano-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T06:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Atletico Madrid are closing in on Nahuel Molina from Udinese, which means that the Spanish side are unlikely to raid Celtic for Josip Juranovic. According to Italian journalist and transfer specialist Fabrizio Romano, a deal appears to be nearing for the right-back to join the La Liga outfit. Romano himself had said that Diego Simone’s Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to give Ange Postecoglou final pieces of the jigsaw if he is to solve puzzle of being competitive in Champions League]]></title>
        <id>0a74235fde0116232a984634c5039c96</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20279916.celtic-need-give-ange-postecoglou-final-pieces-jigsaw-solve-puzzle-competitive-champions-league/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GIVEN they have already sanctioned a transfer spend of over £17m in this window, it may be churlish to call on the Celtic board to back Ange Postecoglou with even more cash. But here we are.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou shuts down Tom Rogic fears as Celtic boss pleads 'leave him alone' - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiELO8z3DKoWVnrOHARDxlFCcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/ange-postecoglou-shuts-down-tom-27487367"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T05:46:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou shuts down Tom Rogic fears as Celtic boss pleads 'leave him alone'  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: THE BID FOR HAMPDEN GLORY: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Four)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-the-bid-for-hampden-glory-the-tommy-burns-story-part-four/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-the-bid-for-hampden-glory-the-tommy-burns-story-part-four/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T05:43:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS set his sights on silverware in his first season as Celtic manager after returning to the club on July 12 1994. The fans’ favourite had winced as he witnessed the Hoops losing in a dramatic penalty-kick shoot-out to First Division Raith Rovers in the League Cup Final at Ibrox only four months after his [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgos Giakoumakis reveals Celtic mystery over Premiership top scorer award as he asks 'where's my trophy?' - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEJzrI_tKhPdbiEjLA_gpXc0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/giorgos-giakoumakis-reveals-celtic-mystery-27485200"/>
        <updated>2022-07-15T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgos Giakoumakis reveals Celtic mystery over Premiership top scorer award as he asks 'where's my trophy?'  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On This Day: Celtic sign Liel Abada, win against Linfield in Belfast]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/on-this-day-celtic-sign-liel-abada-win-against-linfield-in-belfast/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/on-this-day-celtic-sign-liel-abada-win-against-linfield-in-belfast/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T22:34:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On This Day in 2021, Celtic signed Liel Abada. The Israeli winger scored 15 goals and assisted 11 times across 54 appearances in his debut season, earning plaudits across the campaign. Abada has really taken to life in Glasgow’s East End. The 20-year-old arrived from Maccabi Petah Tikva F.C in a deal worth £4m. The Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On This Day: Celtic sign Liel Abada, win against Linfield in Belfast - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEJjsY6rRawGF7Rf-PpqbvX0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/on-this-day-celtic-sign-liel-abada-win-against-linfield-in-belfast/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T22:34:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On This Day: Celtic sign Liel Abada, win against Linfield in Belfast  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 5 Best Celtic Players Of All-Time]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/the-5-best-celtic-players-of-all-time/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/the-5-best-celtic-players-of-all-time/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T22:05:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of the best footballers in the world have donned the green and white played for Celtic. But which players are the best? Let’s find out… Who Are The Best Celtic Players Of All-Time? Celtic is a football club with a legendary history. Over the years, some amazing players have played for the Glasgow team. Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 5 Best Celtic Players Of All-Time - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEND0NZFrcqUbaB1MUPchBOUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/the-5-best-celtic-players-of-all-time/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T22:05:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5 Best Celtic Players Of All-Time  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou addresses ex Celtic star Tom Rogic concerns and insists there's 'no problem' - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEPIpLsr6WlVeo5Lo0Kh4FTkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPLfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/ange-postecoglou-addresses-ex-celtic-24495494"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T21:44:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou addresses ex Celtic star Tom Rogic concerns and insists there's 'no problem'  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leeds United boss Jesse Marsch hails ‘inspiring’ Ange Postecoglou]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/leeds-united-boss-jesse-marsch-hails-inspiring-ange-postecoglou/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/leeds-united-boss-jesse-marsch-hails-inspiring-ange-postecoglou/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T21:35:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leeds United boss Jesse Marsch has revealed his admiration for Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou, after seeing the love for him first hand as the Yorkshire outfit are currently in Australia on a pre-season tour. Being a like-minded individual, Marsch has enjoyed watching Ange and his Celtic side in action after a League and Cup double Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou gives assurances over welfare of former Celtic star Tom Rogic: ‘I think Tom’s fine mate’]]></title>
        <id>3f1b1d601ceb044aa5890a355536bc39</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20279834.ange-postecoglou-gives-assurances-welfare-former-celtic-star-tom-rogic-i-think-toms-fine-mate/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU has moved to ease concerns over former Celtic midfielder Tom Rogic after Australia head coach Graham Arnold expressed his fears over the 29-year-old’s welfare.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart’s high position could be a feature of Celtic’s play says Ange Postecoglou, as manager highlights need for aggression]]></title>
        <id>eea69eb229f9d8ff3fa79c8a246127a1</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20279846.joe-harts-high-position-feature-celtics-play-says-ange-postecoglou-manager-highlights-need-aggression/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NOT content with pushing Joe Hart out of his comfort zone last season by making him take more responsibility with the ball at his feet, it appeared during Celtic’s pre-season camp in Austria and the Czech Republic that he was attempting to convert the keeper into an auxiliary centre-half.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgos Giakoumakis chasing more honours for Celtic after top scorer crown leads to emotional recognition from hometown]]></title>
        <id>abc781ad406f1d766026e06d06c825e4</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20279854.giorgos-giakoumakis-chasing-honours-celtic-top-scorer-crown-leads-emotional-recognition-hometown/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GIORGOS GIAKOUMAKIS jokes that he is still waiting on his trophy to mark his achievement of being the Scottish Premiership’s top scorer last season, but the Celtic striker received an honour that meant a great deal more to him over the summer in any case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Celtic are considering move for Aaron Mooy]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/why-celtic-are-considering-move-for-aaron-mooy/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/why-celtic-are-considering-move-for-aaron-mooy/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T21:28:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy continues to be linked with a Celtic move. The 31-year-old is said to be in Scotland with his wife as he ponders his next steps following his departure from Chinese club Shanghai Port. Ange Postecoglou remained coy over the links with the Australian Internationalist but you know that behind the scenes, the manager Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banik Ostrava boss praises Premier League quality Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/banik-ostrava-boss-praises-premier-league-quality-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/banik-ostrava-boss-praises-premier-league-quality-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T21:24:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the sun went down in the Czech city of Ostrava last night, Celtic looked back on a job well done as we comprehensively beat Banik whilst getting much needed game time into the legs of a raft of our squad. The final result was 4-2 but the Bhoys should have and could have scored Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange refuses to rule out Celtic move for Banik Ostrava striker Ladislav Almàsi]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/ange-refuses-to-rule-out-celtic-move-for-banik-ostrava-striker-ladislav-almasi/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/ange-refuses-to-rule-out-celtic-move-for-banik-ostrava-striker-ladislav-almasi/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T21:06:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After denying reports linking the club with either Edouard Michut or even Aaron Mooy, Ange Postecoglou refused to deny the links recently to Banik Ostrava striker Ladislav Almàsi after playing against the attacker on Wednesday night. Celtic warmed up for their home friendlies by playing the Czech side to finish off their pre-season training camp. Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Legia take action and bow to demands after Celtic match threatened to become farce]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/legia-take-action-and-bow-to-demands-after-celtic-match-threatened-to-become-farce/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/legia-take-action-and-bow-to-demands-after-celtic-match-threatened-to-become-farce/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T20:40:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legia Warsaw have finally listened to supporter feedback and reduced the ticket prices for the upcoming match against Celtic, which will celebrate the career of Artur Boruc. Legia have been dealing with a furious backlash since they announced the cost of attending the fixture next Wednesday night, with reports indicating the goalkeeper would receive a ...
The post Legia take action and bow to demands after Celtic match threatened to become farce appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Legia take action and bow to demands after Celtic match threatened to become farce - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiENUjpjEAxtOqKAq6X8Wzyb8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMLbFpgY</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/legia-take-action-and-bow-to-demands-after-celtic-match-threatened-to-become-farce/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T20:40:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legia take action and bow to demands after Celtic match threatened to become farce  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jon Dahl Tomasson expecting "tough day at the office" in upcoming Celtic Park visit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/jon-dahl-tomasson-expecting-tough-day-at-the-office-in-upcoming-celtic-park-visit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/jon-dahl-tomasson-expecting-tough-day-at-the-office-in-upcoming-celtic-park-visit/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T20:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jon Dahl Tomasson is happy with the direction of Blackburn Rovers’ pre-season work and is counting on a “tough day at the office” when his team arrive at Celtic Park on Saturday. The English Championship side have already made the trip to Scotland, drawing 1-1 with Dundee at Dens Park last night. That wasn’t as ...
The post Jon Dahl Tomasson expecting "tough day at the office" in upcoming Celtic Park visit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here We Go Again With Another Round Of Calvin Bassey Transfer Bingo.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/here-with-go-again-with-another-round-of-calvin-bassey-transfer-bingo/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/here-with-go-again-with-another-round-of-calvin-bassey-transfer-bingo/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T19:57:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We can’t, surely, have gone through so many teams that we’re now with Ajax and Brighton can we? Good God, man, that’s a strange place to be in. But that’s what the headline writers are saying tonight, that both of those clubs want the Englishman. None has shifted from that notorious £25 million valuation, which […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leeds United manager makes stunning Celtic claim - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>CAIiELsmxuVh97aHNFWCFx-mazoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4KKJCzCv9JoDMICkoAY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2022/07/14/leeds-united-manager-celtic-claim/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T19:27:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leeds United manager makes stunning Celtic claim  The Celtic Bhoys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evolving TV rights scene for Celtic as Nordic company enter talks to buy familiar broadcaster]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/evolving-tv-rights-scene-for-celtic-as-nordic-company-enter-talks-to-buy-familiar-broadcaster/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/evolving-tv-rights-scene-for-celtic-as-nordic-company-enter-talks-to-buy-familiar-broadcaster/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T19:10:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here at 67 Hail Hail, we know Celtic supporters love keeping up-to-date with the media scene concerning Scottish football and ultimately the Bhoys. A very interesting snippet of news emerged this week that could end up with direct changes to broadcasts of some Celtic matches while offering an interesting look into the more distant future. ...
The post Evolving TV rights scene for Celtic as Nordic company enter talks to buy familiar broadcaster appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Media Has Failed In A Pitiful Attempt To Turn Celtic Fans Against Our New Coach.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/the-media-has-failed-in-a-pitiful-attempt-to-turn-celtic-fans-against-our-new-coach/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/the-media-has-failed-in-a-pitiful-attempt-to-turn-celtic-fans-against-our-new-coach/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T18:41:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every single day the media finds a new low point, and yesterday one paper – and I can’t even be bothered to name the rag in question because most of you already know which one it was, it’s the one it always is these days – decided to dig up an eons old video of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Technical maturity", "Beautiful football"; Czech media react to Celtic&#039;s win over Banik Ostrava]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/technical-maturity-beautiful-football-czech-media-react-to-celtics-win-over-banik-ostrava/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/technical-maturity-beautiful-football-czech-media-react-to-celtics-win-over-banik-ostrava/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For Celtic, last night’s match was just one stop on the way to facing Aberdeen at the end of July. While Banik Ostrava are also in the midst of pre-match preparations, the friendly held much more meaning for them. That was clear from the atmosphere and spectacle on Wednesday night before kick-off even occurred, but ...
The post "Technical maturity", "Beautiful football"; Czech media react to Celtic&#039;s win over Banik Ostrava appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s Jota Gets Official Champions League Twitter Treatment]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtics-jota-gets-official-champions-league-twitter-treatment/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtics-jota-gets-official-champions-league-twitter-treatment/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T18:26:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jota has been given VIP treatment from the Champions League Twitter account. The account, which has 42 million followers, posted Celtic’s latest signing at Paradise with the hooped scarf held above his head. 🍀 Celtic hero Jota back at Paradise 🍀#UCL pic.twitter.com/odwOhiLU2I — UEFA Champions League (@ChampionsLeague) July 14, 2022 After a fantastic season last […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic fringe player who will welcome Postecoglou&#039;s latest transfer stance - opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/yosuke-ideguchis-celtic-opportunity-has-finally-arrived/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/yosuke-ideguchis-celtic-opportunity-has-finally-arrived/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are few more exhausting things for a football fan than transfer rumours which last an entire summer, only for the move to never materialise. It’s far less incensing when potentially exciting transfer links are extinguished early, before YouTube compilations can be fawned over and potential flight schedules checked. The dust had barely settled on ...
The post The Celtic fringe player who will welcome Postecoglou&#039;s latest transfer stance - opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yosuke Ideguchi’s Celtic opportunity has finally arrived - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEImHYLNGoMb4s0CeLb4-Yz4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMOHTpgY</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/yosuke-ideguchis-celtic-opportunity-has-finally-arrived/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yosuke Ideguchi’s Celtic opportunity has finally arrived  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘He’s Had His Chance’ – McAvennie Writes off Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/hes-had-his-chance-mcavennie-writes-off-celtic-star/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/hes-had-his-chance-mcavennie-writes-off-celtic-star/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T17:59:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were close to offloading Chris Jullien a few weeks ago, but his move to Schalke fell through after personal terms couldn’t be agreed upon. Since the move fell through, he’s been heavily involved in Ange’s pre-season teams after Carl Starfelt’s injury has ruled him out for the preparations for Celtic’s title defence. The manager […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic set the record straight on &#039;wild goose chase&#039; that got some a bit excited]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-set-the-record-straight-on-wild-goose-chase/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-set-the-record-straight-on-wild-goose-chase/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T17:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has moved to clarify reports about Celtic preparing a bid for Paris Saint-Germain talent Edouard Michut – put simply, it doesn’t look like it’s happening. The online Celtic support, including myself, got pretty excited yesterday when reports from Sky Sports and Fabrizio Romano indicated the Bhoys were in a good position to land ...
The post Celtic set the record straight on &#039;wild goose chase&#039; that got some a bit excited appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic set the record straight on ‘wild goose chase’ - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>1488230735</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-set-the-record-straight-on-wild-goose-chase/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T17:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic set the record straight on ‘wild goose chase’  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News
Edouard Michut Celtic transfer quashed by Ange Postecoglou as he addresses Aaron Mooy links  Football Scotland
Incredible twist in Edouard Michut to Celtic transfer saga  The Celtic Bhoys
Edouard Michut: Celtic targeting a £2m deal for Paris Saint-Germain's teenage midfielder  Sky Sports
‘Advanced Talks’ Fabrizio Romano Confirms Exciting Celtic Bid  CeltsAreHere
View Full coverage on Google News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic shopping in the right markets as 2021 target attracts strong EPL interest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-shopping-in-the-right-markets-as-2021-target-attracts-strong-epl-interest/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-shopping-in-the-right-markets-as-2021-target-attracts-strong-epl-interest/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T16:40:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An early Ange Postecoglou transfer target for Celtic is attracting interest from the Premier League, a year after he was touted for a move to Glasgow. Mario Vuskovic, then of Hajduk Split, was allegedly left out of the Croatian side’s matchday squad anticipating a move to Celtic last July. That came after other Croatian reports ...
The post Celtic shopping in the right markets as 2021 target attracts strong EPL interest appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[&#039;Out the door&#039; - McAvennie delivers damning Celtic transfer claim involving &#039;intelligent&#039; ace]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-albian-ajeti-fausto-vera-transfer-gossip-news/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-albian-ajeti-fausto-vera-transfer-gossip-news/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T16:35:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Scotland striker Frank McAvennie has delivered a damning verdict on the future of Celtic forward Albian Ajeti.  The lowdown: Flattered to deceive Signed from West Ham for £5m in 2020 (Sky Sports), the Switzerland international joined the Hoops having failed to score in 12 appearances for the Premier League club. However, the 25-year-old had […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/the-celtic-exchange/</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/the-celtic-exchange/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T16:14:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of our favourite Celtic Podcasts here at More than 90 Minutes Celtic Fanzine is The Celtic Exchange and after their pre-season break the Bhoys are back. Tino Miff & James discuss Celtic’s Transfer Ins & Outs, the evolution of Ange Postecoglou’s Celtic and give their thoughts on the teams pre-season preparations so far! https://celticfanzine.com/product-category/monthly-print-subscription/ […]
The post The Celtic Exchange appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou addresses Wednesday Celtic absence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-ange-postecoglou-eases-reo-hatate-concerns/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-ange-postecoglou-eases-reo-hatate-concerns/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou has eased any concerns regarding Reo Hatate’s absence from Wednesday’s friendly win over Banik Ostrava. The Japan international missed the 4-2 victory, the match marking the Czech club’s centenary celebrations, but as reported by Football Scotland, Postecoglou confirmed that Hatate’s injury was only minor. The Australian said: “He had a slight ...
The post Ange Postecoglou addresses Wednesday Celtic absence appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Postecoglou ‘Buzzing’ for Celtic Support]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/postecoglou-buzzing-for-celtic-support/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/postecoglou-buzzing-for-celtic-support/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a ten-day training camp in Austria and the Czech Republic has come to an end for Celtic, they will return to Celtic Park to take on Blackburn Rovers at the weekend. The 12:30 kick-off has Ange Postecoglou “buzzing”, after playing three matches on the bounce without the Celtic fans. It was a great atmosphere […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Flag Day Tickets On Sale]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-flag-day-tickets-on-sale/</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-flag-day-tickets-on-sale/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T15:55:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A full house is expected at Celtic Park for Flag Day for the opening game of the new season after season tickets sold out a few weeks back. Celtic have just put a limited number of tickets on sale for the game. https://celticfanzine.com/product-category/monthly-print-subscription/ Kick-off v Aberdeen is 4:30pm, Sunday July 31. Match tickets are on […]
The post Celtic Flag Day Tickets On Sale appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fausto Vera Latest]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/fausto-vera-latest/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/fausto-vera-latest/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T15:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s hopes of securing Argentine midfielder Fausto Vera have been significantly boosted as Ange Postecoglou carries on the search for a new midfielder. Corinthians had bid for the player, but Vera’s club Argentinos Juniors rejected the approach with the fee £2 million short of their asking price. [The Daily Record] The Brazilian team have since […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Training Day Update]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-training-day-update/</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-training-day-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T15:32:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans who are planning on attending the training session at Celtic Park on Monday, July 18 should note that the time has now changed to 12 noon start and not 11am as previously advertised. https://celticfanzine.com/product-category/monthly-print-subscription/ Free tickets are available to all season ticket holders and can be collected from all Celtic Stores. Supporters will […]
The post Celtic Training Day Update appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Postecoglou Fails to Rule Out Potential Transfer]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/postecoglou-fails-to-rule-out-potential-transfer/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/postecoglou-fails-to-rule-out-potential-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T15:22:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic has been linked to Banik Ostrava striker Ladislav Almási in recent weeks. Of course, Celtic lined up against the side on Wednesday night, with the Celtic-linked man featuring. Ange Postecoglou quizzed on the speculation regarding Celtic and Almási. The manager failed to give a definitive answer, insisting that his club are linked to new […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star cuts through concerning rumours with definitive intent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-defender-cuts-through-concerning-rumours-with-champions-league-intent/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-defender-cuts-through-concerning-rumours-with-champions-league-intent/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T14:52:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic right-back Josip Juranovic has committed his immediate future to the club amid speculation linking him with a move to Atletico Madrid. Speaking to Croatian outlet RTL, Juranovic said: “I hope there was something in the stories, but honestly I didn’t even ask our manager or anything about it. I didn’t care. “I have to ...
The post Celtic star cuts through concerning rumours with definitive intent appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Postecoglou gives straight answer over Celtic's 'interest' in Ladislav Almasi - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEBEwEOj9PJabsJo3DD76nWMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/ladislav-almasi-celtic-transfer-addressed-27483100"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T14:29:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Postecoglou gives straight answer over Celtic's 'interest' in Ladislav Almasi  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou&#039;s new signing luxury is fine reward for trust in much-improved Celtic talent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/ange-postecoglous-new-signing-luxury-is-fine-reward-for-trust-in-much-improved-celtic-talent/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/ange-postecoglous-new-signing-luxury-is-fine-reward-for-trust-in-much-improved-celtic-talent/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Of all the priority positions for recruiting this transfer window, arguably none were as critical as left-back. Greg Taylor has been one of the most consistent players for Ange Postecoglou’s Celtic, adapting near-seamlessly to the inverted full back role. The 24 year old’s reading of the game and positional awareness have been critical to the ...
The post Ange Postecoglou&#039;s new signing luxury is fine reward for trust in much-improved Celtic talent appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Ange’s Answer On Celtic’s Latest Striker Link Might Well Be Significant.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/blogs/why-anges-answer-on-celtics-latest-striker-link-might-well-be-significant/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/blogs/why-anges-answer-on-celtics-latest-striker-link-might-well-be-significant/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T13:57:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a transfer story which took me somewhat by surprise, as I had not heard of any Celtic interest in the Banik Ostrava striker Ladislav Almasi, who we played against yesterday. (He wore the number 99 shirt.) But it’s a strong enough rumour that Ange was asked about it directly after the match, by […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou earns 'inspiring' tag from EPL boss once linked with role - Glasgow Live]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEB7mqpg5QCUYxG7Fe4CWzncqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow96D9CjDOy_QCMPvp0wU</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowlive.co.uk/sport/celtic-boss-ange-postecoglou-earns-24489938"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T13:27:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou earns 'inspiring' tag from EPL boss once linked with role  Glasgow Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Celtic vs Blackburn Rovers on TV? Channel, stream and kick off details ahead of pre season clash - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEGp2O4P-EPzASvGNCDohwCAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/celtic-vs-blackburn-rovers-tv-27479670"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T12:12:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is Celtic vs Blackburn Rovers on TV? Channel, stream and kick off details ahead of pre season clash  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How The Scotsman Tried To Pour Cold Water On Celtic’s Red Hot Display Yesterday.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/how-the-scotsman-tried-to-pour-cold-water-on-celtics-red-hot-display-yesterday/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/how-the-scotsman-tried-to-pour-cold-water-on-celtics-red-hot-display-yesterday/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T12:10:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is going to be a vintage day for writing about the media. My inbox has a bunch of stories from around the press in Scotland in it, and I’m going to get to them one at a time. Right now I want to marvel at the dismal effort from The Scotsman last night which […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preview: Celtic vs. Blackburn Rovers - prediction, team news, lineups]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sportsmole.co.uk/football/celtic/preview/preview-celtic-vs-blackburn-prediction-team-news-lineups_490025.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.sportsmole.co.uk/football/celtic/preview/preview-celtic-vs-blackburn-prediction-team-news-lineups_490025.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T11:45:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sports Mole previews Saturday's Club Friendlies 1 clash between Celtic and Blackburn Rovers, including predictions, team news and possible lineups.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic&#039;s next transfer steps: How to turn a good window into a great one]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/celtics-next-transfer-steps-how-to-turn-a-good-window-into-a-great-one/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/celtics-next-transfer-steps-how-to-turn-a-good-window-into-a-great-one/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What a difference a year makes. On this day in 2021, Celtic played out a 0-0 draw in a friendly against Bristol City, their third game of pre-season, in preparation for a crunch Champions League qualifier against FC Midtjylland, with only one confirmed and available new signing; Liel Abada. In contrast, all four of Celtic’s ...
The post Celtic&#039;s next transfer steps: How to turn a good window into a great one appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers delusion is like a Jim Carrey film and Celtic fans can smell fake title boast fear - Hotline - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEBKr30rc5XzYAAtJGBCGaUQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/rangers-delusion-like-jim-carrey-27480874"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T11:28:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers delusion is like a Jim Carrey film and Celtic fans can smell fake title boast fear - Hotline  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calmness surrounds Celtic since Ange has been Around]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/calmness-surrounds-celtic-since-ange-has-been-around/</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/calmness-surrounds-celtic-since-ange-has-been-around/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T11:13:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic continued their Pre-season friendly at the Městský Stadion, Ostrava, Czech Republic, the home of Banik Ostrava. Celtic were backed by 100 hardcore fans who made the journey to cheer on the bhoys. https://celticfanzine.com/product-category/monthly-print-subscription/ After a slow start Celtic found themselves a goal down after 7 minutes but by the 13th minute they were back […]
The post Calmness surrounds Celtic since Ange has been Around appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[&#039;Seems like a safe signing&#039; - Sky Sports man makes Celtic claim on &#039;really intelligent&#039; target]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-george-baldock-josip-juranovic-transfer-gossip-news-2/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-george-baldock-josip-juranovic-transfer-gossip-news-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T11:10:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Scotland manager Alex McLeish has delivered his verdict on Celtic‘s pursuit of Sheffield United defender George Baldock.  The lowdown: Celtic interested in Baldock This comes after the Hoops were once again linked with a move for the Greece international recently, having previously been keen on the experienced right back. The 29-year-old is believed to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic star Moussa Dembele 'holds transfer talks' with Manchester United]]></title>
        <id>11a13740204338470d1b7528af280744</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20278930.ex-celtic-star-moussa-dembele-holds-transfer-talks-manchester-united/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T11:05:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REPORTS have emerged stating that former Celtic star Moussa Dembele has held transfer talks with Manchester United.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“I have one final dream left at Legia and that is to have a full stadium,” Boruc’s plea]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/i-have-one-final-dream-left-at-legia-and-that-is-to-have-a-full-stadium-borucs-plea/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/i-have-one-final-dream-left-at-legia-and-that-is-to-have-a-full-stadium-borucs-plea/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T11:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou talked up the benefits of avoiding bounce games at training grounds, or summer friendlies in empty stadiums as he looked back with some satisfaction last night in the two games over the past five days against Rapid Vienna in Austrian capital last Saturday and then against Banik Ostrava in Czech Republic yesterday afternoon Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rare wisdom about making mistakes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rare-wisdom-about-making-mistakes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rare-wisdom-about-making-mistakes/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T11:01:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In many years of writing here I’ve never before used a piece of Charlie Nicholas wisdom; there is not too much to choose from.  One of his comments stuck in my head, though.  A year after Celtic won at Arsenal in the Pierce O’Leary Testimonial, but went on to lose the league, Arsenal thumped Celtic [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 key Celtic impressions from inside training camp on Hart's new role, Bernabei impact and Jullien latest - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEMxF3JrT7IPvmMCmSAvo7a0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/5-key-celtic-impressions-inside-27479818"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T10:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[5 key Celtic impressions from inside training camp on Hart's new role, Bernabei impact and Jullien latest  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Sends Thursday Social Media Message]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/kyogo-sends-thursday-social-media-message/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/kyogo-sends-thursday-social-media-message/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T10:53:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Furuhashi has sent fans a message as Celtic reach the halfway point of pre-season. The Japanese striker was on target in Celtic’s last game, when the side emerged victorious 4-2. Some brilliant movement in the box allowed Kyogo to get into space leaving the defenders scrambling. As Celtic gears up for a big season, […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Update Open Training Day Details]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-update-open-training-day-details/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-update-open-training-day-details/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T10:27:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic has updated the start time for their open training day, citing rail disruption on the bank holiday as the reason. The Bhoys will begin training at noon on Monday, with season ticket holders able to attend for free. It was part of the many promises for renewing a season ticket after the season behind […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRANSFER UPDATE: ‘I’M PRETTY HAPPY WITH THE PROGRESS WE’RE MAKING,’ ADMITS ANGE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/transfer-update-im-pretty-happy-with-the-progress-were-making-admits-ange/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/transfer-update-im-pretty-happy-with-the-progress-were-making-admits-ange/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T10:15:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU insists he will not be rushed into signings as speculation goes into overdrive. The Celtic boss has six weeks to add new faces before the transfer window closes at midnight on August 31 until re-opening in January. Postecoglou has already spent something in the region of £17.5million in signing Cameron Carter-Vickers, Filipe Jota, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“It was Atletico Madrid after all, but I’m at a big club already, Celtic,” Juranovic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/it-was-atletico-madrid-after-all-but-im-at-a-big-club-already-celtic-juranovic/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/it-was-atletico-madrid-after-all-but-im-at-a-big-club-already-celtic-juranovic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T10:09:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not sure how to take the latest comments from Josip Juranovic, although whatever happens Celtic are well placed to benefit. Speaking about the links to Atletico Madrid over the close-season – another story that was a Sky Sports exclusive incidentally – Juranovic is clearly flattered to be linked with the Spanish giants and reckons that Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star Josip Juranovic addresses transfer speculation amid Atletico Madrid interest]]></title>
        <id>e5bcc5009b78bec4240cc427e9b23dd8</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20278683.celtic-star-josip-juranovic-addresses-transfer-speculation-amid-atletico-madrid-interest/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T10:07:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOSIP JURANOVIC admits he's flattered to have been linked with a huge move to Atletico Madrid, but he's just desperate to play in the Champions League with Celtic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero Moussa Dembele holds 'secret' Manchester United transfer talks - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEAXw-Dn2KfIU4S7iGNklWMYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-transfer-news/moussa-dembele-holds-secret-manchester-27479519"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T10:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero Moussa Dembele holds 'secret' Manchester United transfer talks  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I DIDN’T CARE,’ JURANOVIC DISMISSES TRANSFER TALK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-didnt-care-juranovic-dismisses-transfer-talk/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-didnt-care-juranovic-dismisses-transfer-talk/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T09:54:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOSIP JURANOVIC has dismissed speculation linking him with a summer move to Atletico Madrid. The Croatian international right-back insisted he “didn’t care” about the transfer stories as he remained focused on playing for Celtic as he looked forward to performing in the Champions League group stages. Plus the defender, who joined the Hoops a year [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artur Boruc Pleads with Legia Support]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/artur-boruc-pleads-with-legia-support/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/artur-boruc-pleads-with-legia-support/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T09:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic travel to Poland next week to take on Legia Warsaw to bid Artur Boruc farewell, but there are fears that the stadium could be near empty. The Polish club has released their ticket sales for the match, with only 3,000 sold so far. Celtic faces the prospect of playing in a stadium with only […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['It is inspiring' - Leeds United boss on Celtic links and Ange Postecoglou admiration]]></title>
        <id>3767898</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/it-is-inspiring-leeds-united-boss-on-celtic-links-and-ange-postecoglou-admiration-3767898"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T09:41:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leeds United boss Jesse Marsch has revealed his admiration for Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou, while addressing speculation previously linking him with the job.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Champions League group of death and ideal draw scenarios examined - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEEn5H2o0C0bIrSjfF0gy9tQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPPfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/celtic-champions-league-group-death-24485014"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T09:29:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Champions League group of death and ideal draw scenarios examined  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Juranovic Responds to Athletico Madrid Speculation]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/juranovic-responds-to-athletico-madrid-speculation/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/juranovic-responds-to-athletico-madrid-speculation/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T09:24:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Josip Juranovic has responded to speculation regarding his Celtic future. the player has been linked to Premier League clubs, with Athletico Madrid also keen to sign the Celtic player. However, Juranovic isn’t set on a move, admitting he’s happy to be at a “big club”. The news reported by Fabrizio Romano that the 26-year-old is […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou praised by Leeds' Jesse Marsch]]></title>
        <id>0dcd571d844f5417e56a1ec3f5019466</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20278530.celtic-manager-ange-postecoglou-praised-leeds-jesse-marsch/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T09:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LEEDS boss Jesse Marsch has praised Ange Postecoglou and his coaching methods.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artur Boruc in Celtic farewell plea as he begs stayaway Legia fans to turn up even if they want to ABUSE him - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEJXdM93rUAlVgPA61c8BKZcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/artur-boruc-celtic-farewell-plea-27478885"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T09:16:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artur Boruc in Celtic farewell plea as he begs stayaway Legia fans to turn up even if they want to ABUSE him  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfers: Update provided on 3 stars linked with Scottish champions]]></title>
        <id>3767751</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-transfers-update-provided-on-3-stars-linked-with-scottish-champions-3767751"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T08:57:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou is still looking to add to his squad ahead of the start of the Scottish Premiership season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic 'boosted' in bid to sign Fausto Vera as Corinthians pull out of offer]]></title>
        <id>ac4f788c513f14bad99d3d36c4e09023</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20278431.celtic-boosted-bid-sign-fausto-vera-corinthians-pull-offer/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T08:53:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC are said to have received a boost in their hopes of landing Fausto Vera this summer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jesse Marsch Comments on Ange and Celtic’s Success]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/jesse-marsch-comments-on-ange-and-celtics-success/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/jesse-marsch-comments-on-ange-and-celtics-success/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T08:45:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were linked with appointing Jesse Marsch to succeed Neil Lennon last year, but the American manager had decided to take on a challenge at RB Leipzig at the time. He failed to impress with the German club and was sacked halfway through the season. However, he wasted no time and joined Leeds while they […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jesse Marsch salutes 'inspiring' Celtic as Leeds boss raves about Ange Postecoglou's methods - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEL5hxfYkg5A9knjXT2b4gloqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-transfer-news/jesse-marsch-salutes-inspiring-celtic-27478273"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T08:19:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jesse Marsch salutes 'inspiring' Celtic as Leeds boss raves about Ange Postecoglou's methods  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Terribly difficult"; Banik Ostrava boss fronts up on facing Celtic, makes EPL comparison]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/terribly-difficult-banik-ostrava-boss-fronts-up-on-facing-celtic-makes-epl-comparison/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/terribly-difficult-banik-ostrava-boss-fronts-up-on-facing-celtic-makes-epl-comparison/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T08:11:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Banik Ostrava boss Pavel Vrba was left impressed with the performance of Celtic on Wednesday night after watching his team fall to a 4-2 defeat. There was a party atmosphere in the Mestsky Stadion, with Banik celebrating their 100th anniversary. However, Celtic were in no mood to pander to sentimentality, producing a pretty ruthless display. ...
The post "Terribly difficult"; Banik Ostrava boss fronts up on facing Celtic, makes EPL comparison appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: FRUGAL McCANN AND BIG PIERRE: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Three)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-frugal-mccann-and-big-pierre-the-tommy-burns-story-part-three/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-frugal-mccann-and-big-pierre-the-tommy-burns-story-part-three/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T08:10:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS had to revive Celtic after their sensational penalty-kick loss to Raith Rovers in the League Cup Final at Ibrox on the fateful Sunday afternoon of November 27 1994. The shock waves reverberated around the whole of football and Parkhead and the manager realised he would have to spend big money to help turn [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fausto Vera 'auction' dismissed as Celtic get transfer boost over Corinthians hardline stance - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEC3mdwlPqaSi3qLGAv7veJ4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/fausto-vera-auction-dismissed-celtic-27478308"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T08:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fausto Vera 'auction' dismissed as Celtic get transfer boost over Corinthians hardline stance  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“He had a slight knock,” Reo Hatate mystery solved by Celtic manager]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/he-had-a-slight-knock-reo-hatate-mystery-solved-by-celtic-manager/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/he-had-a-slight-knock-reo-hatate-mystery-solved-by-celtic-manager/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T07:52:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first thing we noticed when the Celtic team to play against FC Banik Ostrava yesterday afternoon was posted on social media was that neither Reo Hatate or Daizen Maeda were listed in the squad. We reported: “Neither Reo Hatate not his fellow countryman Daizen Maeda are listed in the squad for today’s game, perhaps Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[POSTECOGLOU PRAISES CELTIC ‘ENERGY’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/postecoglou-praises-celtic-energy/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/postecoglou-praises-celtic-energy/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T07:44:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU is “buzzing” after Celtic’s 4-2 win over Banik Ostrava – and the Hoops boss reckons his players are ready to hit the ground running when the competitive action kicks off. The champions hoisted their strike rate to 14 goals in three games in Austria and the Czech Republic with Kyogo Furuhashi, Matt O’Riley, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate’s Absence Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/reo-hatates-absence-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/reo-hatates-absence-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T07:27:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou has confirmed that Reo Hatate had picked up a knock in training, but it was nothing too serious. The midfielder has been brilliant so far in pre-season, looking promising for the upcoming season. After his performance dipped because of his hectic never-ending season, Celtic fans are set to see the best […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lubo Moravcik pictured at Banik Ostrava v Celtic match]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/lubo-moravcik-pictured-at-banik-ostrava-v-celtic-match/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/lubo-moravcik-pictured-at-banik-ostrava-v-celtic-match/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T07:23:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As gifts go, Lubomir Moravcik is certainly one that God blessed Celtic Football Club immeasurably with when he saw fit to deliver the former Saint Etienne man to us in 1998. Spending four years at the club, Lubo became a cult hero and an icon of modern Celtic and set the standard alongside our King Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou Quashes Another Celtic Transfer Rumour]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/ange-postecoglou-stops-celtic-rumour-in-its-tracks/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/ange-postecoglou-stops-celtic-rumour-in-its-tracks/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T07:15:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic has been linked to Aaron Mooy after he had his contract in China ripped up. However, despite some links to Celtic, the Aussie midfielder won’t be pulling on the green and white hoops next season Ange Postecoglou has confirmed. The midfielder was heavily linked last summer, so suggestions that he could be Glasgow bound […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Yeah, good player, but no” – Ange trashes Sky Sports Michut to Celtic story]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/yeah-good-player-but-no-ange-trashes-sky-sports-michut-to-celtic-story/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/yeah-good-player-but-no-ange-trashes-sky-sports-michut-to-celtic-story/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-14T06:58:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou last tonight denied that Celtic are in the running for either Edouard Michut or Aaron Mooy. However, the manager did reveal he would like to bring in two more players and that he is also willing to wait if need be, but is nevertheless happy with the progress made with player registrations this Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>