<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-10-12T00:43:51.032Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic tipped to be out of sight of Rangers with £60m windfall]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44818</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/11/celtic-tipped-sight-rangers-windfall/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T22:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a lot of football still to be played in this season’s Scottish Premiership campaighn. Celtic have got off to a great early start with a seven-point lead over the Rangers already The Hoops will be looking to build on that lead over the coming weeks as the Ibrox club still look for a […]
Celtic tipped to be out of sight of Rangers with £60m windfall - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fraser Forster picks three Celtic heroes in all-time team]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44846</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/11/fraser-forster-three-celtic-heroes/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T21:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fraser Forster certainly has an interesting place in Celtic history. He was superb during his time at the club and put in some memorable performances. He is definitely one of the best goalkeepers that the Hoops have had since the turn of the century. But then, the manner of his exit the second time around […]
Fraser Forster picks three Celtic heroes in all-time team - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic make announcement about Atletico Madrid game]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44842</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/11/celtic-announcement-atletico-madrid-game/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T19:30:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have not made the start to their Champions League campaign that they would have been hoping for. They find themselves sitting at the bottom of their group, after the first two games and have tougher tests ahead. To be fair, the performances have not been bad but the results certainly have not gone in […]
Celtic make announcement about Atletico Madrid game - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I still don't think': Celtic sent Reo Hatate message that fans will just love]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177268</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-still-dont-think-celtic-sent-reo-hatate-message-that-fans-will-just-love/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate’s engine is seriously starting to warm up now as Brendan Rodgers’ Celtic continue to dominate at the top of the Premiership table. It...
The post 'I still don't think': Celtic sent Reo Hatate message that fans will just love appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unexpected Celtic player could be next to get new contract]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44839</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/11/unexpected-celtic-player-new-contract/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T18:02:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that things change very quickly in football and it does not take long for careers to completely turn around. We have already seen this more than once since the arrival of Brendan Rodgers for a second run as Celtic manager. The first unexpected contract extension that the club handed […]
Unexpected Celtic player could be next to get new contract - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giakoumakis vs Celtic star, Lennoxtown bragging rights; three international matches to watch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177196</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/giakoumakis-vs-celtic-star-lennoxtown-bragging-rights-three-international-matches-to-watch/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The international action gets underway on Thursday and there’s plenty of Celtic interest. Okay, it may not match the joy of actually seeing Brendan Rodgers’...
The post Giakoumakis vs Celtic star, Lennoxtown bragging rights; three international matches to watch appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic ready to reject Glasgow Derby request from Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44835</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/11/celtic-ready-glasgow-derby-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T12:30:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are sitting comfortably at the top of the Scottish Premiership table right now, seven points ahead of the Rangers, who managed to make it to second after a win over St Mirren at the weekend. The Ibrox club are without a manager right now, after showing Michael Beale the exit door, but are expected […]
Celtic ready to reject Glasgow Derby request from Rangers - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Wednesday October 11: An Oath Of Hypocrisy]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18517</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18517"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T12:19:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a couple of things that have been in the news since I last sat down at the keys, and there seems to be a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Malph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers picks his best match as Celtic manager and it's not a demolition derby]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177180</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-picks-his-best-match-as-celtic-manager-and-its-not-a-derby-demolition/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has picked his best match as manager of Celtic, and it wasn’t one of his derby wins. The Hoops boss earned ten wins...
The post Brendan Rodgers picks his best match as Celtic manager and it's not a demolition derby appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic get a big allocation for upcoming clash but a scheduling question remains]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177220</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-get-a-big-allocation-for-hibernian-clash-but-a-scheduling-question-remains/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After some recent frustrations over away allocations, it was good to hear of a big Celtic support being welcomed at Easter Road. Yesterday, I spoke...
The post Celtic get a big allocation for upcoming clash but a scheduling question remains appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premiership vote would be convenient resolution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113040</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/premiership-vote-would-be-convenient-resolution/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T11:03:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reports suggest the Scottish Premiership could provide Newco with a face-saving de-escalation by holding a vote to mandate a fixed percentage of ticket sales for visiting fans. Celtic were permitted 7,000 fans at Ibrox (in what was known as “the Celtic end”) for decades before the drubbings and celebrations became too much for the home [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Young Celtic player gives first interview since summer move; a name to keep an eye on]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177213</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/young-celtic-player-gives-first-interview-since-summer-move-a-name-to-keep-an-eye-on/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Young Celtic player Liam Bonetig has given his first interview since signing for the Hoops during the summer. The centre-back joined from Western Sydney Wanderers...
The post Young Celtic player gives first interview since summer move; a name to keep an eye on appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou eyeing move for former Celtic favourite]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44832</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/11/ange-postecoglou-eyeing-move-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T10:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans were left disappointed when Ange Postecoglou left the club just days after guiding them to the domestic treble last season in order to join Tottenham Hotspur. The Australian had gotten his big chance in Europe with the Hoops and taken it with both hands, winning five trophies in two seasons and playing a […]
Ange Postecoglou eyeing move for former Celtic favourite - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Running for Player of the Year’: Tam McManus says Celtic 25-year-old has never played better]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177253</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/running-for-player-of-the-year-tam-mcmanus-says-celtic-25-year-old-has-never-played-better/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tam McManus thinks Reo Hatate has just produced the best performance of his Celtic career. Brendan Rodgers’ side continued to dominate at the top of...
The post 'Running for Player of the Year’: Tam McManus says Celtic 25-year-old has never played better appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Premiership clubs consider new allocation rule but there's an obvious issue for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177247</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/premiership-clubs-consider-new-allocation-rule-but-theres-an-obvious-issue-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Premiership clubs are considering bringing in a new rule that would guarantee a fixed percentage of stadia to away fans, and Celtic are likely to...
The post Report: Premiership clubs consider new allocation rule but there's an obvious issue for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘How can you’: Kieran Tierney makes Ronny Deila-Celtic claim after Scotland question]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177225</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/how-can-you-kieran-tierney-makes-ronny-deila-celtic-claim-after-scotland-question/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T07:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Ronny Deila at Celtic to Mikel Arteta at Arsenal. Kieran Tierney is grateful for the managers and coaches who have made him the player...
The post ‘How can you’: Kieran Tierney makes Ronny Deila-Celtic claim after Scotland question appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘OUT OF ORDER,’ DALGLISH VERDICT ON CELTIC EURO MISSION]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113034</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/out-of-order-dalglish-verdict-on-celtic-euro-mission/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T06:56:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KENNY DALGLISH reckons Celtic need a rub of the green and to show perseverance if they are to get their rewards in the Champions League. The Hoops goalscoring great has kept an eye on his old club’s exploits in Europe’s elite competition this season which sees them bottom of Group E after back-to-back defeats against [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SFA chief delivers disappointing Hampden news; why Celtic Park wasn't chosen for Euro bid]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177168</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/sfa-chief-delivers-disappointing-hampden-news-explains-why-celtic-park-wasnt-chosen-for-euro-bid/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SFA chief executive Ian Maxwell has been talking about Hampden Park’s involvement in UEFA Euro 2028, and why Celtic Park wasn’t included instead. On Tuesday,...
The post SFA chief delivers disappointing Hampden news; why Celtic Park wasn't chosen for Euro bid appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REVEALED: KYOGO’S AMBITION]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113031</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/revealed-kyogos-ambition/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T06:18:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO FURUHASHI is just one strike away from the 60-goal mark since joining Celtic in a £4.6million move from J-League Vissel Kobe in last July 2021. It’s an excellent return from the Japanese international frontman and even more praiseworthy when you take into consideration he missed four months of his debut campaign with two separate [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Dalglish has some good words and one worry about Celtic star he's watched for years]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177205</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kenny-dalglish-has-some-good-words-and-one-worry-about-celtic-star-hes-watched-for-years/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans may still be learning about Nat Phillips, but Kenny Dalglish has a far greater understanding. The Hoops legend will have spent years watching...
The post Kenny Dalglish has some good words and one worry about Celtic star he's watched for years appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda's puzzling injury; promising signs for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177187</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/some-good-signs-for-celtic-after-puzzling-daizen-maeda-injury/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a bit of a surprise to hear that Daizen Maeda has withdrawn from the Japan international squad due to injury. The Samurai Blue...
The post Daizen Maeda's puzzling injury; promising signs for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I am very proud of Luis"; former Celtic hero is loving watching Palma]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177161</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-am-very-proud-of-luis-former-celtic-hero-is-loving-watching-palma/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emilio Izaguirre is taking a real interest in the fortunes of Luis Palma at Celtic. The pair are strongly connected as the only two Hondurans...
The post "I am very proud of Luis"; former Celtic hero is loving watching Palma appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clear favourite emerges for Rangers job as Celtic watch on]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44829</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/10/clear-favourite-rangers-job-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T21:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most Celtic fans will naturally have some level of interest in who the Rangers end up appointing as their next manager. Their previous two arrived amid a lot of expectations but failed to deal with the challenge presented by the Hoops. Giovanni van Bronckhorst was in the hot seat for just a year while Michael […]
Clear favourite emerges for Rangers job as Celtic watch on - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Manchester City target offered new deal]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44825</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/10/celtic-manchester-city-offered-deal/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T19:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is not often that Celtic and Manchester City are linked with the same player, but one Championship striker seems to have caught the eye of the Scottish and English champions. Of course, the Hoops could do with another option up top with Oh Hyeong-gyu yet to score this season. The player in question is […]
Celtic and Manchester City target offered new deal - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic, Scottish football and the slow death of the away day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177051</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/celtic-scottish-football-and-the-slow-death-of-the-away-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s barely a month goes by now without news of some Scottish club reducing the Celtic allocation for their ground. It’s been a tough few...
The post Celtic, Scottish football and the slow death of the away day appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sergio Aguero praises Celtic target and predicts move]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44819</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/10/sergio-aguero-praises-celtic-move/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T18:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic always have an eye out on some of the best youngsters around the world. The club have done a pretty decent job when it comes to identifying talents in recent years, especially during Ange Postecoglou’s first season as manager at Parkhead. It remains to be seen how things turn out for the signings from […]
Sergio Aguero praises Celtic target and predicts move - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter account offers a glimpse at the new Champions League world; Celtic involved]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177153</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/twitter-account-offers-a-glimpse-at-the-new-champions-league-world-celtic-involved/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a Celtic supporter, there’s a fair chance you’ve heard by now about the UEFA Champions League’s new format. Next summer, the competition will undergo...
The post Twitter account offers a glimpse at the new Champions League world; Celtic involved appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The blockbuster week of fixtures that Celtic will be returning to]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177088</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-blockbuster-week-of-fixtures-that-celtic-will-be-returning-to/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re anything like us there’s a fair chance you’re already fed up of this international break. Okay, the country-based football may not even have...
The post The blockbuster week of fixtures that Celtic will be returning to appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player looks set for Parkhead exit in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44814</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/10/celtic-player-parkhead-exit-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T15:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been through a bit of a journey already this season. They stumbled out of the gates and questions were immediately raised by some about whether they had made the right move by bringing back Brendan Rodgers. But the Hoops have certainly found their feet since then and are on a bit of a […]
Celtic player looks set for Parkhead exit in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic eyeing move for Queens Park Rangers striker]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44811</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/10/celtic-queens-park-rangers-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T12:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are always on the lookout for young talents. We saw proof of that this summer. Despite knowing that they were in the Champions League group stages already, as a result of winning the Premiership last season, the club only went after highly-rated youngsters. The only player they signed with some top-level was Nat Phillips, […]
Celtic eyeing move for Queens Park Rangers striker - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[McGREGOR LEADS CAP PARADE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113026</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/mcgregor-leads-cap-parade/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T11:40:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CALLUM McGREGOR leads the procession of 13 Celtic players on international duty before the Premiership resumes a week on Saturday with a game against Hearts at Tynecastle. The Hoops skipper and Greg Taylor, who claimed his first goal of the season in the 3-1 win over Kilmarnock at the weekend, will be aiming to seal [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic star explains what makes Cameron Carter-Vickers so good]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177043</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-star-explains-what-makes-cameron-carter-vickers-so-good/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moritz Jenz has offered an interesting insight on Celtic defender Cameron Carter-Vickers. The German was a centre-back partner for the American on many occasions last...
The post Former Celtic star explains what makes Cameron Carter-Vickers so good appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Politics and sport]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113025</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/politics-and-sport/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T11:01:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m a friend of one of the Cowans from Glasgow, I got him a ticket for Celtic Park once.  For that family, for Humza Yousaf’s family and the countless more who are mourning, or terrified of what may happen next, I will not give you my hot takes on a situation so tragic and complex [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Every Celtic star still out injured and what we know about their return]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177112</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/every-celtic-star-still-to-return-from-injury-and-what-we-know-about-their-return/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic appear to be over the worst of the injury troubles that have provided a huge challenge at the start of the season. It has...
The post Every Celtic star still out injured and what we know about their return appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['It's mental': Barry Ferguson simply can't believe what has happened to one Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177108</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/its-mental-barry-ferguson-simply-cant-believe-what-has-happened-to-celtics-liam-scales/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T07:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Barry Ferguson has waxed lyrical about Liam Scales and how he has managed to turn his Celtic career around. Despite Brendan Rodgers being without key...
The post 'It's mental': Barry Ferguson simply can't believe what has happened to one Celtic player appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Right now': On-loan Celtic star Nat Phillips sent message he doesn't want to hear]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177053</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/right-now-on-loan-celtic-star-nat-phillips-sent-message-he-doesnt-want-to-hear/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Hartson says Nat Phillips doesn’t start for Brendan Rodgers’ Celtic despite his summer loan move from Liverpool. On paper, you could argue that the...
The post 'Right now': On-loan Celtic star Nat Phillips sent message he doesn't want to hear appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy seems to be loving life after Celtic; class photo and a current Hoops issue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177029</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/aaron-mooy-seems-to-be-loving-life-after-celtic-class-photo-and-a-current-hoops-issue/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy seems to be loving life after Celtic as he shared a class, relaxation photo on Instagram. The Australian international retired from football at...
The post Aaron Mooy seems to be loving life after Celtic; class photo and a current Hoops issue appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic supporters set for a nervy fortnight as defender's far from ideal status confirmed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177014</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-supporters-set-for-a-nervy-fortnight-as-far-from-ideal-carter-vickers-status-confirmed/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cameron Carter-Vickers has only just returned for Celtic, yet he is now away on international duty with the USA. National boss Gregg Berhalter has called...
The post Celtic supporters set for a nervy fortnight as defender's far from ideal status confirmed appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE LIFE O’RILEY: TEN ROLLERCOASTER DAYS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113003</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-life-oriley-ten-rollercoaster-days/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T05:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY stepped onto soccer’s rollercoaster on Saturday September 30 for a breathtaking 10-day spin. The stylish 22-year-old midfielder kicked off the whirlwind sequence of events by signing a new four-year deal on the morning of the Premiership encounter at Motherwell. On pledging his future to the champions, O’Riley, who arrived at Parkhead in January [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I put my Celtic shirt on"; Moritz Jenz explains why he still loves the Hoops]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177035</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-put-my-celtic-shirt-on-moritz-jenz-explains-why-he-still-loves-the-hoops/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moritz Jenz still has a great love for Celtic almost a year on from his departure from the club. The German defender, now at VfL...
The post "I put my Celtic shirt on"; Moritz Jenz explains why he still loves the Hoops appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["We were all jealous"; Liam Scales gives forgotten Celtic star some huge encouragement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177020</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/we-were-all-jealous-liam-scales-gives-forgotten-celtic-star-some-huge-encouragement/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The remarkable rise of Liam Scales at Celtic has given one forgotten Hoops star some huge encouragement. Forward Johnny Kenny is currently out of the...
The post "We were all jealous"; Liam Scales gives forgotten Celtic star some huge encouragement appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player makes admission about Ange Postecoglou’s exit]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44806</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/09/celtic-player-ange-postecoglou-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T23:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate was one of Celtic’s best signings of the Ange Postecoglou era. Last season, he was unquestionably one of the best in the Scottish Premiership and did not look out of place against teams like Real Madrid and RB Leipzig in the Champions League either. It has been a different story since the Australian […]
Celtic player makes admission about Ange Postecoglou’s exit - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton criticises Celtic player for diving vs Kilmarnock]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44803</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/09/chris-sutton-celtic-player-diving/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T21:30:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton played several years of Celtic to great success during his career. Since then, he has gone to establish himself as a popular pundit and continues to enjoy prominence in that field these days. The Englishman is known for keeping things straight and he proved that recently by criticising one of the Hoops’ players. […]
Chris Sutton criticises Celtic player for diving vs Kilmarnock - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers left stunned by player he's found on return to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176809</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-stunned-by-liam-scales-celtic-form/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T20:49:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers reckons Liam Scales is one of the ‘biggest surprises’ of his management career after watching him perform so well for Celtic over the...
The post Brendan Rodgers left stunned by player he's found on return to Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate addresses how he felt about Ange Postecoglou exit & Brendan Rodgers arrival at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177007</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/reo-hatate-addresses-how-he-felt-about-ange-postecoglou-exit-and-brendan-rodgers-arrival-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T20:10:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate says he is focused and ready to perform under Brendan Rodgers, having been challenged by the manager to up his levels in a...
The post Reo Hatate addresses how he felt about Ange Postecoglou exit & Brendan Rodgers arrival at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Odd BBC segment suggests Celtic should have lost out despite what the rules say]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177002</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/odd-bbc-segment-suggests-celtic-should-have-lost-out-despite-what-the-rules-say/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T19:29:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BBC Sportscene has suggested the officials in charge of Celtic’s match against Kilmarnock should have ignored the rules and disallowed Luis Palma’s superb first-half strike....
The post Odd BBC segment suggests Celtic should have lost out despite what the rules say appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic show interest in 'powerful' Championship attacker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176997</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-show-interest-in-powerful-championship-attacker/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T18:51:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have sent scouts to watch QPR attacker Sinclair Armstrong this season, a new report has claimed on Monday. Armstrong, still just 20, has made...
The post Report: Celtic show interest in 'powerful' Championship attacker appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Something has to be done"; Celtic chairman Peter Lawwell speaks out on concerning fixture issue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176991</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/something-has-to-be-done-celtic-chairman-peter-lawwell-speaks-out-on-concerning-fixture-issue/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T18:17:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic chairman Peter Lawwell has called on football organisations to assess the fixture calendar over the coming years as competitions and tournaments expand both at...
The post "Something has to be done"; Celtic chairman Peter Lawwell speaks out on concerning fixture issue appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Karamoko Dembele hits comeback trail with first goal since leaving Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176986</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/video-karamoko-dembele-hits-comeback-trail-with-first-goal-since-leaving-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T17:50:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic kid Karamoko Dembele is starting to make his mark at Blackpool after a big week that included his first league start for the...
The post Video: Karamoko Dembele hits comeback trail with first goal since leaving Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['He's been brave': McFadden says even Celtic star will be 'surprised' by his performances]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176970</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-think-liam-scales-will-be-surprised-celtic-sent-a-message-about-their-in-form-centre-back/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James McFadden thinks even Liam Scales himself will be ‘surprised’ by his performances for Celtic this season. If it wasn’t for the injuries at the...
The post 'He's been brave': McFadden says even Celtic star will be 'surprised' by his performances appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[39 unique items up for grabs in incredible Celtic auction this week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176963</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/39-unique-items-up-for-grabs-in-incredible-celtic-auction-this-week/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T16:50:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend Bertie Auld’s personal collection of football jerseys and programmes will be auctioned this coming Thursday 12th October. Fittingly, the event kicks off at...
The post 39 unique items up for grabs in incredible Celtic auction this week appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic move up places in global Opta Power Rankings after intense schedule of fixtures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176959</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-move-up-places-in-global-opta-power-rankings-after-intense-schedule-of-fixtures/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T16:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s last six fixtures since the September international break were full of ups and downs, home, away and abroad. The Bhoys entered a crucial stage...
The post Celtic move up places in global Opta Power Rankings after intense schedule of fixtures appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player withdraws from national squad with injury]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44800</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/09/celtic-player-withdraws-squad-injury/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T15:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have had more than their fair share of injury problems at the start of the season. Things had started to look up a bit in that regard in recent weeks as quite a few returned to action from the sidelines and others continued their recovery. But now, it looks like Brendan Rodgers might have […]
Celtic player withdraws from national squad with injury - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Concern for Celtic star after Monday update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176956</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-star-pulls-out-of-international-duty-due-to-injury/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T15:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star Daizen Maeda will not be travelling to Japan to take on Canada and Tunisia over the next eight days, his national team confirmed...
The post Concern for Celtic star after Monday update appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero tips Ange Postecoglou favourite for Rangers job]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44797</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/09/celtic-hero-ange-postecoglou-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T12:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A win over St Mirren at the weekend must have taken some pressure off the Rangers’ shoulders and now they are expected to appoint their next manager over the international break. The Ibrox club have a mountain to climb, with Celtic having built up a 7-point lead at the top of the Premiership table after […]
Celtic hero tips Ange Postecoglou favourite for Rangers job - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rivals fall]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112994</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rivals-fall/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T11:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not often Newco are happy to do Celtic a favour but they obliged yesterday. Conceding an early penalty and red card was too much for St Mirren, our nearest challengers, as they slipped seven points behind the champions. A resurgent Reo Hatate inspired Celtic to a comfortable win over Kilmarnock a day earlier, ensuring [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWOL CELT: THE PLOT THICKENS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112992</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/awol-celt-the-plot-thickens/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T10:10:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAVID TURNBULL was nowhere to be seen as Celtic beat Kilmarnock 3-1 at Parkhead at the weekend. Brendan Rodgers omitted the midfielder from his squad for the match against the Ayrshire visitors with summer recruits Odin Holm, a £2.5million purchase from Valarenga, and Paulo Bernardo, on a season-long loan from Benfica, getting the nod for [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS ON REO: ‘HE’S NOT YOUNG, HE’S 25’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112990</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-on-reo-hes-not-young-hes-25/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T09:08:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS reckons Reo Hatate has “come alive” for the first time since the Irishman’s arrival as second time-around Celtic manager in June. The Japanese midfielder has struggled with a loss of form and injury, but sparked in a convincing display in the 3-1 win over Kilmarnock at Parkhead at the weekend. The team boss [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['For a player I admire': Chris Sutton admits he's unhappy with Celtic star's actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176934</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/for-a-player-i-admire-chris-sutton-admits-hes-unhappy-with-celtic-star-reo-hataes-actions/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton has admitted that Reo Hatate dived during Celtic’s 3-1 win over Kilmarnock on Saturday. When Celtic were 2-0 up, Reo Hatate ran at...
The post 'For a player I admire': Chris Sutton admits he's unhappy with Celtic star's actions appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I CANNOT MAKE AN EXCUSE,’ HATATE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112959</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-cannot-make-an-excuse-hatate/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T07:34:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE insists his Man-of-the-Match performance in the 3-1 win over Kilmarnock will act as a turning point as he prepares to prove he can meet the demands of Brendan Rodgers. The Japanese midfielder kicked off the campaign on the substitutes’ bench while David Turnbull got the nod to start in the Flag-Day opener against [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIFTY-EIGHT YEARS AGO: THE ARRIVAL OF A LISBON LION – COURTESY OF THE No.62 TO AUCHENSHUGGLE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=83542</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/fifty-eight-years-ago-the-arrival-of-a-lisbon-lion-courtesy-of-the-no-62-to-auchenshuggle/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T06:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Jim Craig didn’t exactly hit the headlines when he made his first-team debut for Celtic FIFTY-EIGHT years ago. The cultured right-back got the nod from Jock Stein to play in the second leg of the European Cup-Winners’ Cup-tie against Dutch club Go Ahead Deventer on October 7 1965. The Hoops had won the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kris Boyd makes unexpected Celtic admission over Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44779</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/08/kris-boyd-celtic-admission-rangers-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T22:35:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kris Boyd can usually be counted on for some eyebrow-raising comments, especially when talking about Celtic or trying to debate with Chris Sutton. What’s unusual though is that the former Rangers player has actually made a very good comparison when talking about the two Glasgow giants recently. Clearly, it has been a disappointing start to […]
Kris Boyd makes unexpected Celtic admission over Rangers - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic player has been pictured back at Parkhead]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44790</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/08/former-celtic-player-pictured-parkhead/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T21:04:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been on a good run of form recently in domestic competitions. After stumbling out of the gates that had many questioning the reappointment of Brendan Rodgers, the Hoops have gotten things back on track. They are on a winning run in the league at the moment and sit 7 points clear at the […]
Former Celtic player has been pictured back at Parkhead - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['He is top-class': Michael Stewart says there is one thing certain about Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176916</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/he-is-top-class-michael-stewart-says-there-is-one-thing-certain-about-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T19:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Stewart says Celtic’s returning manager Brendan Rodgers is ‘top-class’. In the summer, when Ange Postecoglou, after winning the Treble with Celtic, headed for the...
The post 'He is top-class': Michael Stewart says there is one thing certain about Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£15 million Celtic player tipped to stay despite exit rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44787</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/08/15-million-celtic-player-tipped-stay/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T19:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a number of very talented players on their roster and the club have done a very good job when it comes to agreeing contract extensions with them recently. While Jota and Carl Starfelt did leave over the summer, the remaining core of the squad has stayed put and some have even improved under […]
£15 million Celtic player tipped to stay despite exit rumours - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur ready to sign former Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44778</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/08/tottenham-hotspur-former-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T18:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou is certainly making the most of his chance in the Premier League. The Australian left Celtic in the summer in order to join Tottenham Hotspur. Just like when he had made the move to Parkhead, there were a lot of people unsure about the appointment and many had counted him out even before […]
Tottenham Hotspur ready to sign former Celtic player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Lennoxtown prep that inspired Saturday's 84-touch Celtic masterclass]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176911</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-lennoxtown-prep-that-inspired-saturdays-84-touch-celtic-masterclass/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T17:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate was undoubtedly Celtic’s top performer against Kilmarnock on Saturday He not only won the man of the match award but he was also...
The post The Lennoxtown prep that inspired Saturday's 84-touch Celtic masterclass appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Dalglish delivers a sobering warning for new Rangers boss going up against Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176900</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kenny-dalglish-delivers-a-sobering-warning-for-new-rangers-boss-going-up-against-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T17:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Dalglish reckons Michael Beale’s failure to win derby matches is ultimately what cost him his job and has warned any new manager at Rangers...
The post Kenny Dalglish delivers a sobering warning for new Rangers boss going up against Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star blows away teammate with "scary piece of skill"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176907</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/liam-scales-blown-away-by-what-hes-just-witnessed-from-celtic-hero-reo-hatate/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T16:31:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liam Scales was self-admittedly left in awe of Celtic teammate Reo Hatate on Saturday after his blinding bit of skill that resulted in the Bhoys’...
The post Celtic star blows away teammate with "scary piece of skill" appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Embarrassing"; Kris Boyd left fuming by Rangers gap to Celtic, Sutton enjoys Sky debate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176902</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/embarrassing-kris-boyd-left-fuming-by-rangers-gap-to-celtic-sutton-enjoys-sky-debate/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T16:04:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kris Boyd was not a happy man on Sky Sports duties this afternoon, reviewing Rangers’ decision to part ways with manager Michael Beale. In a...
The post "Embarrassing"; Kris Boyd left fuming by Rangers gap to Celtic, Sutton enjoys Sky debate appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Derek McInnes can't help but praise 'first class' Celtic despite taking bitter VAR route]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176895</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/derek-mcinnes-cant-help-but-praise-first-class-celtic-despite-taking-bitter-var-route/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T15:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kilmarnock manager Derek McInnes was forced to admit Celtic were very good on Saturday afternoon after watching his side slip to a 3-1 defeat in...
The post Derek McInnes can't help but praise 'first class' Celtic despite taking bitter VAR route appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers delivers verdict on Luis Palma's first league start for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176892</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-delivers-verdict-on-luis-palmas-first-league-start-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T15:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers is giving Celtic’s new Bhoys the time and space required to adjust to life in Glasgow, but is increasingly hopeful players such as...
The post Brendan Rodgers delivers verdict on Luis Palma's first league start for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7-UP CELTS: 10-MAN SAINTS PAY THE PENALTY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112952</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/7-up-celts-10-man-saints-pay-the-penalty/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T13:07:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC remain seven points clear at the Premiership pinnacle after St Mirren failed to cut the gap in Paisley this afternoon. Stephen Robinson’s side had the opportunity to redice the advantage to four if they overcame struggling Ibrox opposition, reeling after back-to-back defeats from Aberdeen and Aris and without a manager after sacking Michael Beale [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic tried to sign player now valued at £50 million]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44775</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/08/celtic-tried-sign-player-50-million/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T13:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have done a pretty good job in recent years when it comes to identifying talents. Of course, the first season under the management of Ange Postecoglou was remarkable as they brought in players like Kyogo, Jota, Josip Juranovic, Giorgos Giakoumakis, Cameron Carter-Vickers, Reo Hatate, Daizen Maeda, Matt O’Riley, Liel Abada and more. They were […]
Celtic tried to sign player now valued at £50 million - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic end Scottish Premiership weekend 7 points clear after St Mirren and Rangers result]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176887</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-end-scottish-premiership-weekend-7-points-clear-after-st-mirren-and-rangers-result/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T12:59:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were four points clear of second place heading into the weekend’s Scottish Premiership action and have come out the other side with a seven-point...
The post Celtic end Scottish Premiership weekend 7 points clear after St Mirren and Rangers result appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC SCREEN GEMS SPARKLE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112938</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-screen-gems-sparkle/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T10:41:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC recovered superbly from the disappointment of the stoppage-time Champions League loss to Lazio to keep their eye on the main domestic prize. Kilmarnock had already derailed Brendan Rodgers’ side earlier in the season when they knocked the holders out of the Viaplay League Cup on the plastic pitch at Rugby Park. However, there was no [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trevor Sinclair taunts Rangers with Celtic message after win at Parkhead yesterday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176863</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/trevor-sinclair-taunts-rangers-with-celtic-message-after-win-over-kilmarnock/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trevor Sinclair has taunted managerless Rangers on Twitter after Celtic continued their strong start to the Premiership season. Brendan Rodgers’ side, after losing to Lazio...
The post Trevor Sinclair taunts Rangers with Celtic message after win at Parkhead yesterday appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SURPRISE PACKET’S £7.3m PROBLEM FOR RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112937</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/surprise-packets-7-3m-problem-for-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T10:10:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIAM SCALES is on course to land Brendan Rodgers with a £7.3million problem. The £600,000 recruit from Shamrock Rovers in August 2021 has forced in his way into the Celtic first team with some gutsy performances since he answered the club’s SOS following an injury pile-up only four games into the new season. The Hoops [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers suffer next manager blow as Celtic increase gap]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44772</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/08/rangers-next-manager-celtic-gap/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T10:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers are searching for their fourth manager in two years at the moment, as the Ibrox club struggle to deal with the brilliance of Celtic. Steven Gerrard, Giovanni van Bronckhorst and Michael Beale are the three to have occupied the managerial hot seat during that period of time. Who will be next? A number of […]
Rangers suffer next manager blow as Celtic increase gap - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HAPPY 1st, GREG]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112923</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/happy-1st-greg/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T09:09:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GREG TAYLOR was delighted to get off the mark with the third goal in Celtic’s 3-1 success over Kilmarnock at Parkhead yesterday. The left-back, who claimed three strikes last season, had to wait until the eighth Premiership outing for his first of the new campaign. The breakthrough effort arrived in the 82nd minute and arrived in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HAPPY 25th, ALISTAIR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112922</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/happy-25th-alistair/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T09:09:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THIS time last year, Alistair Johnston was playing for CF Montreal in the MLS and looking forward to featuring for Canada in the winter World Cup Finals in Qatar. Today, the adventurous right-back celebrates his 25th birthday as a Celtic player after winning three domestic honours in his first five months at Parkhead. It has [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HAPPY 700th, BRENDAN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112921</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/happy-700th-brendan/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T09:09:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS celebrated his 700th game as a manager in the 3-1 Premiership triumph over Kilmarnock at Parkhead. The win – his seventh in eight league outings since his June return to the champions – eased the Hoops to seven points clear of St Mirren and 10 ahead of the Ibrox outfit, with both those [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Improved dramatically’: Michael Stewart wowed by Celtic defender who can't be replaced]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176841</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/improved-dramatically-michael-stewart-wowed-by-celtic-defender-who-cant-be-replaced/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Stewart says Greg Taylor has ‘improved dramatically’ in the colours of Celtic. The 25-year-old helped Brendan Rodgers’ side to a 3-1 win over Kilmarnock...
The post ‘Improved dramatically’: Michael Stewart wowed by Celtic defender who can't be replaced appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart uses two words to describe Celtic Park after Kilmarnock win, hails 'brilliant' trio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176821</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/joe-hart-uses-two-words-to-describe-celtic-park-after-kilmarnock-win-hails-brilliant-trio/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T06:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart labelled Celtic Park as ‘very special’ via his Instagram story after the 3-1 win over Kilmarnock. After the heartbreak of midweek, Brendan Rodgers...
The post Joe Hart uses two words to describe Celtic Park after Kilmarnock win, hails 'brilliant' trio appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REO BRAVO: RODGERS HAILS ‘OUTSTANDING’ CELT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112910</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/reo-bravo-rodgers-hails-outstanding-celt/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T05:50:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE answered his critics with a dynamic display that deservely saw him win the Man-of-the-Match accolade in the 3-1 Premiership triumph over Kilmarnock at Parkhead. The Japanese midfielder sparked to life to shred the Rugby Park opponents, score a memorable goal and put in a complete performance in his first full outing of the campaign. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic should sign Manchester United player on loan]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44768</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/07/celtic-sign-manchester-united-loan/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T22:34:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic did sign quite a few players over the course of the summer even though many fans might not have been impressed with the fact that they stuck to signing youngsters rather than going for established and experienced players. Some have impressed since coming in while others have not. That’s just how it goes most […]
Celtic should sign Manchester United player on loan - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic-linked player could join Jose Mourinho’s AS Roma]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44764</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/07/celtic-linked-player-jose-mourinho-roma/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T21:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic might not have signed any high-profile players in the summer, but initial rumours had suggested that they were going to. The Hoops had been linked with some big names as well although ultimately, none of them ended up materialising. Let’s see if the situation changes in future transfer windows. One of the players Celtic […]
Celtic-linked player could join Jose Mourinho’s AS Roma - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BBC radio man tells the brutal truth about Celtic and Rangers; Ibrox fans won't like it]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176818</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/michael-stewart-tells-the-truth-about-celtic-and-rangers-ibrox-fans-wont-like-it/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T19:41:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BBC Radio Scotland pundit Michael Stewart says that Rangers are falling short of Celtic despite using them as a barometer, insisting that the Bhoys are...
The post BBC radio man tells the brutal truth about Celtic and Rangers; Ibrox fans won't like it appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BBC pundit claims Rangers fans struggle to accept Celtic are bigger]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44761</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/07/bbc-pundit-rangers-fans-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T18:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic put up three more points on the board with a 3-1 win over Kilmarnock at the weekend. Reo Hatate, Luis Palma and Greg Taylor were the three players on the scoresheet for the Hoops on the occasion. The result means that they are now ten points clear of the Rangers and seven clear of […]
BBC pundit claims Rangers fans struggle to accept Celtic are bigger - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers left unhappy and calls out VAR officials for strange decision at Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176811</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-left-unhappy-and-calls-out-var-officials-for-strange-decision-at-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T17:03:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers doesn’t think the goal Kilmarnock scored in Celtic’s 3-1 Scottish Premiership victory should have stood due to a foul on defender Greg Taylor....
The post Brendan Rodgers left unhappy and calls out VAR officials for strange decision at Celtic Park appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["That's what I want from him"; Brendan Rodgers lauds "outstanding" Celtic star after Killie win]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176803</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/thats-what-i-want-from-him-brendan-rodgers-lauds-outstanding-celtic-star-after-killie-win/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T16:37:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has been giving his reaction to today’s 3-1 victory over Kilmarnock, which has increased Celtic’s lead over the rest in the Scottish Premiership....
The post "That's what I want from him"; Brendan Rodgers lauds "outstanding" Celtic star after Killie win appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player proves doubters wrong vs Kilmarnock]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44758</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/07/celtic-player-doubters-wrong-kilmarnock/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T16:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Things never stand still at Celtic. The objective is to win every game and one or two bad performances are enough to bring even the best of players under the microscope. The Hoops are on a great run in the league at the moment, but they have struggled to get results in Europe once again. […]
Celtic player proves doubters wrong vs Kilmarnock - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luis Palma verdict, new partnership looks strong; 3 things we learned as Celtic beat Kilmarnock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176795</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/luis-palma-verdict-new-partnership-looking-strong-3-things-we-learned-as-celtic-beat-kilmarnock/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T15:59:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are seven points clear at the top of the Scottish Premiership after a strong 3-1 victory over Kilmarnock at Celtic Park this afternoon. Goals...
The post Luis Palma verdict, new partnership looks strong; 3 things we learned as Celtic beat Kilmarnock appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC 3 KILMARNOCK 1: THREE CHEERS AS REO LEADS THE WAY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112903</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-3-kilmarnock-1-three-cheers-as-reo-leads-the-way/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T15:56:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC 3 KILMARNOCK 1 CELTIC were singing and winning in the rain with an entertaining and well-deserved victory over Kilmarnock at a drenched Parkhead this afternoon. Reo Hatate, Luis Palma and Greg Taylor were the marksmen as the champions eased seven points clear of St Mirren and 10 ahead of the Ibrox outfit who meet [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic v Kilmarnock, GG Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112901</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-kilmarnock-gg-live-updates/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T13:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 15.00. Welcome GG’s (Ronnie’s) daughter Pamela and her family to Celtic Park today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic XI confirmed; 2 changes, big return, broadcast details, instant reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176792</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-vs-kilmarnock-confirmed-2-changes-big-return-broadcast-details-instant-reaction/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T12:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manager Brendan Rodgers has named his Celtic team vs Kilmarnock for today’s Scottish Premiership clash at Celtic Park. The full match squad is as follows:...
The post Celtic XI confirmed; 2 changes, big return, broadcast details, instant reaction appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: CCV STARTS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112898</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-ccv-starts/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T12:50:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CAMERON CARTER-VICKERS will start his first Premiership game in two months when he lines up against Kilmarnock at Parkhead today. The central defender has been missing from the league side since being removed at half-time through injury in the 3-1 win over Aberdeen at Pittodrie on August 13. Carter-Vickers made his comeback as a second-half [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>