<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-09-04T16:12:19.081Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sevilla centre-back rejected chance to sign for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43905</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/04/sevilla-centre-back-chance-sign-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T12:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were very active this summer when it came to the centre-back position. Carl Starfelt departed the club in order to join Celta Vigo, freeing up a spot in the starting XI as a result. On the other hand, the Hoops signed three new centre-backs this summer in the form of Maik Nawrocki, Gustaf Lagerbielke […]
Sevilla centre-back rejected chance to sign for Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘What a Bhoy’: Trevor Sinclair says it’s ‘difficult not to love’ one Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173376</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-a-bhoy-trevor-sinclair-says-its-difficult-not-to-love-one-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trevor Sinclair has lauded the popular Kyogo Furuhashi, as he proved to be the game-changer once again for Celtic against Rangers. The 28-year-old ripped the...
The post ‘What a Bhoy’: Trevor Sinclair says it’s ‘difficult not to love’ one Celtic player  appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ibrox shaken to red brick core]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111766</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ibrox-shaken-to-red-brick-core/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T11:09:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Within the first minute at Ibrox yesterday, Newco sent a long ball forward that tempted Liam Scales into a challenge he missed.  Seconds later the ball ended in the net, only for the assistant to correctly flag offside.  It looked like a portent of doom to come, however, Liam was undeterred.  He threw himself at [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IMAGES: CELTIC DENIED STONEWALL PENALTY-KICK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111744</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/images-celtic-denied-stonewall-penalty-kick/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T10:33:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC should have been awarded a stonewall penalty-kick at Ibrox yesterday – but, amazingly, there has been absolutely no mention of the incident. CQN watched the replay of the entire match and spotted the infringement that should have seen Brendan Rodgers’ side awarded an undeniable spot-kick. In the 25th minute, eventual matchwinner Kyogo Furuhashi raced [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moussa Dembele makes superb claim after Celtic win vs Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43900</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/04/moussa-dembele-celtic-win-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T10:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moussa Dembele is one of the best players that Celtic have had in recent memory. The Frenc striker was superb during his time at Parkhead and he has had an interesting career since leaving for Lyon. He had some great seasons in Ligue 1, which saw him being linked with the likes of Chelsea and […]
Moussa Dembele makes superb claim after Celtic win vs Rangers - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Class': Ally McCoist hails 2 Bhoys, but says Rangers-Celtic 'might be worst I have seen']]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173359</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/class-ally-mccoist-hails-2-bhoys-but-says-rangers-celtic-might-be-worst-i-have-seen/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T08:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ally McCoist has hailed Callum McGregor and Kyogo Furuhashi for their performances following Celtic’s 1-0 against Rangers at Ibrox on Sunday. The former striker thinks...
The post 'Class': Ally McCoist hails 2 Bhoys, but says Rangers-Celtic 'might be worst I have seen' appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO AND THE JOY OF SIX]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111712</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kyogo-and-the-joy-of-six/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T08:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PACY hitman Kyogo Furuhashi is making up for lost time against Ibrox opposition after volleying in a spectacular winner in Govan in the champions’ 1-0 triumph to romp four points clear of their Glasgow rivals after the same amount of Premiership outings. Amazingly, the prolific Japanese striker had never scored against the city neighbours until [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The cold Celtic reality Michael Beale and Rangers are waking up to]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173354</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-cold-celtic-reality-michael-beale-and-rangers-are-waking-up-to/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T07:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s main title rivals Rangers are waking up to a four-point gap and the realisation that even at almost full strength, against a weakened Bhoys...
The post The cold Celtic reality Michael Beale and Rangers are waking up to appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘THEY THREW THEIR BODIES ON THE LINE,’ RODGERS HAILS HIS WINNERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111702</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/they-threw-their-bodies-on-the-line-rodgers-hails-his-winners/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T07:33:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS celebrated a bunch of fives as Kyogo Furuhashi fired Celtic to an exhausting 1-0 triumph at Ibrox on an afternoon many of the visiting players stood up to be counted. The Irishman was taking charge of the Hoops for the sixth time in enemy territory and has now succeeded in five of that [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers explains Celtic Ibrox absences; new Bhoy set to jet off again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173345</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-explains-paulo-bernardo-and-nat-phillips-situations-after-celtic-derby-absence/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T06:57:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was never in the plan to include Paulo Bernardo and Nat Phillips in yesterday’s Celtic squad at Ibrox, Brendan Rodgers revealed on the day....
The post Brendan Rodgers explains Celtic Ibrox absences; new Bhoy set to jet off again appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Left in awe; Callum McGregor's superb dressing room message to Celtic teammate at Ibrox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173347</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/left-in-awe-callum-mcgregors-superb-dressing-room-message-to-kyogo-after-celtic-derby-winner/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T06:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic captain Callum McGregor told Kyogo Furuhashi he might be one of the best strikers he’s ever seen after his glorious winner against Rangers at...
The post Left in awe; Callum McGregor's superb dressing room message to Celtic teammate at Ibrox appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James Tavernier reacts to Ibrox boos after losing to Celtic again]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43891</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/03/james-tavernier-reacts-ibrox-boos-losing-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T22:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be interesting to find out where James Tavernier ranks in terms of Rangers captains when it comes to his record against Celtic. The right-back was on the losing side in the Glasgow Derby once again, as the Hoops walked out of Ibrox with a 1-0 victory. Kyogo Furuhashi scored the winner on the […]
James Tavernier reacts to Ibrox boos after losing to Celtic again - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo explains why he did not celebrate Celtic’s goal vs Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43876</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/03/kyogo-celebrate-celtic-goal-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T20:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a stunning and surreal moment when Kyogo Furuhashi scored for Celtic at Ibrox on Sunday. When the ball found the back of the net the reactions all around were very unusual for the normal maelstrom that is the Glasgow Derby. Now, the Japanese forward has himself explained why he was hesitant to celebrate. […]
Kyogo explains why he did not celebrate Celtic’s goal vs Rangers - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss explains why Nat Phillips was dropped vs Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43884</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/03/celtic-boss-nat-phillips-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T19:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Perhaps it speaks more about the other moves made, but in many ways, Nat Phillips was Celtic’s marquee signing of the summer. The Liverpool centre-back has been brought in on a season-long loan amidst the long list of injury problems that Brendan Rodgers’ team are facing at this point in time. That did not stop […]
Celtic boss explains why Nat Phillips was dropped vs Rangers - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo: Two stars celebrate Celtic win from within Ibrox dressing room on Instagram]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173340</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/photo-matt-oriley-and-liel-abada-celebrate-celtic-win-from-within-ibrox-dressing-room-on-instagram/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T18:38:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There can’t be many things sweeter in football than celebrating a win in the away dressing room of your fiercest rivals, but that’s exactly what...
The post Photo: Two stars celebrate Celtic win from within Ibrox dressing room on Instagram appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Fans No Problem Lets Party]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58359</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/bad-week-for-the-bears/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T17:38:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All good things come in 3’s as they say so this weekend couldn’t be any better and today completed my ‘treble’. My only daughter got married on Friday and we were back in sunny Donegal for the nuptials as they head to New York for the honeymoon. Now it really couldn’t get much better but […]
The post No Fans No Problem Lets Party appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero takes dig at Todd Cantwell after Glasgow Derby]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43881</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/03/celtic-hero-todd-cantwell-glasgow-derby/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T17:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a match that most Celtic fans did not expect to win, which makes the result even sweeter. The Hoops had struggled for form at the start of this season, winning just two of their four games till now. On the other hand, the Rangers were coming off a 5-1 defeat at the hands […]
Celtic hero takes dig at Todd Cantwell after Glasgow Derby - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers fans meltdown after another loss to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43870</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/03/rangers-fans-another-loss-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T14:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans were worried going into the game away at Ibrox. They had not looked convincing the entire season and were winless in their previous two matches. On the other hand, the Rangers were coming off of a 5-1 defeat at the hands of PSV in midweek but overall, their supporters seemed to be more […]
Rangers fans meltdown after another loss to Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers reacts with superb BBC interview as Celtic leave Ibrox fans booing Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173325</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-reacts-with-superb-bbc-interview-as-below-strength-celtic-leave-ibrox-fans-booing-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T13:52:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers was a happy man after watching his Celtic team beat Rangers 1-0 at Ibrox today, fully satisfied with the efforts of his players....
The post Brendan Rodgers reacts with superb BBC interview as Celtic leave Ibrox fans booing Rangers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['World class': Neil Lennon blown away by 3 Celtic players after win over Rangers at Ibrox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173311</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/world-class-neil-lennon-blown-away-by-3-celtic-players-after-win-over-rangers-at-ibrox/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon waxed lyrical about Kyogo Furuhashi, Callum McGregor and Liam Scales after Celtic beat Rangers 1-0 at Ibrox on Sunday. Celtic’s main man up...
The post 'World class': Neil Lennon blown away by 3 Celtic players after win over Rangers at Ibrox appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘He enjoys playing against Rangers’: Chris Sutton hails Celtic player today at Ibrox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173291</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/he-enjoys-playing-against-rangers-chris-sutton-hails-celtic-player-today-at-ibrox/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton has hailed Kyogo Furuhashi for his ‘brilliant’ goal as Celtic beat Rangers 1-0 at Ibrox on Sunday. What a way to answer the...
The post ‘He enjoys playing against Rangers’: Chris Sutton hails Celtic player today at Ibrox appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RANGERS 0 CELTIC 1: TRUE GRIT CELTS AS KYOGO CRACKS IT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111693</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rangers-0-celtic-1-true-grit-celts-as-kyogo-cracks-it/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T13:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RANGERS 0 CELTIC 1   JUST CHAMPION! Celtic showed the true grit of title winners to claim a precious victory at Ibrox in the dramatic High Noon shoot-out. Kyogo Furuhashi was the man who claimed the glory goal just before the break, but this was an overall performance from a collection of players who did [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Criticised star turns it round, Kyogo class; 3 things we learned as weakened Celtic beat Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173286</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/priceless-class-captain-turns-it-up-3-things-we-learned-as-weakened-celtic-show-up-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T12:58:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crisis, what crisis? Celtic’s injury-ravaged and depleted squad have shown up rivals Rangers with a massive 1-0 victory at Ibrox. Brendan Rodgers and his team...
The post Criticised star turns it round, Kyogo class; 3 things we learned as weakened Celtic beat Rangers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BROONY AXED]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111690</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/broony-axed/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T10:12:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic skipper Scott Brown has been sacked by Fleetwood Town. The English third-tier side relieved the Hoops legend of his managerial duties following “a difficult run of results”. The team languish 23rd in League One after six matches with just one point. Brown’s team last picked up a point in the draw with Carlisle [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Rangers’ v Celtic, Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111686</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rangers-v-celtic-live-updates-21/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T10:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 12:00.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: ABADA STARTS, PALMA ON STAND-BY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111657</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-abada-starts-palma-on-stand-by/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T09:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIEL ABADA returns to the Celtic line-up for the first Glasgow derby of the season at Ibrox this afternoon. The Israeli winger, who comes in for South Korean Yang Hyun-jun, is the only change from the side that drew 0-0 with St Johnstone last weekend. Abada will be hoping to stage an action replay of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No new Bhoys: Celtic XI confirmed, one change, global TV details, instant reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173281</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-vs-rangers-confirmed-one-change-no-debuts-global-tv-details-instant-reaction/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T09:51:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manager Brendan Rodgers has named his Celtic team vs Rangers for today’s Scottish Premiership match at Ibrox. The full match squad is as follows: Starting...
The post No new Bhoys: Celtic XI confirmed, one change, global TV details, instant reaction appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend Scott Brown sacked from first management job; statement released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173274</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-legend-scott-brown-sacked-from-first-management-job-statement-released/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T09:28:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend Scott Brown has been sacked as Fleetwood Town manager just a few weeks into the new season. A statement on the club’s official...
The post Celtic legend Scott Brown sacked from first management job; statement released appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[the rangers V CELTIC Matchday Minizine]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58352</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/the-rangers-v-celtic-matchday-minizine/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T09:13:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Click into image to download the rangers v CELTIC Match day Mini-zine. Hit subscribe to get match day edition in your inbox every time.
The post the rangers V CELTIC Matchday Minizine appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers fans make Michael Beale U-turn before facing Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43796</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/03/rangers-fans-michael-beale-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T09:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic announced their seventh summer signing in Luis Palma on Wednesday evening, the Rangers were sent packing from the Champions League qualifiers. Michael Beale wasn’t able to guide his team to the main stage of the competition, as they were defeated 5 -1 by PSV in the second leg of their matchup. As the […]
Rangers fans make Michael Beale U-turn before facing Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["We're really excited"; Brendan Rodgers talks up new Celtic signings ahead of Ibrox trip]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173271</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/were-really-excited-brendan-rodgers-talks-up-new-celtic-signings-ahead-of-ibrox-trip/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T08:50:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers called for Celtic signings in the last week of the summer transfer window and he got three of them – Luis Palma, Nat...
The post "We're really excited"; Brendan Rodgers talks up new Celtic signings ahead of Ibrox trip appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers sends clear message to Celtic dressing room ahead of Rangers test]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173268</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-sends-clear-message-to-celtic-dressing-room-ahead-of-rangers-test/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T08:16:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers will be making firm judgments on his Celtic players at Ibrox today, feeling that this is the kind of game where he can...
The post Brendan Rodgers sends clear message to Celtic dressing room ahead of Rangers test appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Champions League Draw Player Reactions]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58330</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/champions-league-draw-player-reactions/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T07:59:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After galloping towards the Scottish premier league title last season, Celtic were rewarded with direct rout into the group stages of the worlds premier club competition.  Celtic fans were in a fortunate position of watching on as clubs battled it out across Europe for the final few places at the top table of European football. […]
The post Champions League Draw Player Reactions appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘THIS IS WHERE YOU GET JUDGED AS A CELTIC PLAYER,’ RODGERS’ RALLYING CALL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111680</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/this-is-where-you-get-judged-as-a-celtic-player-rodgers-rallying-call/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T07:48:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has told his Celtic players to prepare for Judgement Day at Ibrox this afternoon. It’s an occasion when the Hoops will have to stand up to be counted in a partisan arena where there will not be a solitary Hoops supporter to add encouragement. On the last occasion at the same ground, Ange [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Dalglish makes Celtic derby scoreline prediction; thinks new signing can thrive vs Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173265</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kenny-dalglish-makes-celtic-derby-scoreline-prediction-thinks-new-signing-can-thrive-vs-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T07:47:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Liverpool legend Kenny Dalglish has given a big thumbs up to the signing of Nat Phillips from the Anfield side, believing he can...
The post Kenny Dalglish makes Celtic derby scoreline prediction; thinks new signing can thrive vs Rangers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big debut, Palma and Bernardo decisions; Celtic team news and Predicted XI vs Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173261</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/big-debut-palma-and-bernardo-decisions-celtic-predicted-xi-vs-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T07:25:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today’s a major test for Brendan Rodgers and Celtic, travelling away to rivals Rangers for the first derby of the Scottish Premiership season. After two...
The post Big debut, Palma and Bernardo decisions; Celtic team news and Predicted XI vs Rangers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Raving’: Tam McManus shares exciting info Greek source told him about Celtic new boy Palma]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173241</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/raving-tam-mcmanus-shares-exciting-info-greek-source-told-him-about-celtic-new-boy-luis-palma/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tam McManus has shared that he has been told by a former teammate in Greece that Celtic new boy, Luis Palma is a ‘top, top’...
The post ‘Raving’: Tam McManus shares exciting info Greek source told him about Celtic new boy Palma appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A YEAR AGO TODAY: CELTIC 4 RANGERS 0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111678</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/a-year-ago-today-celtic-4-rangers-0/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T06:57:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EXACTLY a year ago today, Celtic went on the goal rampage as they thumped Giovanni van Bronckhorst’s Ibrox visitors by four clear goals. Liel Abada, who has just signed a new deal at the champions, walloped in two efforts and Filipe Jota added the other after a spectacular solo sprint as the Hoops roared their [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: HITTING THE BOOS WITH BRENDAN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111675</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-hitting-the-boos-with-brendan/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T06:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BOOS and jeers bouncing around a stadium on the south side of Glasgow around two o’clock this afternoon would be a sweet cacophony to the ears of Brendan Rodgers. Not so welcoming was the noise that emanated from a section of Celtic Park last weekend when there was the predictable and pitiful reaction from so-called [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘There is absolutely': Peter Grant states if Nat Phillips will start for Celtic v Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173225</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/there-is-absolutely-peter-grant-states-if-nat-phillips-will-start-for-celtic-v-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T05:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant has backed on-loan Liverpool star Nat Phillips to make his Celtic debut against Rangers on Sunday at Ibrox. The Bhoys landed Nat Phillips’...
The post ‘There is absolutely': Peter Grant states if Nat Phillips will start for Celtic v Rangers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RANGERS v CELTIC: 5-MINUTE QUIZ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111620</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rangers-v-celtic-5-minute-quiz-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T04:15:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC take on Michael Beale’s team in the first derby of the season at Ibrox at noon today. As ever, no quarter will be asked or given in the rarefied atmosphere of this fixture. How much can you remember about recent encounters against the Govan club? Have a go on CQN’s fun five-minute quiz to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS v RANGERS (Part Six): MIGHTY MOUSSA TOP OF THE HIT PARADE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111659</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-v-rangers-part-six-mighty-moussa-top-of-the-hit-parade/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T04:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS resumes hostilities with Ibrox opposition in the High Noon showdown in enemy territory today. The returning Celtic manager has not figured in the derby fixture for four years and nine months. Rodgers has already been involved in 13 of the no-holds-barred encounters after first arriving at Parkhead in May 2016. The Irishman has enjoyed [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers calls out media over Celtic rumour]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43861</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/02/brendan-rodgers-media-celtic-rumour/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T22:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have done quite a bit of business over the course of the summer transfer window, bringing in nine new players in total. Seven have arrived on a permanent basis while two have been brought in one loan. Out of them, only one is more than 23 years of age, Nat Phillips of Liverpool, who […]
Brendan Rodgers calls out media over Celtic rumour - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Champions League Watch: Lazio deliver big statement win to turn around poor Serie A start]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173214</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-champions-league-watch-lazio-deliver-big-statement-win-to-turn-around-poor-serie-a-start/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T20:45:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that we know Celtic’s opponents for the upcoming UEFA Champions League group stage, it’s time to keep up with the goings on at all...
The post Celtic Champions League Watch: Lazio deliver big statement win to turn around poor Serie A start appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers wants Celtic to sign another Liverpool player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43857</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/02/brendan-rodgers-celtic-sign-liverpool/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T20:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic pulled off a late loan move for Nat Phillips this summer and there are high expectations that the Liverpool centre-back will be able to improve the Hoops’ defence. He has not gotten a lot of chances with the Reds but when he has been on the pitch, he has not looked out of place […]
Brendan Rodgers wants Celtic to sign another Liverpool player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic secure dream draw ahead of Champions League Group Stage]]></title>
        <id>http://celticunderground.net/?p=6630</id>
        <link href="http://celticunderground.net/celtic-secure-dream-draw-ahead-of-champions-league-group-stage/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T20:28:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will face Atletico Madrid, Lazio, and Feyenoord in Group E, In a somewhat surprising draw in comparison to previous Champions League seasons, where Celtic faced the likes of Real Madrid, Bayern Munich, Barcelona, and Manchester City in the group stages. Celtic centre-back Gustaf Lagerbielke spoke of the task facing Celtic against respected Champions League […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Alternative Glasgow Derby Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58339</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/the-alternative-glasgow-derby-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T19:31:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matt McGlone from the Alternative View joins More than 90 Minutes Editor, Andrew Milne to chat about all things Celtic. In this episode of the Celtic Soul Podcast they chat about the departure of Ange, the season so far, the second coming of Brendan Rodgers and the Glasgow Derby.
The post The Alternative Glasgow Derby Preview appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Brendan Rodgers identifies long-term Celtic replacement for Joe Hart; enquiry was made]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173207</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/report-brendan-rodgers-looking-at-liverpool-talent-as-celtics-long-term-joe-hart-replacement/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T19:27:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic didn’t sign a goalkeeper during the summer transfer window but a new report has stated that Brendan Rodgers is eyeing a Liverpool talent as...
The post Report: Brendan Rodgers identifies long-term Celtic replacement for Joe Hart; enquiry was made appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic turned down £7 million bid for important player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43853</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/02/celtic-7-million-bid-important-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T19:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were very busy over the course of the summer transfer window, both in terms of incomings and outgoings. Whether that has made any positive impact or not is a different discussion altogether. Brendan Rodgers’ team have not made the best start to the campaign and look like mere shells of Ange Postecoglou’s winning machine […]
Celtic turned down £7 million bid for important player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Net Spend summer transfer window 2023/24]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173201</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-net-spend-summer-transfer-window-2023-24/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T18:13:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s summer transfer window wasn’t without action, with lots of deals done in and out of the club. While some fans may feel the Bhoys...
The post Celtic Net Spend summer transfer window 2023/24 appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More than 90 Minutes Meets Luis Palma]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58332</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/more-than-90-minutes-meets-luis-palma/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T18:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 90 Minutes, Martin Donaldson and the Celtic Fan Media chat to Honduran international Luis Palma. Luis arrived in Glasgow on 30th August to sign a 5 year deal with the champions and immediately claimed he was ready to face our Glasgow rivals in the derby match on Sunday.  The 23 year old winger […]
The post More than 90 Minutes Meets Luis Palma appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Beale claims Rangers turned down new Celtic signing]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43849</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/02/michael-beale-rangers-celtic-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T17:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were busy in the last few days of the summer transfer window, trying to bring in players who could help the team after the Hoops stumbled out of the gates this season. It remains to be seen how successful they were in their quest. The club did make three late additions. Luis Palma was […]
Michael Beale claims Rangers turned down new Celtic signing - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Story created outside of the club"; Rodgers addresses Celtic spend & lack of big money players]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173203</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-addresses-celtics-summer-spend-and-lack-of-big-money-players/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T16:42:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has provided some candid thoughts on the way the summer transfer window went for Celtic, stating that the spending and approach was all...
The post "Story created outside of the club"; Rodgers addresses Celtic spend & lack of big money players appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 goals in 6 games for highly-rated Celtic youngster as B team pick up crucial Saturday win]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173196</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/superb-rocco-vata-form-continues-as-b-team-pick-up-crucial-saturday-win/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T15:54:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic prospect Rocco Vata has put all the recent transfer speculation behind him to score his seventh goal in six matches for the B team...
The post 7 goals in 6 games for highly-rated Celtic youngster as B team pick up crucial Saturday win appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["It's wasted it"; Lennon and McCulloch agree after Rangers pettiness damaged Celtic clash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173115</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/its-wasted-it-lennon-and-mcculloch-agree-that-rangers-pettiness-has-damaged-celtic-clash/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will have no fans in attendance for Sunday’s first derby of the season against Rangers. The allocation furore has been well covered ever since...
The post "It's wasted it"; Lennon and McCulloch agree after Rangers pettiness damaged Celtic clash appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have Champions League decisions to make as Monday deadline approaches]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173187</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-have-champions-league-squad-decisions-to-make-as-monday-deadline-approaches/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will have to name their ‘List A’ of Champions League players by Monday night. The Hoops are back in the group stage of European...
The post Celtic have Champions League decisions to make as Monday deadline approaches appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic linked with free transfer for Premier League winner]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43845</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/02/celtic-free-transfer-premier-league/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T12:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The summer transfer window is in the books and Celtic made nine additions to their squad. Despite that, many fans feel disappointed with the signings that the club made. There was a need for established and experienced players with the Champions League group stage coming up and a treble to defend. Instead, they stuck to […]
Celtic linked with free transfer for Premier League winner - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bernardo bang on plan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111658</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/bernardo-bang-on-plan/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T12:13:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paulo Bernardo’s signature on a loan-to-buy-option concluded Celtic’s business last night. It follows the same scouting, recruitment and commercial parth established with Jota two years earlier. At 21, he is bang on plan. If Celtic are to make a significant leap forward, we will not do it with mid-20s honest pros. Talent needs to be [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feyenoord boss shares his Celtic thoughts; indirect involvement in Rodgers return]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173180</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/feyenoord-boss-arne-slot-shares-his-celtic-thoughts-indirect-involvement-in-rodgers-return/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feyenoord boss Arne Slot has given his thoughts on Celtic and the rest of our Champions League group. Celtic were placed in to Group E...
The post Feyenoord boss shares his Celtic thoughts; indirect involvement in Rodgers return appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: McGREGOR, CONDUCTOR IN SEARCH OF AN ORCHESTRA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111655</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-mcgregor-conductor-in-search-of-an-orchestra/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T10:47:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WITH the clock ticking down all too quickly against St Johnstone, did you notice the selfless lung-bursting 50-yard sprint from Callum McGregor to recover the ball and attempt to set another Celtic attack in motion? In the fading moments, opposition keeper Dimitar Mitov rose to a right-wing corner-kick from Matt O’Riley to get both fists [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cause for optimism; the entire Celtic squad depth picture after frantic few days]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173171</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/cause-for-optimism-the-entire-celtic-squad-depth-picture-after-hectic-few-days/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been a hectic few days but the Celtic squad is now set for the challenges ahead. The club signed nine players over the course...
The post Cause for optimism; the entire Celtic squad depth picture after frantic few days appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton turns the heat up on Michael Beale ahead of Celtic clash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173144</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/chris-sutton-turns-the-heat-up-on-michael-beale-ahead-of-celtic-clash/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton has turned the heat up on Rangers manager Michael Beale ahead of Celtic’s visit to Ibrox on Sunday. It’s the first derby of...
The post Chris Sutton turns the heat up on Michael Beale ahead of Celtic clash appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic boost for Glasgow Derby]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43835</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/02/brendan-rodgers-celtic-glasgow-derby/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T09:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The summer transfer window is done and dusted. Celtic made nine signings over the course of it even though rumours of record-breaking offers and marquee signings proved to be well wide of the mark. Instead, the most high-profile addition that the club made was bringing in Nat Phillips on loan from Liverpool. And even that […]
Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic boost for Glasgow Derby - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£7m BID BOOTED AS CELTIC DEAL IN ABADA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111645</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/7m-bid-booted-as-celtic-deal-in-abada/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T08:56:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIEL ABADA signed an enhanced deal with Celtic just hours after the champions had knocked a £7million bid for the Israeli winger. Portuguese giants Sporting Lisbon were prepared to pay DOUBLE the fee the Hoops had shelled out for the Israeli international when he joined from Maccabi Petah Tikva in July 2021. However, the Parkhead [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic injury return for Ibrox; offers thoughts on potential debuts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173158</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-confirms-celtic-injury-return-for-ibrox-offers-thoughts-on-potential-debuts/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has confirmed that Hyeongyu Oh is available for Celtic at Ibrox on Sunday. The South Korean returned to training this week alongside the...
The post Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic injury return for Ibrox; offers thoughts on potential debuts appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REVEALED: CELTIC CHAMPIONS LEAGUE FIXTURES]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111642</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/revealed-celtic-champions-league-fixtures/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T07:54:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC will kick off their Champions League Group E campaign with a game against Feyenoord in Rotterdam on Tuesday September 19. It will be an intriguing clash against the club that denied Jock Stein’s side a second European Cup triumph in 1970 when Ove Kindvall claimed the winner two minutes from the end of extra-time [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s Champions League fixtures confirmed; tasty match-ups, qualification verdict]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173152</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-champions-league-fixtures-confirmed-tasty-match-ups-qualification-verdict/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T07:05:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have found out their fixtures for the upcoming UEFA Champions League group stage campaign. On Thursday, the Hoops were placed in to Group E...
The post Celtic’s Champions League fixtures confirmed; tasty match-ups, qualification verdict appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£18.25m: RODGERS’ CASH SPLASH: ALL THE INS AND OUTS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111633</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/18-25m-rodgers-cash-splash-all-the-ins-and-outs/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T06:50:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS spent £18.25million in strengthening his Celtic squad this summer for the challenges that lie ahead at home and abroad. You can add £1million to that total which is the fee agreed for Japanese midfielder Tomoki Iwata when his initial loan move from Yokohama F Marinos became permanent. The highest outlay was the £4.3million [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rodgers has things to say about Ibrox allocation furore but all hope isn't lost for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173131</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-has-things-to-say-about-ibrox-allocation-furore-but-all-hope-isnt-lost-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T06:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers had things to say about the Celtic and Rangers allocation furore at his Friday meeting with the print media. The Celtic manager is...
The post Rodgers has things to say about Ibrox allocation furore but all hope isn't lost for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic star makes definitive statement over debut at Ibrox; Rodgers has a decision to make]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173124</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/luis-palma-declares-himself-ready-for-celtic-debut-at-ibrox-now-rodgers-has-a-decision-to-make/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing Luis Palma says he is ready to make his debut at Ibrox on Sunday. It’s a huge weekend for the Hoops as...
The post New Celtic star makes definitive statement over debut at Ibrox; Rodgers has a decision to make  appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Bit surprised"; Rodgers has his say on Haksabanovic Instagram post as Celtic exit is confirmed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173138</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/bit-surprised-rodgers-has-his-say-on-haksabanovic-instagram-post-as-celtic-exit-is-confirmed/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers says he was surprised to hear about Sead Haksabanovic’s pointed Celtic Instagram post. Last Sunday morning, less than a day after our goalless...
The post "Bit surprised"; Rodgers has his say on Haksabanovic Instagram post as Celtic exit is confirmed appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Every incoming and outgoing deal Celtic completed on transfer deadline day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173103</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/every-incoming-and-outgoing-deal-celtic-completed-on-transfer-deadline-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another year, another deadline day – but just who were the incoming and outgoings at Celtic Park… Celtic incomings on Deadline Day There was only...
The post Every incoming and outgoing deal Celtic completed on transfer deadline day appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kieran Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS v RANGERS (Part Five)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111583</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-v-rangers-part-five/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T04:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is preparing for a return to Glasgow derby action after an absence of over four and a half years when he takes Celtic to Ibrox tomorrow. The second time-around Hoops gaffer enjoyed phenomenal success against the city rivals in his first spell between May 2016 and February 2019. Rodgers faced the Govan club [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player could make last-minute Deadline Day exit]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43832</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/01/celtic-player-last-deadline-day-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T22:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have certainly had an eventful summer transfer window and it is set to close in hours. The club have made nine signings this time around but none of then can be considered as a marquee addition. It is Nat Phillips, the Liverpool centre-back, who comes with the biggest name value out of them and […]
Celtic player could make last-minute Deadline Day exit - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch: New Celtic Bhoy Paulo Bernardo's wonder goal in Portuguese top-flight]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173105</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/watch-new-celtic-bhoy-paulo-bernardos-wonder-goal-in-portuguese-top-flight/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T21:32:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paulo Bernardo has officially signed for Celtic on a season-long loan deal, with the Bhoys holding the option to make the midfielder’s move permanent. The...
The post Watch: New Celtic Bhoy Paulo Bernardo's wonder goal in Portuguese top-flight appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JUST CHAMPION: BERNARDO IS RECRUIT No.9]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111628</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/just-champion-bernardo-is-recruit-no-9/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T20:38:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PAULO BERNARDO signed a season-long loan deal from Benfica tonight to become Celtic’s NINTH recruit of the summer. Brendan Rodgers beat the midnight transfer deadline to capture the highly-rated 21-year-old midfielder. As in the previous temporary transfer arrangement with the Lisbon club for Filipe Jota, there is an option to buy if the playmaker impresses [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crucial clause included in Celtic deal for Paulo Bernardo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173098</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-have-option-to-make-paulo-bernardo-move-permanent-as-club-make-official-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T20:12:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have officially signed Paulo Bernardo on a season-long loan from Benfica but, crucially, will have the option to buy the midfielder should he impress...
The post Crucial clause included in Celtic deal for Paulo Bernardo appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player’s Deadline Day exit officially announced]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43827</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/01/celtic-deadline-day-exit-announced/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T20:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were always expected to be involved on Deadline Day considering the start that the club have made to the season. It was not hard to see that this team needed reinforcements if they were to get the season back on track. In the first few weeks of the campaign, they had looked sluggish and […]
Celtic player’s Deadline Day exit officially announced - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Very good signing’: Tam McManus blown away by Celtic deal involving 'quality' player]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173081</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/very-good-signing-tam-mcmanus-blown-away-by-celtic-deal-involving-quality-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T19:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tam McManus has hailed Celtic for the signing of Nat Phillips from Liverpool by describing it as ‘very good’. Celtic snapped up Nat Phillips’ talents...
The post ‘Very good signing’: Tam McManus blown away by Celtic deal involving 'quality' player appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Italian club close off Celtic interest in 19-goal forward for now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173075</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/sydney-van-hooijdonk-option-closed-off-after-celtic-interest/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T18:55:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sydney van Hooijdonk won’t be joining Celtic this summer after being told by Bologna that they will be rejecting all advances for him. Son of...
The post Italian club close off Celtic interest in 19-goal forward for now appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic make unexpected Deadline Day announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43824</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/01/celtic-make-deadline-day-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T18:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There seems to be a positivity around Celtic Park that was not there even a couple of days ago. The club have made an underwhelming start to the campaign but their moves over the last few days have given the fans hope that things can be brought back on track. Luis Palma and Nat Phillips […]
Celtic make unexpected Deadline Day announcement - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Abada’s potential]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111627</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/abadas-potential/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T18:03:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t take this to heart too soon, but Liel Abada has the potential to eclipse anyone else currently in the Celtic squad.  The natural instinct he has demonstrated inside the box since he arrived as a teenager two years ago, is gold dust. The Great Swede was 26 when he came to Glasgow, having spend [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic knock back late £7m bid]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173068</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-knocked-back-7m-bid-for-liel-abada-before-contract-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T17:51:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s commitment to Liel Abada is a significant step forward in the relationship between club and player, especially now it has emerged that the Bhoys...
The post Report: Celtic knock back late £7m bid appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers reacts as Bhoys fight off many clubs to make superb contract announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173064</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-says-celtic-have-fought-off-significant-interest-with-contract-move/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T17:17:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liel Abada has committed his long-term future to Celtic, signing a four-year deal that keeps him at the club until the summer of 2027. Abada...
The post Brendan Rodgers reacts as Bhoys fight off many clubs to make superb contract announcement appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic reject Deadline Day transfer bid from Serie A club]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43821</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/01/celtic-reject-deadline-day-bid/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T17:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been very active in the transfer market over the last few days. It is not hard to understand why either considering how much they have struggled out of the gates this season. The team has looked like a mere shell of their treble-winning selves from the previous campaign and additions were clearly needed. […]
Celtic reject Deadline Day transfer bid from Serie A club - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TV interview offers late transfer deadline day hope for Celtic fans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173058</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-tv-interview-offers-late-deadline-day-hope-for-celtic-support/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T16:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Celtic are expected to announce the arrival of Portuguese midfielder Paulo Bernardo on deadline day, there is still hope of more arriving beyond him...
The post TV interview offers late transfer deadline day hope for Celtic fans appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midfielder involved in late transfer window drama but exit is good news for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173043</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/ismaila-soro-involved-in-late-transfer-window-drama-but-its-good-news-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T16:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ismaila Soro has officially left Celtic on a permanent basis, signing for Beitar Jerusalem in Israel despite some later transfer window drama involving a Greek...
The post Midfielder involved in late transfer window drama but exit is good news for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The minimum allocation Celtic will receive for each Champions League away day; big Rome hopes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173037</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-minimum-allocation-celtic-will-receive-for-each-champions-league-away-day-big-rome-hopes/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic found out their tasty Champions League group stage fate on Thursday. The Hoops were the final team drawn in to Group E, following major...
The post The minimum allocation Celtic will receive for each Champions League away day; big Rome hopes appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I DID SPEAK TO HIM,’ REVEALS RODGERS AFTER STAR’S COMMENTS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111624</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-did-speak-to-him-reveals-rodgers-after-stars-comments/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T14:52:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has revealed he was “a bit surprised” by Sead Haksabanovic’s comments on social media at the weekend. The Sweden-born Montenegro international winger appeared on his Instagram account to say: “If they don’t see your value maybe you’re not at the right place.” It appeared to be clear indication Haksabanovic, who arrived in a [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rodgers names incoming Celtic transfer but further update isn't nearly as promising]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173041</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/rodgers-endorses-paulo-bernardo-celtic-deal-but-further-update-isnt-nearly-as-promising/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T13:49:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers says that Paulo Bernardo will be joining the club. The Benfica man was widely understood to be coming in on transfer...
The post Rodgers names incoming Celtic transfer but further update isn't nearly as promising appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As good as it gets at centre half]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111622</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/as-good-as-it-gets-at-centre-half/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T13:15:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week I wrote that Celtic were lucky their central defensive crisis happened during the transfer window.  They had time to make their move, although the requirement could not have been easy to fit. A player was needed who could play in the Champions League alongside a young Swedish defender who is new to the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First glimpse of Palma and Phillips in training as another injured Celtic star returns]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173029</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/first-glimpse-of-palma-and-phillips-in-training-as-another-injured-celtic-star-returns/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans have been given a first glimpse of Luis Palma and Nat Phillips in training. The Honduran winger and English centre-back have joined the...
The post First glimpse of Palma and Phillips in training as another injured Celtic star returns appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic set to dodge £113m star in Champions League; high-profile move agreed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173010</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-set-to-dodge-joao-felix-danger-but-true-firepower-will-still-be-coming-to-glasgow/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are set to dodge the talents of Joao Félix in their upcoming UEFA Champions League campaign, according to a report. The Atletico Madrid and...
The post Report: Celtic set to dodge £113m star in Champions League; high-profile move agreed appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Medical complete as Celtic set to make Deadline Day signing]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43819</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/01/medical-celtic-deadline-day-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T12:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been pretty busy over the last few days as they try to strengthen this squad, after an underwhelming start to the season. The club have already announced a couple of signings recently. Luis Palma is believed to have been signed in a £3.5 million deal from Aris FC while Nat Phillips has arrived […]
Medical complete as Celtic set to make Deadline Day signing - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I am sure’: Andy Walker reacts to possible deadline day exit of Celtic player he ‘liked’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173015</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/i-am-sure-andy-walker-reacts-to-possible-deadline-day-exit-of-celtic-player-he-liked/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andy Walker has backed a deadline day exit for Celtic winger, Sead Haksabanovic. The 24-year-old made his feelings clear after Celtic’s dropped points at home...
The post ‘I am sure’: Andy Walker reacts to possible deadline day exit of Celtic player he ‘liked’ appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fragile Feyenoord offers hope]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111619</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/fragile-feyenoord-offers-hope/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T11:01:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The status of this Champions League group is officially….alright .  In yesterday’s blog I said our draw was all about Pot 3.  Turns out, this wasn’t the case.  Feyenoord, our Pot 1 opponents, are the weakest we are ever likely to draw from that tier.  They earned their spot by being Dutch champions and benefiting [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The fee Celtic could receive for failed Ange signing as two clubs battle it out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173006</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/the-fee-celtic-could-receive-for-sead-haksabanovic-as-two-clubs-battle-it-out/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T10:42:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stoke City and PAOK are the two main contenders to sign apparent wantaway Celtic talent Sead Haksabanovic in the closing stages of the transfer window....
The post The fee Celtic could receive for failed Ange signing as two clubs battle it out appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic kick out two late English transfer offers; new plan and position for Academy talent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173003</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-kick-out-two-late-english-transfer-offers-new-plan-and-position-for-academy-talent/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T09:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been courting interest in two big talents at the club over the past couple of days but have so far rejected advances. The...
The post Celtic kick out two late English transfer offers; new plan and position for Academy talent appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic make long-awaited early morning announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43814</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/01/celtic-make-early-morning-announcement-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T09:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is safe to say that things have not been going Celtic’s way at the start of this season. They won their opening two games, but their performances left a lot to be desired. Then they were knocked out of the Scottish League Cup at the hands of Kilmarnock in the second round itself, a […]
Celtic make long-awaited early morning announcement - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feyenoord star asked directly about Celtic; takes a familiar route]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172988</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/feyenoord-star-asked-directly-about-celtic-takes-a-familiar-route/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T08:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feyenoord defender Bart Nieuwkoop was asked directly about Celtic following Thursday’s big draw. The Dutch champions have been drawn in to the same Champions League...
The post Feyenoord star asked directly about Celtic; takes a familiar route appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘ANYTHING CAN HAPPEN,’ O’RILEY EURO VERDICT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111615</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/anything-can-happen-oriley-euro-verdict/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T08:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY ignored recent transfer speculation to focus on Celtic’s Champions League challenge after the money-spinning ballot in Monaco yesterday. The Hoops have been paired with former Euro foes Feyenoord, Atletico Madrid and Lazio and the stylish midfielder is relishing the opportunity of pitting his wits among the game’s elite. O’Riley, a £1.5million bargain buy [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Georgios Samaras makes a surprising contribution to Celtic transfer business]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172981</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/georgios-samaras-makes-a-surprising-contribution-to-celtic-transfer-business/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic favourite Georgios Samaras was involved in the transfer of Luis Palma, according to a report. The Hoops announced the signing of the Honduras international...
The post Georgios Samaras makes a surprising contribution to Celtic transfer business appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HATATE GUESSING GAME]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111613</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hatate-guessing-game/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T07:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE could be about to end the guessing game by signing a new deal at Celtic. The Japanese midfielder knocked back a contract extension at the champions nine days ago, as CQN reported. However, there are indications the 25-year-old international may now join his countrymen Kyogo Furuhashi and Daizen Maeda in penning new terms [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic unveil 'limited edition jersey' and it's already a popular one; cost and release date]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172995</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-unveil-limited-edition-jersey-and-its-already-a-popular-one-cost-and-release-date/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T07:33:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have finally unveiled the new ‘limited edition jersey’ and it’s well worth the wait. Supporters have known about the Adidas throwback kit for months....
The post Celtic unveil 'limited edition jersey' and it's already a popular one; cost and release date appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC STAR DEAL HIJACK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111610</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-star-deal-hijack/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T06:50:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[STOKE CITY are planning to hijack Sead Haksabanovic’s proposed move to Greek club PAOK. The Championship side, managed by former Hamilton Accies boss Alex Neil, are making an eleventh-hour bid for the Sweden-born Montenegrin international winger. Haksabanovic, who arrived at the champions in August last year in a £1.7million switch from Rubin Kazan, hinted via [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["It had to be"; Feyenoord tweet picks up on class Celtic connection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172937</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/it-had-to-be-feyenoord-tweet-picks-up-on-class-celtic-connection/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feyenoord have made the obvious Celtic connection after being drawn with the Hoops in the UEFA Champions League group stage. Atletico Madrid and Lazio are...
The post "It had to be"; Feyenoord tweet picks up on class Celtic connection appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nat Phillips training status confirmed by Celtic team-mate; Ibrox question remains]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172974</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/nat-phillips-training-status-confirmed-by-celtic-team-mate-ibrox-question-remains/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing Nat Phillips has already been training at Lennoxtown as this weekend’s derby at Ibrox looms. Phillips was announced as a Celtic player...
The post Nat Phillips training status confirmed by Celtic team-mate; Ibrox question remains appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I CAN’T WAIT TO GET GOING,’ PHILLIPS EYES IBROX DEBUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111596</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-cant-wait-to-get-going-phillips-eyes-ibrox-debut/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T06:12:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEW BHOY Nat Phillips is hoping Brendan Rodgers throws him at the deep end after agreeing a six-month loan switch from Liverpool. The centre-back became the EIGHTH signing of the summer when he answered the SOS before the derby at Ibrox on Sunday. A variety of injuries has robbed the champions of Cameron Carter-Vickers, Maik [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic left-back latest; may not be entirely pleasing for supporters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172945</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/the-left-back-update-that-may-not-be-entirely-pleasing-for-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are still looking to sign a left-back on transfer deadline day, however no move is currently close. That’s the latest update from Sky Sports’...
The post Report: Celtic left-back latest; may not be entirely pleasing for supporters appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andy Robertson issues four-word response after Nat Phillips joins Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172950</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/andy-robertson-issues-four-word-response-after-nat-phillips-joins-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T05:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andy Robertson has told Nat Phillips ‘good luck, big man’ on Instagram after the Liverpool centre-back secured a loan deal to Celtic until January. Celtic...
The post Andy Robertson issues four-word response after Nat Phillips joins Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS v RANGERS (Part Four)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111571</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-v-rangers-part-four/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T04:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is preparing for a return to Glasgow derby action after an absence of over four and a half years when he takes Celtic to Ibrox on Sunday. The second time-around Hoops gaffer enjoyed phenomenal success against the city rivals in his first spell between May 2016 and February 2019. Rodgers faced the Govan [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer Deadline Day: Potential Celtic signings and 4 players who could leave]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172905</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/transfer-deadline-day-potential-celtic-signings-and-4-players-who-could-leave/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer deadline day is underway and Brendan Rodgers remains busy in the sales as Celtic strive to seal some last-ditch signings and grant a few...
The post Transfer Deadline Day: Potential Celtic signings and 4 players who could leave appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kieran Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic offered chance to sign Champions League winner for free]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43810</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/31/celtic-offered-champions-league-winner/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T22:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have announced the signings of Luis Palma and Nat Phillips. The Hoops need to make a few more additions before the summer transfer window slams shut though as there are a few positions on the pitch where they seem to be weak at the moment. One of them has to be left-back. Greg Taylor […]
Celtic offered chance to sign Champions League winner for free - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Grandads CSC Podcast:  Apply Within]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18475</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18475"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T22:25:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic Grandad CSC all get together to discuss the Champions League draw which sees Celtic in Group E with trips to Rotterdam Rome and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Desi Mond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player poised to join Stoke City with medical set]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43807</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/31/celtic-player-stoke-city-medical/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T21:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been busy with incomings over the last few days. They have already announced the signing of Luis Palma from Aris FC and the loan arrival of Nat Phillips from Liverpool. But on the other hand, there could be a few who head for the exit door before the summer transfer window slams shut […]
Celtic player poised to join Stoke City with medical set - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Promising report indicates late transfer surge at Celtic even after Phillips and Bernardo deals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172886</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/promising-report-indicates-late-transfer-surge-at-celtic-even-after-phillips-and-bernardo-deals/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T19:51:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are looking for “at least two more” signings after the move for defender Nat Phillips and the widely reported quest to land midfielder Paulo...
The post Promising report indicates late transfer surge at Celtic even after Phillips and Bernardo deals appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic reject Leeds United’s £10 million bid for key player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43804</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/31/celtic-reject-leeds-united-bid/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T19:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Things are heating up at Celtic Park in the final days of the summer transfer window. The club have been very active when it comes to incomings. They have already announced the arrivals of Luis Palma from Aris FC and Nat Phillips on loan from Liverpool. It is believed that they are close to getting […]
Celtic reject Leeds United’s £10 million bid for key player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Decent profile’: John Hartson sends Celtic transfer plea & reacts to links with 21-year-old]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172910</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/decent-profile-john-hartson-sends-celtic-transfer-plea-reacts-to-links-with-21-year-old/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Hartson has urged Celtic to bring in another striker before Friday’s transfer deadline day. Brendan Rodgers’ side have the best forward in the league...
The post ‘Decent profile’: John Hartson sends Celtic transfer plea & reacts to links with 21-year-old appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The verdict and reaction as Celtic draw tasty UEFA Champions League group; dates and details]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172908</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-verdict-and-reaction-as-celtic-draw-tasty-uefa-champions-league-group-dates-and-details/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T17:03:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been drawn against Feyenoord, Atletico Madrid and Lazio in the group stages of the UEFA Champions League after a ceremony in Monaco this...
The post The verdict and reaction as Celtic draw tasty UEFA Champions League group; dates and details appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CHAMPIONS LEAGUE: CELTIC v FEYENOORD, ATLETICO MADRID AND LAZIO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111593</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/champions-league-celtic-v-feyenoord-atletico-madrid-and-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T16:56:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC face three former European foes after the Champions League draw in Monaco this evening. Brendan Rodgers’ side will face Feyenoord, Atletico Madrid and Lazio for three intriguing ties in Group E of Europe’s elite competition. The Hoops will take on the Dutch title winners who, of course, overcame Jock Stein’s side in the San [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andy Robertson 'little bit jealous' of Liverpool teammate's Celtic move; Van Dijk helps sell it]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172898</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/andy-robertson-little-bit-jealous-of-liverpool-to-celtic-move-as-virgil-van-dijk-helps-sell-summer-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T15:49:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic defender Nat Phillips has shared he’s heard nothing but good things about the Bhoys from his green-and-white supporting Liverpool teammates. Phillips has joined...
The post Andy Robertson 'little bit jealous' of Liverpool teammate's Celtic move; Van Dijk helps sell it appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic reject transfer bid from Premier League club]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43800</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/31/celtic-reject-bid-premier-league/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T15:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are very busy at this point in time, as they try to improve their squad before the summer transfer window comes to an end. They have already brought in Luis Palma from Aris FC while loan deals for Nat Phillips of Liverpool and Paulo Bernardo of Benfica are believed to be very close as […]
Celtic reject transfer bid from Premier League club - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers speaks as Celtic officially sign up EPL player; Bhoys beat other clubs to deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172888</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-speaks-as-celtic-officially-sign-up-liverpool-player-bhoys-beat-other-clubs-to-deal/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T15:13:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have officially announced the signing of defender Nat Phillips from Liverpool on a short-term loan deal. The Scottish champions are taking Phillips to Scotland...
The post Brendan Rodgers speaks as Celtic officially sign up EPL player; Bhoys beat other clubs to deal appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's total summer spend after Luis Palma deal with more on the way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172883</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtics-total-summer-spend-after-luis-palma-deal-with-more-on-the-way/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T14:23:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s total summer transfer spend is ticking closer and closer to £20m as the Bhoys look to complete even more business in the final hours...
The post Celtic's total summer spend after Luis Palma deal with more on the way appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's next two signings now look imminent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172878</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtics-next-two-signings-now-look-imminent/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T13:52:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the announcement of Celtic’s move for Luis Palma, the club are now closing in on two more players who have already travelled or are...
The post Celtic's next two signings now look imminent appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['He has done exceptionally well': Peter Grant excited by claims Celtic to sign 'warrior']]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172851</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/he-has-done-exceptionally-well-pat-bonner-excited-by-claims-celtic-to-sign-warrior/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant thinks Celtic are signing a ‘warrior’ in Nat Phillips as he closes in on a season-long loan move from Liverpool. Brendan Rodgers has...
The post 'He has done exceptionally well': Peter Grant excited by claims Celtic to sign 'warrior' appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premier League player has agreed terms to join Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43793</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/31/premier-league-player-agreed-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T12:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans were disappointed with the club’s transfer activity over the summer but one has to admit that they are starting to pick up the pace now. The signing of Luis Palma was officially announced recently, and the Honduran international arrives amidst a lot of expectations and is being viewed as the potential replacement for […]
Premier League player has agreed terms to join Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rivals change narrative after Champions League failure but Celtic picture is different - opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172835</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/rivals-change-the-narrative-after-champions-league-failure-but-celtic-picture-is-different/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Listening to the coverage following PSV’s comprehensive dismantling of Rangers on Wednesday night, you’d be forgiven for thinking Celtic may as well not bother in...
The post Rivals change narrative after Champions League failure but Celtic picture is different - opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s all about Pot 3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111570</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/its-all-about-pot-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T11:05:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a strategic problem.  The great Neil Lennon European campaign of 2019 is slipping from our coefficient status, and we have done little of note since.  Neil’s team are the only Celtic side to win a European group, finishing above Lazio, Rennes and Cluj.  Four wins, a draw and defeat in a dead rubber [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Incredible"; What Klopp, van Dijk and Robertson have said about Celtic bound Nat Phillips]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172804</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/incredible-what-klopp-van-dijk-and-robertson-have-said-about-celtic-bound-nat-phillips/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are expected to complete the loan signing of Nat Phillips from Liverpool before Friday’s transfer deadline. The English central-defender is in Glasgow to put...
The post "Incredible"; What Klopp, van Dijk and Robertson have said about Celtic bound Nat Phillips appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kieran Tierney had the Celtic support on his mind after Real Sociedad unveiling question]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172825</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kieran-tierney-had-the-celtic-support-on-his-mind-at-real-sociedad-unveiling/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kieran Tierney had the Celtic support on his mind at his Real Sociedad unveiling. The Scotland defender has joined the Basque outfit on a season-long...
The post Kieran Tierney had the Celtic support on his mind after Real Sociedad unveiling question appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Trio could depart Celtic in coming days; update on goalkeeper]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172788</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/trio-likely-to-depart-celtic-in-coming-days-siegrist-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Celtic bid to strengthen the squad in the coming days, a number of players are also likely to depart the scene. Already this morning...
The post Report: Trio could depart Celtic in coming days; update on goalkeeper appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Productive Palma seventh arrival]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111550</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/productive-palma-seventh-arrival/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T09:09:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Luis Palma (23) became our latest recruit when he arrived yesterday from Aris Saloniki on a five-year contract.  He is an inverted left winger, who has on occasion played through the middle.  Aris finished a distant fifth in Greece last season, elevated to this position by a very productive Luis. He was designated penalty taker [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midfielder set to travel to Glasgow as Celtic move close]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43790</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/31/midfielder-glasgow-celtic-move-close/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T09:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already announced the signing of Luis Palma. They are also believed to be closing in on a move for Nat Phillips on a season-long loan. But the Hoops do not seem to have any plans of stopping there either. The club have made an underwhelming start to the season and they seem determined […]
Midfielder set to travel to Glasgow as Celtic move close - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Had a good laugh"; Luis Palma opens up on chat with Celtic favourite]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172843</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/had-a-good-laugh-luis-palma-opens-up-on-emilio-izaguirre-celtic-chat/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing Luis Palma has been speaking about his chat with Emilio Izaguirre prior to making the move to Scotland. Palma was announced as...
The post "Had a good laugh"; Luis Palma opens up on chat with Celtic favourite appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOLO CELTS IN CHAMPIONS LEAGUE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111535</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/solo-celts-in-champions-league/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T07:09:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC will carry the banner for Scotland as the country’s only representatives in the Champions League. The Hoops will be on a solo mission after Michael Beale’s Ibrox side were thrashed 5-1 by PSV Eindhoven with the Dutch taking their place in this evening’s all-star draw on a 7-3 aggregate scoreline. The Parkhead club now [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Thursday August 31: It’s Turning Out Nice Again]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18470</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18470"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T06:58:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Luis Palma has joined Celtic for the sum of £3,5m.         Looks like he can play a bit as well. Have we…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Malph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marc Crosas pokes fun at Rangers as Ibrox hilarity brings Celtic a welcome financial boost]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172795</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/marc-crosas-pokes-fun-at-rangers-as-ibrox-hilarity-brings-celtic-a-great-financial-boost/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will be the only Scottish side in the UEFA Champions League group stage draw after Rangers fell to a hilarious defeat against PSV. The...
The post Marc Crosas pokes fun at Rangers as Ibrox hilarity brings Celtic a welcome financial boost appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ABADA TO SIGN NEW DEAL – TEN MONTHS LATE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111530</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/abada-to-sign-new-deal-ten-months-late/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T06:24:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIEL ABADA is about sign a bumper new deal at Celtic – TEN months after his original offer from the champions. The Israeli international winger was presented with enhanced terms at the same time as striker Giorgos Giakoumakis on November 1 last year, as CQN reported. Both Abada and the hitman stalled on accepting the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Injured Celtic duo return to training ahead of Ibrox; Haksabanovic status]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172819</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/injured-celtic-duo-return-to-training-ahead-of-ibrox-haksabanovic-status/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Injured Celtic duo Hyeongyu Oh and Yuki Kobayashi have returned to training ahead of Sunday’s trip to Ibrox. Brendan Rodgers‘ side are busy preparing for...
The post Injured Celtic duo return to training ahead of Ibrox; Haksabanovic status appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘GOOD MOMENTS,’ NEW BHOY PALMA’S PROMISE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111528</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/good-moments-new-bhoy-palmas-promise/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T06:06:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC new Bhoy Luis Palma is standing by for a quickfire debut at Ibrox on Sunday. The 23-year-old Honduran international has sealed his £3.5million switch to the champions from Greek outfit Aris Thessaloniki – and he promises to hit the ground running. Palma, who agreed a contract until 2028, said: “I could not be any [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Significant business expected; late Celtic transfer plans spelled out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172780</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/all-eyes-on-a-left-back-as-exciting-late-celtic-transfer-plans-are-spelled-out/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have less than two days to complete further transfer business. The summer window will slam shut on Friday at midnight and it seems very...
The post Report: Significant business expected; late Celtic transfer plans spelled out appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luis Palma sends online message to the Celtic fans and his story is about to move very quickly]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=172810</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/luis-palma-sends-online-message-to-the-celtic-support-but-his-story-is-about-to-move-very-quickly/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T05:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Luis Palma has sent his first message to the Celtic support after signing for the club. The Honduras international’s move from Aris Thessaloniki was announced...
The post Luis Palma sends online message to the Celtic fans and his story is about to move very quickly appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS v RANGERS (Part Three)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111506</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-v-rangers-part-three/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-31T04:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is preparing for a return to Glasgow derby action after an absence of over four and a half years when he takes Celtic to Ibrox on Sunday. The second time-around Hoops gaffer enjoyed phenomenal success against the city rivals in his first spell between May 2016 and February 2019. Rodgers faced the Govan [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>