<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-07-13T04:13:20.301Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jota faces potential ban after leaving Celtic for Al-Ittihad]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42563</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/12/jota-faces-ban-celtic-al-ittihad/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T22:05:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The transfer of Jota from Celtic to Al-Ittihad was quite an eye opening deal in many ways. It was no surprise that the Portuguese winger was wanted by another club. He had made a tremendous impact for the Hoops over the past couple of seasons. But his destination was perhaps a major surprise to most […]
Jota faces potential ban after leaving Celtic for Al-Ittihad - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic told they don’t need to sign £16 million free agent]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42575</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/12/celtic-told-need-free-agent/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T20:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are expected to bring in several fresh faces this summer in an attempt to strengthen Brendan Rodgers’ squad for the upcoming season. Till now, they have signed Odin Thiago Holm and Marco Tilio. Both are very highly-rated talents and might go on to become superstars at Parkhead but at the same time, they are […]
Celtic told they don’t need to sign £16 million free agent - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wolves marketing figure references Celtic disappointment after South Korea shambles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166998</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/wolves-marketing-figure-shares-celtic-disappointment-after-south-korea-shambles/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T20:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A key marketing figure at Wolves has been talking up his side’s upcoming clash against Celtic. It was announced on Wednesday that Brendan Rodgers’ men will face the Premier League team in Dublin on Saturday 29 July. The game will take place at the glorious Aviva Stadium, with kick-off at 2pm. The Hoops were originally ...
The post Wolves marketing figure references Celtic disappointment after South Korea shambles appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The two former Celtic Treble winners still looking for a club]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=167008</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-two-former-celtic-treble-winners-still-looking-for-a-club/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T19:45:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The transfer window is a part of the season that all football fans love. The excitement of new players coming in coupled with the possibility of the club raking in millions whenever one of our top players are sold makes what would be a boring part of the year with no football that little bit ...
The post The two former Celtic Treble winners still looking for a club appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Odin Thiago Holm just getting started as Celtic begin with slow-mo hype]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166994</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/odin-thiago-holm-just-getting-started-as-celtic-begin-with-slow-mo-hype-another-star-absent/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic started their hype of summer signing Odin Thiago Holm on Wednesday. It’s three weeks since the Norwegian was signed from Valerenga on a five-year contract. The Celtic first-team were on holiday at that stage, and have since returned with the squad now in Portugal. Over the past few weeks while the players have been ...
The post Odin Thiago Holm just getting started as Celtic begin with slow-mo hype appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[€20 million Celtic target confirms he wants summer move]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42570</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/12/20-million-celtic-target-wants-move/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T19:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with plenty of high profile names in recent times, as it is believed that the club could be targeting a few marquee signings in the ongoing summer transfer window. It remains to be seen how things play out. The likes of Scott McTominay, Donny van de Beek, Kieran Tierney and a […]
€20 million Celtic target confirms he wants summer move - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fresh Donny van de Beek news should worry Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42566</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/12/donny-van-de-beek-news-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T17:35:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rumours have suggested that Celtic could try to pull off a few marquee signings this summer in order to strengthen Brendan Rodgers’ squad, as they look to defend their treble and also make an impact in the Champions League. And one player that they have been linked with lately is Manchester United midfielder, Donny van […]
Fresh Donny van de Beek news should worry Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic manager Neil Lennon lays out the unenviable task ahead for Michael Beale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166991</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-manager-neil-lennon-lays-out-the-unenviable-task-ahead-for-michael-beale/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new season ahead brings fresh optimism for every supporter base of every club. Only two teams can win the league but all teams go into the new season believing that they can, at least, win a cup of some sort. Well, that’s if Celtic stop hoovering them all up at the rate of knots ...
The post Former Celtic manager Neil Lennon lays out the unenviable task ahead for Michael Beale appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why this is the summer of opportunity for Celtic's former POTY; it could start tonight]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166985</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/why-this-is-the-summer-of-opportunity-for-celtics-david-turnbull-it-could-start-tonight/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is something about David Turnbull that makes me warm to him as a Celtic player. Now, I don’t know if it was because in that instantly forgettable COVID season he was the one shining light in what was a pretty shocking year for the club. Or maybe it’s because I love to see Scottish ...
The post Why this is the summer of opportunity for Celtic's former POTY; it could start tonight appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A rare media treat; Daizen Maeda makes one thing clear about Celtic in Japan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166967</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/a-rare-media-treat-daizen-maeda-makes-one-thing-clear-about-celtic-in-japan/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic attacker Daizen Maeda has given a rare interview to club media in Portugal. The Japanese attacker is part of the Celtic squad being put through their paces by manager Brendan Rodgers. The Hoops are due to face Portuguese side Portimonense this evening although the game will be a very low-key affair. Maeda may feature ...
The post A rare media treat; Daizen Maeda makes one thing clear about Celtic in Japan appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Darren O'Dea credits backroom man for Celtic B progress despite defeat to Sligo Rovers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166969</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/darren-odea-credits-backroom-man-for-celtic-b-progress-despite-defeat-to-sligo-rovers/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not just Brendan Rodgers’ men that are preparing for the new season ahead. The youngsters in the Celtic B team have also started their preparations for another year in the Lowland League. The young Hoops took part in a friendly in Ireland against Sligo Rovers last night ahead of the new season kick-off in ...
The post Darren O'Dea credits backroom man for Celtic B progress despite defeat to Sligo Rovers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic favourites to sign €20 million Brazilian winger]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42558</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/12/celtic-favourites-sign-brazilian-winger/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T12:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are rumoured to be looking to bring in some marquee players this summer in order to strengthen Brendan Rodgers’ squad. One area where they certainly need reinforcements at the moment is on the wings. They have seen a nailed on starter like Jota leave recently, leaving a big gap there. Jota arrived at the […]
Celtic favourites to sign €20 million Brazilian winger - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Willie Miller names versatile Celtic defender to fill priority position at Aberdeen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166953</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/willie-miller-names-versatile-celtic-defender-to-fill-priority-position-at-aberdeen/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic had a number of players out on loan last season and whilst many of them had successful seasons, there are others that did struggle to make a name for themselves. One that did impress was Liam Scales. The Celtic defender spent a full season on loan at Aberdeen. After a shaky start to his ...
The post Willie Miller names versatile Celtic defender to fill priority position at Aberdeen appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Returning loan player and an interesting midfield; Celtic Predicted XI vs Portimonense]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166938</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/returning-loan-player-and-an-interesting-midfield-celtic-predicted-xi-vs-portimonense/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are back in action on Wednesday evening against Portuguese side Portimonense. It’s 39 days since we clinched our latest treble with a 3-1 Scottish Cup final victory over Inverness Caledonian Thistle at Hampden. To say that a lot has changed since then would be an understatement. Ange Postecoglou has departed the club and been ...
The post Returning loan player and an interesting midfield; Celtic Predicted XI vs Portimonense appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summer fitness claims never stack up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109774</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/sumer-fitness-claims-never-stack-up/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T11:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a week of hard training, Celtic take to the field for their first preseason friendly today when they face Portimonense this evening.  The Portuguese side finished 15th in the topflight last season, a comfortable 8 points above relegation, although only one spot above the play-offs. We face the same side on Saturday before flying [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic are the main contenders to sign Brazilian winger]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166939</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-are-the-main-contenders-to-sign-brazilian-winger-tete/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been named as one of the main contenders to sign Shakhtar Donetsk winger, Tete. A report from Ukrainian outlet Sport Novyny has said that the 23-year-old intends to leave the club due to fears for his safety due to the ongoing conflict in the region. Tete joined Donetsk in 2019 as a product ...
The post Report: Celtic are the main contenders to sign Brazilian winger appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[€5 million Celtic flop closes in on move to Swansea City]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42555</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/12/5-million-celtic-flop-swansea-city/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T10:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been very good with their signings in recent times. That was not always the case though. In fact, one of the biggest reasons behind their struggles in the 2020/21 campaign was the terrible summer transfer window that they had that time around. Not one player that was brought in during those few months […]
€5 million Celtic flop closes in on move to Swansea City - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A pleasing sight from Celtic training and Brendan Rodgers gets a mic'd up moment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166933</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/pleasing-kyogo-furuhashi-sight-in-celtic-training-as-brendan-rodgers-gets-a-micd-up-moment/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T09:47:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Furuhashi has been seen back in training with Celtic in Portugal. Brendan Rodgers‘ side are in the Algarve as preparations step up ahead of the new season. The team are due to face Portuguese top-flight side Portimonense this evening, although that match will be played behind closed doors. The team have been training in ...
The post A pleasing sight from Celtic training and Brendan Rodgers gets a mic'd up moment appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic TV interviews in Portugal take a different turn; rising star put in front of the mic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166924</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-celtic-tv-interviews-in-portugal-take-a-different-turn-rising-star-put-in-front-of-the-mic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T09:13:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rising star Daniel Kelly is the latest player to speak to Celtic TV in Portugal. The Hoops first-team squad are in the Algarve, where they will will face Primeira Liga outfit Portimonense later on Wednesday. The likes of Callum McGregor, Daizen Maeda and Reo Hatate could all feature in the fixture but Celtic‘s stars of ...
The post The Celtic TV interviews in Portugal take a different turn; rising star put in front of the mic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Boyle talks up Brendan Rodgers’ summer signing; exciting times ahead for the Celtic fans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166918</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/martin-boyle-talks-up-brendan-rodgers-summer-signing-exciting-times-ahead-for-the-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T08:44:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic fans may well still be lamenting the loss of Jota this summer. The Portuguese winger was a huge fan favourite over his two years at the club but finally ended his brief, but successful, stay in Glasgow with a move to Al-Ittihad in Saudi Arabia. Jota’s trickery on the wing will be missed ...
The post Martin Boyle talks up Brendan Rodgers’ summer signing; exciting times ahead for the Celtic fans appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Brendan Rodgers must offer a new Celtic deal to 25-year-old international]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166916</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/why-brendan-rodgers-must-offer-a-new-celtic-deal-to-25-year-old-international/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All the excitement over Celtic offering new deals to the likes of Kyogo Furuhashi, Daizen Maeda and Callum McGregor did two things over the last two weeks. For one, it offset the disappointment of losing Portuguese winger Jota to Al-Ittihad and secondly, it put to bed the speculation that former Celtic manager, Ange Postecoglou could ...
The post Why Brendan Rodgers must offer a new Celtic deal to 25-year-old international appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A TALE OF TWO KEEPERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109763</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/a-tale-of-two-keepers/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T07:17:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S £4.5million misfit Vasilis Barkas is on the brink of joining English Championship side Swansea City. And the Greek flop could face former Hoops glove rival Conor Hazard in the new season after the Irishman signed for newly-promoted Plymouth Argyle. Both keepers had dropped down the ranks at the champions behind first-choice Joe Hart and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conor Hazard love extends far and wide; Celtic stars from multiple eras react to departure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166898</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/conor-hazard-love-extends-far-and-wide-celtic-stars-from-multiple-eras-react-to-departure/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T06:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic stars from multiple eras have been reacting after Conor Hazard departed the club. The Northern Irish goalkeeper has signed for Plymouth Argyle, for an undisclosed fee. Hazard took to Instagram on Tuesday evening to share a post of him in the Home Park side’s colours, with an accompanying message reading: “Delighted to sign at ...
The post Conor Hazard love extends far and wide; Celtic stars from multiple eras react to departure appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New name but a familiar look; Jacynta finds her next club after Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166904</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/new-name-but-a-familiar-look-jacynta-finds-her-next-club-after-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T06:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic FC Women star Jacynta Galabadaarachchi has found her next club. The attacker departed Celtic around a week ago after an enjoyable two-and-a-half year spell in Glasgow. Jacynta tormenting SWPL defenders in the hoops was a sight to behold, and something similar may occur next season, in a funny way. That’s because she had ...
The post New name but a familiar look; Jacynta finds her next club after Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic rearrange pre-season friendly; tickets on presale today]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166909</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-pre-season-friendly-rearranged-tickets-on-presale-today/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T05:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s pre-season friendly with English Premier League side Wolves has been rearranged and tickets go on pre-sale today on Ticketmaster. The original match that was organised in South Korea as part of the Asia Tour later this month but was cancelled due to Wolves pulling out of the fixture stating that the tour organisers failed ...
The post Celtic rearrange pre-season friendly; tickets on presale today appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…LASSAD NOUIOUI?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109739</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-lassad-nouioui/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T05:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LASSAD NOUIOUI signed a two-year deal at Celtic on September 2 2012 as a free agent after quitting Spanish top-flight club Deportivo La Coruna. Expectation levels were high for the French-born striker, who won two international caps for his adopted nation Tunisia, after he had performed for three years in La Liga. Peter Lawwell, then [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC v WOLVES IN DUBLIN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109758</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-wolves-in-dublin/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T05:09:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC will play Wolves at the Aviva Stadium on Saturday July 29 with a 2pm kick-off. The clubs were due to face each other in South Korea a fortnight today, but the match was scrapped with both sides withdrawing due to “financial and logistical” issues with organisers. Brendan Rodgers’ men are scheduled to take on [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC CONFIDENTIAL: FANS EUPHORIC AND ENRAGED AFTER TITLE WIN: DAVIE HAY REVEALS ALL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=75485</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-celtic-fans-euphoric-and-enraged-after-title-win-davie-hay-reveals-all/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T05:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Davie Hay concludes his inside tales during an eventful and ultimately successful 1997/98 season. The former player and manager had been chief scout for most of Wim Jansen’s solitary campaign as Hoops boss that saw the Parkhead men derail Rangers’ bid for 10 in a row – and go on and lift the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WELCOME BACK TO CELTIC: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part One)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=93495</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/welcome-back-to-celtic-the-tommy-burns-story-part-one/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T04:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS returned to his beloved Celtic as manager EXACTLY twenty-nine years ago today. It was an emotional and controversial homecoming for the Hoops legend as he left Kilmarnock in acrimonious circumstances to take over from the sacked Lou Macari. Celtic were accused of ‘tapping’ the boss while he was in charge at the Ayrshire [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic must avoid high-profile Premier League loan deals]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42533</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/11/celtic-premier-league-loan-deals/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T22:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a few potential loan deals Celtic are being linked with this summer. They are mainly English Premier League players looking for a fresh opportunity and it would raise serious questions about the Hoops’ planning if any of them end up happening. In the long run, they would help the club at all. Three […]
Celtic must avoid high-profile Premier League loan deals - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£2.6 million Celtic transfer target joins FC Midtjylland]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42547</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/11/celtic-transfer-target-joins-midtjylland/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T21:05:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have two great options up top right now in the form of Kyogo and Oh Hyeon-gyu. The Japanese forward has been the main man for the Hoops in recent times, and found the back of the net on 34 occasions last season. On the other hand, the South Korean striker has impressed as well, […]
£2.6 million Celtic transfer target joins FC Midtjylland - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano’s £35 million update is great news for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42543</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/11/fabrizio-romano-35-million-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T19:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Celtic appointed Brendan Rodgers as manager for a second stint in the Parkhead hot seat, rumours had suggested that the Northern Irishman had been promised a significant transfer budget in order to reshape the squad. Since then, we have seen Jota leave in a £25 million move to Al-Ittihad. And now, it looks like […]
Fabrizio Romano’s £35 million update is great news for Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic comments that feel particularly pertinent as more away fans are shut out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166840</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-joe-hart-comments-that-feel-particularly-pertinent-as-more-celtic-away-fans-are-shut-out/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart doesn’t seem to be the biggest fan of Celtic receiving a small allocation for Tynecastle. The Hoops received just over 1,200 tickets for trips to Hearts last season, but that number will be almost halved in the coming campaign. The Jambos are said to be reducing our allocation due to “high season ticket ...
The post The Celtic comments that feel particularly pertinent as more away fans are shut out appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Brendan Rodgers hype is real as yet another Ange favourite talks up Celtic boss]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166890</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-brendan-rodgers-hype-is-real-as-yet-another-postecoglou-favourite-talks-up-celtic-boss/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T17:45:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carl Starfelt is the latest Celtic player to speak positively about Brendan Rodgers. It’s been an intriguing few weeks as we see our first-team stars return to training under their new boss. The vast majority of the squad were brought to the club by former Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou, and it’s been particularly interesting to ...
The post The Brendan Rodgers hype is real as yet another Ange favourite talks up Celtic boss appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Celtic player completes Parkhead exit this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42539</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/11/another-celtic-player-completes-exit-3/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T17:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already seen Jota leave Parkhead this summer, in a £25 million move to Al-Ittihad. The Portuguese winger departing is a major blow without doubt and he will need to be replaced. Now, another club hero has headed out of the exit door as well, but his departure is not as high profile and […]
Another Celtic player completes Parkhead exit this summer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UEFA confirm even more big Champions League changes are coming Celtic's way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166885</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/uefa-confirm-even-more-big-champions-league-changes-are-coming-celtics-way/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T16:52:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More big changes are coming to the UEFA Champions League from 2024/25 and Celtic will be affected. As you’ll know by now, European football’s premier club competition is undergoing a major revamp from next season. The new Champions League format will see the traditional group stage ditched in favour of a new single league phase ...
The post UEFA confirm even more big Champions League changes are coming Celtic's way appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former EPL 'keeper tells how Martin O'Neill 'disappeared' and scuppered his move to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166867</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-epl-keeper-tells-how-martin-oneill-disappeared-and-scuppered-his-move-to-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former West Ham United and Newcastle goalkeeper, Shaka Hislop has spoken out about how Celtic were looking to sign him back in 2002 when Martin O’Neill was the manager. The former Trinidad and Tobago international goalkeeper revealed on ESPN’s YouTube podcast how the then-goalkeeping coach, Terry Gennoe was speaking to him about the move and ...
The post Former EPL 'keeper tells how Martin O'Neill 'disappeared' and scuppered his move to Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic exit confirmed as backup player joins English Championship side]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166875</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-exit-confirmed-as-backup-player-joins-english-championship-side/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conor Hazard has finally ended his nine-year affiliation with Celtic after penning a three-year deal with English Championship side, Plymouth Argyle. The Northern Ireland international underwent a medical yesterday and it seems all has gone well as Plymouth announced the move on their official website this afternoon. Hazard signed for Celtic back in 2014 from ...
The post Celtic exit confirmed as backup player joins English Championship side appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The vague SPFL rule that allows clubs to cut Celtic allocation; what can be done]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166857</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-vague-spfl-rule-that-allows-hearts-and-rangers-to-cut-celtic-allocation-what-can-be-done/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will receive just 650 tickets for league matches away to Hearts next season. The BBC say that the Tynecastle club are cutting away allocations next season for every team other than rivals Hibernian. The move is said to be a result of large season ticket sales in Gorgie, but it will continue to squeeze ...
The post The vague SPFL rule that allows clubs to cut Celtic allocation; what can be done appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['They are very important to me' - Kyogo Furuhashi pays tribute to the Celtic supporters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166858</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/they-are-very-important-to-me-kyogo-furuhashi-pays-tribute-to-the-celtic-supporters/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Furuhashi has paid tribute to the Celtic support in an interview with Celtic TV. The Hoops striker was asked how important the fans were in helping him settle at the club when he signed and into home life in Scotland when he revealed just how important the supporters are to him. Kyogo said [Celtic ...
The post 'They are very important to me' - Kyogo Furuhashi pays tribute to the Celtic supporters appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I WANT TO SEE THEIR SMILES,’ KYOGO AIMS TO PLEASE THE FANS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109749</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-want-to-see-their-smiles-kyogo-aims-to-please-the-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T14:08:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MASTER marksman Kyogo Furuhashi is determined to make sure Celtic are smiles better in the new season. The Japanese international striker, who has fired in 54 goals in his 83 appearances spread over two seasons at Parkhead, delighted the Hoops fans when he signed a new four-year deal a week ago, as CQN reported. Kyogo [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers reaffirms fringe player's importance to Celtic's first-team squad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166853</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-reaffirms-james-forrests-importance-to-celtics-first-team-squad/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic continue their preparations for the new season ahead at their training camp in Portugal, Brendan Rodgers took time out to praise James Forrest as the Celtic legend’s testimonial date approaches. The Celtic manager paid tribute to Forrest and urged fans to fill the stadium on the 1st of August and after speaking about ...
The post Brendan Rodgers reaffirms fringe player's importance to Celtic's first-team squad appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano tells of Jeremie Frimpong’s transfer ‘priority’; what it could mean for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166848</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/fabrizio-romano-tells-of-jeremie-frimpongs-transfer-priority-what-it-could-mean-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s all gone quiet on the Celtic transfer front over the last few days. Yes, as 67 Hail Hail highlighted last night, there has been sporadic rumours of interest in some players but nothing really concrete since the signing of Marco Tilio. But that doesn’t mean our transfer interests end there. Celtic still holds a ...
The post Fabrizio Romano tells of Jeremie Frimpong’s transfer ‘priority’; what it could mean for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carlos Borges to Celtic transfer update amid rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42532</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/11/carlos-borges-celtic-transfer-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T12:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have made moves for some highly-rated youngsters this summer. They have brought in Odin Thiago Holm from Valerenga and Marco Tilio from Melbourne City FC. Rumours have suggested that they might be closing in on a move for South Korean youth international, Yang Hyun-jun of Gangwon FC. Another superb young talent that they have […]
Carlos Borges to Celtic transfer update amid rumours - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind-the-scenes video offers fascinating insight in to Celtic star's role in training]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166828</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/behind-the-scenes-celtic-video-offers-fascinating-insight-in-to-joe-harts-role-in-training/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart is Celtic’s number-one goalkeeper but he may have another important role at the club. The Englishman has produced plenty of big moments over the past two years, helping the team to five domestic trophies under Ange Postecoglou. Now, with Brendan Rodgers in charge, the expectation is that Hart will continue between the sticks ...
The post Behind-the-scenes video offers fascinating insight in to Celtic star's role in training appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Tynecastle a more difficult place to visit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109743</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/making-tynecastle-a-more-difficult-place-to-visit/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T11:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why are Hearts proposing to limit the number of away fans to a few hundred, a move which would have consequence for only Celtic and Newco?  It will allow them to sell more season tickets, which would bring in more money.  It would also tip the competitive balance in their favour – no massed ranks [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: No approach from Celtic for Carlos Borges despite City Football Group links]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166842</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/no-approach-from-celtic-for-carlos-borges-despite-city-football-group-links/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are not in for Manchester City teenager Carlos Borges right now, according to a report. The attacker’s name has been on the lips of many Celtic supporters so far this summer, even though there has never been a concrete report linking us with him. As we covered yesterday, the name of Borges and Young ...
The post Report: No approach from Celtic for Carlos Borges despite City Football Group links appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic major contributors as SWPL chief talks up 'unimaginable' numbers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166830</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/celtic-major-contributors-as-swpl-chief-talks-up-unimaginable-numbers/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fran Alonso’s Celtic really captured the imagination of the Celtic fans last season. The Women had us all on the crest of a wave as they kept the challenge of the league title going to the last day of the season. Celtic did look out of it at one point, especially after a defeat to ...
The post Celtic major contributors as SWPL chief talks up 'unimaginable' numbers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star shares family post as injury intrigue continues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166809</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alistair-johnston-shares-family-image-as-injury-intrigue-continues/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Alistair Johnston has shared an amusing family post as intrigue over his fitness continues. The Canadian has been a complete revelation since his January switch from CF Montréal. He’s won the hearts and minds of virtually every Celtic supporter, as well as a hat-trick of trophies. Johnston became an important player for Ange ...
The post Celtic star shares family post as injury intrigue continues appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon tips Manchester United player to join Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42527</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/11/neil-lennon-manchester-united-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T09:30:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are rumoured to be eyeing a few marquee signings this summer in order to boost Brendan Rodgers’ squad ahead of another campaign in the UEFA Champions League group stage and the Hoops have three trophies to defend as well. We have already seen them being linked with one Manchester United player in the form […]
Neil Lennon tips Manchester United player to join Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Darren O'Dea is cautious ahead of Celtic B friendly; Sligo manager recognises club bond]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166820</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/why-darren-odea-is-cautious-ahead-of-celtic-b-friendly-sligo-manager-recognises-club-bond/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic prepare for their upcoming season in Portugal, the B team head to Ireland to face Sligo Rovers in a pre-season friendly. The youngsters will be without the likes of Rocco Vata, Bruno Davidson and Tobi Oluwayemi and Darren O’Dea has highlighted that whilst he has been delighted with the preparations so far, he ...
The post Why Darren O'Dea is cautious ahead of Celtic B friendly; Sligo manager recognises club bond appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Maybe Celtic’s that place for him” - Neil Lennon on recent links with international midfielder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166795</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/maybe-celtics-that-place-for-him-neil-lennon-on-recent-links-with-donny-van-de-beek/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T07:51:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s recent link with Manchester United’s Donny Van De Beek yesterday was a bit of a surprising one. As 67 Hail Hail discussed on the site yesterday, any potential move is likely to be a loan move but should the club pull this one off, it would be an incredible piece of transfer business. Van ...
The post “Maybe Celtic’s that place for him” - Neil Lennon on recent links with international midfielder appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Europa League side weighing up offer for Celtic talent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166789</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/report-celtic-talent-matt-oriley-subject-of-transfer-interest-4-clubs-potential-offer-ahead/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T06:16:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the big-money sale of Jota to Al-Ittihad, Celtic are doubtful keen on the exit of other important talents from last year’s treble-winning squad but it seems they could soon be contending with bids for midfielder Matt O’Riley. The Scottish Daily Mail [11/07 print edition] reports that several sides are showing interest in the Danish ...
The post Report: Europa League side weighing up offer for Celtic talent appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘HE’S ABSOLUTELY THE RIGHT MAN, MATE,’ ANGE’S VERDICT ON RODGERS’ RETURN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109675</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hes-absolutely-the-right-man-mate-anges-verdict-on-rodgers-return/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T06:11:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU had no hesitation in endorsing the merits of Brendan Rodgers as the Irishman continues his preparation for his second stint as Celtic manager. Asked about the qualities of his successor as he returns to the job after an absence of over four years, the Greek-Australian gaffer said: “He’s absolutely the right man, mate. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic youngster set for crucial UEFA Champions League match tonight]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166785</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/celtic-youngster-set-for-crucial-uefa-champions-league-match-tonight/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T05:40:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Believe it or not, the 2023/24 UEFA Champions League kicks off tonight with the first qualifying round – as teams go through the knockout gauntlet for a place in the money-spinning group stages of the competition. Celtic don’t enter the competition until September, with the draw for those all-important groups coming at the end of ...
The post Celtic youngster set for crucial UEFA Champions League match tonight appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…BERAM KAYAL?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109671</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-beram-kayal/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T05:15:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BERAM KAYAL became one of Neil Lennon’s best signings for Celtic first time around when the 22-year-old midfielder arrived in July 2010. The Israel international, who cost £1.25million from Maccabi Haifa, could be relied upon to put in a solid display in the engine room of the team with the ability to win challenges and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["He was constantly messaging me"; Postecoglou on interactions with Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166781</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/he-was-constantly-messaging-me-postecoglou-on-interactions-with-celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T05:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur manager Ange Postecoglou has shared that he and Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers have had many interactions since he departed Japan for Glasgow. Rodgers has replaced the Australian in the Celtic hot seat, with Postecoglou taking part in his first Spurs press conference since being appointed in London. He went over a variety of ...
The post "He was constantly messaging me"; Postecoglou on interactions with Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC CONFIDENTIAL: TITLE IN SIGHT – AND SACKED AGAIN: DAVIE HAY REVEALS ALL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=75444</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-confidential-title-in-sight-and-sacked-again-davie-hay-reveals-all/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T04:45:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Davie Hay continues his inside stories of Wim Jansen’s successful title-winning debut season in 1997/98. The former Hoops player and manager was a right-hand man and chief scout in the Dutchman’s backroom team as the Parkhead club were handed the task of preventing Rangers from claiming the historic 10 in a row. In [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans will be delighted with Marco Tilio’s claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42481</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/10/celtic-fans-marco-tilio-claim/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T22:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic get their preparations for next season underway with a return to training, one player will be hoping to get off to his usual fast start. Marco Tilio joined the club from Melbourne City FC recently and is getting settled to life in Scotland. He does though have a history of making a quick […]
Celtic fans will be delighted with Marco Tilio’s claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic suffer blow in race for Manchester City talent]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42519</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/10/celtic-blow-manchester-city-talent/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T21:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are expected to strengthen their squad this summer in preparation for another Champions League group stage campaign, while they have a treble to defend as well. There have been rumours about some marquee signings but till now, the Hoops have focused on signing highly-rated young talents. Odin Thiago Holm and Marco Tilio have already […]
Celtic suffer blow in race for Manchester City talent - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic contract theory that paves the way for big signings - opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166778</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-celtic-contract-theory-that-paves-the-way-for-big-signings/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T20:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s notable that two of Celtic’s biggest stars have had their contracts renewed recently, despite there being no major rush to do so. Both captain Callum McGregor and talismanic striker Kyogo Furuhashi have committed years more to Celtic – neither renewal was likely to have come cheaply. There’s no great source when it comes to ...
The post The Celtic contract theory that paves the way for big signings - opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers shares how Ange regular can improve under his watch at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166774</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/how-brendan-rodgers-aims-to-improve-daizen-maeda-further-under-his-watch-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T19:46:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has hailed the qualities that Daizen Maeda brings to the Celtic team but reckons the coaching staff can help him improve even further next season. Maeda is one of the players to have recently signed a new contract at the Bhoys, alongside Kyogo Furuhashi and Callum McGregor. The attacker has signed on until ...
The post Brendan Rodgers shares how Ange regular can improve under his watch at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[La Liga giants want to sign Celtic player this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42516</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/10/la-liga-giants-celtic-player-summer/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T19:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been very successful in recent seasons, winning five of the last six domestic competitions. One of the biggest reasons behind that is their superb record when it comes identifying and signing the right players. That also means though, that clubs from abroad will be keeping an eye on them. We have already seen […]
La Liga giants want to sign Celtic player this summer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The EA Sports and Celtic Park situation as club share new game promo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166767</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-ea-sports-and-celtic-park-situation-as-club-share-new-game-promo/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have shared a promotional image for the new EA Sports football video game. On Monday afternoon, the club retweeted a cover image from EA FC 24 to their 900,000 followers on Twitter. The image is a major promo for the new football simulation that will follow on from the immensely popular FIFA series when ...
The post The EA Sports and Celtic Park situation as club share new game promo appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic players we're still waiting to see back in training; image of fan favourite]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166758</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-celtic-players-were-still-waiting-to-see-back-in-training-club-share-image-of-fan-favourite/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic first-team are currently in Portugal continuing their preparations for the new season. For the majority, it’s the start of the second week of training, while our international stars are enjoying (or enduring) their first day back. The players underwent two sessions in the Algarve on Monday, with the official Twitter account describing the ...
The post The Celtic players we're still waiting to see back in training; image of fan favourite appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou makes superb Celtic claim despite leaving]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42512</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/10/ange-postecoglou-celtic-claim-leaving/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T18:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou arrived at Celtic as pretty much an unknown in the European game, despite of his successes in Japan and Australia. It did not take the manager too long to become a fan favourite though and he guided the Hoops to five trophies in his two seasons in the Parkhead hot seat. Postecoglou would […]
Ange Postecoglou makes superb Celtic claim despite leaving - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 7 youngsters spotted getting a big chance in Celtic's Portugal training camp pictures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166756</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/the-7-youngsters-spotted-getting-a-big-chance-in-celtics-portugal-training-camp-pictures/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A number of last season’s Celtic B regulars have made the trip with the senior squad for this week’s training camp in Portugal, per pictures published over the last couple of days. Brendan Rodgers has promised to ramp up the intensity of pre-season preparations over the next fortnight and these young prospects are getting a ...
The post The 7 youngsters spotted getting a big chance in Celtic's Portugal training camp pictures appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carlos Borges, Fabian Rieder and the curious summer Celtic transfer window]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166746</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/carlos-borges-fabian-rieder-and-the-curious-summer-celtic-transfer-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There have been plenty of speculative headlines about Celtic interest in names such as Carlos Borges of Manchester City and Young Boys midfielder Fabian Rieder this summer, but in a curious twist from the usual rumour mill, the original links to this pair didn’t come from the press. Both Borges’ and Rieder’s names came up ...
The post Carlos Borges, Fabian Rieder and the curious summer Celtic transfer window appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Callum McGregor has said about finishing his career at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166747</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-callum-mcgregor-has-said-about-finishing-his-career-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor has spoken previously about planning to finish his playing career at Celtic. The Hoops captain has signed a contract extension at the club, tying him down until the summer of 2028. By then McGregor will be 35 years old and in the latter stages of his career. At that stage, it would seem ...
The post What Callum McGregor has said about finishing his career at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda on how football is different in Scotland; what makes the Celtic fans go 'wild']]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166741</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/daizen-maeda-on-how-football-is-different-in-scotland-what-makes-the-celtic-fans-go-wild/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The one thing that the Japanese players have brought to Celtic’s style of football is their relentless hard work for the team. Players like Kyogo Furuhashi, Daizen Maeda and Reo Hatate are full of energy and don’t stop running for the whole ninety minutes. We even saw it from Tomoki Iwata when he was being ...
The post Daizen Maeda on how football is different in Scotland; what makes the Celtic fans go 'wild' appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou hails "outstanding" Celtic figure and predicts a pleasing future]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166737</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-hails-outstanding-brendan-rodgers-and-predicts-a-pleasing-celtic-future/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou expects Celtic to enjoy more success under Brendan Rodgers. It’s over a month since the Australian left the club to move to Tottenham Hotspur. Celtic appointed Brendan Rodgers as his successor soon after with the club now looking to the future. Postecoglou met the media for the first time as Spurs boss on ...
The post Ange Postecoglou hails "outstanding" Celtic figure and predicts a pleasing future appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star's extra work in Japan to be ready for Brendan Rodgers pre-season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166733</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/reo-hatates-extra-work-in-japan-to-be-ready-for-brendan-rodgers-celtic-pre-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This Celtic team are renowned for their fitness ability. And it was all borne from the former Celtic manager, Ange Postecoglou’s mantra of ‘We Never Stop’. For the past two seasons, we literally didn’t. We could count on two hands and two feet the number of late goals the team scored to turn what would ...
The post Celtic star's extra work in Japan to be ready for Brendan Rodgers pre-season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The next contract extension Celtic must take care of - Opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166723</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-next-contract-extension-celtic-must-take-care-of/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The amount of new contract extensions being announced by Celtic over the last week or so has certainly taken the sting out of losing Jota to the Saudi Arabian league. The new deals handed out to Callum McGregor, Daizen Maeda and Kyogo Furuhashi have sent out a real positive message to the Celtic support. Even ...
The post The next contract extension Celtic must take care of - Opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic interested in signing Manchester United player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42508</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/10/celtic-signing-manchester-united-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T14:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rumours have been doing the rounds that Celtic could be making some marquee signings this summer in order to make sure that Brendan Rodgers’ team is competitive in the Champions League. It will be interesting to see how that plays out but they are certainly being linked with some big names for sure. It was […]
Celtic interested in signing Manchester United player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou asked Celtic step-up question as history repeats itself]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166721</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-asked-celtic-step-up-question-as-history-repeats-itself/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T13:23:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou has been speaking at his first Tottenham Hotspur press conference. The Australian, who won five trophies in his two years at Celtic, departed for London just over a month ago. Celtic have since appointed Brendan Rodgers and the Hoops support are looking forward to what may be to come this ...
The post Ange Postecoglou asked Celtic step-up question as history repeats itself appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic hold interest in Donny van de Beek; loan exit from Manchester United most likely]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=166716</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/report-celtic-hold-interest-in-donny-van-de-beek-loan-exit-from-manchester-united-most-likely/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T12:27:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hold interest in Manchester United midfielder Donny van de Beek, according to a report. New Hoops boss Brendan Rodgers has already strengthened his midfield this summer, with Odin Thiago Holm joining from Valerenga. However, Aaron Mooy has retired from football and many Celtic supporters will feel the club need at least one more addition ...
The post Report: Celtic hold interest in Donny van de Beek; loan exit from Manchester United most likely appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘PRIVILEGE,’ RODGERS HAILS ‘HEARTBEAT OF THIS TEAM’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109668</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/privilege-rodgers-hails-heartbeat-of-this-team/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T12:21:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS admits it is a “privilege” to work with Callum McGregor, the player he rates as the “heartbeat of this team”. The returning Celtic manager welcomed the news the captain had signed a new five-year deal which will keep him at the champions until he is 35. McGregor has been pivotal in the Hoops’ [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘HUGELY PROUD,’ ADMITS McGREGOR AS HE COMMITS TO CELTIC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109663</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hugely-proud-admits-mcgregor-as-he-commits-to-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T11:51:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CALLUM McGREGOR admitted he was “absolutely delighted” to sign a new five-year deal with Celtic. And then the 30-year-old captain declared: “There’s only one place that I want to play football and that’s here.” McGregor, who replaced the legendary Scott Brown as the team’s onfield leader at the start of the remarkable 2021/22 campaign, said: [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[€2.5 million striker drops possible Celtic transfer hint]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42504</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/10/striker-drops-possible-celtic-hint/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T11:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already made a couple of additions to their squad this summer, with the signings of Odin Thiago Holm and Marco Tilio. A third addition seems close as well, as it looks like it is only a matter of time before Yang Hyun-jun ends up at Parkhead. And fans would expect more fresh faces […]
€2.5 million striker drops possible Celtic transfer hint - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor, Celtic’s fittest ever player]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109661</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/callum-mcgregor-celtics-fittest-ever-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T10:59:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whatever doubts existed about the first team squad, we all knew there was no chance of Callum McGregor leaving.  This morning, Celtic announced the captain has signed a five-year contract which will keep him at the club until he turns 35.  It is likely to be his last in the game and will be structured [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ONE-TIME WONDERBHOY IS THIRD RATE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109655</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/one-time-wonderbhoy-is-third-rate/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T07:35:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ONE-TIME Celtic wonder Bhoy Dylan McGeouch has signed for English third-tier side Carlisle United. The midfielder was tipped for a massive future by Neil Lennon when he made his Hoops home debut as an 18-year-old prospect on November 26 2011. McGeouch came on for James Forrest in a league match against St Mirren at Parkhead [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I LOVE YOU FOR LIFE,’ JOTA’S HEARTFELT MESSAGE TO CELTIC FANS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109652</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-love-you-for-life-jotas-heartfelt-message-to-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T06:29:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FILIPE JOTA has sent a heartfelt message to Celtic fans following his rapid £25million exit for Saudi Arabian club Al-Ettihad. The fans’ favourite bowed out with the third goal in the Hoops’ 3-1 Scottish Cup Final triumph over Inverness Caley Thistle at Hampden on June 3. Jota was pivotal to the team’s success as they [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RETURN OF THE ROCK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109646</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/return-of-the-rock/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T05:53:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CAMERON CARTER-VICKERS is ahead of schedule as he prepares to make his return. The USA World Cup centre-back missed the last six games of the season – including the treble-sealing Scottish Cup Final triumph – after undergoing knee surgery. Carter-Vickers, the rock in the Hoops rearguard, bowed out of the action after a Man-of-the-Match performance [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHATEVER HAPPENED TO…PAWEL BROZEK?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109627</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whatever-happened-to-pawel-brozek/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T05:15:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[POLISH striker Pawel Brozek was brought to Celtic on loan from Turkish outfit Trabzonspor in January 2012. He returned to his parent club four months later after firing blanks in only three appearances for the Hoops. Brozek made just one start for the club in a league encounter against Motherwell at Fir Park on April [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC CONFIDENTIAL:  X-FACTOR BRATTBAKK, DAVIE HAY REVEALS ALL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=54684</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-confidential-x-factor-brattbakk-davie-hay-reveals-all/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T05:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Davie Hay continues his inside stories as he details the changes in Wim Jansen’s team as the new-look Hoops prepared to derail Rangers’ bid for 10 successive titles in the 1997/98 campaign. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE, the former player and manager opens up in a massive year of change at the club as he [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MO JOHNSTON: THE LYING GAME]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=64871</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/mo-johnston-the-lying-game/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T04:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EXACTLY thirty-four years ago today, Mo Johnston turned his back on Celtic, the club he professed to love, to join Rangers. Author Alex Gordon, who has written fifteen Celtic books including ‘50 Flags Plus One‘, a tribute to the club’s first 51 untainted titles, devoted a chapter in his first newspaper memoirs, ‘Jinx Dogs Burns [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic closer to signing £2 million winger this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42500</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/09/celtic-closer-2-million-winger/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-09T22:35:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic made a fast start to the summer, confirming deals for Odin Thiago Holm and Marco Tilio. Both are very highly rated talents, who are believed to have big futures ahead of them. Thus, they could prove to be great signings for the Hoops in the long term. Since then, things have moved a bit […]
Celtic closer to signing £2 million winger this summer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports man makes Kieran Tierney Celtic return claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42496</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/09/sky-sports-kieran-tierney-celtic-return/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-09T21:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kieran Tierney left Celtic in the summer of 2019 in a Scottish record £25 million move to join Arsenal. The left-back had come through the youth ranks at Parkhead and was one of the club’s best players. Thus, him leaving was a major blow for sure. Could there be a return on the cards in […]
Sky Sports man makes Kieran Tierney Celtic return claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£2.6 million Celtic target looks set to join FC Midtjylland]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42493</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/09/celtic-target-set-join-fc-midtjylland/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-09T19:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic had a fantastic record of identifying and signing players during the time of Ange Postecoglou as the manager of the club. And fans will be hoping for that run to continue even though the Australian has left Parkhead to in order to join Tottenham Hotspur. The Hoops have brought in Brendan Rodgers as his […]
£2.6 million Celtic target looks set to join FC Midtjylland - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jota finally breaks silence in emotional message to Celtic fans]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42488</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/09/jota-silence-emotional-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-09T18:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were handed a major blow this summer, with Jota leaving the club in order to join Al-Ittihad. On one hand, the Hoops are believed to have received a transfer fee in the region of £25 million including add-ons, which is huge. But on the other hand, they have lost one of their most important […]
Jota finally breaks silence in emotional message to Celtic fans - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player set to undergo medical with exit close]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42484</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/09/celtic-player-medical-exit-close/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-09T11:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It will be important for Celtic to strengthen their squad this summer, with three trophies to defend next season as well as Champions League group stage football guaranteed. The club have already brought in Odin Thiago Holm and Marco Tilio. A move for Yang Hyun-jun appears to be close as well while rumours have suggested […]
Celtic player set to undergo medical with exit close - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player tipped to stay on despite exit rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42477</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/09/celtic-player-tipped-stay-exit-rumours/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-09T09:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are expected to bring in multiple new faces this summer in order to strengthen the squad as well as reshape it to fit the vision and plans of Brendan Rodgers. On the other hand, quite a few are expected to leave as well, as they have struggled for playing time at Parkhead and might […]
Celtic player tipped to stay on despite exit rumours - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS REVEALS CELT WHO WILL HAVE ‘REALLY GOOD IMPACT’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109624</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-reveals-celt-who-will-have-really-good-impact/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-09T09:02:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS insists evergreen winger James Forrest still has a crucial role to play for Celtic. The Scotland international, who celebrated his 32nd birthday during the week as CQN reported, was hindered by persistent injury during Ange Postecoglou’s debut campaign. And Forrest was used sparingly last term as fitness problems curtailed his outings in the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART: BONNER POSES ‘THE BIG QUESTION’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109621</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/joe-hart-bonner-poses-the-big-question/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-09T08:06:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LEGENDARY Celtic keeper Pat Bonner reckons Joe Hart faces a make-or-break period in the early stages of Brendan Rodgers’ return. The 36-year-old former England No.1 is entering the final 12 months of his Hoops contract after joining the champions in a cut-price £1million switch from Spurs in August 2021. Ironically, Ange Postecoglou, the manager who [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£7m MISFITS IN CELTIC EXIT SETBACK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=109594</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/7m-misfits-in-celtic-exit-setback/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-09T05:31:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S £7million misfits Albian Ajeti and Ismaila Soro have been dealt stebacks as they head for the Hoops exit. The flop frontman, who cost £5million from West Ham in August 2020, and the midfielder, a £2million arrival from Israeli outfit Bnei Yehuda seven months earlier, have both returned to the champions after season-long loans. Ajeti, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pop superstar Niall Horan pictured with Celtic jerseys]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=42473</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/07/08/pop-niall-horan-pictured-celtic-jerseys/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-08T22:05:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have one of the biggest fan bases in the world and very often people fail to realise how widespread the support for the Hoops is, because they play in the Scottish Premiership. The club have a long list of celebrity fans as well. That includes names like Rod Stewart, Lewis Capaldi, Snoop Dogg and […]
Pop superstar Niall Horan pictured with Celtic jerseys - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>