<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-10-03T12:19:57.631Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switched-on Celtic star already making great noises about move to Scotland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176141</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/switched-on-hyunjun-yang-already-making-great-noises-about-move-to-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic winger Hyunjun Yang seems to be settling in well to life in Scotland. The South Korean winger made the switch from Gangwon in late...
The post Switched-on Celtic star already making great noises about move to Scotland appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["So proud of you"; Brown, Cahill, Duffy and more react to Celtic great's very personal message]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176219</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/so-proud-of-you-brown-cahill-duffy-and-more-react-to-celtic-great-tom-rogics-big-message/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T11:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic hero Tom Rogic has announced his retirement from football at the age of 30. Rogic spent nine years on our books, joining as...
The post "So proud of you"; Brown, Cahill, Duffy and more react to Celtic great's very personal message appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Barcelona star returns to Celtic Park after playing in famous 2012 night]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176134</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/former-barcelona-star-returns-to-celtic-park-after-playing-in-famous-2012-night/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A number of Lazio personnel will arrive at Celtic Park with previous experience on their side. The likes of Ciro Immobile and Danilo Cataldi were...
The post Former Barcelona star returns to Celtic Park after playing in famous 2012 night appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CL hopes, Tom, Mick hustling for his job]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112712</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/cl-hopes-tom-mick-hustling-for-his-job/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T11:03:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been so long since Celtic progressed into the knockout rounds of the Champions League we dare not allow expectations to take root in our heads.  For now, at least, the prospect is a live one.  The result against Lazio at Celtic Park tomorrow night will give us a real insight into where our [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic vs Lazio referee has already been involved in Ibrox controversy this season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176114</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-vs-lazio-referee-has-already-been-involved-in-ibrox-controversy-this-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donatas Rumšas will be the man in charge when Celtic face Lazio this Wednesday. It’s set to be a huge evening in Glasgow as we...
The post Celtic vs Lazio referee has already been involved in Ibrox controversy this season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano drops late-night news that will affect Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44658</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/03/fabrizio-romano-late-night-news-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T10:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Celtic’s transfer business over the recent years has been a bit inconsistent. They were incredible during the summer of 2021 and the winter of 2022, building the core of the team by signing many players who would go on to be first-team starters. But other than that, it […]
Fabrizio Romano drops late-night news that will affect Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[’Laughing’: Celtic icon Neil Lennon slams Rangers-Postecoglou claim after Beale's sacking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176195</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-icon-neil-lennon-slams-rangers-ange-postecoglou-claim-after-michael-beales-sacking/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T09:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon has fired back at a Rangers fan who suggested that his supporters were ‘jealous’ when Celtic first appointed Ange Postecoglou as their manager...
The post ’Laughing’: Celtic icon Neil Lennon slams Rangers-Postecoglou claim after Beale's sacking appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WILL THE REAL REO HATATE PLEASE STAND UP?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112710</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/will-the-real-reo-hatate-please-stand-up-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T08:37:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE, a dynamic performer last season, has yet to complete 90 minutes in a Celtic game this time around. Admittedly hampered by injury, the 25-year-old Japanese midfielder has yet to get into his stride with the team now facing their tenth game of the campaign in the Champions League Group E encounter against Lazio [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INVINCIBLE RETIRES: THANKS FOR THE MEMORIES, TOM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112706</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/invincible-retires-thanks-for-the-memories-tom/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T07:56:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC Invincible Tom Rogic has quit football – at the age of 30. The Wizard of Oz, a Hoops fans’ favourite, has hung up his boots after leaving West Brom at the end of the season. Rogic had been out of football for four months before Steve Bruce took him to the Championship club on [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Fair play': Barry Ferguson can't deny Celtic truth after Rangers sack Michael Beale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176156</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/barry-ferguson-cant-deny-celtic-truth-after-rangers-sack-michael-beale/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Barry Ferguson couldn’t deny that there is a ‘spirit building’ at Celtic after Rangers sacked Michael Beale. As Celtic produced a stunning win at Motherwell...
The post 'Fair play': Barry Ferguson can't deny Celtic truth after Rangers sack Michael Beale appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic unveil well-intentioned Champions League merch but they're unlikely to be big sellers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176121</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-unveil-well-intentioned-champions-league-merch-but-theyre-unlikely-to-be-big-sellers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have unveiled some new merchandise that is unlikely to be a big seller. The Hoops are back in the UEFA Champions League for the...
The post Celtic unveil well-intentioned Champions League merch but they're unlikely to be big sellers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liverpool fume at VAR shambles but they got a better explanation than Celtic last season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176154</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/liverpool-fume-at-var-shambles-but-they-got-a-better-explanation-than-celtic-last-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some Celtic fans may have been scratching their heads a little bit during the Tottenham Hotspur vs Liverpool game on Saturday. As you’ll no doubt...
The post Liverpool fume at VAR shambles but they got a better explanation than Celtic last season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano's big Jeremie Frimpong report should play right into Celtic's hands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176127</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/fabrizio-romanos-big-jeremie-frimpong-report-should-play-right-into-celtics-hands/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic defender Jeremie Frimpong is set to sign a new deal with Bayer Leverkusen. That’s according to well-known transfer guru Fabrizio Romano who offered...
The post Fabrizio Romano's big Jeremie Frimpong report should play right into Celtic's hands appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Charlton under-14s"; former Celtic hero's brutal trolling of Michael Beale continues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176148</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/charlton-under-14s-celtic-hero-chris-suttons-brutal-trolling-of-michael-beale-continues/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T05:17:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic hero Chris Sutton’s brutal trolling of Michael Beale has continued. The Englishman was dismissed as Rangers manager at the weekend after his side...
The post "Charlton under-14s"; former Celtic hero's brutal trolling of Michael Beale continues appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIRTHDAY BHOY ABADA’S EURO HOPE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=83303</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/birthday-bhoy-abadas-euro-hope/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T04:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIEL ABADA is hoping for a belated birthday celebration when Celtic take on Lazio in the Champions League Group E encounter at Parkhead tomorrow night. The exciting Israel international winger turns 22 today, but, alas, the nearest he will get to the action against the Serie A cracks will be a seat in the stand when [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans react as Arsene Wenger claim goes viral]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44654</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/02/celtic-fans-arsene-wenger-claim/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T22:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers find themselves without a manager once again. This has not been an uncommon situation for them in recent years, to be honest. Whoever arrives next will be their fourth head coach in less than two years. During that period of time, they have won one trophy compared to Celtic’s five. Of course, there will […]
Celtic fans react as Arsene Wenger claim goes viral - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Favourite named for Rangers job as Celtic race ahead]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44652</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/02/favourite-named-rangers-job-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T21:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a four-point lead in the Premiership over second-placed St Mirren and seven points ahead of the Rangers. The Hoops seem to be showing no signs of slowing down both on and off the pitch though. The situation is very different when it comes to Ibrox. They find themselves without a manager for the […]
Favourite named for Rangers job as Celtic race ahead - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James McFadden highlights Celtic star who has been ‘sensational’ this season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176092</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/james-mcfadden-highlights-celtic-star-who-has-been-sensational-this-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The game of Matt O’Riley is just going from strength to strength at Celtic. After impressing under Ange Postecoglou, it feels as though the 22-year-old...
The post James McFadden highlights Celtic star who has been ‘sensational’ this season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero makes superb tweet after Michael Beale sack]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44649</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/02/celtic-hero-tweet-michael-beale/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T19:34:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is safe to say that Michael Beale’s time at Ibrox did not turn out as he would have envisioned. The manager had come in amidst a lot of expectations and hype but failed to deliver. He was not able to win a single trophy during his time with the Rangers and did not even […]
Celtic hero makes superb tweet after Michael Beale sack - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As rivals fracture Brendan Rodgers shows unity with Celtic hierarchy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176089</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/as-rivals-fracture-brendan-rodgers-shows-unity-with-celtic-hierarchy/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T18:52:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers demonstrated the unity at Celtic with comments in the wake of Saturday’s thrilling win over Motherwell. Luis Palma and Matt O’Riley scored late...
The post As rivals fracture Brendan Rodgers shows unity with Celtic hierarchy appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Michael Beale comments on Celtic that look even more foolish now after Rangers sacking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176084</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-michael-beale-comments-on-celtic-that-look-even-more-foolish-now-after-rangers-sacking/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T18:20:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Beale was far from a shy and retiring character during his spell as a manager in Scottish football, but in truth, the controversial comments...
The post The Michael Beale comments on Celtic that look even more foolish now after Rangers sacking appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bayern Munich player does not regret leaving Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44646</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/02/bayern-munich-regret-leaving-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T18:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have continued to enjoy success on the pitch for a long time now. They have won 11 of the last 12 league campaigns and if something unexpected does not happen, they should be able to clinch this one as well. But that does not mean that the Hoops have been successful in all aspects […]
Bayern Munich player does not regret leaving Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Lazio and Man City star left impressed by Celtic ahead of Champions League showdown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176079</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-lazio-and-man-city-star-left-impressed-by-celtic-ahead-of-champions-league-showdown/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T17:55:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Lazio and Man City attacker Rolando Bianchi reckons Celtic will be competitive against the Italians on Wednesday night – and the rest of their...
The post Former Lazio and Man City star left impressed by Celtic ahead of Champions League showdown appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Motherwell publish sensational new footage of Celtic heartbreaker and celebration drama]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176076</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/motherwell-publish-sensational-new-footage-of-celtic-heartbreaker-and-celebration-drama/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T17:20:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘Football can be so cruel’ is the verdict of Motherwell Football Club this Monday evening as they reflect on a weekend of so close, yet...
The post Motherwell publish sensational new footage of Celtic heartbreaker and celebration drama appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['That’s where Celtic’: Kris Boyd makes Celtic claim on Sky after Rangers sack Michael Beale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176058</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/thats-where-celtic-kris-boyd-makes-celtic-claim-on-sky-after-rangers-sack-michael-beale/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T16:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kris Boyd has praised Celtic for getting the job done on the domestic stage and winning the trophies after Rangers sacked Michael Beale. The former...
The post 'That’s where Celtic’: Kris Boyd makes Celtic claim on Sky after Rangers sack Michael Beale appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic concern after shocker of a Motherwell challenge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175970</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-addresses-greg-taylor-celtic-concern-after-heavy-motherwell-tackle-nat-phillips-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T16:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers is hoping that Greg Taylor won’t be suffering from any ill effects resulting from a heavy Motherwell challenge on him late on in...
The post Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic concern after shocker of a Motherwell challenge appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have golden chance to put immediate pressure on Steven Davis, Alex Rae and Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176053</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/celtic-have-golden-chance-to-put-immediate-pressure-on-steven-davis-alex-rae-and-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T14:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that Celtic’s rivals Rangers have sacked their manager, attention is turning to the upcoming list of fixtures for both Glasgow teams and what the...
The post Celtic have golden chance to put immediate pressure on Steven Davis, Alex Rae and Rangers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Lineker makes fantastic claim about Celtic on air]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44640</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/02/gary-lineker-makes-claim-celtic-air/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T13:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are coming off quite the week. They got themselves a dramatic 2-1 win over Motherwell at Fir Park. The Hoops went ahead in the 87th minute through Luis Palma, as the Honduran international scored his first goal for the club. Most fans thought that was the winner before the home team equalised in the […]
Gary Lineker makes fantastic claim about Celtic on air - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIG DEAL: CELTIC TARGET TWO MORE STARS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112702</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/big-deal-celtic-target-two-more-stars/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T11:38:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CAMERON CARTER-VICKERS and Greg Taylor are in line to become the next Celtic players to be offered extended contracts. The Hoops hierarchy want the defenders to follow the recent trend of EIGHT stars who have signed enhanced terms at the champions. Matt O’Riley became the latest star to pledge his immediate future to the Parkhead men [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sisyphus FC’s endless struggle to catch Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112701</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/sisyphus-fcs-endless-struggle-to-catch-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T11:06:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That late winner by Matt O’Riley was the start of a great weekend for Celtic, as later, main challengers St Mirren could only manage a draw at Kilmarnock.  The fact that this result is better than Celtic managed there in the League Cup is no comfort to the Paisley side’s title aspirations. St Mirren are [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic look ready to hold talks with two more players]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44636</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/02/celtic-ready-talks-two-players/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T10:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been very active in recent times and taking a number of steps in the positive direction. Yes, the club’s signings in the summer came under a lot of criticism and understandably so. They decided to go for only highly-rated youngsters and no real experience was brought to the club. The shortcoming of that […]
Celtic look ready to hold talks with two more players - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S MAKE-OR-BREAK SCHEDULE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112696</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtics-make-or-break-schedule/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T07:16:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC are preparing for the make-or-break challenge of 19 games in three months that will go a long way to determining success this season. Brendan Rodgers’ men kick off the gruelling schedule with a Champions League encounter against Lazio at Parkhead on Wednesday night. The Hoops, with four other encounters in football’s elite club tourney [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHO’S NEXT FOR THE POISONED CHALICE?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112692</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/whos-next-for-the-poisoned-chalice/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T06:37:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE manager’s job at Ibrox has become football’s poisoned chalice. Michael Beale, who ill-advisably termed Ange Postecoglou “lucky” last season, was unceremoniously sacked after the 3-1 home loss to Aberdeen at the weekend, as CQN reported last night. The Englishman became the second Govan gaffer to be dismissed inside 12 months as he followed Giovanni [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Mad’: Gary Lineker makes Celtic comment during his The Rest is Football Podcast]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176037</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/mad-gary-lineker-makes-celtic-comment-during-his-the-rest-is-football-podcast/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T06:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Lineker says Celtic’s stunning comeback win at Motherwell was one of his ‘moments of the week’. The BBC presenter and former England striker noted...
The post ‘Mad’: Gary Lineker makes Celtic comment during his The Rest is Football Podcast  appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘7.27 rating’: How Celtic loanee Sead Haksabanovic faired in Stoke's stunning comeback win]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176012</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/7-27-rating-how-celtic-loanee-sead-haksabanovic-faired-in-stoke-citys-stunning-comeback-win/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-02T06:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s fair to say that Sead Haksabanovic might not don the Celtic colours again following the manner of his exit this summer. The 24-year-old joined...
The post ‘7.27 rating’: How Celtic loanee Sead Haksabanovic faired in Stoke's stunning comeback win appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Beale’s old Celtic claim goes viral after Rangers exit]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44608</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/01/michael-beale-old-celtic-claim-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-01T22:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That was some weekend if you are a Celtic fan. For Michael Beale and supporters of the Rangers, it was pretty much the opposite. The results, after a disappointing start to the season have led to the departure of the Ibrox boss, less than a year after he was brought in as Giovanni van Bronckhorst’s […]
Michael Beale’s old Celtic claim goes viral after Rangers exit - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans react as Rangers announce Michael Beale sack]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44621</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/01/celtic-fans-react-rangers-michael-beale/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-01T21:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The revolving door at Ibrox continues to remain in motion as the Rangers will now be on the lookout for their fourth manager in the space of less than two years. It started when Steven Gerrard left in order to join Aston Villa in November 2021. He was replaced by Giovanni van Bronckhorst, who was […]
Celtic fans react as Rangers announce Michael Beale sack - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Comedy’: Celtic legend Chris Sutton issues brutal reaction as Rangers sack Michael Beale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175974</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/comedy-celtic-legend-chris-sutton-issues-brutal-reaction-as-rangers-sack-michael-beale/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-01T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It wasn’t so long ago that some thought that Ange Postecoglou wasn’t going to last long at Celtic. Yet, as of Sunday evening, Rangers have...
The post ‘Comedy’: Celtic legend Chris Sutton issues brutal reaction as Rangers sack Michael Beale appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BEALE GETS THE BOOT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112689</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/beale-gets-the-boot/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-01T20:15:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MICHAEL BEALE has been given the boot – after just 10 months in charge of the Ibrox club. The under-pressure boss was sacked this evening following the team’s third Premiership loss this season after going down 3-1 at home to Aberdeen yesterday. That defeat followed Celtic winning 1-0 at the same venue at the start [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers hype bubble bursts in face of gap to Celtic as Michael Beale is sacked]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175972</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/rangers-hype-bubble-bursts-in-face-of-gap-to-celtic-as-michael-beale-is-sacked/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-01T20:02:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Beale has been sacked as manager of Rangers tonight, leaving Ibrox less than a year after taking charge. Beale has been heading for this...
The post Rangers hype bubble bursts in face of gap to Celtic as Michael Beale is sacked appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player wants to leave permanently next year]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44615</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/01/celtic-player-wants-leave-next-year/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-01T19:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have quite a big squad at this point in time. While there are some areas where they could do with more top-quality reinforcements, overall, they have plenty of options across the pitch. As a result, there are quite a few who struggled to get consistent playing time. Some are still at the club while […]
Celtic player wants to leave permanently next year - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic tipped to 'dominate' Lazio in UEFA Champions League this week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175967</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kenny-dalglish-delivers-bullish-verdict-on-celtics-chances-vs-lazio-in-uefa-champions-league/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-01T18:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Dalglish reckons Celtic can turn the tide on their UEFA Champions League form this Wednesday with a win at home to Lazio. The Bhoys...
The post Celtic tipped to 'dominate' Lazio in UEFA Champions League this week appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jota drops Instagram hint boosting Celtic return hope]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44609</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/01/jota-instagram-celtic-return-hope/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-01T17:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jota was one of Celtic’s most important players during the Ange Postecoglou era and certainly had a big hand in them winning five trophies over the previous two seasons. Not only did he contribute with both goals and assists but he was also someone with a lot of flair and the ability to rise up […]
Jota drops Instagram hint boosting Celtic return hope - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Miller buries his head in the sand with Michael Beale, Celtic and Rangers assessment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175964</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kenny-miller-buries-his-head-in-the-sand-with-michael-beale-celtic-and-rangers-assessment/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-01T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Miller doesn’t think the time is quite right for Rangers to sack Michael Beale and he reckons Celtic will be dropping ‘more points than...
The post Kenny Miller buries his head in the sand with Michael Beale, Celtic and Rangers assessment appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I don't’: Kris Boyd teased in Sky Sports studios as Celtic winner goes in at Motherwell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175942</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/extraordinary-kris-boyd-teased-in-sky-sports-studios-as-celtic-winner-goes-in-at-motherwell/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-01T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kris Boyd was teased in the Sky Sports studios as Brendan Rodgers Celtic secured a stunning 2-1 win at Motherwell. The former Rangers striker was...
The post ‘I don't’: Kris Boyd teased in Sky Sports studios as Celtic winner goes in at Motherwell appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio manager Maurizio Sarri angry before facing Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44605</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/01/lazio-manager-maurizio-sarri-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-01T15:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic lost their opening Champions League group stage game of the season against Feyenoord. It was a decent display in the first half but all their good work was undone by conceding an avoidable goal and then seeing two players sent off. As a result, their next game in the competition, against Lazio at Parkhead, […]
Lazio manager Maurizio Sarri angry before facing Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio talisman Ciro Immobile managing injury concern ahead of Celtic Park trip]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175936</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/lazio-talisman-ciro-immobile-managing-injury-concern-ahead-of-celtic-park-trip/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-01T13:53:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio superstar Ciro Immobile only managed to play 15 minutes off the bench for his club on Saturday night after picking up a knock in...
The post Lazio talisman Ciro Immobile managing injury concern ahead of Celtic Park trip appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['It is Beale's': Chris Sutton’s 23-word message after dramatic day for Celtic & Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175920</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/it-is-michael-beales-chris-suttons-message-after-dramatic-day-for-celtic-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-01T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton put it mildly on Twitter but he thinks Brendan Rodgers’ Celtic had a ‘good day’ in the Premiership on Saturday. Given the outrageous...
The post 'It is Beale's': Chris Sutton’s 23-word message after dramatic day for Celtic & Rangers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic seem to replace Ange Postecoglou catchphrase with new one]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44602</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/01/celtic-replace-ange-postecoglou-new/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-01T10:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic got themselves a morale-boosting and potentially title race-defining win at the weekend. With 96 minutes gone, it looked like they were set to drop points away at Fir Park. But then, they would pull out victory from the jaws of a draw as Matt O’Riley found the winner in the 97th minute of the […]
Celtic seem to replace Ange Postecoglou catchphrase with new one - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIVE ALIVE: CELTIC’S SURPRISE ‘GOAL MACHINE’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112684</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/five-alive-celtics-surprise-goal-machine/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-01T10:28:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YOU would have got long odds on Matt O’Riley being Celtic’s top goalscorer going into October. Remarkably, though, the midfielder who netted a meagre three times last season is now one ahead of Kyogo Furuhashi in the marksman stakes after his dramatic stoppage-time winner against Motherwell at Fir Park. His exquisite sidefoot finish from Greg [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HAPPY DAZE, CALLUM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112677</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/happy-daze-callum/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-01T09:35:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CALLUM McGREGOR must have sensed a hint of deja vu against Motherwell yesterday. The Celtic captain danced a jig of joy as he celebrated goals from Luis Palma and Matt O’Riley that gave the champions a crucial 2-1 victory at Fir Park. And McGregor may have remembered an afternoon from December 2016 when he also revelled [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS IN A TIME WARP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112675</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-in-a-time-warp/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-01T09:32:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS would have been forgiven for thinking he had walked into a time warp at Fir Park yesterday. The first time the Irishman encountered the venue was back on the Sunday afternoon of December 3 2016 when he was in charge of Celtic in his debut campaign. The confrontation against Mark McGhee’s Motherwell side was [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘MOST ENJOYABLE MOMENT,’ O’RILEY CAPS HAPPY DAY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112601</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/most-enjoyable-moment-oriley-caps-happy-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-01T06:32:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY attempted to relive “probably the most enjoyable moment on a football pitch” after his exquisite finish to claim a 2-1 victory against Motherwell at Fir Park. The stylish Celtic midfielder completed one of the team’s greatest all-time grand finales when he materialised at the back post to sidefoot a superb Greg Taylor cross [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘What a player’: Luis Palma blown away by Celtic star after stunning win over Motherwell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175898</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/what-a-player-luis-palma-blown-away-by-celtic-star-after-stunning-win-over-motherwell/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-01T05:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s never easy, is it? What a weekend of Premiership action for Celtic and star midfielder, Matt O’Riley. There are ways to win football matches;...
The post ‘What a player’: Luis Palma blown away by Celtic star after stunning win over Motherwell appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PARADISE LOST: WHEN BIG YOGI LEFT CELTIC (Part Three)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112390</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/end-of-an-era-part-three/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-01T04:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend John ‘Yogi’ Hughes played his final game 52 years ago. The club’s eighth-highest goalscorer with 189 strikes had his last hurrah at Parkhead when he played in the 3-0 European Cup victory over BK 1903 Copenhagen to help the team through to the next round on a 4-2 aggregate scoreline. Hughes was devastated [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE JOCK STEIN YEARS (Part Twenty-One)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=83296</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-jock-stein-years-part-twenty-one/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-01T04:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Jock Stein had an extraordinary impact on the Parkhead club after returning as manager in March 1965. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE,  Alex Gordon, author of fifteen publications on Celtic, opened his book files on the Parkhead great for an absorbing twenty-one part series. Today, in Part Twenty-One of our fascinating look back at these landmark [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic must sign Chelsea winger on loan in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44595</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/30/celtic-must-sign-chelsea-winger-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T22:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic made nine additions to their squad over the summer, bringing in seven players on a permanent basis and two more on loan deals. But there are a few positions where they might still be a bit light on options. One of them might very well be on the wings, as they saw Jota leave […]
Celtic must sign Chelsea winger on loan in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Journalist claims Celtic player’s transfer value now more than £15m]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44592</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/30/journalist-claims-celtic-player-15m/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T20:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic pulled off a number of great moves during the time of Ange Postecoglou as the manager of the club, especially during that remarkable first season. The likes of Kyogo, Cameron Carter-Vickers and Reo Hatate grab most of the headlines when there is talk about the Australian’s best signings at Parkhead. But there is one […]
Journalist claims Celtic player’s transfer value now more than £15m - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Stewart sums up the difference between Celtic and Rangers right now after Saturday drama]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175895</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/michael-stewart-sums-up-the-difference-between-celtic-and-rangers-right-now-after-saturday-drama/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T19:47:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Stewart believes Rangers are badly lacking the game-winning attributes that Celtic possess within Brendan Rodgers’ squad, despite question marks also being raised about the...
The post Michael Stewart sums up the difference between Celtic and Rangers right now after Saturday drama appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Brendan Rodgers told Celtic stars in dressing room after astonishing win over Motherwell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175877</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/what-brendan-rodgers-told-celtic-stars-in-dressing-room-after-astonishing-win-over-motherwell/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T19:10:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been a fantastic day in the Scottish Premiership for Celtic. Not only did the Bhoys pick up all three points away to Motherwell, but...
The post What Brendan Rodgers told Celtic stars in dressing room after astonishing win over Motherwell appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio suffer massive blow before trip to Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44587</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/30/lazio-suffer-trip-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T19:02:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have had a brilliant weekend. They were nowhere near their best, once again, but managed to find a way to win with a winner coming from Matt O’Riley in the 97th minute of the game. On the other hand, they saw the Rangers lose at Ibrox to Aberdeen. The defeat leaves them seven points […]
Lazio suffer massive blow before trip to Celtic Park - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio suffer another blow ahead of Celtic Park trip]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175888</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/lazio-suffer-saturday-blow-ahead-of-celtic-park-trip/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T18:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio suffered another Serie A blow ahead of their trip to Celtic Park this week, losing to AC Milan 2-0 on Saturday evening. Maurizio Sarri’s...
The post Lazio suffer another blow ahead of Celtic Park trip appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic take possible dig at Rangers’ loss to Aberdeen]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44583</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/30/celtic-take-rangers-loss-aberdeen/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T17:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a completely different weekend for the two Glasgow giants. Celtic grabbed victory from the jaws of a draw twice. First, they went ahead in the 87th minute against Motherwell at Fir Park. And then they found a winner in the 97th minute. On the other hand, the Rangers ended up losing 3-1 to […]
Celtic take possible dig at Rangers’ loss to Aberdeen - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luis Palma sends class Instagram message after scoring first goal for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175879</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/luis-palma-sends-class-instagram-message-after-scoring-first-goal-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T17:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Luis Palma has fully bought into the Celtic mentality after his starring role off the bench in Saturday’s dramatic win over Motherwell at Fir Park....
The post Luis Palma sends class Instagram message after scoring first goal for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC SEVEN CLEAR WITH BEALE IN BLUNDERLAND]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112597</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-seven-clear-with-beale-in-blunderland/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T16:07:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CHAMPIONS Celtic swept SEVEN points clear of Michael Beale’s Ibrox side after another day of Premiership drama. Brendan Rodgers’ Hoops outfit claimed a thrilling 2-1 victory over Motherwell at Fir Park when Matt O’Riley struck an exquisite winner in the seventh minute of stoppage-time. So, the Parkhead men, looking for their twelfth title in 13 years, got the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meltdown at Ibrox as Rangers are embarrassed and Matt O'Riley magic surges Celtic clear]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175870</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/meltdown-at-ibrox-as-rangers-are-embarrassed-and-matt-oriley-magic-surges-celtic-clear/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T16:04:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have ended the Scottish Premiership weekend four points clear of second-placed St Mirren and seven points clear of supposed title rivals Rangers. An astonishing...
The post Meltdown at Ibrox as Rangers are embarrassed and Matt O'Riley magic surges Celtic clear appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers fans react as they fall 7 points behind Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44580</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/30/rangers-fans-react-points-behind-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T16:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The clock might be ticking on Michael Beale’s time as the manager of the Rangers. Celtic could have easily dropped points this weekend when they saw Motherwell equalise in the 95th minute of the game at Fir Park. But showing the character of champions, Brendan Rodgers’ side found the winner in the 97th minute through […]
Rangers fans react as they fall 7 points behind Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PANIC? NO CHANCE: ‘WE DELIVERED,’ RODGERS SALUTES HIS STOPPAGE-TIME STARS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112591</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/panic-no-chance-we-delivered-rodgers-salutes-his-stoppage-time-stars/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T15:06:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DELIGHTED Brendan Rodgers praised his victorious Celtic players as they refused to push the panic button in the remarkable conclusion in the champions’ 2-1 triumph at Fir Park. The visitors, with 70 per cent of possession, dominated the encounter against a stubborn Motherwell side content to sit back, soak up the pressure and look to hit [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MOTHERWELL 1 CELTIC 2: OH, YES, AS O’RILEY STAGES LATE, LATE SHOW]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112579</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/motherwell-1-celtic-2-oh-yes-as-oriley-stages-late-late-show/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T13:36:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MOTHERWELL 1 CELTIC 2  MATT O’RILEY celebrated his new contract with a sensational winning goal at Fir Park. The encounter had ebbed and flowed in the fading moments when it looked as though Luis Palma had struck to give the champions a crucial victory with three minutes to go. Remarkably, Well levelled in the fifth [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Motherwell v Celtic, GG Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112540</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/motherwell-v-celtic-gg-live-updates/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T10:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 12:30.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: GREEN LIGHT FOR YANG]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112575</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-green-light-for-yang/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T10:25:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOUTH KOREAN winger Yang Hyun-jun has been brought into the Celtic line-up for this afternoon’s Premiership clash with Motherwell at Fir Park. The summer recruit replaces James Forrest, who made a rare start in the 3-0 win over Livingston in West Lothian a week ago today. The evergreen forward was sacrificed before the half-hour mark [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic officially make fantastic triple announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44576</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/30/celtic-officially-triple-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T10:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been on a bit of a roll lately. After a stumbling start to the season, their results and performances have certainly improved, as the players seem to be coming to grips with Brendan Rodgers’ system of football. On the other hand, a number of them have been committing their futures to the club […]
Celtic officially make fantastic triple announcement - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘BRILLIANT,’ BRENDAN HAILS MATT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112570</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/brilliant-brendan-hails-matt/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T09:36:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has hailed Matt O’Riley as “a joy to coach and work with” on the day the midfielder signed a new four-year deal at the champions. The smooth 22-year-old playmaker had been at the centre of a transfer guessing game as he pondered putting pen to paper to extend his contract until 2027. Rodgers admitted [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston is already seeing the lighter side of Celtic's two red cards in Rotterdam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175849</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alistair-johnston-is-already-seeing-the-lighter-side-of-celtics-two-red-cards-in-rotterdam/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T08:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston has been reflecting on his first taste of UEFA Champions League football with Celtic. The Canadian was one of four Hoops players taking...
The post Alistair Johnston is already seeing the lighter side of Celtic's two red cards in Rotterdam appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DONE DEAL: ‘GRATEFUL’ O’RILEY SIGNS FOR FOUR YEARS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112566</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/done-deal-grateful-oriley-signs-for-four-years/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T08:27:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY has pledged his immediate future to Celtic by signing a four-year deal today. The announcement comes just 24 hours after the news Reo Hatate had also agreed a contract extension as Brendan Rodgers continues to consolidate the backbone of his squad. O’Riley becomes the EIGHTH Bhoy to sign on in recent times following [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Barry Hepburn reminds us of the struggle Celtic face with young stars]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175858</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/barry-hepburn-reminds-us-of-the-struggle-celtic-face-with-young-stars/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic youngster Barry Hepburn has been speaking about his last few years with Bayern Munich. The Scottish winger is back in his homeland after...
The post Barry Hepburn reminds us of the struggle Celtic face with young stars appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Partnership resumed, attacking switch; Celtic Predicted XI vs Motherwell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175865</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/partnership-resumed-attacking-switch-celtic-predicted-xi-vs-motherwell/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T07:50:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic make the trip to Fir Park today to take on Motherwell in the Scottish Premiership, aiming to keep their points lead at the top...
The post Partnership resumed, attacking switch; Celtic Predicted XI vs Motherwell appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Don't want to show your face"; Johnston on the pressure of Celtic and living in Glasgow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175842</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/dont-want-to-show-your-face-alistair-johnston-on-the-pressure-of-celtic-and-living-in-glasgow/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Alistair Johnston has been speaking about the pressure associated with playing for the club and living in Glasgow. Johnston has made a huge...
The post "Don't want to show your face"; Johnston on the pressure of Celtic and living in Glasgow appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: QUESTIONS FOR Mr BEATON]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112564</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-questions-for-mr-beaton/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T07:02:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AM I alone in believing Joe Hart was extremely unlucky to be removed from proceedings at Livingston last weekend? The 36-year-old keeper experienced a red card being flashed under his snoot for the first time in a distinguished career which kicked off two decades ago with Shrewsbury Town and had been virtually blemish-free until trigger-happy [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic return to Motherwell for first time since hugely embarrassing SFA moment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175828</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-return-to-motherwell-for-first-time-since-hugely-embarrassing-sfa-moment/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are back at Motherwell on Saturday for the first time since a hugely embarrassing moment for the SFA. The Hoops visited Fir Park twice...
The post Celtic return to Motherwell for first time since hugely embarrassing SFA moment appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["As soon as his name was linked"; Celtic star shares initial reaction to Rodgers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175835</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alistair-johnston-is-absolutely-loving-brendan-rodgers-shares-celtic-squads-initial-reaction/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Alistair Johnston sounds like he’s absolutely loving working under Brendan Rodgers. The Canada international had to wait patiently for his chance to impress...
The post "As soon as his name was linked"; Celtic star shares initial reaction to Rodgers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MOTHERWELL v CELTIC: 5-MINUTE QUIZ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112490</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/motherwell-v-celtic-5-minute-quiz-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T05:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have enjoyed some rousing duels at Fir Park over the years and the two old foes lock horns again at the venue in the 12.30pm kick-off today. The Hoops overcame Motherwell 2-1 in their last visit in November last year when a Filipe Jota ‘goal’ was controversially ruled out to spark VAR controversy. How much [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘THE DAY WEE JINKY BROKE MY HEART,’ By TOMMY GEMMELL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=72547</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-day-wee-jinky-broke-my-heart-by-tommy-gemmell/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T05:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JIMMY JOHNSTONE, the Greatest-Ever Celtic Player as voted by the Hoops supporters, was born on this day in 1944. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE, author Alex Gordon takes a look through his files for tales of the Hoops legend. Alex co-authored Tommy Gemmell’s autobiography, ‘All The Best‘, published by CQN in 2014, and talked about his [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WEE JINKY: BY THE LIONS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=97440</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/wee-jinky-by-the-lions/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T05:01:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JIMMY JOHNSTONE, the Greatest-Ever Celtic Player as voted by the Hoops supporters, was born on this day in 1944. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE, author Alex Gordon takes a look through his book files for tales of the Hoops legend. Alex devoted a chapter of his tribute book to the European Cup-winning team, ‘Lisbon Lions: The [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE JIMMY JOHNSTONE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=54963</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-unforgettable-jimmy-johnstone/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T05:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JIMMY JOHNSTONE, the Greatest-Ever Celtic Player as voted by the Hoops supporters, was born on this day in 1944. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE, author Alex Gordon takes a look through his files for tales of the Hoops legend. Alex devoted a chapter of his tribute book to the European Cup-winning team, ‘Lisbon Lions: The 40th [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PARADISE LOST: WHEN BIG YOGI LEFT CELTIC (Part Two)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112389</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/paradise-lost-when-big-yogi-left-celtic-part-two/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T04:30:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend John ‘Yogi’ Hughes played his last game for the club 52 years ago. The club’s eighth-highest goalscorer with 189 strikes had his last hurrah at Parkhead when he played in the 3-0 European Cup victory over BK 1903 Copenhagen to help the team through to the next round on a 4-2 aggregate scoreline. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE JOCK STEIN YEARS (Part Twenty)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=83257</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-jock-stein-years-part-twenty/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-30T04:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Jock Stein had an extraordinary impact on the Parkhead club after returning as manager in March 1965. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE,  Alex Gordon, author of fifteen publications on Celtic, has opened his book files on the Parkhead great for an absorbing twenty-one part series. Today, in Part Twenty of our fascinating look back at these [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[English Championship manager admits to copying Celtic style]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44572</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/29/english-manager-admits-copying-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T22:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic played some of the best football in recent memory during their two years under the management of Ange Postecoglou. The Australian did a fantastic job of combining effectiveness with beautiful football. And it led to the club winning five trophies over the course of the two seasons he was in Glasgow. Postecoglou’s style of […]
English Championship manager admits to copying Celtic style - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key Celtic starter tipped to leave the club next year]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44570</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/29/key-celtic-tipped-leave-next-year/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T20:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have done a pretty good job when it comes to agreeing contract extensions with a number of their important players. It is vital that they not only hold on to their best performers but keep them happy as well. Of course, just because they have signed a new deal does not mean that they […]
Key Celtic starter tipped to leave the club next year - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three changes on the cards; Celtic team news ahead of Motherwell test]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175825</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/three-changes-on-the-cards-celtic-team-news-ahead-of-motherwell-test/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T20:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers will be forced into making at least one change to Saturday’s eleven against Motherwell, but more tweaks could be made to his Celtic...
The post Three changes on the cards; Celtic team news ahead of Motherwell test appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou admits his forever love for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44566</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/29/ange-postecoglou-forever-love-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T19:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou did a fantastic job in the two years that he was the manager of Celtic. When he arrived, not many people gave him a chance. At the end of the day, he was a relative unknown who had achieved success in Japan and Australia, but never even managed a top-flight club in Europe. […]
Ange Postecoglou admits his forever love for Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[English Championship boss left blown away and inspired by Celtic performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175817</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/english-championship-boss-left-blown-away-and-inspired-by-celtic-performance/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T18:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plymouth Argyle manager Steven Schumacher has revealed that Celtic’s Scottish League Cup Final win over Rangers earlier in the year was the basis for a...
The post English Championship boss left blown away and inspired by Celtic performance appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Celtic stars make it onto global 'wonderkids' list as FC 24 launches]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175814</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/3-celtic-stars-make-it-onto-global-wonderkids-list-as-fc-24-launches/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T17:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three of Celtic’s brightest young talents have found their way onto a list of the best ‘wonderkids’ in football, according to new EA Sports video...
The post 3 Celtic stars make it onto global 'wonderkids' list as FC 24 launches appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liverpool’s Jurgen Klopp makes superb Celtic claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44561</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/29/liverpools-jurgen-klopp-makes-superb-celtic-claim/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T17:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jurgen Klopp is one of the best managers of his generation. What he achieved during his time at Borussia Dortmund and is continuing to do at Liverpool, as he put the German at the very top of the game. One man who is looking to reach those lofty heights in Ange Postecoglou. After a superb […]
Liverpool’s Jurgen Klopp makes superb Celtic claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou makes brilliant Celtic comments in new Sky Sports interview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175809</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-makes-it-clear-how-much-he-still-loves-celtic-in-new-sky-sports-interview/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T16:21:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou still watches Celtic from afar and has reaffirmed how much he loved his time in Glasgow, in a new interview with Sky Sports....
The post Ange Postecoglou makes brilliant Celtic comments in new Sky Sports interview appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic finally make long-awaited evening announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44556</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/29/celtic-long-awaited-evening-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T16:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have done a great job when it comes to keeping the core of their squad together despite the departure of Ange Postecoglou somewhat out of the blue. Jota and Carl Starfelt might have left in the summer but other than that, they have held on to all of their key players. And not just […]
Celtic finally make long-awaited evening announcement - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REO BRAVO: ‘I LOVE PLAYING FOR CELTIC,’ SAYS HATATE AS HE SIGNS 5-YEAR DEAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112547</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/reo-bravo-i-love-playing-for-celtic-says-hatate-as-he-signs-5-year-deal/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T15:52:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE admitted his love of Celtic as he signed on at the champions until 2028. The fans’ favourite ended the guessing game this afternoon as he finally agreed the contract to pledge his immediate future to the Parkhead men. It’s another boost for manager Brendan Rodgers as Hatate joins his countrymen Kyogo Furuhashi and Daizen [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers left buzzing with "great news" coming out of Celtic; major agreement reached]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175804</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-and-reo-hatate-react-after-big-contract-extension/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T15:50:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder Reo Hatate has signed a new five-year contract with the club, committing his future until 2028. The Japanese star has impressed since signing...
The post Brendan Rodgers left buzzing with "great news" coming out of Celtic; major agreement reached appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic announce defender has signed three-year deal]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44553</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/29/celtic-announce-defender-three-year-deal/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T14:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been very active in the last few months when it comes to handing contract extensions. The likes of Callum McGregor, Kyogo Furuhashi, Daizen Maeda, Liel Abada, Stephen Welsh and Anthony Ralston have all put pen to paper on new deals. The Hoops are believed to be looking to agree fresh terms with two […]
Celtic announce defender has signed three-year deal - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I'm only turning 25"; Anthony Ralston's intimate Celtic press conference]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175795</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/im-only-turning-25-anthony-ralstons-intimate-celtic-press-conference/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Ralston was in front of the media on Friday ahead of Celtic’s match against Motherwell this weekend. The Hoops are playing in the Saturday...
The post "I'm only turning 25"; Anthony Ralston's intimate Celtic press conference appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Motherwell man has media room laughing after Daizen Maeda Celtic remark]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175765</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/motherwell-man-has-media-room-laughing-after-daizen-maeda-celtic-remark/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T13:19:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Motherwell man Paul McGinn was in good form when speaking to the media ahead of his side’s clash against Celtic. The Scotland international, the older...
The post Motherwell man has media room laughing after Daizen Maeda Celtic remark appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic announce great news about youngster after reported Premier League interest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175784</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/celtic-announce-great-mitchel-frame-news-after-premier-league-interest/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T11:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic youngster Mitchel Frame has signed a new three-year deal at the club. The club confirmed the news on Friday afternoon, with the 17-year-old’s new...
The post Celtic announce great news about youngster after reported Premier League interest appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chance for champions to extend lead over St Mirren]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112518</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/chance-for-champions-to-extend-lead-over-st-mirren/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T11:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two weeks ago, Motherwell were neck-and-neck with Celtic at the top of the table.  A home defeat to St Mirren and another reversal at Ibrox has seen them slip to fourth in the table, but the devil is in the detail. The Lanarkshire side battered St Mirren but failed to make any of their 20 [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Johnston rivalry, Rodgers' German, goalkeeping poetry; three amusing sights from Celtic training]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175776</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/johnston-rivalry-rodgers-german-goalkeeping-poetry-three-amusing-sights-from-celtic-training/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic first-team squad will have been making the most of some extra time on the training pitch this week. While our League Cup exit...
The post Johnston rivalry, Rodgers' German, goalkeeping poetry; three amusing sights from Celtic training appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘ONLY THE STRONGEST WILL SURVIVE,’ BRENDAN’S MANTRA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112516</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/only-the-strongest-will-survive-brendans-mantra/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T08:44:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has spelled out his demands on his Celtic players as he prepares for his ninth game in charge since his second coming. The 50-year-old Irishman has endured mixed fortunes on his return following an absence of four and a half years. The holders went out of the Viaplay League Cup at the first [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[READY STEADY JOE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112512</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ready-steady-joe/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T07:54:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART will miss only his third Premiership game since joining Celtic in August 2021 when he sits out tomorrow’s visit to Fir Park to take on Motherwell. The 36-year-old 75 times-capped England international copped an automatic one-match suspension when he saw red in the 3-0 win over Livingston in West Lothian. Hart, who was [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premiership boss calls for VAR talks featuring Celtic after more controversy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175768</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/malky-mackay-calls-for-var-talks-featuring-celtic-after-midweek-controversy/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malky Mackay has called for VAR talks, featuring Celtic, after more recent controversy. The Ross County manager wasn’t happy after decisions went against his side...
The post Premiership boss calls for VAR talks featuring Celtic after more controversy appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘OF COURSE WE WANT TO KEEP HIM,’ INSISTS RODGERS IN KEY MAN TALKS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112507</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/of-course-we-want-to-keep-him-insists-rodgers-in-key-man-talks/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T07:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS admits Celtic would “love to keep” Matt O’Riley. But the Hoops boss acknowledges the on-fire midfielder might not commit to a long-term contract at the champions. O’Riley has been a revelation since arriving at Parkhead in January 2022 in a cut-price £1.5million switch from English third-tier club MK Dons. His value has soared during [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has spoken to international manager about uncapped Celtic star]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175736</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-has-spoken-to-international-manager-about-uncapped-celtic-star/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has spoken to Denmark manager Kasper Hjulmand about Celtic star Matt O’Riley. The attacker has been in great form recently, arguably playing the...
The post Brendan Rodgers has spoken to international manager about uncapped Celtic star appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["He gave us his number"; class Rodgers gesture has stuck with upcoming Celtic opponent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175759</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/he-gave-us-his-number-class-rodgers-gesture-has-stuck-with-upcoming-celtic-opponent/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stuart Kettlewell is likely to look up to someone like Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers. The Motherwell boss is making waves in Lanarkshire, after revitalising the...
The post "He gave us his number"; class Rodgers gesture has stuck with upcoming Celtic opponent appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["The club were very supportive"; Rodgers explains why Celtic rejected £10m summer offer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175744</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-club-were-very-supportive-rodgers-explains-why-celtic-rejected-10m-summer-offer/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has explained why the club rejected a late offer for Matt O’Riley this summer. Hoops attacker O’Riley was the subject of...
The post "The club were very supportive"; Rodgers explains why Celtic rejected £10m summer offer appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nat Phillips set to save Brendan Rodgers a major Celtic headache]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175752</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/nat-phillips-set-to-save-brendan-rodgers-a-major-celtic-headache/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nat Phillips looks set to return for Celtic imminently, saving Brendan Rodgers a major headache next week. The Liverpool defender, on loan at Celtic until...
The post Nat Phillips set to save Brendan Rodgers a major Celtic headache appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PARADISE LOST: WHEN BIG YOGI LEFT CELTIC (Part One)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=82839</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/paradise-lost-when-big-yogi-left-celtic-part-one/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T04:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EXACTLY 52 years ago today, Celtic legend John ‘Yogi’ Hughes played his final game for his boyhood idols. The club’s eighth-highest goalscorer with 189 strikes had his last hurrah at Parkhead when he played in the 3-0 European Cup victory over BK 1903 Copenhagen to help the team through to the next round on a 4-2 [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE JOCK STEIN YEARS (Part Nineteen)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=76584</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-jock-stein-years-part-nineteen/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T04:15:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Jock Stein made an extraordinary immediate impact on the Parkhead club when he returned as manager in March 1965. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE,  Alex Gordon, author of fifteen publications on Celtic, has opened his book files on the Parkhead great for an absorbing twenty-one part series. Today, in Part Nineteen of our fascinating look back [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>