<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-09-29T06:13:25.312Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["The club were very supportive"; Rodgers explains why Celtic rejected £10m summer offer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175744</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-club-were-very-supportive-rodgers-explains-why-celtic-rejected-10m-summer-offer/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has explained why the club rejected a late offer for Matt O’Riley this summer. Hoops attacker O’Riley was the subject of...
The post "The club were very supportive"; Rodgers explains why Celtic rejected £10m summer offer appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nat Phillips set to save Brendan Rodgers a major Celtic headache]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175752</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/nat-phillips-set-to-save-brendan-rodgers-a-major-celtic-headache/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nat Phillips looks set to return for Celtic imminently, saving Brendan Rodgers a major headache next week. The Liverpool defender, on loan at Celtic until...
The post Nat Phillips set to save Brendan Rodgers a major Celtic headache appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PARADISE LOST: WHEN BIG YOGI LEFT CELTIC (Part One)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=82839</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/paradise-lost-when-big-yogi-left-celtic-part-one/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T04:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EXACTLY 52 years ago today, Celtic legend John ‘Yogi’ Hughes played his final game for his boyhood idols. The club’s eighth-highest goalscorer with 189 strikes had his last hurrah at Parkhead when he played in the 3-0 European Cup victory over BK 1903 Copenhagen to help the team through to the next round on a 4-2 [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE JOCK STEIN YEARS (Part Nineteen)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=76584</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-jock-stein-years-part-nineteen/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T04:15:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Jock Stein made an extraordinary immediate impact on the Parkhead club when he returned as manager in March 1965. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE,  Alex Gordon, author of fifteen publications on Celtic, has opened his book files on the Parkhead great for an absorbing twenty-one part series. Today, in Part Nineteen of our fascinating look back [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss confirms club have plan to replace starter in the future]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44521</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/28/celtic-boss-confirms-club-plan-replace-starter-future/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T22:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were pretty active in the recent summer transfer window, bringing in nine new players in total. Seven of them arrived on a permanent basis while two are on loan. Still, a lot of fans were left disappointed. The club did not bring in any established stars and they appeared to have missed out on […]
Celtic boss confirms club have plan to replace starter in the future - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Rangers player claims he was ‘worried’ for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44543</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/28/former-rangers-player-claims-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T21:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic did not make a good start to the season under the management of Brendan Rodgers, as it looked like they were taking some time to come to grips with the Northern Irishman’s system. Things have improved quite a bit in recent weeks though and they have put up some pretty good results, including a […]
Former Rangers player claims he was ‘worried’ for Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero Chris Sutton makes Steven Gerrard claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44540</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/28/celtic-chris-sutton-steven-gerrard-claim/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T19:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are currently leading the Premiership title race once again, as they sit two points clear at the top of the table. St Mirren sit at second while the Rangers are four points behind Brendan Rodgers’ side. One also has to take into consideration that the Hoops have not made a great start to their […]
Celtic hero Chris Sutton makes Steven Gerrard claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Superb news as Celtic star returns to training after 6-week absence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175729</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/cameron-carter-vicker-takes-big-step-forward-towards-celtic-return/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T18:50:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cameron Carter-Vickers has returned to training with the Celtic group this week, Brendan Rodgers has confirmed in a media conference. Carter-Vickers has been missing since...
The post Superb news as Celtic star returns to training after 6-week absence appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chelsea urged to make move for Celtic player in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44530</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/28/chelsea-urged-move-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T18:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A number of Celtic players have been linked with moves away in recent times and overall, the club have done well to keep the core of their squad together. Yes, they have seen the likes of Jota and Carl Starfelt leave while Aaron Mooy retired at the end of last season. But other than that, […]
Chelsea urged to make move for Celtic player in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Phenomenal’: Peter Grant says if Celtic star scored more goals then 'he wouldn't be here']]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175717</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/phenomenal-peter-grant-says-if-celtic-star-scored-more-goals-then-he-wouldnt-be-here/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant thinks Daizen Maeda wouldn’t be a Celtic player if he scored more goals for the club. The combination of the Japan star’s work...
The post ‘Phenomenal’: Peter Grant says if Celtic star scored more goals then 'he wouldn't be here' appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers makes unexpected Celtic contract admission]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44532</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/28/rodgers-makes-celtic-contract-admission/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T16:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic stumbled out of the gates under the management of Brendan Rodgers this season but seem to be starting to find their feet now. There have been plenty of positive signs in recent weeks and they are only expected to get better as more players return to fitness and get back into the team. One […]
Brendan Rodgers makes unexpected Celtic contract admission - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven years ago today; a special Celtic Park night that could have been even more memorable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175706</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/seven-years-ago-today-a-special-celtic-park-night-that-could-have-been-even-more-memorable/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T15:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s exactly seven years since Celtic and Manchester City played out a thrilling 3-3 draw in the UEFA Champions League. It was Brendan Rodgers‘ first...
The post Seven years ago today; a special Celtic Park night that could have been even more memorable appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The next managerial steps for Celtic hero Scott Brown could be very interesting - opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175657</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-next-managerial-steps-for-celtic-hero-scott-brown-could-be-very-interesting/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic favourite Scott Brown is unemployed after leaving Fleetwood Town recently. The former Hoops skipper was relieved of his duties by the League One side...
The post The next managerial steps for Celtic hero Scott Brown could be very interesting - opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Injured Celtic player set to return in time to face Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44525</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/28/injured-celtic-player-return-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T15:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have had to deal with a number of injury problems at the start of the season. Combine that with the fact that they have a ‘new’ manager in place in the form of Brendan Rodgers and several fresh faces who were signed over the summer, and it is not hard to understand why the […]
Injured Celtic player set to return in time to face Lazio - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic defender masterminds cup shock against Premier League side; dream run continues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175697</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-defender-masterminds-cup-shock-against-premier-league-side-dream-run-continues/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic defender Gary Caldwell appears to be doing well in his latest managerial job. The ex-Hoops star is now in charge of League One...
The post Former Celtic defender masterminds cup shock against Premier League side; dream run continues appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers makes Motherwell pitch point after Livingston pain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175642</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-makes-motherwell-pitch-point-after-livingston-pain/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has been speaking about Motherwell ahead of our weekend meeting. Rodgers‘ Hoops have already navigated a series of challenging away trips...
The post Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers makes Motherwell pitch point after Livingston pain appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We need to hear from Crawford Allen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112505</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/we-need-to-hear-from-crawford-allen/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T11:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We don’t have a dog in the fight over refereeing standards at last night’s League Cup game at Ibrox.  Livingston and even the perennial Ibrox media holdouts were aghast at a decision which led to the opening goal and subsequent VAR approval. However, we remain the only club who SFA Head of Refereeing, Crawford Allan, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HATATE: RODGERS IN THE DARK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112502</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hatate-rodgers-in-the-dark/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T10:21:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS admits he is in the dark over Reo Hatate’s contract situation. The Japanese midfielder has yet to sign an enhanced extension on his current deal which expires in June 2026. Hatate’s countrymen Kyogo Furuhashi and Daizen Maeda – as well as skipper Callum McGrgeor, Anthony Ralston and Stephen Welsh – have altready signed new [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic youngster continues to rise down south; could haunt Postecoglou this weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175685</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-youngster-continues-to-rise-down-south-could-haunt-postecoglou-this-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic youngster Ben Doak is continuing to rise down south. The 17-year-old hot prospect is earning greater recognition with Liverpool, seemingly with every passing...
The post Former Celtic youngster continues to rise down south; could haunt Postecoglou this weekend appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SAD HAKSABANOVIC – AT THE DOUBLE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112483</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/sad-haksabanovic-at-the-double/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T08:09:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SEAD HAKSABANOVIC has suffered misery in a League Cup competition for the second time in two months. Celtic’s Sweden-born Montenegrin international winger joined Stoke City on a season-long loan after taking to Instagram to state his unhappiness at failing to start for the champions since the return of Brendan Rodgers. Haksabanovic sent the veiled message [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Excellent news’: John Hartson loving what he is hearing about Celtic duo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175671</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/excellent-news-john-hartson-loving-what-he-is-hearing-about-celtics-matt-oriley-and-reo-hatate/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Hartson says it’s ‘excellent news’ that Matt O’Riley and Reo Hatate could be about to sign new contracts at Celtic. Celtic have been pretty...
The post ‘Excellent news’: John Hartson loving what he is hearing about Celtic duo appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Rodgers went up in people's estimations"; former Celtic hero loved weekend moment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175649</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-hero-thinks-brendan-rodgers-just-went-up-in-a-lot-of-peoples-estimations/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic hero John Hartson reckons Brendan Rodgers has gone up in a lot of people’s estimations after a class weekend moment. Celtic had just...
The post "Rodgers went up in people's estimations"; former Celtic hero loved weekend moment appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sutton's amusing take on controversial Ibrox moment but Celtic may not be laughing this weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175634</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/sutton-has-an-amusing-take-on-controversial-ibrox-moment-but-celtic-may-not-be-laughing-this-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will be next to sample the joys of Willie Collum after the referee had a controversial midweek moment at Ibrox. The experienced whistler was...
The post Sutton's amusing take on controversial Ibrox moment but Celtic may not be laughing this weekend appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic avoid inconvenient midweek fixture change]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175664</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-avoid-inconvenient-midweek-fixture-change/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s upcoming trip to Ross County in the Premiership will be remaining in a weekend slot. For just the second time in eight seasons, we...
The post Celtic avoid inconvenient midweek fixture change appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio's fortunes change ahead of Celtic clash; evening of "many difficulties"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175628</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/lazios-fortunes-change-ahead-of-celtic-clash-evening-of-many-difficulties/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio’s fortunes have changed ahead of their trip to Celtic Park next week after they secured an important midweek victory. As we covered over the...
The post Lazio's fortunes change ahead of Celtic clash; evening of "many difficulties" appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIG TG AND CELTIC’S EURO ELITE GLORY GOAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=28210</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/big-tg-and-celtics-euro-elite-glory-goal/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T04:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY GEMMELL scored Celtic’s first-ever European Cup goal exactly FIFTY-SEVEN YEARS ago today. The legendary full-back was on target as Jock Stein’s men overcame FC Zurich 2-0 in the first leg of their opening round as they made their debut in the elite tournament at a packed Parkhead on September 28 1966. And Gemmell, who [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE JOCK STEIN YEARS (Part Eighteen)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=83089</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-jock-stein-years-part-eighteen/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T04:15:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Jock Stein made an extraordinary immediate impact on the Parkhead club when he returned as manager in March 1965. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE,  Alex Gordon, author of fifteen publications on Celtic, has opened his book files on the Parkhead great for an absorbing twenty-one part series. Today, in Part Eighteen of our fascinating look back [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Motherwell boss sends blunt message before Celtic game]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44490</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/27/motherwell-boss-beat-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T22:31:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next up for Celtic in the league is an away trip on Saturday to Fir Park as they are set to take on fourth-placed Motherwell. It could be a tough game for Brendan Rodgers’ side following the 3-0 win away at Livingston last weekend, even though they were down to ten men after Joe Hart […]
Motherwell boss sends blunt message before Celtic game - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou’s Tottenham eyeing Celtic-linked player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44512</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/27/ange-postecoglou-tottenham-eyeing-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T21:02:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans were left very disappointed when Ange Postecoglou decided to leave the club mere days after guiding them to a treble in order to join Tottenham Hotspur. But at the end of the day, most understood the Australian’s decision and wished him well. The Hoops went out and got the best replacement possible to […]
Ange Postecoglou’s Tottenham eyeing Celtic-linked player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premier League legend admits he rejected Manchester United to join Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44509</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/27/premier-league-manchester-united-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T19:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a common sight these days to see youngsters leave Celtic in order to join clubs in England. That was not always the case though. In the past, there have been plenty of examples of players who have chosen the Glasgow giants over big teams in the English top flight. One player who falls […]
Premier League legend admits he rejected Manchester United to join Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero claims new signing is not ready for Champions League]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44504</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/27/celtic-hero-signing-champions-league/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T18:02:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were pretty active over the course of the summer transfer window, bringing in nine fresh faces to Parkhead. Seven of them have joined the club on a permanent basis while two are on loan deals. Despite that, the Hoops faced a lot of criticism because many fans felt that enough experience was not brought […]
Celtic hero claims new signing is not ready for Champions League - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Anyone who plays alongside him': Andy Walker says Celtic have a 'special' star at the club]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175617</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/anyone-who-plays-alongside-him-andy-walker-says-celtic-have-a-special-star-at-the-club/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andy Walker has joined the deserved praise that has been coming Daizen Maeda’s way this past week after his Celtic performance against Livingston. Sometimes in...
The post 'Anyone who plays alongside him': Andy Walker says Celtic have a 'special' star at the club appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roy Keane makes Celtic vs Rangers claim to Gary Neville]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44499</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/27/roy-keane-celtic-rangers-gary-neville/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T15:30:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and the Rangers share arguably the greatest rivalry in all of football. So much so that almost every Glasgow Derby is considered make or break. If there is one thing that matters most in the Scottish game after trophies, it winning the big game at Parkhead, Ibrox or even Hampden Park. Naturally, it means […]
Roy Keane makes Celtic vs Rangers claim to Gary Neville - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The new Brendan Rodgers Celtic era could be about to get a huge vote of confidence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175528</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-new-brendan-rodgers-celtic-era-could-be-about-to-get-a-huge-vote-of-confidence/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new Brendan Rodgers era at Celtic could be about to get a huge vote of confidence with Reo Hatate close to agreeing a contract...
The post The new Brendan Rodgers Celtic era could be about to get a huge vote of confidence appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers not falling into Lazio trap but a big Celtic opportunity exists]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175514</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/__trashed-4/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers isn’t reading much into Lazio’s start to the season as their trip to Celtic Park looms. The Serie A side face Celtic next...
The post Brendan Rodgers not falling into Lazio trap but a big Celtic opportunity exists appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend named favourite to manage English club]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44496</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/27/celtic-favourite-manage-english-club/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T13:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is always interesting to follow the career paths of Celtic legends as they retire from playing and step into management. Of course, there is always the possibility and the hope that they could one day make a triumph return to Parkhead in order to manage the club. And there are a few such potential […]
Celtic legend named favourite to manage English club - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One key Celtic star has managed to escape contract talk; should be next on the list - opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175575</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/one-key-celtic-star-has-managed-to-escape-contract-talk-should-be-next-on-the-list/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have noticed that Celtic are carrying out a fair bit of positive contract work at present. At this stage, it may well be...
The post One key Celtic star has managed to escape contract talk; should be next on the list - opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BROONY REVENGE?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112478</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/broony-revenge/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T12:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Scott Brown has emerged as a shock favourite for the manager’s job at Cheltenham Town. The struggling English third-tier club, who have taken just one point from their first nine games, hope to announce their new boss before Saturday’s trip to Lincoln. Brown, who is 1/4 favourite with the bookies according to Gloucestershire Live, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This is how it feels to be Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58427</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/this-is-how-it-feels-to-be-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T11:53:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While attending a music festival in Murcia, Spain at the weekend for the first time in years I listened to a Celtic game on the radio. We could not locate a bar showing the game or get it online so we enjoyed a few beers on the balcony of our hotel. Still buzzing from the […]
The post This is how it feels to be Celtic appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Ralston's touching family message after proud Celtic moment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175581</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/anthony-ralstons-touching-family-message-after-proud-celtic-moment/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Ralston had a touching message of thanks to his family and friends after signing a new deal at Celtic. Ralston’s contract extension was announced...
The post Anthony Ralston's touching family message after proud Celtic moment appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ralston, rarity and mystery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112457</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ralston-rarity-and-mystery/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T11:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the many mysteries of football is why Anthony Ralston (now 24) was so far out the picture in the latter stages of Neil Lennon’s tenure.  Kris Ajer, Moritz Bauer, Jeremie Frimpong and Jonjoe Kenny were all selected at right back ahead of him.  When he was brought back into the fold by Ange [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The unclear James McCarthy Lennoxtown situation; what Celtic boss said last month]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175552</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-unclear-james-mccarthy-lennoxtown-situation-what-celtic-boss-said-last-month/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There was some chatter in Celtic circles on Tuesday when James McCarthy wasn’t included in an official team photograph. It was the club’s ‘2023/24 team...
The post The unclear James McCarthy Lennoxtown situation; what Celtic boss said last month appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Unbelievable’: Roy Keane makes Celtic-Rangers comment today after Gary Neville's criticism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175589</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/unbelievable-roy-keane-makes-celtic-rangers-comment-today-after-gary-nevilles-criticism/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T08:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roy Keane referenced Celtic’s games against Rangers when in discussion with Gary Neville about how teams possibly over-celebrate. The former right-back was critical of how...
The post ‘Unbelievable’: Roy Keane makes Celtic-Rangers comment today after Gary Neville's criticism appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JOE HART SEES RED – AGAIN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112435</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/joe-hart-sees-red-again/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T08:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT took Joe Hart a lifetime in football and 737 games before he saw red. The 36-year-old 75 times-capped England keeper was ordered off for the first time in his illustrious career in Celtic’s 3-0 win over Livingston in West Lothian on Saturday. And Hart was red-carded for the second time in three days as [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWOL McCARTHY MYSTERY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112432</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/awol-mccarthy-mystery/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T07:43:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JAMES McCARTHY is so far out of the picture at Celtic he was not included in the club’s team photo yesterday. The 32-year-old former Republic of Ireland international midfielder joined the Hoops in August 2021 as a free agent after coming out of contract at Crystal Palace. McCarthy still has two years of his deal to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Wednesday September 27: Who’ll Stop The Pain ?]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18499</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18499"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T06:52:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With an enforced break ahead of the trip to Fir Park on Saturday, a match not..as yet…scheduled for Sky Sports, the manager may well look…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Malph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Leeds put in a bid': Peter Grant tells Celtic star 'take a leaf out of Matt O'Riley's book']]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175534</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/leeds-put-in-a-bid-peter-grant-tells-celtic-star-take-leaf-out-of-matt-orileys-book/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant has told Celtic star Reo Hatate to ‘take a leaf out of Matt O’Riley’s book’ by forgetting about outside noise and performing on...
The post 'Leeds put in a bid': Peter Grant tells Celtic star 'take a leaf out of Matt O'Riley's book' appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HATATE: CRUCIAL 72 HOURS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112425</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hatate-crucial-72-hours/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T06:43:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE Reo Hatate contract saga at Celtic could be over within the next 72 hours. The 25-year-old midfielder and the champions are now close to an extension agreement that will bring the Japanese international in line with Kyogo Furuhashi and Daizen Maeda. Discussions between Hatate, who joined from Kawasaki Frontale in January 2022, and the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Spoke to Brendan"; the obvious Celtic loan candidate after Duncan Ferguson talks take place]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175517</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/spoke-to-brendan-the-obvious-celtic-loan-candidate-after-duncan-ferguson-talks-take-place/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Duncan Ferguson has already had some talks with Brendan Rodgers about Celtic loan players. The retired forward was confirmed as the new manager of Inverness...
The post "Spoke to Brendan"; the obvious Celtic loan candidate after Duncan Ferguson talks take place appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rodgers is seeing positive signs every day at Celtic; class Maeda weekend scenes put to him]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175506</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-is-seeing-positive-signs-every-day-at-celtic-class-daizen-maeda-scenes-put-to-him/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers says he is seeing growth from his team every day. It’s been a challenging start to life back in the Celtic...
The post Rodgers is seeing positive signs every day at Celtic; class Maeda weekend scenes put to him appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Whether he plays"; Rodgers alludes to Celtic man's game-time after big Tuesday news]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175499</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/whether-he-plays-rodgers-alludes-to-ralston-game-time-after-new-celtic-contract/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has been speaking about Anthony Ralston after the Celtic defender signed a contract extension. Celtic announced on Tuesday that the Scotland international had...
The post "Whether he plays"; Rodgers alludes to Celtic man's game-time after big Tuesday news appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE JOCK STEIN YEARS (Part Seventeen)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=83033</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-jock-stein-years-part-seventeen/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T04:15:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Jock Stein made an extraordinary immediate impact on the Parkhead club when he returned as manager in March 1965. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE,  Alex Gordon, author of fifteen publications on Celtic, has opened his book files on the Parkhead great for an absorbing twenty-one part series. Today, in Part Seventeen of our fascinating look back [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable journalist drops superb late-night Celtic update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44487</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/26/reliable-journalist-late-celtic-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T22:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Except for the 2-0 defeat at the hands of Feyenoord away at De Kuip in their Champions League group stage opener, it has been a good few weeks for Celtic for sure. The club seem to be rediscovering their form on the pitch and getting some wins, as well as goals. Earlier in the day, […]
Reliable journalist drops superb late-night Celtic update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: McGowan delivers the Hatate news Celtic fans have been waiting for; transfer protection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175493</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/stephen-mcgowan-delivers-the-reo-hatate-news-celtic-fans-have-been-waiting-for-transfer-protection/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T21:35:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder Reo Hatate is close to agreeing a contract extension at the club, according to a report. The midfielder has been a terrific performer...
The post Report: McGowan delivers the Hatate news Celtic fans have been waiting for; transfer protection appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder ready to play as centre-back or wing-back]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44485</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/26/celtic-midfielder-centre-back-wing/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T21:04:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic might be dealing with a lot of injuries at this point in time but when everybody is back fit and available, they will have a very deep roster. So, a challenge for Brendan Rodgers would be to make sure that he gives enough playing time to everyone. And if there is one thing we […]
Celtic midfielder ready to play as centre-back or wing-back - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player missing from official 2023/24 squad photo]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44482</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/26/celtic-player-missing-squad-photo/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T19:31:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a big squad at this point in time. They added nine fresh faces to their ranks over the summer, with seven arriving on a permanent basis while two were signed on loan deals. On the other hand, we have seen key players like Jota and Carl Starfelt leave while Aaron Mooy retired at […]
Celtic player missing from official 2023/24 squad photo - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another upcoming Celtic clash could follow Motherwell pay-per-view example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175456</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/another-upcoming-celtic-clash-could-follow-motherwell-pay-per-view-example/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s trip to Motherwell this weekend won’t be shown on regular television. Our visit to Fir Park hasn’t been selected for live coverage by Sky...
The post Another upcoming Celtic clash could follow Motherwell pay-per-view example appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Player who left Celtic for free now valued at £50 million]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44478</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/26/player-left-celtic-free-50-million/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T18:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There have been quite a few ‘what could have been’ stories around Celtic in recent years. Whether it be Andy Robertson not getting his chance at the club or the Hoops failing to get a deal done for players like John McGinn and Ivan Toney, who have gone on to show their quality at the […]
Player who left Celtic for free now valued at £50 million - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic set for much-improved Madrid allocation but it still may not be enough]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175378</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-set-for-much-improved-madrid-allocation-but-it-still-may-not-be-enough/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic support will receive a much-improved allocation for this season’s trip to Madrid. The Hoops are making a habit of visiting the Spanish capital...
The post Celtic set for much-improved Madrid allocation but it still may not be enough appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['The speed': Kenny Miller wowed by Celtic star who stops Rangers' key player from performing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175472</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-speed-kenny-miller-wowed-by-celtic-star-who-stops-rangers-key-player-from-performing/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Miller has waxed lyrical about Daizen Maeda after he put on a masterclass during Celtic’s 3-0 win over Livingston on Saturday. The 25-year-old showcased...
The post 'The speed': Kenny Miller wowed by Celtic star who stops Rangers' key player from performing appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIG DEAL: RALSTON THANKS RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112418</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/big-deal-ralston-thanks-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T16:18:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANTHONY RALSTON admits his debt to Brendan Rodgers after signing a new four-year deal. The Celtic and Scotland defender first joined the club at the age of eight in 2007, became a professional at 16 and made his first-team debut a year later. Rodgers played his part at the beginning of Ralston’s first-team career at the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic make afternoon announcement about new deal]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44472</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/26/celtic-make-announcement-new-deal/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T15:30:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have done a very good job in recent times when it comes to agreeing new deals with some of their most important players. Kyogo Furuhashi, Callum McGregor, Daizen Maeda, Liel Abada and Stephen Welsh have all put pen to paper on contract extensions. Talks are rumoured to be taking place with Reo Hatate and […]
Celtic make afternoon announcement about new deal - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ibrox boos are the perfect sound for a Celtic support growing in confidence - opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175409</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/ibrox-boos-are-the-perfect-sound-for-a-celtic-support-growing-in-confidence/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Premiership weekend started with positive scenes amongst the Celtic support and ended with frustration for Rangers fans. On the face of it, both sides...
The post Ibrox boos are the perfect sound for a Celtic support growing in confidence - opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everton eyeing move for brilliant former Celtic target]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44468</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/26/everton-eyeing-former-celtic-target/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T13:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic found themselves in a difficult situation in the summer. The club had just won the Treble but then saw Ange Postecoglou depart the club for Tottenham Hotspur. While the Australian’s decision disappointed the fans, it was understandable to some degree as well. The Hoops needed to bring in a replacement quickly. They were linked […]
Everton eyeing move for brilliant former Celtic target - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Mentality challenge"; class Celtic footage picks up on weekend Callum McGregor moment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175416</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/mentality-challenge-class-celtic-footage-picks-up-weekend-callum-mcgregor-team-talk/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor’s pre-Livingston message has been shown in a class Celtic TV video. The Hoops were worthy 3-0 winners at the Tony Macaroni Arena on...
The post "Mentality challenge"; class Celtic footage picks up on weekend Callum McGregor moment appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic man's situation has improved after first competitive appearances under Rodgers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175396</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/things-are-looking-a-whole-lot-better-for-tomoki-iwata-at-celtic-next-steps/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tomoki Iwata’s situation at Celtic is looking a whole lot better than it was a week ago. The Japanese midfielder hadn’t made a competitive appearance...
The post Celtic man's situation has improved after first competitive appearances under Rodgers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to expect from returning central defenders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112406</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/what-to-expect-from-returning-central-defenders/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T11:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the second half of last season, right back Alistair Johnston eclipsed the form of left back Greg Taylor.  That scenario has flipped so far this season, in part due to Greg’s resurgence, but it is fair to say Alistair has yet to hit top form. Livingston on Saturday was only Alistair’s third full 90 [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘SEIZE THE OPPORTUNITY,’ IWATA AIMS TO IMPRESS RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112408</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/seize-the-opportunity-iwata-aims-to-impress-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T10:50:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMOKI IWATA insists he will continue to work hard to impress Brendan Rodgers. The versatile performer, who was Japan’s Player of the Year before arriving at Celtic in January, had to wait until a week ago today to make his first appearance for the Irishman. Iwata was pitched into the Champions League opener against Feyenoord [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Tavernier’s heart must sink"; Sutton loving rising Celtic star, anticipates change of position]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175406</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/taverniers-heart-must-sink-sutton-loving-rising-celtic-star-anticipates-change-of-position/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton has been talking up Daizen Maeda after his terrific display for Celtic at the weekend. The Japan international was one of our top...
The post "Tavernier’s heart must sink"; Sutton loving rising Celtic star, anticipates change of position appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[’Shake of the head’: Sky presenter shares what Livi player told him about Celtic's Maeda]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175418</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/shake-of-the-head-sky-presenter-shares-what-livi-player-told-him-about-celtics-daizen-maeda/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T08:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gordon Duncan has shared that a Livingston player told him that he ‘couldn’t believe’ how much Celtic star Daizen Maeda runs without the ball. It...
The post ’Shake of the head’: Sky presenter shares what Livi player told him about Celtic's Maeda appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's immense Champions League challenge was highlighted at the weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175363</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-immense-champions-league-challenge-was-highlighted-at-the-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Celtic were placed into Group E of this season’s UEFA Champions League there was a general sense that we had done quite well for...
The post Celtic's immense Champions League challenge was highlighted at the weekend appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch: Summer signing's first steps as a Celtic player; long-awaited debut looming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175384</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/watch-marco-tilios-first-steps-as-a-celtic-player-long-awaited-debut-looming/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marco Tilio is closing in on his long-awaited Celtic debut after taking a big step at the weekend. The Australian winger was part of a...
The post Watch: Summer signing's first steps as a Celtic player; long-awaited debut looming appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘STEAL OF THE CENTURY,’ SUTTON RATES THE CELT OPPONENTS MUST HATE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112379</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/steal-of-the-century-sutton-rates-the-celt-opponents-must-hate/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:55:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAIZEN MAEDA is “the steal of the century”, according to Celtic goalscoring great Chris Sutton. The one-time England international striker claims the non-stop Japanese speedster is a player the opposition must hate – while his team-mates thrive on his dynamic drive throughout his minutes on the pitch. Sutton played alongside Didier Agathe at the Hoops [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The trademark Brendan Rodgers devilment is back as he delivers promising Celtic thoughts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175390</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-promising-celtic-weekend-words-with-a-hint-of-devilment/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers says his Celtic side are still a long way from where he wants them to be. The Hoops have started the Premiership season...
The post The trademark Brendan Rodgers devilment is back as he delivers promising Celtic thoughts appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Scottish club make big-name managerial appointment; two former Celtic players miss out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175371</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/scottish-club-make-big-name-managerial-appointment-two-former-celtic-players-miss-out/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inverness Caledonian Thistle will appoint Duncan Ferguson as their new manager on Tuesday morning. The Highland side are currently bottom of the Championship and parted...
The post Report: Scottish club make big-name managerial appointment; two former Celtic players miss out appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[O’RILEY REWARD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112372</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/oriley-reward/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T05:10:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY is on the brink of an international reward following his blistering start to the season. The Celtic midfielder will almost certainly receive his first senior call-up for his adopted nation Denmark for next moth’s Euro 24 qualifiers against Kazakhstan and San Marino. Former Fulham prospect O’Riley, who played for England at youth level, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE JOCK STEIN YEARS (Part Sixteen)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=82961</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-jock-stein-years-part-sixteen/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-26T04:15:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Jock Stein had an extraordinary impact on the Parkhead club after returning as manager in March 1965. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE,  Alex Gordon, author of fifteen publications on Celtic, has opened his book files on the Parkhead great for an absorbing twenty-one part series. Today, in Part Sixteen of our fascinating look back at [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jota transfer under Al-Ittihad microscope amid Celtic return rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44446</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/25/jota-transfer-celtic-return-rumours/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T22:30:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many outstanding questions about the way Jota’s transfer from Celtic to Al-Ittihad has worked out. It may have secured a mega contract for the Portuguese winger, but in playing terms, it appears to be turning into a nightmare. He seems to be out of first-team plans already and his future is in doubt […]
Jota transfer under Al-Ittihad microscope amid Celtic return rumours - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[24-year-old Liverpool player would be ideal signing for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44460</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/25/24-year-old-liverpool-player-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T21:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already signed one player from Liverpool, albeit on loan for just the first half of the season. Nat Phillips arrived in the late stages of the summer transfer window and it remains to be seen how he does. The start has not been great as he is already dealing with fitness issues and […]
24-year-old Liverpool player would be ideal signing for Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic talks ongoing as 22-year-old heads for career breakthrough]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175350</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-latest-on-matt-orileys-future-after-stellar-celtic-form/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T20:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O’Riley is continuing discussions with Celtic about signing a new long-term contract after a stellar start to the 2023/24 season. O’Riley has been one...
The post Celtic talks ongoing as 22-year-old heads for career breakthrough appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[’Those two’: BBC pundit says there’s no-one better than Celtic duo when down to ten men]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175346</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/those-two-bbc-pundit-says-theres-no-one-better-than-celtic-duo-when-down-to-ten-men/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T20:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Richard Foster has praised the efforts of Daizen Maeda and Kyogo Furuhashi as Celtic battled to a deserved 3-0 win over Livingston with ten men...
The post ’Those two’: BBC pundit says there’s no-one better than Celtic duo when down to ten men appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fiery Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers hits back at stirring media narrative]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175325</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/fiery-celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-hits-back-at-stirring-media-narrative/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T19:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers reckons some people will be trying to ‘drive a wedge’ between him and the club’s board in the early stages of...
The post Fiery Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers hits back at stirring media narrative appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jota to Celtic update amid rumours of January return]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44457</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/25/jota-celtic-update-january-return/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T19:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jota left Celtic in the summer, somewhat out of the blue, in order to join Al-Ittihad. It was one of the biggest transfers in Scottish football history. While the Hoops did pocket a significant transfer fee, they did also lose one of their most important players and the absence of the Portuguese winger has been […]
Jota to Celtic update amid rumours of January return - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘He has got better & better’: Neil Lennon says improvements of Celtic 25-year-old endless]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175327</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/he-has-got-better-better-neil-lennon-says-improvements-of-celtic-25-year-old-endless/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T19:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon has waxed lyrical about Daizen Maeda and how he has just got ‘better and better’ as his Celtic career has progressed.  The 25-year-old...
The post ‘He has got better & better’: Neil Lennon says improvements of Celtic 25-year-old endless appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss admitted making Virgil van Dijk mistake]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44454</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/25/celtic-boss-virgil-van-dijk-mistake/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T18:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Virgil van Dijk was a top player even while he was at Celtic. It was clear that he was a class apart. But not many would have foreseen the success that the Dutchman would achieve after departing Parkhead. He established himself at Southampton before making the move to Liverpool, where he has won everything possible. […]
Celtic boss admitted making Virgil van Dijk mistake - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artur Boruc thinks £4.3m summer Celtic signing will pay off for the Bhoys despite tricky start]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175322</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/artur-boruc-provides-maik-nawrocki-celtic-hope/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T17:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic goalkeeper Artur Boruc reckons that summer signing Maik Nawrocki will come good for the Bhoys despite his disappointing injury setback. The central defender...
The post Artur Boruc thinks £4.3m summer Celtic signing will pay off for the Bhoys despite tricky start appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic man rejects chance to complete Parkhead exit]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44448</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/25/celtic-man-rejects-parkhead-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T15:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is quite a bit of positivity around Celtic at the moment. Certainly a lot more than what was there following the defeat away to Kilmarnock followed by a goalless draw to St Johnstone. Since then, the Hoops have been on a decent run even though they did suffer a 2-0 loss at the hands […]
Celtic man rejects chance to complete Parkhead exit - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic announced as November testimonial opponents]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175315</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-announced-as-november-testimonial-opponents/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T13:40:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Celtic select side will take on fellow Scottish Premiership outfit Dundee in November to celebrate Cammy Kerr’s testimonial. Kerr has been a long-serving player...
The post Celtic announced as November testimonial opponents appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports man confirms superb update on Celtic talks]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44443</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/25/sky-sports-man-confirms-celtic-talks-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T12:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic stumbled out of the gates this season but they have found some form lately. They have kept four straight clean sheets in the league and sit atop the Premiership table, bouncing back nicely after their early elimination from the Scottish League Cup. They did lose their Champions League group stage opener against Feyenoord away […]
Sky Sports man confirms superb update on Celtic talks - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt of the Match]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112364</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/matt-of-the-match/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T11:02:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On its own, winning 0-3 at Livingston would not move the dial, but the manner of Saturday’s win surely did.  Joe Hart’s (correctly awarded) red card sent the flare up, Celtic would have to play on plastic for over an hour with 10 men.  This followed a tiring game in Rotterdam, where they finished with [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S RED CARD MYSTERY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112359</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtics-red-card-mystery/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T08:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have had three players red-carded in under an hour of action in their last two games against Feyenoord and Livingston. Amazingly, that is the SAME number of sendings-off amassed by the champions during the entirety of last season. Swedish new Bhoys Gustaf Lagerbiekle and Odin Holm were dismissed in the 2-0 loss in the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS KNOWS THE SCORE – JUST ASK MAEDA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112351</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-knows-the-score-just-ask-maeda/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T07:27:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has added fortune-teller to his many qualities as Celtic manager. Marathon man Daizen Maeda produced another inexhaustible display as he covered the plastic and netted a spectacular third goal in a grand finale to the champions’ 3-0 win in Livingston at the weekend. And the Japanese international forward was not one bit surprised to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Monday September 25: Back In Our Arms Again?]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18497</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18497"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T07:18:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 3-0 win with ten men against the twelve of Livingston ?   Despite the best intentions of on loan influential midfielder John Beaton ?…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Malph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC COACH KNOCKS BACK BOSS MOVE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112344</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-coach-knocks-back-boss-move/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T06:37:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DARREN O’DEA, the Celtic B team coach, will NOT be pursuing a move to take charge of Inverness Caley Thistle. The former Republic of Ireland international central defender had been linked with the vacant post at the Championship side after Billy Dodds was sacked five weeks ago. The one-time Scotland striker led the Highlanders to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE JOCK STEIN YEARS (Part Fifteen)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=78941</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-jock-stein-years-part-fifteen/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-25T04:15:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Jock Stein had an extraordinary impact on the Parkhead club after returning as manager in March 1965. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE,  Alex Gordon, author of fifteen publications on Celtic, has opened his book files on the Parkhead great for an absorbing twenty-one part series. Today, in Part Fifteen of our fascinating look back at these [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers hero makes brave claim about league leaders Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44422</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/24/rangers-hero-claim-leaders-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-24T22:34:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic continue to lead the Premiership after winning away at Livingston. And while the Rangers have gotten some positive results recently, the situation around Ibrox does not seem to be the best. Most of their fans appear to have given up on Michael Beale already, as have several pundits, building pressure on the manager. Kenny […]
Rangers hero makes brave claim about league leaders Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STOP ME IF YOU’VE HEARD THIS ONE BEFORE]]></title>
        <id>http://celticunderground.net/?p=6683</id>
        <link href="http://celticunderground.net/stop-me-if-youve-heard-this-one-before/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-24T21:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I ended my last article on Brendan Rodgers on a positive note.  Surely having brought him back with the appropriate salary then mistakes from the previous term would have been learned and we ‘d be moving forward on a united front.   In particular transfer windows would see him not looking particularly downbeat and end with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Critical Bill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player sent clear message after major mistake]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44435</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/24/celtic-player-message-major-mistake/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-24T21:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic stuck to their strategy of signing highly-rated youngsters even though fans had been hoping that some established players would be brought in, who could make an immediate impact in the Champions League. Unfortunately, the club’s experience was on full show in their group stage opener against Feyenoord. Celtic were a goal down but still […]
Celtic player sent clear message after major mistake - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers tells "under the radar" Celtic star how to take his game to the highest level]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175312</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-tells-under-the-radar-celtic-star-how-to-take-his-game-to-the-highest-level/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-24T19:49:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has urged midfielder Matt O’Riley to commit himself to Celtic attacks and add even more goals to his game. O’Riley has been one...
The post Brendan Rodgers tells "under the radar" Celtic star how to take his game to the highest level appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic manager claims he could manage Real Madrid]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44429</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/24/former-celtic-manager-real-madrid/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-24T19:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have had some great managers in recent years as well as some mediocre ones. That has not stopped the club from being consistently successful. They have won 11 out of the last 12 league titles and five domestic trebles over the last seven seasons. That is quite the run for any team in the […]
Former Celtic manager claims he could manage Real Madrid - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artur Boruc throws backing behind under-fire Celtic star; sends superb UCL fan message]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175309</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/artur-boruc-throws-backing-behind-joe-hart-after-celtic-errors-delivers-champions-league-verdict/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-24T19:21:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artur Boruc reckons Celtic have a ‘top-class’ goalkeeper in Joe Hart and believes the Bhoys can start to pick up positive results in their UEFA...
The post Artur Boruc throws backing behind under-fire Celtic star; sends superb UCL fan message appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["The fun was gone"; Former boss gets honest about Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=175305</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-wasnt-ready-for-it-ronny-deila-gets-honest-about-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-24T18:37:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic manager Ronny Deila has been speaking about his time in charge of the club, with his candid comments providing insight on his mindset...
The post "The fun was gone"; Former boss gets honest about Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>