<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-11-20T18:13:30.732Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player suffers injury concern on international duty]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45745</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/20/celtic-injury-concern-international-duty/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T18:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already dealt with and continue to deal with a number of fitness issues. Just at this moment, they have three key starters out of action for the foreseeable future in the form of Reo Hatate, Daizen Maeda and Liel Abada. Thus, Brendan Rodgers’ side deserve a lot of credit for continuing to produce […]
Celtic player suffers injury concern on international duty - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic make contact about crowd-pleasing January signing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181006</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/italian-newspaper-provides-more-on-celtic-and-sydney-van-hooijdonk-speculation/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T17:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have reportedly enquired about a move for Bologna striker Syndey van Hooijdonk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pundit compares Celtic squad to Rangers with firm verdict; two players who will worry Clement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180982</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/davie-provan-says-celtic-look-much-stronger-than-rangers-duo-noted-as-particular-problem-for-clement/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T17:31:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic winger Davie Provan has highlighted Celtic’s squad depth with Liel Abada and Daizen Maeda in particular catching the Scotsman’s eye. Provan, who played...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic left waiting on injury situation after international manager's comments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181002</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-left-waiting-on-luis-palma-situation-as-honduras-boss-flags-up-concern/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T15:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic winger Luis Palma has picked up an injury whilst on international duty for Honduras.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic summer signing could play for another club before he makes Bhoys debut]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180987</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/marco-tilios-quest-to-play-for-celtic-could-take-a-detour/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic winger Marco Tilio has admitted that he would be open to a loan spell away from the Hoops if he can't break into the first team before January.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Grown a lot"; Hyeongyu Oh talks up the Celtic experience to South Korean media]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180994</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/hyeongyu-oh-talks-up-the-celtic-experience-to-south-korean-media/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T14:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic striker Hyengou Oh has spoken about how Scottish football has helped him become a more physical player. Oh is currently preparing for a World...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC LEADER’S HECTIC SCHEDULE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114404</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-leaders-hectic-schedule/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T14:33:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC skipper Callum McGregor faces another hectic summer schedule as Scotland brought down the curtain on the Euro 2024 qualifying campaign in the 3-3 draw with Norway at Hampden last night. The influential Hoops midfield leader will be aiming to be involved in the Scottish Cup Final at Hampden on the iconic date of May [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic make first enquiries for £4 million-rated striker]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45741</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/20/celtic-make-first-enquiries-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T14:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic might need to sign a striker in the upcoming January transfer window. Kyogo remains the first-choice and the Japanese forward continues to deliver the goods up top for the Hoops. On the other hand, after a slow start under the management of Brendan Rodgers, Oh Hyeon-gyu is starting to find the back of the […]
Celtic make first enquiries for £4 million-rated striker - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player considering leaving on loan in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45736</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/20/celtic-player-leaving-loan-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T12:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic might still have some areas where they need to improve but overall, Brendan Rodgers has a lot of options to pick his starting XI from. There are some players who are struggling to get into the team though and departing Parkhead, on loan or on a permanent basis, might be the right step for […]
Celtic player considering leaving on loan in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rationalising the wingers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114391</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rationalising-the-wingers/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T12:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the time, you and I talked about the hoard of wingers at the club after the summer’s transfer business.  James Forrest, Mikey Johnston, Liel Abada, Daizen Maeda, Luis Palma, Yang and Marco Tilio.  That’s seven players for two starting spots; it was always going to be a handful keeping everyone happy.  Marco got his [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEW BHOY POISED TO LEAD CELTIC CLEAR-OUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114384</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/new-bhoy-poised-to-lead-celtic-clear-out/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T07:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MARCO TILIO, who hasn’t figured in the Celtic first team since his June arrival, could be heading for the Hoops exit. The Australian winger, a £3million recruit on a five-year deal from Melbourne City, has been hampered with injury and his career has stalled at the champions. Now the 22-year-old forward, who played for 10 [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE BERTIE AULD: PART SIX: ‘WHY I SAID NO TO EVERTON AND YES TO BIRMINGHAM’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=86808</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-unforgettable-bertie-auld-part-six-why-i-said-no-to-everton-and-yes-to-birmingham/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T05:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bertie Auld was tailor-made for a Celtic team that played with a swashbuckling sense of adventure. CQN are celebrating the life and incredible times of the Hoops legend in an EXCLUSIVE series with extracts from his best-selling autobiography, ‘A Bhoy Called Bertie’, co-authored by his friend and writer Alex Gordon. The story continues with [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic appear to have pulled off absolute transfer masterstroke]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45689</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/19/celtic-absolute-transfer-masterstroke/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T22:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The international break can be quite mixed for Celtic fans. On one hand, it is pleasing to see the club’s players getting recognition with their national teams. But there is always a worry over them potentially getting injured while away. The Hoops already have enough fitness problems to deal with as it is. But one […]
Celtic appear to have pulled off absolute transfer masterstroke - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers compares Celtic duo with Liverpool icons]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45727</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/19/brendan-rodgers-celtic-duo-liverpool/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T21:05:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has been at some top clubs over the course of his career and has a result, he has gotten the opportunity to work with many world-class players. Of course, the Northern Irishman has won most of his silverware while at Celtic but that does not mean that he has not had success elsewhere. […]
Brendan Rodgers compares Celtic duo with Liverpool icons - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player told he will need to make Parkhead exit]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45723</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/19/celtic-player-told-parkhead-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T19:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a pretty deep roster at this point in time but there are quite a few players who did not seem to be a major part of Brendan Rodgers’ plans. It remains to be seen what the future holds for them. Of course, Liam Scales’ rise from the bottom of the centre-back pecking order […]
Celtic player told he will need to make Parkhead exit - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic keep SWPL pressure on Rangers with big Sunday win, surge clear of City]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180977</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/celtic-keep-swpl-pressure-on-rangers-with-big-sunday-win-surge-clear-of-city/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T18:21:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SWPL increasingly looks like it could become a two-horse title race between Celtic and Rangers this season after a bad day for Glasgow City....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder admits uncertainty over Parkhead future]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45717</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/19/celtic-midfielder-admits-parkhead-future/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T18:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic already have a pretty big roster of players and one would expect them to part ways with some in the upcoming January transfer window. There are quite a few who are not getting enough chances right now and do not seem to have much hope of a better situation in the future either. For […]
Celtic midfielder admits uncertainty over Parkhead future - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers responds to class Kolo Toure comments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180972</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-responds-to-class-kolo-toure-comments/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T17:57:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has described Kolo Toure as one of the nicest people he has ever encountered in his life after glowing comments from...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Real signs of potential"; Chris Sutton is excited about the future of young Celtic duo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180965</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-delivers-verdict-on-celtic-progress-of-luis-palma-and-hyeongyu-oh/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton hasn’t hidden his feelings on the quality of the Celtic squad this season, nor his frustrations with recruitment during the summer transfer window....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms "analytically brilliant" coach followed him to Celtic from Leicester]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180960</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-praises-analytically-brilliant-coach-who-followed-him-to-celtic-from-leicester/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T15:53:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has been speaking about his backroom staff at Celtic this season, highlighting the hard work they put in to support him at Lennoxtown...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's 11 games in 38 days; full schedule, injuries, TV details, predictions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180953</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtics-11-games-in-38-days-full-schedule-injuries-tv-details-predictions/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T15:16:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re less than a week away from Celtic taking to the pitch again after the international break and it will be the start of a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic reportedly in the running to bring back former player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45713</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/19/celtic-bring-back-former-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T13:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already signed nine players since the arrival of Brendan Rodgers as the manager of the club, seven on a permanent basis and two on loan. Despite that, it does feel like there are some holes in the current squad which have not been filled. And hopefully, they will concentrate on those positions in […]
Celtic reportedly in the running to bring back former player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic interested in signing Tottenham Hotspur target]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45709</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/19/celtic-signing-tottenham-hotspur-target/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T10:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are always on the lookout for top young talents. In recent times, the club have spread their scouting network further and wider. Results have been somewhat mixed so far. Their signings in the first season under the management of Ange Postecoglou were spectacular. But since then, the success rate has been somewhat questionable. Many […]
Celtic interested in signing Tottenham Hotspur target - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SHOT-SHY CELT APOLOGISES TO BOSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114375</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/shot-shy-celt-apologises-to-boss/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T09:53:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OH HYEON-GYU fired blanks in South Korea’s 5-0 win over Singapore in the World Cup qualifier – and insisted he was letting down coach Jurgen Klinsmann. The Celtic powerhouse is still awaiting his first goal at this level and missed out again after coming on as a 70th minute substitute in his country’s goal romp. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UNSEEN CELT EDGES CLOSER TO DEBUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114369</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/unseen-celt-edges-closer-to-debut/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T08:54:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MARCO TILIO edged closer to his long-awaited Celtic debut when he made a cameo appearance for Australia in their 2-1 win over Qatar last night. The winger, who cost £3million when he arrived from Melbourne City on a five-year deal in June, has been nowhere near a place in Brendan Rodgers’ matchday squad. Tilio has been [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MISERY FOR CELTIC DUO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114363</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/misery-for-celtic-duo/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T08:20:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIAM SCALES and Mikey Johnston couldn’t prevent the Netherlands overcoming the Republic of Ireland 1-0 in Amsterdam last night. Stephen Kenny’s side’s dismal Euro 24 qualifying campaign came to a halt with Burnley’s on-loan Hoffenheim striker Wout Weghorst claiming the winner in the 12th minute. The Irish manager is under pressure after guiding his nation to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE BERTIE AULD: PART FIVE: ‘SHATTERING BLOW AS CELTIC WANT TO SELL ME’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=86800</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-unforgettable-bertie-auld-part-five-shattering-blow-as-celtic-want-to-sell-me/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T05:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bertie Auld was the most irrepressible Celtic player of Jock Stein’s all-conquering team of the sixties. CQN has been celebrating the life and incredible times of the Hoops legend in an EXCLUSIVE series with extracts from his best-selling autobiography, ‘A Bhoy Called Bertie’, co-authored by his friend and writer Alex Gordon. The story [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Liam Scales verdict as Celtic defender takes on difficult Dutch attack in Amsterdam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180946</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-liam-scales-verdict-as-celtic-defender-takes-on-difficult-dutch-attack-in-amsterdam/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T21:46:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Liam Scales will be disappointed that his Republic of Ireland side suffered their latest defeat away to the Netherlands on Saturday night but...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston international break bonus for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180941</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alistair-johnston-international-break-bonus-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T20:56:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star Alistair Johnston managed to avoid a gruelling short turnaround double-header against Jamaica after he was omitted from the Canada starting eleven on Saturday....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic 'keeping tabs' on breakthrough Premiership midfielder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180937</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-keeping-tabs-on-breakthrough-premiership-midfielder/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T20:18:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are one of the clubs credited with interest in Motherwell midfielder Lennon Miller after bursting onto the Scottish Premiership scene but there is a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cold water poured on £4m Celtic January transfer idea]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180934</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/chris-sutton-pours-cold-water-on-celtic-january-transfer-speculation/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T19:38:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker Chris Sutton doesn’t think the Bhoys will be spending significant amounts of cash on a forward in the January transfer window. Brendan...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two former Celtic players pictured back in Glasgow]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45705</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/18/two-former-celtic-players-glasgow/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T19:35:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are home to footballers from all around the world and it is always good to see former players back in town. On this occasion, a couple of them will be on the opposition side though. The Scotland national team are set to take on Norway soon in the UEFA EURO Qualifiers even though Steve […]
Two former Celtic players pictured back in Glasgow - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star confirmed for elite Saturday night test vs £35m Liverpool talent; how to watch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180930</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-defender-confirmed-for-elite-saturday-night-test-vs-netherlands-how-to-watch/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T18:57:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Liam Scales has been named in the Republic of Ireland team for a daunting away test against the Netherlands on Saturday night. Scales...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Brendan Rodgers told Kyogo to break through big Celtic barrier]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180927</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-brendan-rodgers-told-kyogo-to-break-through-big-celtic-barrier/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T18:18:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s fair to say Kyogo Furuhashi’s debut campaign in the UEFA Champions League with Celtic was a big disappointment for him. The Japanese star featured...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liam Scales makes superb claim about Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45699</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/18/liam-scales-makes-claim-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T18:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody at Celtic has enjoyed as meteoric a rise this season as Liam Scales. It is hard to believe that even a few months ago, most people believed that his Parkhead career was as good as over. He had spent the previous campaign out on loan at Aberdeen and even though he did well, there […]
Liam Scales makes superb claim about Celtic Park - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 duels won; Celtic star earns "excellent" verdict after first international start in a year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180921</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/reaction-and-verdict-as-celtic-star-cameron-carter-vickers-makes-first-usa-start-in-a-year/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T17:31:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[United States national team manager Gregg Berhalter was pleased with the performance of Celtic defender Cameron Carter-Vickers after his first international start in a year....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rising Celtic star now nominated for national overseas award alongside £100m man]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180917</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-liam-scales-now-nominated-for-national-award-alongside-two-top-premier-league-talents/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T16:43:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rise in status of Celtic defender Liam Scales continues apace this weekend after he was nominated for a national award in his native Ireland....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Funny Brendan Rodgers moment captures the spotlight in new Celtic video]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180914</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/funny-brendan-rodgers-moment-captures-the-spotlight-in-new-celtic-video/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T16:13:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic poked a bit of fun at Brendan Rodgers’ changing perception amongst supporters in the club’s new Christmas advert, with a moment that has become...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Celtic star qualifies for EURO 2024 and it could be huge for Bhoys form]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180908</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/another-celtic-star-qualifies-for-euro-2024-and-it-could-be-big-for-bhoys-form/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T15:25:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Scotland’s official qualification for next year’s European Championships booked a place for Callum McGregor and the rest of the Celtic contingent in the Scottish...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newcastle United in pole position for former Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45695</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/18/newcastle-united-pole-position-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T15:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have had a number top quality players over the years who have moved away after a few successful seasons at Parkhead. The grass is not always greener on the other side though. Of course, things have worked out for some. Just have a look at how Virgil van Dijk’s career has played out. He […]
Newcastle United in pole position for former Celtic player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero steals the show and makes headlines as he embarrasses Porto star on national duty]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180902</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-hero-steals-the-show-and-makes-headlines-as-he-embarrasses-porto-star-on-international-duty/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T14:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star Luis Palma was one of the stars of the show for Honduras overnight as he produced an effective display to help beat Mexico...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton rules out Celtic signing £3 million Hearts player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45687</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/18/chris-sutton-celtic-hearts-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T13:30:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are enjoying a decent run of form, at least domestically. But they might find themselves in a tough situation in January. The Hoops do not have a lot of squad depth in certain positions. On the other hand, the AFC Asian Cup is scheduled to start early next year. Both Kyogo Furuhashi and Oh […]
Chris Sutton rules out Celtic signing £3 million Hearts player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS’ SMILES BETTER – AT THE DOUBLE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114358</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-smiles-better-at-the-double/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T11:24:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO FURUHASHI and Matt O’Riley are on their way to becoming Celtic’s Dream Team double-act. The prolific striker and the stylish playmaker are dovetailing expertly in the champions’ line-up with the Japanese hitman now on the 62-goal mark after 101 appearances. O’Riley has added six strikes to his vast repertoire of talents, including next week’s opponents [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC STRIKER SEARCH: SHANKLAND? ‘FORGET ABOUT IT,’ INSISTS SUTTON]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114348</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-striker-search-shankland-forget-about-it-insists-sutton/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T08:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS will be lumbered with a massive striking dilemma when three of his top frontmen are missing during the Asia Cup. The Hoops boss will almost certainly be without his top marksman Kyogo Furuhashi and his back-up Oh Hyeon-gyu when the forwards are called up by Japan and South Korea respectively, a predicament flagged up [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: ECHOES OF THE DIM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114322</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-echoes-of-the-dim/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T06:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MY dad took me to my first game at Celtic Park sixty years ago – November 9 1963 – and we watched Stevie Chalmers score a hat-trick as Jimmy McGrory’s team won 5-3 against Partick Thistle. If Nazi mortar fire had been a bit more precise, that treasured afternoon would never have occurred and my [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE BERTIE AULD: PART FOUR: ‘HOW I MADE CELTIC HISTORY’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=86764</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-unforgettable-bertie-auld-part-four-how-i-made-celtic-history/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T05:30:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bertie Auld dovetailed with his good friend Bobby Murdoch into making the Celtic midfield the envy of Europe during Jock Stein’s all-conquering side’s sweep through the sixties. CQN has been celebrating the life and incredible times of the Celtic legend in an EXCLUSIVE series with extracts from his best-selling autobiography, ‘A Bhoy Called [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor admits to one change in Celtic dressing room]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45682</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/17/callum-mcgregor-celtic-dressing-room/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T23:35:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor is someone who has seen it all and done it all at Celtic. He has risen through the ranks at the club, going from a ball boy to captain. And naturally, he has been part of a lot of different dressing rooms over the years. With the armband in his possession now, he […]
Callum McGregor admits to one change in Celtic dressing room - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic man linked with move to Manchester United]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45673</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/17/former-celtic-linked-manchester-united/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T21:35:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been home to some interesting names over the years. And that is not limited to just on the pitch action. There are many working behind the scenes at Parkhead as well and some of them have seen their careers head in a positive direction after joining the Hoops. One such name could be […]
Former Celtic man linked with move to Manchester United - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player tipped for position change by commentator]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45670</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/17/celtic-player-tipped-position-change/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T19:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic find themselves in an interesting situation right now. They stumbled out of the gates this season but have quite certainly found their feet in recent months. That being said, they are dealing with quite a few injuries at this point in time and could that lead to Brendan Rodgers coming up with some innovative […]
Celtic player tipped for position change by commentator - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender tipped for position change by overseas media]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180886</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alistair-johnston-position-change-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston is currently on international duty, with two pundits in his homeland posing the question of whether he could play in midfield for Canada....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sydney van Hooijdonk opens door to exit amid Celtic links]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45667</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/17/sydney-van-hooijdonk-celtic-links/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T18:05:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic could find themselves in need of a striker in January. The AFC Asian Cup will start early next year and there is a possibility that both Kyogo Furuhashi and Oh Hyeon-gyu could be selected by their respective national teams. One would expect the likes of Japan and South Korea to make deep runs in […]
Sydney van Hooijdonk opens door to exit amid Celtic links - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dutch striker suggests potential club exit after summer Celtic interest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180872</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/sydney-van-hooijdonk-suggests-january-exit-is-possible-after-summer-celtic-reports/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T17:11:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bologna striker Sydney van Hooijdonk has hinted at a potential move to Celtic in January. 

Van Hooijdonk, the son of former Celtic striker Pierre, has only made five Serie A appearances this season, failing to start a single game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker coaching role announced]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180880</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-striker-leigh-griffiths-takes-next-career-step/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Griffiths will continue to play in a player-coach role for the Australian side, who compete in the Football West State League Division 1.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic recruitment chief linked with Manchester United]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180864</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/man-united-consider-former-celtic-recruitment-chief-for-key-role/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[English Premier League giants Manchester United are reportedly interested in former Celtic recruitment chief Lee Congerton for the role of Sporting Director.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant reckons Celtic's Asian Cup solution lies close to home]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180853</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/peter-grant-reckons-celtics-asian-cup-solution-lies-close-to-home/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T15:18:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant has reacted to rumours linking Hearts striker Lawrence Shankland with a move to Celtic]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former EPL star fell out with agent when Celtic transfer fell through]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180858</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-premier-league-star-fell-out-with-agent-when-celtic-transfer-fell-through/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T14:43:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Leicester and Newcastle right-back Danny Simpson has revealed that a move to Celtic collapsed back in 2019.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star admits he could end up leaving the club soon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180847</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/mikey-johnston-admits-time-is-ticking-on-celtic-career/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T14:13:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic winger Mikey Johnston has spoken about his future at the club, admitting he needs to force his way into the starting 11 before January.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player sounds open to Parkhead exit in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45664</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/17/celtic-player-parkhead-exit-january-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T14:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a pretty sizeable squad at this point. Many feel that there are too many players for Brendan Rodgers to give enough playing time to everybody. Naturally, there are quite a few who are struggling to get into the team and there is speculation over their future. And it is expected that some will […]
Celtic player sounds open to Parkhead exit in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HAIL THE SIX-GOAL HISTORY BHOY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=85196</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hail-the-six-goal-history-bhoy/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T13:20:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DIXIE DEANS  stepped into the spotlight EXACTLY half a century ago as Celtic routed Partick Thisle 7-0 in a league game at Parkhead. The chunky hitman went on a goal rampage and scored a DOUBLE hat-trick in a breathtaking performance in front of 22,000 ecastic home fans on the afternoon of November 17 1973. Deans became [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IT’S A WINNER: KYOGO SPARKLES IN CELTIC’S CHRISTMAS FILM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114340</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/its-a-winner-kyogo-sparkles-in-celtics-christmas-film/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T13:02:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO FURUHASHI has been shining at Celtic ever since he thumped in a superb hat-trick on his Parkhead debut back on August 8 2021. The Japanese striker, bought for £4.6million from J-League outfit Vissel Kobe just over a week beforehand, treated the Hoops fans with a display of what was to come as he shredded [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou signing must leave Celtic in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45660</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/17/ange-postecoglou-leave-celtic-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T12:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have many Celtic players, who have benefited from the arrival of Brendan Rodgers as manager over the summer. Liam Scales has gone from being near the bottom of the pecking order to a regular starter. Matt O’Riley’s game has seen clear improvement as well and he might be the best in Scottish football right […]
Ange Postecoglou signing must leave Celtic in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crown Office and the cover up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114338</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-crown-office-and-the-cover-up/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T12:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The criminal justice system in Scotland (and south of the border) is on its knees.  It lacks funds to appropriately prosecute crime, this week I spoke to a shopkeeper who closed a business which flourished for decades, citing, among other things, the inability to deter shoplifters. So what does this have to do with football?  [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CALMAC, CRY-BABIES AND SHENANIGANS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114334</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/calmac-cry-babies-and-shenanigans/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T09:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CALLUM McGREGOR will take his place in the midfield against Norway at Hampden on Sunday evening as Scotland bring down the curtain on a successful Euro 24 qualifying campaign. The Celtic captain played his part in the country reaching the summer Finals in Germany and they had already sealed their place among Europe’s elite before [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MAKE-OR-BREAK FOR ONE-TIME WONDERBHOY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114330</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/make-or-break-for-one-time-wonderbhoy/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T08:27:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MIKEY JOHNSTON has set himself a January target to make the breakthrough at Celtic. The one-time wonder Bhoy, who broke into the team as a teenager during Brendan Rodgers’ first spell as manager, has played only 25 first-team minutes this season. Johnston, now 24, came on as a second-half substitute in the scoreless stalemate with Hibs [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE BERTIE AULD: PART THREE: ‘CHEEKY CHARLIE TULLY – A MIX OF JINKY AND BESTIE’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=86712</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-unforgettable-bertie-auld-part-three-cheeky-charlie-tully-a-mix-of-jinky-and-bestie/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T05:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bertie Auld was one of the key components in Jock Stein’s all-conquering Celtic team of the sixties. CQN has been celebrating the life and incredible times of the club legend in an EXCLUSIVE series with extracts from his best-selling autobiography, ‘A Bhoy Called Bertie’, co-authored by his friend and writer Alex Gordon. The [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend linked with Scottish Premiership return]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45657</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/16/celtic-legend-linked-premiership-return/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T22:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic do appear to have their future sorted in terms of a manager. Brendan Rodgers was brought back in the summer for a second stint in the Parkhead hot seat and it is hard to imagine that the Hoops would choose to part ways with the Northern Irishman anytime soon, unless something completely unexpected happens. […]
Celtic legend linked with Scottish Premiership return - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 first-team stars get Thursday night run out as Celtic play their part in fun vs Dundee]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180842</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/5-first-team-stars-get-thursday-night-run-out-as-celtic-play-their-part-in-fun-vs-dundee/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T21:46:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fielded a strong defence for tonight’s Cammy Kerr Testimonial against Dundee at Dens Park. Scott Bain, Stephen Welsh, Yuki Kobayashi, Gustaf Lagerbielke and Alexandro...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable source confirm Celtic interest in £3 million player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45654</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/16/reliable-source-celtic-interest-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T21:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic might have brought in a number of new players to the club over the summer but they are expected to remain busy in the January transfer window as well in an attempt to further strengthen Brendan Rodgers’ squad. Most fans view striker and goalkeeper as two positions in need of reinforcements. On the other […]
Reliable source confirm Celtic interest in £3 million player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic set to open contract talks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180837</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/liam-scales-could-land-big-celtic-reward-for-recent-form/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T20:59:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has indicated that representatives of Liam Scales and Celtic will soon be in discussions regarding a new contract at the club. Scales has...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic target hard-working attacker ahead of January; could have lightning-quick rise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180831</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-transfer-target-could-have-lightning-quick-rise-as-bhoys-show-intense-interest/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T20:21:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kanji Okunuki has only been at current club Nurnberg for a few months but Celtic are showing intense interest his services ahead of the January...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jota regrets leaving Celtic as new manager makes decision]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45649</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/16/jota-regrets-leaving-celtic-manager/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T19:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One major problem Celtic faced in the summer was the exit of Jota. The Portuguese winger had been a key player for the Hoops for the previous two seasons and was arguably the club’s most creative outlet. As a result, they needed to find a replacement for him, as he departed for Al-Ittihad in a […]
Jota regrets leaving Celtic as new manager makes decision - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic forward Hyeongyu Oh makes positive noises in South Korean media]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180817</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-forward-hyeongyu-oh-makes-positive-noises-in-south-korean-media/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T19:23:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyeongyu Oh has told media outlets in his homeland South Korea that he is growing in confidence with Celtic and is ready to take his...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Won every duel: Celtic hero amongst top-rated for Scotland despite criticism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180819</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-hero-greg-taylor-amongst-top-rated-for-scotland-despite-criticism/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:58:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Greg Taylor was given a big opportunity to impress for Scotland this evening and can take some credit for his performance. Taylor hadn’t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premier League winner admits he was close to joining Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45642</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/16/premier-league-winner-close-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have signed a number of players from the Premier League over the years. In fact, before their recent transformation of the transfer policy following the arrival of Ange Postecoglou in the summer of 2021, the Hoops would often look towards the English top flight to find solutions to their problems. Of course, it is […]
Premier League winner admits he was close to joining Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic interest in Allsvenkan star 'legitimate' as scouts take a close look]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180814</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-interest-in-allsvenkan-star-legitimate-as-scouts-take-a-close-look/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T17:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were first linked with a move for Nathaniel Adjei two weeks ago and another outlet has now corroborated the first Sky Sports update. It...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic men Neil Lennon and Scott Brown in the frame for Premiership job]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180809</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-men-neil-lennon-and-scott-brown-in-the-frame-for-premiership-job/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T16:54:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two former Celtic icons are in the running to replace Malky Mackay at Scottish Premiership side Ross County. The Scottish Daily Mail [16/11 print edition,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lots to talk about in Dublin … John Hartson]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58463</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/dublin-john-hartson/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T16:31:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Hartson will be back on stage at Peadar Browns, Dublin on Friday night. Just over a year since his last visit to the venue. So much has happend over the last year at Celtic Park. Ange leaving, Brendan returning and a treble of trophies to admire in the trophy room at Celtic Park from […]
The post Lots to talk about in Dublin … John Hartson appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic Select side playing away to Dundee tonight]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180804</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-celtic-select-side-playing-away-to-dundee-tonight/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T16:24:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Celtic Select side, thought primarily to be made up of youngsters, will take on a Dundee XI at Dens Park tonight for Cammy Kerr’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roy Keane on the Gordan Strachan phonecall that ended time at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180788</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/roy-keane-on-the-gordan-strachan-phonecall-that-ended-time-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T14:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic midfielder concedes spell was "embarrassing" due to injury setbacks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Worst Dinner Party Ever – Etims Podcast]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18537</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18537"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T14:11:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Desi, Hector and Monty are joined by BBC Sportsounds latest Soup taker, Ralph Malph to discuss the recent Celtics goings on as well as various…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Desi Mond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manchester United legend admits regret at joining Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45640</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/16/manchester-united-legend-regret-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T14:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic has been the home to many legends over the years. Not too long ago, several Premier League icons moved up north in the latter stages of their career to play for one of the two Glasgow giants. That theme has changed in recent years as other destinations have become more popular due to a […]
Manchester United legend admits regret at joining Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic linked with transfer move for in-form 24-year-old]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45636</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/16/celtic-linked-transfer-move-form/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T12:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic signed nine players in the summer transfer window, with seven arriving on a permanent basis while two were brought in on loan deals. But the club are expected to be active when it comes to making signings, in January as well. There are still a few gaps in Brendan Rodgers’ squad that need to […]
Celtic linked with transfer move for in-form 24-year-old - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic-Newco financials: Celtic’s huge advantage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114314</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-newco-financials-celtics-huge-advantage/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T12:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the surprising elements when we compare Celtic and Newco’s accounts is that the former have a higher wage bill: Celtic, £60m; Newco, £64m, despite Celtic having a bonus liability for winning all three trophies.  The variance is even more stark than it looks.  Celtic’s wage figure includes 130 retail staff, Newco’s retail operation [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC LEGENDS IN BOSS LINK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114313</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-legends-in-boss-link/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T11:25:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legends Neil Lennon and Scott Brown have been linked with the manager’s job at Ross County. Ironically, the post became vacant after the sacking of another former Hoops player Malky Mackay, as CQN reported yesterday. Lennon and Brown, the manager and captain who dovetailed to guide the Parkhead club to a phenomenal quadruple treble [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REVEALED: ENGLISH CLUB WHO KNOCKED BACK BIG ANGE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114311</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/revealed-english-club-who-knocked-back-big-ange/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T10:20:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU quit Celtic in June only a couple of days after sealing a world record eighth domestic silverware clean sweep. Forty-eight hours after the 3-1 Scottish Cup Final win over Inverness Caley Thistle at Hampden on Saturday June 3, the Greek-Australian boss was on his way to Spurs. Postecoglou’s two-year reign at Parkhead ended [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC STEP UP STRIKER SEARCH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114295</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-step-up-striker-search/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T07:14:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have been monitoring Japanese striker Kanji Okunuki who is currently with Bundelsiga second-tier outfit Nuremberg. Brendan Rodgers has identified another attack-leader as a priority signing during the January transfer window with his current options narrowed to Kyogo Furuhashi and Oh Hyeon-gyu with Daizen Maeda on stand-by. Okunuki, who has called into his country’s senior [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>