<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-09-14T20:10:34.987Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Get him in’: John Hartson urges Rodgers to start 26-year-old for Celtic v Dundee]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174317</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/get-him-in-john-hartson-urges-brendan-rodgers-to-start-26-year-old-for-celtic-v-dundee/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Hartson wants to see Nat Phillips earn his first minutes in the colours of Celtic ahead of domestic football returning this weekend.  Many expected...
The post ‘Get him in’: John Hartson urges Rodgers to start 26-year-old for Celtic v Dundee appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boosted by 3 injury returns as Rodgers also provides Carter-Vickers and Nawrocki update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174312</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boosted-by-3-injury-returns-as-brendan-rodgers-also-provides-carter-vickers-and-nawrocki-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T19:26:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers says Reo Hatate, Marco Tilio and Yuki Kobayashi have all returned to Celtic training during the international break. The trio have been missing...
The post Celtic boosted by 3 injury returns as Rodgers also provides Carter-Vickers and Nawrocki update appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manager rejects Rangers job after loss to Celtic at Ibrox]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44186</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/14/manager-rangers-job-loss-celtic-ibrox/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T19:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Beale’s future at Ibrox is in serious doubt after he saw his side lose to Celtic at home. The team were booed at full-time and it looks like the manager might be on borrowed time now. It does seem like the Rangers might already be searching for his replacement but have already been turned […]
Manager rejects Rangers job after loss to Celtic at Ibrox - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pressure On: Celtic force Rangers into looking at manager change with approach reportedly made]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174309</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/pressure-on-celtic-force-rangers-into-looking-at-manager-change-with-approach-reportedly-made/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T18:01:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fallout of Celtic’s superb 1-0 win at Ibrox just before the international break continues to haunt Rangers, with reports indicating their hierarchy are strongly...
The post Pressure On: Celtic force Rangers into looking at manager change with approach reportedly made appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic confirm signing of defender on three-year deal]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44182</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/14/celtic-confirm-defender-three-year-deal/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T17:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The summer transfer window may have closed with Celtic making nine additions to their squad, seven on a permanent basis and two on loan. But the Hoops are continuing to strengthen the club as a whole, even if not the senior side. And they have added another defender to their B Team roster. Celtic signed […]
Celtic confirm signing of defender on three-year deal - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic stars react to their EA Sports FC 24 ratings; highest & lowest in squad, one is delighted]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174306</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-stars-react-to-their-ea-sports-fc-24-ratings-highest-and-lowest-in-squad/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T16:56:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of the Celtic squad have been taking part in a special challenge at Lennoxtown during the international break, in partnership with EA Sports and...
The post Celtic stars react to their EA Sports FC 24 ratings; highest & lowest in squad, one is delighted appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Longer period than expected"; Celtic star takes to Instagram after injury sickener]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174302</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/longer-period-than-expected-celtic-star-takes-to-instagram-after-injury-sickener/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T16:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic winger Liel Abada has updated supporters on his situation after picking up an injury on international duty with Israel earlier this month. Manager Brendan...
The post "Longer period than expected"; Celtic star takes to Instagram after injury sickener appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simon Donnelly says 'something special is brewing' with player Celtic sold under Postecoglou]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174285</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/simon-donnelly-says-something-special-is-brewing-with-player-celtic-sold-under-ange-postecoglou/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans wouldn’t be surprised to hear that Ben Doak is receiving rave reviews after his dazzling display for Scotland U21s recently. The Liverpool winger,...
The post Simon Donnelly says 'something special is brewing' with player Celtic sold under Postecoglou appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REVEALED: WHY BOSS SNUBBED FIVE STARS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111934</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/revealed-why-boss-snubbed-five-stars/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T14:57:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has revealed the reasoning behind three of his summer signings being left out of his Champions League squad. The Celtic boss omitted Polish defender Maik Nawrocki, Australian winger Marco Tilio and South Korean midfielder Kwon Hyeon-kyu from his 25-man pool for the forthcoming fixtures against Atletico Madrid, Lazio and Feyenoord. The champaign will [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Celtic stars we're expecting big things from in the UEFA Champions League]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174213</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/three-celtic-stars-were-expecting-big-things-from-in-the-uefa-champions-league/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re now a matter of days away from Celtic’s return to the UEFA Champions League. It’s just over 11 months since we last featured in...
The post Three Celtic stars we're expecting big things from in the UEFA Champions League appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: CELTIC KICK-OFF SWITCH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111927</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-celtic-kick-off-switch/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T14:21:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S Premiership game against Motherwell at Fir Park a fortnight on Saturday has had a kick-off switch. The match was due to commence at 3pm, but will now begin at 12.30pm at the request of both clubs. The earlier start for an encounter which is NOT being broadcast live by Sky Sports could aid recovery time for [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘SHAME,’ RODGERS CONFIRMS ABADA SETBACK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111926</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/shame-rodgers-confirms-abada-setback/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T14:07:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has confirmed that winger Liel Abada WILL be sidelined for the remainder of this year. It was originally feared the Israeli ace would be out for five months, as CQN reported earlier today, but it looks as though that may be too severe although his period in recuperation will be lengthy. Rodgers reckons [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rodgers in Confident Mood]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58384</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/rodgers-in-confident-mood/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T13:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The international break is over and Celtic get back to business this Saturday against Dundee. Media reports are suggesting that Liel Abada has picked up an injury while away on international duty with Israel and he could be ruled out for the next 5 months. Confidence should be high after our last outing at Ibrox […]
The post Rodgers in Confident Mood appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic sent blunt message by former Feyenoord player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44177</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/14/celtic-message-former-feyenoord-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T12:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will be kicking off their 2023/24 Champions League group stage campaign with a game against Feyenoord away at De Kuip. It will not be an easy task for the Hoops at all, as they have made an inconsistent start to the campaign and it is hard to predict which version of the Hoops will […]
Celtic sent blunt message by former Feyenoord player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Young Celtic stars about to embark on another UEFA adventure; TV arrangements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174234</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/young-celtic-stars-about-to-embark-on-another-vital-uefa-adventure-tv-arrangements/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While most of the UEFA-related Celtic talk at present is about the Champions League, there is another competition getting underway next Tuesday. The first-team’s involvement...
The post Young Celtic stars about to embark on another UEFA adventure; TV arrangements appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch: The outrageous Nat Phillips piece of skill that was brought up at Celtic press conference]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174206</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/watch-the-outrageous-nat-phillips-piece-of-skill-that-was-brought-up-at-celtic-press-conference/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nat Phillips almost certainly hasn’t been brought to Celtic to produce moments of extreme skill, yet he clearly has it in his locker. Back in...
The post Watch: The outrageous Nat Phillips piece of skill that was brought up at Celtic press conference appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The true cost of the Celtic squad; doesn't make great reading ahead of Champions League]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174226</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-true-cost-of-the-celtic-squad-reported-doesnt-make-great-reading-ahead-of-champions-league/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are inside the top 100 for the most expensive squads in world football. The information has been provided by CIES Football Observatory — a...
The post The true cost of the Celtic squad; doesn't make great reading ahead of Champions League appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Training Revision Loop urgently required]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111924</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/training-revision-loop-urgently-required/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T11:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If concerns are realised and Liel Abada’s injury, sustained on international duty with Israel, results in him missing five months of the season, it will be a huge blow to Celtic, as well as the player.  Liel was an instant hit when he arrived in Glasgow two years ago as a 19-year-old.  His goals and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ABADA FIVE-MONTH INJURY FEARS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111921</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/abada-five-month-injury-fears/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T10:46:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC winger Liel Abada faces a sickening FIVE-MONTH injury lay-off. The 21-year-old raider returned early from Israel’s international break after sustaining a muscle strain in training, as CQN stated at the weekend. Abada was checked out by the Hoops medical team and it appears the problem is a lot more serious than originally thought. Reports [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Absolutely, John McGinn': Andy Walker makes claim about Celtic 30-year-old fans will love]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174248</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/absolutely-john-mcginn-andy-walker-makes-bold-claim-about-celtic-30-year-old-fans-will-love/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andy Walker says Celtic midfielder Callum McGregor would start for England, alongside the likes of John McGinn, Andy Robertson and Kieran Tierney. All are either...
The post 'Absolutely, John McGinn': Andy Walker makes claim about Celtic 30-year-old fans will love appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laughter all well and good but Celtic star has hit upon a major safety concern at Ibrox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174191</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/laughter-all-well-and-good-but-nat-phillips-has-hit-upon-a-major-celtic-safety-concern-at-ibrox/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing Nat Phillips has revealed that he was at Ibrox for the team’s recent derby win over Rangers. The Liverpool loanee joined the...
The post Laughter all well and good but Celtic star has hit upon a major safety concern at Ibrox appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key Celtic player could be out for rest of 2023 with injury]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44173</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/14/key-celtic-player-rest-2023-injury/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T09:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have had terrible luck with injuries this season already. The likes of Cameron Carter-Vickers, Maik Nawrocki and Stephen Welsh are out for the foreseeable future with medium to long-term issues. And now, it looks like another key player could be set to join, in a major blow for Brendan Rodgers’ side. The Glasgow Derby […]
Key Celtic player could be out for rest of 2023 with injury - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘ITCHING TO GO,’ INSISTS NEW BHOY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111917</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/itching-to-go-insists-new-bhoy/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T08:10:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEW Bhoy Nat Phillips insists he can cope with the pressure at Celtic. The centre-back, who has signed a loan deal from Liverpool until January, missed out on a quickfire debut in the champions’ 1-0 win at Ibrox, but still caught the flavour of a hectic Glasgow derby. Phillips, whose dad Jimmy had a season [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Celtic stars who should have benefitted greatly from the international break]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174241</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/three-celtic-stars-who-should-have-benefitted-greatly-from-the-international-break/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s first team stars should all be back in training on Thursday as the team gears up for their next match. It’s the best part...
The post Three Celtic stars who should have benefitted greatly from the international break appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender shares fitness update after some Ibrox murmurings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174199</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-defender-nat-phillips-shares-fitness-update-after-some-ibrox-murmurings/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Nat Phillips has offered a reassuring fitness update as he closes in on his debut for the club. The Englishman was unable to...
The post Celtic defender shares fitness update after some Ibrox murmurings appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: The Rocco Vata hype continues but it may not be good news for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174220</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-rocco-vata-hype-continues-but-it-may-not-be-good-news-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hype around Celtic youngster Rocco Vata is continuing to grow. The 18-year-old is yet to feature competitively for Celtic this season, after getting some...
The post Report: The Rocco Vata hype continues but it may not be good news for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic plan for Nat Phillips is clear as defender addresses looming January decision]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174185</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-celtic-plan-for-nat-phillips-is-clear-as-defender-addresses-looming-january-decision/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent Celtic signing Nat Phillips was an impressive performer as he met the Scottish media for the first time on Wednesday. The English defender, signed...
The post The Celtic plan for Nat Phillips is clear as defender addresses looming January decision appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE JOCK STEIN YEARS (Part Four)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=55161</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-jock-stein-years-part-four/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T04:15:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Jock Stein made an extraordinary immediate impact on the Parkhead club when he returned as manager in March 1965. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE, author Alex Gordon, who has written fifteen publications on Celtic, has opened his book files on the Parkhead great for an absorbing twenty-one part series. Today, in Part Four of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JOHNNY DOYLE: GREAT UNCAPPED CELTS (Part Ten)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.cqnmagazine.com/?p=5623</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/johnny-doyle-great-uncapped-celts-part-eleven/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T04:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CQN is turning the spotlight again on the Celtic players who never had the honour of playing for their country. Johnny Doyle was a £90,000 signing for the Hoops in 1975 – the club’s record fee at the time – and he became a player who never gave less than 100 per cent for the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player makes superb Zlatan Ibrahimovic claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44168</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/13/celtic-player-zlatan-ibrahimovic-claim/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T23:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have certainly made quite a few additions to their squad over the summer. Mostly, they have stuck to bringing in highly-rated young talents from around the world. The results appear to be mixed till now. The likes of Odin Thiago Holm, Gustaf Lagerbielke and Yang Hyun-jun have made positive starts. On the other hand, […]
Celtic player makes superb Zlatan Ibrahimovic claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic summer signing’s father used to play for Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44165</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/13/celtic-summer-signing-father-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T21:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Very rarely have players represented both Celtic and the Rangers over the years. Also, there are very few who have signed for the Hoops, whose father used to play for the Ibrox club. And yet, there is one in Brendan Rodgers’ current squad. That is none other than Nat Phillips, who was brought in on […]
Celtic summer signing’s father used to play for Rangers - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nat Phillips explains why he left Liverpool to join Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44162</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/13/nat-phillips-liverpool-join-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T20:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nat Phillips is the most high-profile signing that Celtic made this summer. Even he arrived on loan for only the first half of the season and out of necessity more than anything else, as Cameron Carter-Vickers, Maik Nawrocki and Stephen Welsh are all out injured for the foreseeable future. Bringing in the Liverpool defender was […]
Nat Phillips explains why he left Liverpool to join Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic criticised for ignoring Scottish international player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44159</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/13/celtic-criticised-scottish-international/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T18:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have signed highly-rated young talents from all over the world in recent years and it has served them very well on the pitch. Just this summer, they brought in players from leagues in South Korea, Australia, Norway, Sweden, Greece, Poland, Portugal and England. They did not sign any Scottish player though. That does not […]
Celtic criticised for ignoring Scottish international player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022 Celtic summer signing now facing a struggle under Brendan Rodgers - opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174149</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/alexandro-bernabei-now-facing-a-struggle-under-brendan-rodgers-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Things are not looking good for Alexandro Bernabei after he was left out of Celtic’s UEFA Champions League squad. The Hoops ‘List A’ selection was...
The post 2022 Celtic summer signing now facing a struggle under Brendan Rodgers - opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gareth Bale mentions Celtic in Ange Postecoglou claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44155</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/13/gareth-bale-celtic-ange-postecoglou/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T15:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gareth Bale is the most decorated British footballer in history and he often does not get the credit that he deserves for what he achieved at Real Madrid. The Welshman scored in more than one Champions League final and won the competition five times, a record he shares with several of his former teammates. He […]
Gareth Bale mentions Celtic in Ange Postecoglou claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers sets a clear target for Celtic in the UEFA Champions League]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174142</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-sets-a-clear-target-for-celtic-in-the-uefa-champions-league/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has been speaking about the UEFA Champions League with less than a week to go before Celtic get this season’s campaign underway. It’s...
The post Brendan Rodgers sets a clear target for Celtic in the UEFA Champions League appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HEY, BIG SPENDER: £54.2m CELTIC IN CASH SPLASH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111913</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hey-big-spender-54-2m-celtic-in-cash-splash/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T14:43:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have spent £54.2million in assembling the squad currently at the disposal of Brendan Rodgers. That’s the total amount of cash the champions have splashed over the recent seasons which also takes in the likes of David Turnbull who arrived from Motherwell for £2.75million in the summer of 2020. The financial data has been released [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic man shares message after international efforts go under the radar; Hoops chances]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174157</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/hyeokkyu-kwon-shares-message-after-international-efforts-go-under-the-radar-celtic-chances/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player Hyeokkyu Kwon has shared a message after being away on international duty with the South Korea under-23 side. The holding midfielder, who joined...
The post Celtic man shares message after international efforts go under the radar; Hoops chances appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Injury consequence for Champions League squad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111912</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/injury-consequence-for-champions-league-squad/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T11:04:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The injury crisis in central defence had an interesting consequence for Celtic’s Champions League squad, announced yesterday.  As things stand, we have only two fit central defenders who have played for the club, Liam Scales and Gustaf Lagerbielke.  Nat Phillips is fit but has yet to make his debut. As recently as a month ago, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Pleasure': Jude Bellingham's verdict on Scotland's midfield after facing Celtic's McGregor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174164</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/pleasure-jude-bellinghams-verdict-on-scotlands-midfield-after-facing-celtics-callum-mcgregor/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic captain Callum McGregor faced one of his toughest tests on Tuesday night following Scotland’s 3-1 defeat to England at Hampden Park.  Jude Bellingham was...
The post 'Pleasure': Jude Bellingham's verdict on Scotland's midfield after facing Celtic's McGregor appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maik Nawrocki news doesn't appear to be good after Celtic squad announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174101</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/maik-nawrocki-news-doesnt-appear-to-be-good-after-celtic-squad-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic man Maik Nawrocki appears to be some way from making his return from injury, judging by developments on Tuesday. The Polish central defender, signed...
The post Maik Nawrocki news doesn't appear to be good after Celtic squad announcement appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers making a mistake not playing Celtic ace]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44152</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/13/brendan-rodgers-mistake-celtic-ace/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T10:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers’ return to Celtic Park has been up-and-down till now. The Hoops made a questionable start to the season for sure and are already out of the Scottish League Cup. But then, the win over the Rangers away at Ibrox has settled a lot of nerves and convinced the doubters that the Northern Irishman […]
Brendan Rodgers making a mistake not playing Celtic ace - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic round-up; Callum McGregor vs England verdict as Bernardo, Holm and Kyogo all feature]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174107</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-round-up-callum-mcgregor-vs-england-verdict-as-bernardo-holm-and-kyogo-all-feature/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tuesday was a busy day for some of Celtic’s stars as the international programme drew to a close. The first break of the season arrived...
The post Celtic round-up; Callum McGregor vs England verdict as Bernardo, Holm and Kyogo all feature appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GREEN LIGHT FOR HATATE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111883</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/green-light-for-hatate/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T08:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE is poised to make his return from injury against Dundee at Parkhead on Saturday as the champions continue their quest for Premiership points. The influential Japanese midfielder has been missing since a 25-minute second-half cameo in the 3-1 win over Aberdeen at Pittodrie exactly a month ago. Hatate suffered a muscular injury that [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers is bullish; thinks Celtic have already encountered major moment this season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174117</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-is-bullish-thinks-celtic-have-already-had-their-gibraltar-moment-this-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers had plenty of interesting things to say about Celtic on Tuesday. As we’ve already covered, the Hoops boss offered a pretty positive injury...
The post Brendan Rodgers is bullish; thinks Celtic have already encountered major moment this season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss shares great Reo Hatate news that extends beyond positive injury update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174083</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-shares-great-reo-hatate-news-that-extends-beyond-positive-injury-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers has shared some great news about Reo Hatate. The Japanese midfielder — arguably our most talented player — has endured a...
The post Celtic boss shares great Reo Hatate news that extends beyond positive injury update appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Irish outlet rave about Celtic youngster as he steals the show in midweek]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174135</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/irish-outlet-rave-about-rocco-vata-as-celtic-man-steals-the-show-in-midweek/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic youngster Rocco Vata was the standout performer for the Republic of Ireland’s under-21s on Tuesday evening. The young Irish side kept up their 100%...
The post Irish outlet rave about Celtic youngster as he steals the show in midweek appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers shares positive injury update but two Celtic stars not mentioned by name]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174090</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-shares-positive-injury-update-but-two-celtic-stars-not-mentioned-by-name/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers shared a largely positive injury update on Tuesday. It’s been a challenging few weeks for the Hoops with a number of...
The post Brendan Rodgers shares positive injury update but two Celtic stars not mentioned by name appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing produces in overnight international; Hoops debut soon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174125</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/luis-palma-produces-in-overnight-honduras-clash-celtic-are-next/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summer Celtic signing Luis Palma was among the goalscorers in an emphatic midweek win for Honduras. The Central American country were in CONCACAF Nations League...
The post New Celtic signing produces in overnight international; Hoops debut soon appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE JOCK STEIN YEARS (Part Three)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=55150</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-jock-stein-years-part-three/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T04:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Jock Stein made an extraordinary immediate impact on the Parkhead club when he returned as manager in March 1965. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE series, author Alex Gordon, who has written fifteen books on Celtic, has opened his publication files on the Parkhead great. Today, in Part Three of our fascinating look back at [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JOHNNY DIVERS: GREAT UNCAPPED CELTS (Part Nine)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.cqnmagazine.com/?p=5054</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/johnny-divers-great-uncapped-celts-part-nine/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T04:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CQN is turning the spotlight again on the Celtic players who never had the honour of playing for their country. Johnny Divers was a goalscoring phenomenon who netted the first goal in a 4-0 win over Dundee United at Tannadice in August 1965 that kicked off the historic first nine in row. He had been [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic tipped to sign another Liverpool player amid links]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44148</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/12/celtic-sign-another-liverpool-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T22:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already signed one player from Liverpool recently in the form of Nat Phillips, who arrived on loan for the first half of the season. It was a move made out of necessity more than anything else. Celtic have players like Cameron Carter-Vickers, Stephen Welsh and Maik Nawrocki out for the foreseeable future. So, […]
Celtic tipped to sign another Liverpool player amid links - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OFF NIGHT FOR SCOTS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111872</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/off-night-for-scots/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T21:13:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SCOTLAND were off colour, off target and off the pace as they lost 3-1 to England in the 150th Anniversary Match at Hampden this evening. There was also bad news from Norway where the hosts beat Georgia 2-1 in the Scots’ Euro group in the game in which a draw would have seen Steve Clarke’s [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou makes emotional claim about Celtic fans]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44144</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/12/ange-postecoglou-claim-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T20:31:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou is one of the most popular Celtic managers in recent memory. Not only did the Australian win over the fans with wins, trophies and the style of football that his team played but also with his conduct off the pitch as well. A cheeky one-liner was never far away and he seemed to […]
Ange Postecoglou makes emotional claim about Celtic fans - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou explains why he left Celtic for Tottenham]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44140</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/12/ange-postecoglou-left-celtic-tottenham/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T19:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were dealt a blow when Ange Postecoglou left the club, merely days after winning a domestic treble with the Hoops, in order to join Tottenham Hotspur. The lead-up to the Scottish Cup final had been dominated by rumours of his potential exit and the fans’ worst fears soon came true. Postecoglou had proven himself […]
Ange Postecoglou explains why he left Celtic for Tottenham - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms major Celtic injury boost]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44137</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/12/brendan-rodgers-celtic-injury-boost/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T17:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There has been very little good news for Celtic when it comes to the injury front. One player after another has gone down with fitness issues at the start of the season, leaving Brendan Rodgers with limited options to pick his team from. That contributed to the stumbling start they made to the campaign, even […]
Brendan Rodgers confirms major Celtic injury boost - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Paulo Bernardo state of play as Celtic debut comes in to focus]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174021</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-paulo-bernardo-state-of-play-as-celtic-debut-comes-in-to-focus/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paulo Bernardo could make his Celtic debut this weekend against Dundee. The midfielder joined us on a season-long loan from Benfica on the final day...
The post The Paulo Bernardo state of play as Celtic debut comes in to focus appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou signing must leave after Celtic decision]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44135</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/12/ange-postecoglou-signing-leave-celtic-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T15:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A change in managers is always an interesting time for a club and the players, and Celtic certainly are going through a transitional phase right now. Ange Postecoglou left at the end of last season in order to join Tottenham Hotspur while Brendan Rodgers has been brought in as the Australian’s replacement. Of course, Rodgers’ […]
Ange Postecoglou signing must leave after Celtic decision - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic set for big billing in Champions League opener as new television era begins]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173999</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-set-for-big-billing-in-champions-league-opener-as-the-tnt-sports-era-begins/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic get their UEFA Champions League campaign underway next Tuesday. It may not feel like it right now, with international football dominating the headlines, but...
The post Celtic set for big billing in Champions League opener as new television era begins appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: NAWROCKI OUT OF EURO SQUAD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111868</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-nawrocki-out-of-euro-squad/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T14:48:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has been forced to leave crocked Maik Nawrocki out of Celtic’s 25-man Champions League squad . The £4.3million centre-back who arrived from Legia Warsaw in the summer suffered a hamstring problem during the Hoops’ 1-0 Viaplay League Cup loss to Kilmarnock at Rugby Park just over three weeks ago. It was announced Nawrocki [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[€5 million Celtic player left out of Champions League squad]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44132</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/12/5-million-celtic-champions-league-squad/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T13:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will be kicking off their Champions League campaign in a week when they take on Feyenoord away in the Netherlands. The Hoops were not able to win a single game in Europe’s elite competition last season despite putting in a few impressive performances and finished bottom of their group as a result. They will […]
€5 million Celtic player left out of Champions League squad - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The potential for at least one Celtic debut this weekend; problem area looking better]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174006</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/the-potential-for-at-least-one-celtic-debut-this-weekend-centre-back-situation-improves/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic centre-back situation will already have improved by the time Saturday’s clash against Dundee rolls around. The Hoops are back in Premiership action against...
The post The potential for at least one Celtic debut this weekend; problem area looking better appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Right at the top': Ange Postecoglou shares what he 'tells everyone' about Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174056</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/right-at-the-top-ange-postecoglou-shares-what-he-tells-everyone-about-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has shared that he ‘keeps saying to everyone’ that Celtic should be ‘top’ of the bucket list of clubs you want to be...
The post 'Right at the top': Ange Postecoglou shares what he 'tells everyone' about Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Park's unlikely starring role the last time Scotland faced England in a friendly]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173990</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-parks-unlikely-starring-role-the-last-time-scotland-faced-england-in-a-friendly/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scotland face England in a friendly on Tuesday evening at Hampden Park. The match is uncompetitive by definition, yet it is sure to be a...
The post Celtic Park's unlikely starring role the last time Scotland faced England in a friendly appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor’s five mountains in five weeks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111867</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/callum-mcgregors-five-mountains-in-five-weeks/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T11:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If results to their way, Scotland will tonight become the first team to qualify for the Euro 2024 in Germany next summer.  Norway and Georgia are both on four points.  A draw would see them move to five, 10 behind Scotland with three games remaining. Either way, automatic qualification is inevitable, as, with Spain remaining [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I don't': Sutton mentions Callum McGregor & says England star doesn't get into Scotland XI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174035</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-dont-sutton-mentions-callum-mcgregor-says-england-star-doesnt-get-into-scotland-xi/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton name-dropped Celtic captain Callum McGregor whilst stating that England star Jordan Henderson doesn’t get into Scotland’s XI. Celtic’s main man in the middle...
The post 'I don't': Sutton mentions Callum McGregor & says England star doesn't get into Scotland XI appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic influence already clear to see as Luis Palma shares photo from Honduras]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174028</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-influence-already-clear-to-see-as-luis-palma-shares-photo-from-honduras/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T09:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic influence is already clear to see as Luis Palma shared a photograph from Honduras. The recent Hoops signing is back in his homeland...
The post Celtic influence already clear to see as Luis Palma shares photo from Honduras appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHEN HARRY MET BROONY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111858</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/when-harry-met-broony/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T08:22:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC hero Scott Brown came face to face with rival skipper Harry Kane before the Scotland v England Euro 2018 qualifier at a sunkissed Hampden on the afternoon of June 10 2017. It turned out to be an epic confrontation between the opposite onfield leaders during a thrilling 2-2 stalemate after the hosts had fought [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic youngster shares Rodgers hope for next season as surprise midfield talk emerges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174014</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/bosun-lawal-shares-brendan-rodgers-hope-for-next-season-surprise-celtic-midfield-option-emerges/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bosun Lawal still seems to be hopeful about a future career at Celtic. The 20-year-old has played a handful of games for the Hoops since...
The post Celtic youngster shares Rodgers hope for next season as surprise midfield talk emerges appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HEARD THE ONE ABOUT HAMPDEN’S HEROES AND VILLAINS? CELTIC HERO REVEALS ALL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111839</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/heard-the-one-about-hampdens-heroes-and-villains-celtic-hero-reveals-all/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T07:39:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JUST over six years and three months ago, Leigh Griffiths sent two soaring long-range free-kicks beyond the grasping fingers of Joe Hart at Hampden Park in a crucial Euro 2018 qualifier. A late goal from Harry Kane gave England a 2-2 draw with Scotland, a loss of two points that went a long way to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic leave former Ibrox man feeling "a little bit silly" after glorious derby triumph]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173983</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-leave-former-ibrox-man-feeling-a-little-bit-silly-after-glorious-derby-triumph/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s over a week since Celtic silenced the doubters with a glorious derby win at Ibrox. With multiple injuries to contend with, and no supporters...
The post Celtic leave former Ibrox man feeling "a little bit silly" after glorious derby triumph appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo braced for big Japan chance after an injury that will interest Celtic fans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173976</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kyogo-furuhashi-braced-for-big-japan-chance-after-an-injury-that-will-interest-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Furuhashi could be set for his big opportunity to impress in a Japan shirt on Tuesday. The in-form Hoops forward was an unused substitute...
The post Kyogo braced for big Japan chance after an injury that will interest Celtic fans appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Joe Hart and Leigh Griffiths scenes that reached Celtic circles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173961</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-joe-hart-and-leigh-griffiths-banter-that-reached-celtic-circles/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart and Leigh Griffiths had plenty of chat to catch up on when they first met at Celtic in the summer of 2021. The...
The post The Joe Hart and Leigh Griffiths scenes that reached Celtic circles appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Hibernian boss credits Celtic move which opened doors to Scottish football]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173968</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/new-hibernian-boss-credits-celtic-move-which-opened-doors-to-scottish-football/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Hibernian manager Nick Montgomery has credited a move Celtic made in 2021 with opening doors from Australian to Scottish football. The move in question...
The post New Hibernian boss credits Celtic move which opened doors to Scottish football appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE JOCK STEIN YEARS (Part Two)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=55147</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-jock-stein-years-part-two/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T04:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Jock Stein made an extraordinary immediate impact on the Parkhead club when he returned as team boss in March 1965. The 38th anniversary of the passing of the Hoops great, at the age of 62, was marked by CQN on Sunday. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE,  author Alex Gordon, who has had fifteen Celtic works published, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TOM McADAM: GREAT UNCAPPED CELTS (Part Eight)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.cqnmagazine.com/?p=4982</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/tom-mcadam-great-uncapped-celts-part-eight/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T04:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CQN is turning the spotlight again on the Celtic players who never had the honour of playing for their country. Club legend Billy McNeill converted Tom McAdam from striker to centre-back – and the player was consistently immense following the dramatic career switch. He became a key man for the Hoops and a fans’ favourite [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aiden McGeady makes questionable claim about Celtic fans]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44128</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/11/aiden-mcgeady-makes-questionable-claim-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T22:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Celtic decided to bring back Brendan Rodgers to replace Ange Postecoglou in the Parkhead hot seat, the reaction of the fans was always going to be a major talking point. After all, the Northern Irishman had left a bitter taste in the mouths of many by leaving in the middle of the season to […]
Aiden McGeady makes questionable claim about Celtic fans - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers hero makes U-turn after Celtic win at Ibrox]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44125</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/11/rangers-hero-celtic-win-ibrox/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T21:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are just four games into the league season and nothing is even close to being settled. Yet, the mood in the camps of the two Glasgow giants are completely opposite. Celtic must be delighted following their win at Ibrox, a result that not many saw coming and has acted as a major confidence boost […]
Rangers hero makes U-turn after Celtic win at Ibrox - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star set for elite test at int'l level ahead of Champions League campaign; how to watch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173956</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-star-set-for-elite-test-at-international-level-ahead-of-champions-league-campaign-how-to-watch/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T20:20:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic captain Callum McGregor will go through excellent preparation for the Bhoys’ upcoming Champions League group stage with an appearance for Scotland on Tuesday night....
The post Celtic star set for elite test at int'l level ahead of Champions League campaign; how to watch appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feyenoord handed major problem for Celtic match]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44122</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/11/feyenoord-handed-problem-celtic-match/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T19:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will kick off their Champions League group stage campaign a little over a week later with an away trip to take on Feyenoord. Of course, the Hoops are the only Scottish club in Europe’s elite competition this season after the Rangers failed to make it, having been knocked out from the qualifiers by another […]
Feyenoord handed major problem for Celtic match - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 big changes Brendan Rodgers could make to Celtic team]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173953</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/4-big-changes-brendan-rodgers-could-make-to-celtic-team-vs-dundee/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T18:20:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re not far away from Celtic returning to action after the international break and everyone remains on a high from last week’s derby win. A...
The post 4 big changes Brendan Rodgers could make to Celtic team appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liverpool player tipped to join Celtic permanently in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44118</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/11/liverpool-player-join-celtic-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T17:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were busy during the summer transfer window even though they received quite a bit of criticism for the moves they did make. The club opted to go for highly rated youngsters rather than going for established and experienced names, even though there had been rumours about high-profile signings following the reappointment of Brendan Rodgers […]
Liverpool player tipped to join Celtic permanently in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Buzzing" £25m man explains his transfer decision after summer of Celtic rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173948</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/buzzing-kieran-tierney-explains-his-la-liga-decision-after-summer-of-celtic-and-arsenal-rumours/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T15:34:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kieran Tierney has spoken about his move to La Liga this season and the decision to leave Arsenal on loan, after a summer of rumours...
The post "Buzzing" £25m man explains his transfer decision after summer of Celtic rumours appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player completes transfer to Sheffield United]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44115</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/11/celtic-player-transfer-sheffield-united/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T13:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have continued to add talented youngsters to their side, in hopes that they would develop into first-team stars and eventually be transferred for much bigger fees. That is the strategy that the Hoops have followed for a long time now and it would come as a surprise to anyone who has supported the club […]
Celtic player completes transfer to Sheffield United - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revolving medical door, A-League coup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111838</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/revolving-medical-door-a-league-coup/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T11:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There appears to be a revolving door on the Lennoxtown medical room.  Just as we hoped to see players return from injury, Liel Abada picked up a strain on international duty with Israel and is expected to be out of action for a month.  We are not short of wingers in the squad, but we [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BROONY GUESSING GAME ENDS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111834</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/broony-guessing-game-ends/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T09:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SPECULATION that Scott Brown could be in the running for the Hibs manager’s job has finally come to an end. The Easter Road club issued a statement this morning confirming the appointment of Nick Montgomery as their new boss on a three-year contract. The 41-year-old head coach has left Aussie outfit Central Coast Mariners to replace [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports man names key signing Celtic failed to make]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44112</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/11/sky-sports-man-signing-celtic-failed/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T09:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were pretty active over the summer transfer window even if most fans were not happy that the club did not bring in any established and high-profile names. Instead, they continued to sign highly-rated youngsters with the potential to develop into key players at Parkhead. Let’s see if the strategy pays off or not. It […]
Sky Sports man names key signing Celtic failed to make - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘GOD WILLING, MATT SIGNS A NEW DEAL,’ CELTIC HERO REVEALS WISH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111831</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/god-willing-matt-signs-a-new-deal-celtic-hero-reveals-wish/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T07:23:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC hero Peter Grant hopes his old club make Matt O’Riley an offer he can’t refuse. The former Hoops midfield battler is an enthusiastic admirer of the Londoner after their time together at Fulham. Grant was in charge of youth development at the Craven Cottage club and had no hesitation in upgrading 15-year-old O’Riley to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NIGHT CELTIC HIT TEN – WITH ONLY TWO GOALSCORERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=96209</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/night-celtic-hit-ten-with-only-two-goalscorers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T04:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC hit hapless Hamilton Accies with a ten-goal hurricane exactly FIFTY-FIVE years ago as Bobby Lennox and Stevie Chalmers went on the rampage in an unforgettable evening in the east end of Glasgow. Jock Stein’s all-conquering Hoops heroes were unstoppable in a League Cup encounter as they annihilated their shell-shocked opponents with the lightning-swift raiders each [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE JOCK STEIN YEARS (Part One)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=55137</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-jock-stein-years-part-one/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T04:15:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE 38th anniversary of the passing of Celtic legend Jock Stein, at the age of 62, was marked by CQN yesterday. In an exciting in-depth analysis, CQN will spotlight the astounding Celtic managerial years of Big Jock, his extraordinary impact on the club and his remarkable legacy. Author Alex Gordon, who has written fifteen publications on [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HARRY HOOD: GREAT UNCAPPED CELTS (Part Seven)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.cqnmagazine.com/?p=4932</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/harry-hood-great-uncapped-celts-part-seven/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-11T04:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CQN is turning the spotlight once again on the Celtic players who never had the honour of playing for their country. Harry Hood was Jock Stein’s fourth major signing for the club – following Joe McBride, Willie Wallace and Tommy Callaghan – when he arrived from Clyde in 1969. He became a key player for [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero takes dig at Kris Boyd for hilarious miss]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44088</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/10/celtic-hero-kris-boyd-miss/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T23:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a not great time for Rangers fans and former players like Kris Boyd. They have been defeated again by a Celtic side and Chris Sutton couldn’t resist a joke on the occasion. The Hoops had a team of past stars entering the revived Scottish Masters alongside the Ibrox club, Hibernian and Hearts at […]
Celtic hero takes dig at Kris Boyd for hilarious miss - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Old comments go viral as Michael Beale on brink after losing to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44104</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/10/comments-michael-beale-losing-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T21:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Beale currently finds himself in an unenviable situation at Ibrox. He saw his side lose at home to an out-of-form Celtic last weekend, thanks to a superb strike from Kyogo Furuhashi. And the result, combined with their 7-3 aggregate loss to PSV in the UEFA Champions League qualifiers, appears to have left the manager […]
Old comments go viral as Michael Beale on brink after losing to Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Bargains of the millennium’ – Kenny Dalglish on Celtic signing]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44100</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/10/bargains-kenny-dalglish-celtic-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T19:30:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been pretty impressive when it comes to identifying talents in recent years. Of course, a large part of that credit has to go to Ange Postecoglou. The Australian’s arrival as manager in 2021 changed the transfer methods of the club to a club extent and they have spread their networks further and wider […]
‘Bargains of the millennium’ – Kenny Dalglish on Celtic signing - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday columns show Celtic have put Beale under severe pressure even a full week after derby win]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173943</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/sunday-columns-show-celtic-have-put-michael-beale-under-severe-pressure-even-a-full-week-after-derby-win/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T19:14:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s derby win last week has prompted an outcry across the city akin to their season-ending. A solitary goal from Kyogo Furuhashi has sent rival...
The post Sunday columns show Celtic have put Beale under severe pressure even a full week after derby win appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moussa Dembele shares beautiful Celtic throwback]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44096</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/10/moussa-dembele-shares-celtic-throwback/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T18:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moussa Dembele is one of the best players that Celtic have had in recent years. He was absolutely brilliant during his time at Parkhead and became an absolute fan favourite. He was a stalwart from Brendan Rodgers’ first stint as the manager of the club and continues to show his love for the Hoops to […]
Moussa Dembele shares beautiful Celtic throwback - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Like Rodgers has a new £10m player"; Chris Sutton excited by potential resurgence at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173940</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/like-rodgers-has-a-new-10m-player-chris-sutton-excited-by-potential-resurgence-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T16:38:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton is looking forward to seeing Reo Hatate back in the Celtic line-up after the international break, feeling he could take the Bhoys midfield...
The post "Like Rodgers has a new £10m player"; Chris Sutton excited by potential resurgence at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic icon Scott Brown replaced by sacked Hibs boss at Fleetwood; two Bhoys loanees impacted]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173925</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-icon-scott-brown-replaced-by-sacked-hibs-boss-at-fleetwood-two-bhoys-loanees-impacted/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T15:41:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fleetwood Town have announced that Lee Johnson, recently sacked by Hibernian, will be taking charge of the club following the departure of Scott Brown. Celtic...
The post Celtic icon Scott Brown replaced by sacked Hibs boss at Fleetwood; two Bhoys loanees impacted appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic pair rested as international demolition prompts managerial sacking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173920</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-pair-rested-as-international-demolition-prompts-managerial-sacking/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T15:11:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic duo Daizen Maeda and Kyogo Furuhashi only had a place on the bench for Japan’s victory over Germany this weekend, but got a close-up...
The post Celtic pair rested as international demolition prompts managerial sacking appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Ledley makes superb claim about Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44092</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/10/joe-ledley-claim-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T15:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have made an up-and-down start to this campaign. They won their first two games but the performances left a lot to be desired. Those were followed by a loss and a draw, which caused the fans to worry heading into the Glasgow Derby. But then, Brendan Rodgers’ side rose to the occasion and won […]
Joe Ledley makes superb claim about Celtic player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic hero finds a spark to pile misery on Rangers pundits and their nightmare week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173915</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-hero-finds-a-spark-to-pile-misery-on-rangers-pundits-and-their-nightmare-week/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T14:43:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not been a great week for those of a Rangers persuasion, has it? Celtic’s fine work in last Sunday’s derby, won by a Kyogo...
The post Former Celtic hero finds a spark to pile misery on Rangers pundits and their nightmare week appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Dalglish says Celtic got "one of the transfer bargains of the millennium" from £4m deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173907</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kenny-dalglish-says-celtic-got-one-of-the-transfer-bargains-of-the-millennium-from-4m-deal/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T13:54:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend Kenny Dalglish has lauded striker Kyogo Furuhashi after scoring yet another derby goal last weekend. The Japanese forward now has six goals in...
The post Kenny Dalglish says Celtic got "one of the transfer bargains of the millennium" from £4m deal appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic urged to bring back former striker on free transfer]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44085</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/10/celtic-urged-bring-back-former-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T12:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic could do with another striker at this point in time. There were suggestions that the club were looking for one towards the end of the summer transfer window but an addition up top was not made. Luis Palma is capable of playing in a more central role as well though, so perhaps he could […]
Celtic urged to bring back former striker on free transfer - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CROCKED CELT ‘SEEMS TO BE ANGRY’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111825</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/crocked-celt-seems-to-be-angry/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-10T09:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIEL ABADA has joined the growing Celtic injury list – and he could face a MONTH on the sidelines to add to Brendan Rodgers’ woes. The Israeli wing ace has been sent home from his country’s international squad after sustaining a knock in training. The Hoops medical staff will check the extent of the problem, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>