<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-10-10T12:19:22.503Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic eyeing move for Queens Park Rangers striker]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44811</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/10/celtic-queens-park-rangers-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T12:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are always on the lookout for young talents. We saw proof of that this summer. Despite knowing that they were in the Champions League group stages already, as a result of winning the Premiership last season, the club only went after highly-rated youngsters. The only player they signed with some top-level was Nat Phillips, […]
Celtic eyeing move for Queens Park Rangers striker - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[McGREGOR LEADS CAP PARADE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113026</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/mcgregor-leads-cap-parade/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T11:40:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CALLUM McGREGOR leads the procession of 13 Celtic players on international duty before the Premiership resumes a week on Saturday with a game against Hearts at Tynecastle. The Hoops skipper and Greg Taylor, who claimed his first goal of the season in the 3-1 win over Kilmarnock at the weekend, will be aiming to seal [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic star explains what makes Cameron Carter-Vickers so good]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177043</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-celtic-star-explains-what-makes-cameron-carter-vickers-so-good/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moritz Jenz has offered an interesting insight on Celtic defender Cameron Carter-Vickers. The German was a centre-back partner for the American on many occasions last...
The post Former Celtic star explains what makes Cameron Carter-Vickers so good appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Politics and sport]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113025</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/politics-and-sport/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T11:01:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m a friend of one of the Cowans from Glasgow, I got him a ticket for Celtic Park once.  For that family, for Humza Yousaf’s family and the countless more who are mourning, or terrified of what may happen next, I will not give you my hot takes on a situation so tragic and complex [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Every Celtic star still out injured and what we know about their return]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177112</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/every-celtic-star-still-to-return-from-injury-and-what-we-know-about-their-return/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic appear to be over the worst of the injury troubles that have provided a huge challenge at the start of the season. It has...
The post Every Celtic star still out injured and what we know about their return appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['It's mental': Barry Ferguson simply can't believe what has happened to one Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177108</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/its-mental-barry-ferguson-simply-cant-believe-what-has-happened-to-celtics-liam-scales/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T07:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Barry Ferguson has waxed lyrical about Liam Scales and how he has managed to turn his Celtic career around. Despite Brendan Rodgers being without key...
The post 'It's mental': Barry Ferguson simply can't believe what has happened to one Celtic player appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Right now': On-loan Celtic star Nat Phillips sent message he doesn't want to hear]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177053</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/right-now-on-loan-celtic-star-nat-phillips-sent-message-he-doesnt-want-to-hear/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Hartson says Nat Phillips doesn’t start for Brendan Rodgers’ Celtic despite his summer loan move from Liverpool. On paper, you could argue that the...
The post 'Right now': On-loan Celtic star Nat Phillips sent message he doesn't want to hear appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy seems to be loving life after Celtic; class photo and a current Hoops issue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177029</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/aaron-mooy-seems-to-be-loving-life-after-celtic-class-photo-and-a-current-hoops-issue/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy seems to be loving life after Celtic as he shared a class, relaxation photo on Instagram. The Australian international retired from football at...
The post Aaron Mooy seems to be loving life after Celtic; class photo and a current Hoops issue appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic supporters set for a nervy fortnight as defender's far from ideal status confirmed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177014</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-supporters-set-for-a-nervy-fortnight-as-far-from-ideal-carter-vickers-status-confirmed/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cameron Carter-Vickers has only just returned for Celtic, yet he is now away on international duty with the USA. National boss Gregg Berhalter has called...
The post Celtic supporters set for a nervy fortnight as defender's far from ideal status confirmed appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE LIFE O’RILEY: TEN ROLLERCOASTER DAYS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=113003</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-life-oriley-ten-rollercoaster-days/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T05:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY stepped onto soccer’s rollercoaster on Saturday September 30 for a breathtaking 10-day spin. The stylish 22-year-old midfielder kicked off the whirlwind sequence of events by signing a new four-year deal on the morning of the Premiership encounter at Motherwell. On pledging his future to the champions, O’Riley, who arrived at Parkhead in January [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I put my Celtic shirt on"; Moritz Jenz explains why he still loves the Hoops]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177035</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-put-my-celtic-shirt-on-moritz-jenz-explains-why-he-still-loves-the-hoops/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moritz Jenz still has a great love for Celtic almost a year on from his departure from the club. The German defender, now at VfL...
The post "I put my Celtic shirt on"; Moritz Jenz explains why he still loves the Hoops appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["We were all jealous"; Liam Scales gives forgotten Celtic star some huge encouragement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177020</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/we-were-all-jealous-liam-scales-gives-forgotten-celtic-star-some-huge-encouragement/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-10T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The remarkable rise of Liam Scales at Celtic has given one forgotten Hoops star some huge encouragement. Forward Johnny Kenny is currently out of the...
The post "We were all jealous"; Liam Scales gives forgotten Celtic star some huge encouragement appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player makes admission about Ange Postecoglou’s exit]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44806</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/09/celtic-player-ange-postecoglou-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T23:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate was one of Celtic’s best signings of the Ange Postecoglou era. Last season, he was unquestionably one of the best in the Scottish Premiership and did not look out of place against teams like Real Madrid and RB Leipzig in the Champions League either. It has been a different story since the Australian […]
Celtic player makes admission about Ange Postecoglou’s exit - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton criticises Celtic player for diving vs Kilmarnock]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44803</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/09/chris-sutton-celtic-player-diving/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T21:30:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton played several years of Celtic to great success during his career. Since then, he has gone to establish himself as a popular pundit and continues to enjoy prominence in that field these days. The Englishman is known for keeping things straight and he proved that recently by criticising one of the Hoops’ players. […]
Chris Sutton criticises Celtic player for diving vs Kilmarnock - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers left stunned by player he's found on return to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176809</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-stunned-by-liam-scales-celtic-form/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T20:49:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers reckons Liam Scales is one of the ‘biggest surprises’ of his management career after watching him perform so well for Celtic over the...
The post Brendan Rodgers left stunned by player he's found on return to Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate addresses how he felt about Ange Postecoglou exit & Brendan Rodgers arrival at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177007</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/reo-hatate-addresses-how-he-felt-about-ange-postecoglou-exit-and-brendan-rodgers-arrival-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T20:10:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate says he is focused and ready to perform under Brendan Rodgers, having been challenged by the manager to up his levels in a...
The post Reo Hatate addresses how he felt about Ange Postecoglou exit & Brendan Rodgers arrival at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Odd BBC segment suggests Celtic should have lost out despite what the rules say]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=177002</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/odd-bbc-segment-suggests-celtic-should-have-lost-out-despite-what-the-rules-say/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T19:29:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BBC Sportscene has suggested the officials in charge of Celtic’s match against Kilmarnock should have ignored the rules and disallowed Luis Palma’s superb first-half strike....
The post Odd BBC segment suggests Celtic should have lost out despite what the rules say appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic show interest in 'powerful' Championship attacker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176997</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-show-interest-in-powerful-championship-attacker/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T18:51:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have sent scouts to watch QPR attacker Sinclair Armstrong this season, a new report has claimed on Monday. Armstrong, still just 20, has made...
The post Report: Celtic show interest in 'powerful' Championship attacker appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Something has to be done"; Celtic chairman Peter Lawwell speaks out on concerning fixture issue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176991</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/something-has-to-be-done-celtic-chairman-peter-lawwell-speaks-out-on-concerning-fixture-issue/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T18:17:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic chairman Peter Lawwell has called on football organisations to assess the fixture calendar over the coming years as competitions and tournaments expand both at...
The post "Something has to be done"; Celtic chairman Peter Lawwell speaks out on concerning fixture issue appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Karamoko Dembele hits comeback trail with first goal since leaving Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176986</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/video-karamoko-dembele-hits-comeback-trail-with-first-goal-since-leaving-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T17:50:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic kid Karamoko Dembele is starting to make his mark at Blackpool after a big week that included his first league start for the...
The post Video: Karamoko Dembele hits comeback trail with first goal since leaving Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['He's been brave': McFadden says even Celtic star will be 'surprised' by his performances]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176970</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-think-liam-scales-will-be-surprised-celtic-sent-a-message-about-their-in-form-centre-back/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James McFadden thinks even Liam Scales himself will be ‘surprised’ by his performances for Celtic this season. If it wasn’t for the injuries at the...
The post 'He's been brave': McFadden says even Celtic star will be 'surprised' by his performances appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[39 unique items up for grabs in incredible Celtic auction this week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176963</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/39-unique-items-up-for-grabs-in-incredible-celtic-auction-this-week/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T16:50:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend Bertie Auld’s personal collection of football jerseys and programmes will be auctioned this coming Thursday 12th October. Fittingly, the event kicks off at...
The post 39 unique items up for grabs in incredible Celtic auction this week appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic move up places in global Opta Power Rankings after intense schedule of fixtures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176959</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-move-up-places-in-global-opta-power-rankings-after-intense-schedule-of-fixtures/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T16:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s last six fixtures since the September international break were full of ups and downs, home, away and abroad. The Bhoys entered a crucial stage...
The post Celtic move up places in global Opta Power Rankings after intense schedule of fixtures appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player withdraws from national squad with injury]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44800</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/09/celtic-player-withdraws-squad-injury/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T15:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have had more than their fair share of injury problems at the start of the season. Things had started to look up a bit in that regard in recent weeks as quite a few returned to action from the sidelines and others continued their recovery. But now, it looks like Brendan Rodgers might have […]
Celtic player withdraws from national squad with injury - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Concern for Celtic star after Monday update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176956</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-star-pulls-out-of-international-duty-due-to-injury/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T15:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star Daizen Maeda will not be travelling to Japan to take on Canada and Tunisia over the next eight days, his national team confirmed...
The post Concern for Celtic star after Monday update appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero tips Ange Postecoglou favourite for Rangers job]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44797</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/09/celtic-hero-ange-postecoglou-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T12:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A win over St Mirren at the weekend must have taken some pressure off the Rangers’ shoulders and now they are expected to appoint their next manager over the international break. The Ibrox club have a mountain to climb, with Celtic having built up a 7-point lead at the top of the Premiership table after […]
Celtic hero tips Ange Postecoglou favourite for Rangers job - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rivals fall]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112994</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rivals-fall/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T11:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not often Newco are happy to do Celtic a favour but they obliged yesterday. Conceding an early penalty and red card was too much for St Mirren, our nearest challengers, as they slipped seven points behind the champions. A resurgent Reo Hatate inspired Celtic to a comfortable win over Kilmarnock a day earlier, ensuring [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWOL CELT: THE PLOT THICKENS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112992</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/awol-celt-the-plot-thickens/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T10:10:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAVID TURNBULL was nowhere to be seen as Celtic beat Kilmarnock 3-1 at Parkhead at the weekend. Brendan Rodgers omitted the midfielder from his squad for the match against the Ayrshire visitors with summer recruits Odin Holm, a £2.5million purchase from Valarenga, and Paulo Bernardo, on a season-long loan from Benfica, getting the nod for [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS ON REO: ‘HE’S NOT YOUNG, HE’S 25’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112990</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-on-reo-hes-not-young-hes-25/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T09:08:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS reckons Reo Hatate has “come alive” for the first time since the Irishman’s arrival as second time-around Celtic manager in June. The Japanese midfielder has struggled with a loss of form and injury, but sparked in a convincing display in the 3-1 win over Kilmarnock at Parkhead at the weekend. The team boss [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['For a player I admire': Chris Sutton admits he's unhappy with Celtic star's actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176934</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/for-a-player-i-admire-chris-sutton-admits-hes-unhappy-with-celtic-star-reo-hataes-actions/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T08:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton has admitted that Reo Hatate dived during Celtic’s 3-1 win over Kilmarnock on Saturday. When Celtic were 2-0 up, Reo Hatate ran at...
The post 'For a player I admire': Chris Sutton admits he's unhappy with Celtic star's actions appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I CANNOT MAKE AN EXCUSE,’ HATATE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112959</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-cannot-make-an-excuse-hatate/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T07:34:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE insists his Man-of-the-Match performance in the 3-1 win over Kilmarnock will act as a turning point as he prepares to prove he can meet the demands of Brendan Rodgers. The Japanese midfielder kicked off the campaign on the substitutes’ bench while David Turnbull got the nod to start in the Flag-Day opener against [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIFTY-EIGHT YEARS AGO: THE ARRIVAL OF A LISBON LION – COURTESY OF THE No.62 TO AUCHENSHUGGLE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=83542</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/fifty-eight-years-ago-the-arrival-of-a-lisbon-lion-courtesy-of-the-no-62-to-auchenshuggle/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-09T06:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Jim Craig didn’t exactly hit the headlines when he made his first-team debut for Celtic FIFTY-EIGHT years ago. The cultured right-back got the nod from Jock Stein to play in the second leg of the European Cup-Winners’ Cup-tie against Dutch club Go Ahead Deventer on October 7 1965. The Hoops had won the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kris Boyd makes unexpected Celtic admission over Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44779</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/08/kris-boyd-celtic-admission-rangers-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T22:35:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kris Boyd can usually be counted on for some eyebrow-raising comments, especially when talking about Celtic or trying to debate with Chris Sutton. What’s unusual though is that the former Rangers player has actually made a very good comparison when talking about the two Glasgow giants recently. Clearly, it has been a disappointing start to […]
Kris Boyd makes unexpected Celtic admission over Rangers - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic player has been pictured back at Parkhead]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44790</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/08/former-celtic-player-pictured-parkhead/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T21:04:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been on a good run of form recently in domestic competitions. After stumbling out of the gates that had many questioning the reappointment of Brendan Rodgers, the Hoops have gotten things back on track. They are on a winning run in the league at the moment and sit 7 points clear at the […]
Former Celtic player has been pictured back at Parkhead - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['He is top-class': Michael Stewart says there is one thing certain about Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176916</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/he-is-top-class-michael-stewart-says-there-is-one-thing-certain-about-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T19:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Stewart says Celtic’s returning manager Brendan Rodgers is ‘top-class’. In the summer, when Ange Postecoglou, after winning the Treble with Celtic, headed for the...
The post 'He is top-class': Michael Stewart says there is one thing certain about Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£15 million Celtic player tipped to stay despite exit rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44787</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/08/15-million-celtic-player-tipped-stay/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T19:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a number of very talented players on their roster and the club have done a very good job when it comes to agreeing contract extensions with them recently. While Jota and Carl Starfelt did leave over the summer, the remaining core of the squad has stayed put and some have even improved under […]
£15 million Celtic player tipped to stay despite exit rumours - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur ready to sign former Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44778</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/08/tottenham-hotspur-former-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T18:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou is certainly making the most of his chance in the Premier League. The Australian left Celtic in the summer in order to join Tottenham Hotspur. Just like when he had made the move to Parkhead, there were a lot of people unsure about the appointment and many had counted him out even before […]
Tottenham Hotspur ready to sign former Celtic player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Lennoxtown prep that inspired Saturday's 84-touch Celtic masterclass]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176911</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-lennoxtown-prep-that-inspired-saturdays-84-touch-celtic-masterclass/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T17:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate was undoubtedly Celtic’s top performer against Kilmarnock on Saturday He not only won the man of the match award but he was also...
The post The Lennoxtown prep that inspired Saturday's 84-touch Celtic masterclass appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Dalglish delivers a sobering warning for new Rangers boss going up against Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176900</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kenny-dalglish-delivers-a-sobering-warning-for-new-rangers-boss-going-up-against-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T17:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Dalglish reckons Michael Beale’s failure to win derby matches is ultimately what cost him his job and has warned any new manager at Rangers...
The post Kenny Dalglish delivers a sobering warning for new Rangers boss going up against Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star blows away teammate with "scary piece of skill"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176907</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/liam-scales-blown-away-by-what-hes-just-witnessed-from-celtic-hero-reo-hatate/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T16:31:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liam Scales was self-admittedly left in awe of Celtic teammate Reo Hatate on Saturday after his blinding bit of skill that resulted in the Bhoys’...
The post Celtic star blows away teammate with "scary piece of skill" appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Embarrassing"; Kris Boyd left fuming by Rangers gap to Celtic, Sutton enjoys Sky debate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176902</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/embarrassing-kris-boyd-left-fuming-by-rangers-gap-to-celtic-sutton-enjoys-sky-debate/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T16:04:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kris Boyd was not a happy man on Sky Sports duties this afternoon, reviewing Rangers’ decision to part ways with manager Michael Beale. In a...
The post "Embarrassing"; Kris Boyd left fuming by Rangers gap to Celtic, Sutton enjoys Sky debate appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Derek McInnes can't help but praise 'first class' Celtic despite taking bitter VAR route]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176895</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/derek-mcinnes-cant-help-but-praise-first-class-celtic-despite-taking-bitter-var-route/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T15:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kilmarnock manager Derek McInnes was forced to admit Celtic were very good on Saturday afternoon after watching his side slip to a 3-1 defeat in...
The post Derek McInnes can't help but praise 'first class' Celtic despite taking bitter VAR route appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers delivers verdict on Luis Palma's first league start for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176892</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-delivers-verdict-on-luis-palmas-first-league-start-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T15:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers is giving Celtic’s new Bhoys the time and space required to adjust to life in Glasgow, but is increasingly hopeful players such as...
The post Brendan Rodgers delivers verdict on Luis Palma's first league start for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7-UP CELTS: 10-MAN SAINTS PAY THE PENALTY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112952</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/7-up-celts-10-man-saints-pay-the-penalty/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T13:07:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC remain seven points clear at the Premiership pinnacle after St Mirren failed to cut the gap in Paisley this afternoon. Stephen Robinson’s side had the opportunity to redice the advantage to four if they overcame struggling Ibrox opposition, reeling after back-to-back defeats from Aberdeen and Aris and without a manager after sacking Michael Beale [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic tried to sign player now valued at £50 million]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44775</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/08/celtic-tried-sign-player-50-million/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T13:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have done a pretty good job in recent years when it comes to identifying talents. Of course, the first season under the management of Ange Postecoglou was remarkable as they brought in players like Kyogo, Jota, Josip Juranovic, Giorgos Giakoumakis, Cameron Carter-Vickers, Reo Hatate, Daizen Maeda, Matt O’Riley, Liel Abada and more. They were […]
Celtic tried to sign player now valued at £50 million - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic end Scottish Premiership weekend 7 points clear after St Mirren and Rangers result]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176887</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-end-scottish-premiership-weekend-7-points-clear-after-st-mirren-and-rangers-result/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T12:59:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were four points clear of second place heading into the weekend’s Scottish Premiership action and have come out the other side with a seven-point...
The post Celtic end Scottish Premiership weekend 7 points clear after St Mirren and Rangers result appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC SCREEN GEMS SPARKLE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112938</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-screen-gems-sparkle/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T10:41:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC recovered superbly from the disappointment of the stoppage-time Champions League loss to Lazio to keep their eye on the main domestic prize. Kilmarnock had already derailed Brendan Rodgers’ side earlier in the season when they knocked the holders out of the Viaplay League Cup on the plastic pitch at Rugby Park. However, there was no [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trevor Sinclair taunts Rangers with Celtic message after win at Parkhead yesterday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176863</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/trevor-sinclair-taunts-rangers-with-celtic-message-after-win-over-kilmarnock/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trevor Sinclair has taunted managerless Rangers on Twitter after Celtic continued their strong start to the Premiership season. Brendan Rodgers’ side, after losing to Lazio...
The post Trevor Sinclair taunts Rangers with Celtic message after win at Parkhead yesterday appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SURPRISE PACKET’S £7.3m PROBLEM FOR RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112937</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/surprise-packets-7-3m-problem-for-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T10:10:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIAM SCALES is on course to land Brendan Rodgers with a £7.3million problem. The £600,000 recruit from Shamrock Rovers in August 2021 has forced in his way into the Celtic first team with some gutsy performances since he answered the club’s SOS following an injury pile-up only four games into the new season. The Hoops [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers suffer next manager blow as Celtic increase gap]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44772</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/08/rangers-next-manager-celtic-gap/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T10:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers are searching for their fourth manager in two years at the moment, as the Ibrox club struggle to deal with the brilliance of Celtic. Steven Gerrard, Giovanni van Bronckhorst and Michael Beale are the three to have occupied the managerial hot seat during that period of time. Who will be next? A number of […]
Rangers suffer next manager blow as Celtic increase gap - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HAPPY 1st, GREG]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112923</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/happy-1st-greg/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T09:09:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GREG TAYLOR was delighted to get off the mark with the third goal in Celtic’s 3-1 success over Kilmarnock at Parkhead yesterday. The left-back, who claimed three strikes last season, had to wait until the eighth Premiership outing for his first of the new campaign. The breakthrough effort arrived in the 82nd minute and arrived in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HAPPY 25th, ALISTAIR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112922</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/happy-25th-alistair/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T09:09:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THIS time last year, Alistair Johnston was playing for CF Montreal in the MLS and looking forward to featuring for Canada in the winter World Cup Finals in Qatar. Today, the adventurous right-back celebrates his 25th birthday as a Celtic player after winning three domestic honours in his first five months at Parkhead. It has [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HAPPY 700th, BRENDAN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112921</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/happy-700th-brendan/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T09:09:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS celebrated his 700th game as a manager in the 3-1 Premiership triumph over Kilmarnock at Parkhead. The win – his seventh in eight league outings since his June return to the champions – eased the Hoops to seven points clear of St Mirren and 10 ahead of the Ibrox outfit, with both those [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Improved dramatically’: Michael Stewart wowed by Celtic defender who can't be replaced]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176841</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/improved-dramatically-michael-stewart-wowed-by-celtic-defender-who-cant-be-replaced/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Stewart says Greg Taylor has ‘improved dramatically’ in the colours of Celtic. The 25-year-old helped Brendan Rodgers’ side to a 3-1 win over Kilmarnock...
The post ‘Improved dramatically’: Michael Stewart wowed by Celtic defender who can't be replaced appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart uses two words to describe Celtic Park after Kilmarnock win, hails 'brilliant' trio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176821</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/joe-hart-uses-two-words-to-describe-celtic-park-after-kilmarnock-win-hails-brilliant-trio/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T06:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart labelled Celtic Park as ‘very special’ via his Instagram story after the 3-1 win over Kilmarnock. After the heartbreak of midweek, Brendan Rodgers...
The post Joe Hart uses two words to describe Celtic Park after Kilmarnock win, hails 'brilliant' trio appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REO BRAVO: RODGERS HAILS ‘OUTSTANDING’ CELT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112910</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/reo-bravo-rodgers-hails-outstanding-celt/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-08T05:50:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE answered his critics with a dynamic display that deservely saw him win the Man-of-the-Match accolade in the 3-1 Premiership triumph over Kilmarnock at Parkhead. The Japanese midfielder sparked to life to shred the Rugby Park opponents, score a memorable goal and put in a complete performance in his first full outing of the campaign. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic should sign Manchester United player on loan]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44768</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/07/celtic-sign-manchester-united-loan/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T22:34:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic did sign quite a few players over the course of the summer even though many fans might not have been impressed with the fact that they stuck to signing youngsters rather than going for established and experienced players. Some have impressed since coming in while others have not. That’s just how it goes most […]
Celtic should sign Manchester United player on loan - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic-linked player could join Jose Mourinho’s AS Roma]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44764</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/07/celtic-linked-player-jose-mourinho-roma/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T21:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic might not have signed any high-profile players in the summer, but initial rumours had suggested that they were going to. The Hoops had been linked with some big names as well although ultimately, none of them ended up materialising. Let’s see if the situation changes in future transfer windows. One of the players Celtic […]
Celtic-linked player could join Jose Mourinho’s AS Roma - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BBC radio man tells the brutal truth about Celtic and Rangers; Ibrox fans won't like it]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176818</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/michael-stewart-tells-the-truth-about-celtic-and-rangers-ibrox-fans-wont-like-it/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T19:41:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BBC Radio Scotland pundit Michael Stewart says that Rangers are falling short of Celtic despite using them as a barometer, insisting that the Bhoys are...
The post BBC radio man tells the brutal truth about Celtic and Rangers; Ibrox fans won't like it appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BBC pundit claims Rangers fans struggle to accept Celtic are bigger]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44761</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/07/bbc-pundit-rangers-fans-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T18:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic put up three more points on the board with a 3-1 win over Kilmarnock at the weekend. Reo Hatate, Luis Palma and Greg Taylor were the three players on the scoresheet for the Hoops on the occasion. The result means that they are now ten points clear of the Rangers and seven clear of […]
BBC pundit claims Rangers fans struggle to accept Celtic are bigger - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers left unhappy and calls out VAR officials for strange decision at Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176811</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-left-unhappy-and-calls-out-var-officials-for-strange-decision-at-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T17:03:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers doesn’t think the goal Kilmarnock scored in Celtic’s 3-1 Scottish Premiership victory should have stood due to a foul on defender Greg Taylor....
The post Brendan Rodgers left unhappy and calls out VAR officials for strange decision at Celtic Park appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["That's what I want from him"; Brendan Rodgers lauds "outstanding" Celtic star after Killie win]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176803</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/thats-what-i-want-from-him-brendan-rodgers-lauds-outstanding-celtic-star-after-killie-win/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T16:37:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has been giving his reaction to today’s 3-1 victory over Kilmarnock, which has increased Celtic’s lead over the rest in the Scottish Premiership....
The post "That's what I want from him"; Brendan Rodgers lauds "outstanding" Celtic star after Killie win appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player proves doubters wrong vs Kilmarnock]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44758</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/07/celtic-player-doubters-wrong-kilmarnock/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T16:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Things never stand still at Celtic. The objective is to win every game and one or two bad performances are enough to bring even the best of players under the microscope. The Hoops are on a great run in the league at the moment, but they have struggled to get results in Europe once again. […]
Celtic player proves doubters wrong vs Kilmarnock - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luis Palma verdict, new partnership looks strong; 3 things we learned as Celtic beat Kilmarnock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176795</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/luis-palma-verdict-new-partnership-looking-strong-3-things-we-learned-as-celtic-beat-kilmarnock/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T15:59:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are seven points clear at the top of the Scottish Premiership after a strong 3-1 victory over Kilmarnock at Celtic Park this afternoon. Goals...
The post Luis Palma verdict, new partnership looks strong; 3 things we learned as Celtic beat Kilmarnock appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC 3 KILMARNOCK 1: THREE CHEERS AS REO LEADS THE WAY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112903</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-3-kilmarnock-1-three-cheers-as-reo-leads-the-way/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T15:56:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC 3 KILMARNOCK 1 CELTIC were singing and winning in the rain with an entertaining and well-deserved victory over Kilmarnock at a drenched Parkhead this afternoon. Reo Hatate, Luis Palma and Greg Taylor were the marksmen as the champions eased seven points clear of St Mirren and 10 ahead of the Ibrox outfit who meet [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic v Kilmarnock, GG Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112901</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-kilmarnock-gg-live-updates/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T13:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 15.00. Welcome GG’s (Ronnie’s) daughter Pamela and her family to Celtic Park today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic XI confirmed; 2 changes, big return, broadcast details, instant reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176792</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-vs-kilmarnock-confirmed-2-changes-big-return-broadcast-details-instant-reaction/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T12:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manager Brendan Rodgers has named his Celtic team vs Kilmarnock for today’s Scottish Premiership clash at Celtic Park. The full match squad is as follows:...
The post Celtic XI confirmed; 2 changes, big return, broadcast details, instant reaction appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: CCV STARTS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112898</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-ccv-starts/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T12:50:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CAMERON CARTER-VICKERS will start his first Premiership game in two months when he lines up against Kilmarnock at Parkhead today. The central defender has been missing from the league side since being removed at half-time through injury in the 3-1 win over Aberdeen at Pittodrie on August 13. Carter-Vickers made his comeback as a second-half [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss tips Premiership manager for Rangers job]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44755</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/07/celtic-premiership-manager-rangers-job/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T12:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has already outlasted one Rangers manager since returning to Celtic earlier in the summer. Michael Beale was shown the exit door following their 3-1 defeat at the hands of Aberdeen, which saw the side fall seven points behind the Hoops in the league. It remains to be seen who ends up taking the […]
Celtic boss tips Premiership manager for Rangers job - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best is to come as Celtic fans wait for a proper look at summer arrival]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176784</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-best-is-to-come-as-celtic-fans-wait-for-a-proper-look-at-paulo-bernardo/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic support are still waiting for their first proper look at summer arrival Paulo Bernardo. The Portuguese youth international was an exciting signing late...
The post The best is to come as Celtic fans wait for a proper look at summer arrival appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star says relationship with Brendan Rodgers is slightly different from first spell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176719</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-star-says-relationship-with-brendan-rodgers-is-slightly-different-from-first-spell/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic captain Callum McGregor says that his relationship with Brendan Rodgers has changed slightly from their first spell together. The midfielder was still a young...
The post Celtic star says relationship with Brendan Rodgers is slightly different from first spell appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 changes, attacking switch; Celtic Predicted XI vs Kilmarnock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176774</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/3-changes-attacking-switch-celtic-predicted-xi-vs-kilmarnock/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic take on Kilmarnock in the Scottish Premiership this afternoon, knowing a win will send them further clear of St Mirren and Rangers ahead of...
The post 3 changes, attacking switch; Celtic Predicted XI vs Kilmarnock appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DAVID TURNBULL MYSTERY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112891</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/david-turnbull-mystery/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T09:11:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAVID TURNBULL kicked off this season in the Celtic first team ahead of Reo Hatate. The gifted midfielder proved Brendan Rodgers’ judgement correct when he netted a double in the Premiership opening-day 4-2 win over Ross County at Parkhead on August 5. Turnbull, though, was anchored among the substitutes in the 2-1 Champions League loss [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The strange Kilmarnock factor that leaves Celtic not knowing what to expect]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176743</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/the-strange-kilmarnock-factor-that-leaves-celtic-not-knowing-what-to-expect/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kilmarnock are the only Scottish side to have beaten Celtic so far this season. We may only be at the start of October and seven...
The post The strange Kilmarnock factor that leaves Celtic not knowing what to expect appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate talks Rodgers, injury, supporters and Celtic happiness in rare interview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176772</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/reo-hatate-talks-rodgers-injury-supporters-and-celtic-happiness-in-rare-interview/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate has offered some interesting insight in a rare Celtic TV interview. The Japanese midfielder agreed a new five-year contract last week, committing his...
The post Reo Hatate talks Rodgers, injury, supporters and Celtic happiness in rare interview appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star isn't shying away from the revenge factor at play this weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176727</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/callum-mcgregor-isnt-shying-away-from-the-celtic-revenge-factor-this-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor seems to have revenge on his mind for Celtic against Kilmarnock this weekend. The Hoops skipper was part of the side that went...
The post Celtic star isn't shying away from the revenge factor at play this weekend appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: PERENNIAL LOSER IN THE KILLING FIELDS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112887</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-perennial-loser-in-the-killing-fields/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T08:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE tag of perennial loser is not one that is likely to be welcomed by Brendan Rodgers. The Celtic boss demands to be judged at the elevated level of the Champions League and he will not need any reminding his record in this arena is simply awful. Rodgers was battered by disturbing stats in the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["How about an ugly goal"; Chris Sutton has some thoughts after Celtic Park visit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176763</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/how-about-an-ugly-goal-chris-sutton-has-some-thoughts-after-celtic-park-visit/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T07:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton was at Celtic Park on Wednesday to see the Hoops go down to Lazio. It was a gutting climax for us all as...
The post "How about an ugly goal"; Chris Sutton has some thoughts after Celtic Park visit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers explains contentious Celtic substitution against Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176734</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-explains-contentious-celtic-substitution-against-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has explained his decision to bring Cameron Carter-Vickers on against Lazio. The American was introduced to the action for Nat Phillips during the...
The post Brendan Rodgers explains contentious Celtic substitution against Lazio appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["He has qualities"; Celtic boss Rodgers gets involved in next Rangers manager chat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176757</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/he-has-qualities-celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-gets-involved-in-next-rangers-manager-chat/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers has offered some of his own opinion in chat about who the next manager of Rangers should be. Rodgers didn’t take...
The post "He has qualities"; Celtic boss Rodgers gets involved in next Rangers manager chat appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic vs Kilmarnock status as severe weather warning issued for Glasgow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176751</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/the-celtic-vs-kilmarnock-status-as-severe-weather-warning-issued-for-glasgow/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are scheduled to face Kilmarnock on Saturday, amid a severe weather warning for Glasgow and other parts of Scotland. On Friday evening, police urged...
The post The Celtic vs Kilmarnock status as severe weather warning issued for Glasgow appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC v KILMARNOCK: 5-MINUTE QUIZ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112873</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-kilmarnock-5-minute-quiz-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T04:45:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC can extend their advantage at the top of the Premiership today when they take on Kilmarnock at Parkhead. The champions’ nearest challengers play in Paisley at noon tomorrow when St Mirren face Ibrox opposition with Steven Davis in chage after the sacking of Michael Beale following the 3-1 thumping from Aberdeen last weekend. How [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE: STAND AND DELIVER]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112870</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/reo-hatate-stand-and-deliver/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-07T04:30:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE failed to deliver in the Celtic engine room during the anticlimactic 2-1 Champions League loss against Lazio at Parkhead in midweek. Brendan Rodgers urgently required all his players functioning at their highest levels in a must-win encounter, but the Japanese midfielder, so influential when he is at the peak of his powers, didn’t [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers drops hint about long-term Celtic future]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44752</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/06/brendan-rodgers-drops-hint-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T22:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Ange Postecoglou left the club in order to join Tottenham Hotspur in the summer, merely days after winning the domestic treble, Celtic were put in a difficult position. They were losing a world-class manager, who had guided them to five trophies in two years, exceeding all expectations. Thus, they needed a suitable replacement. And […]
Brendan Rodgers drops hint about long-term Celtic future - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Colin Kazim-Richards calls former Celtic boss the ‘worst coach’]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44746</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/06/colin-kazim-richards-calls-former-celtic-boss-worst-coach/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T21:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colin Kazim-Richards was only at Celtic for some months. He joined the club in early February of 2016 and was gone that very summer. Even in that short spell of time, one manager was able to make quite an impression on the former Turkish international and not the kind he would have been hoping for. […]
Colin Kazim-Richards calls former Celtic boss the ‘worst coach’ - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two returns, potential first league start; Celtic team news ahead of Kilmarnock test]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176714</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/two-returns-potential-first-league-start-celtic-team-news-ahead-of-kilmarnock-test/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T20:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s squad is getting stronger as the weeks pass and Brendan Rodgers is able to call upon a number of players that he couldn’t last...
The post Two returns, potential first league start; Celtic team news ahead of Kilmarnock test appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The uncomfortable Celtic reality for Rangers that doesn't change whoever replaces Michael Beale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176711</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-uncomfortable-celtic-reality-for-rangers-that-doesnt-change-whoever-replaces-michael-beale/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T19:36:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers may have made a managerial change earlier in the season than they did last year, but it doesn’t change the fact that only a...
The post The uncomfortable Celtic reality for Rangers that doesn't change whoever replaces Michael Beale appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers sent Celtic message amid Frank Lampard talk]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44742</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/06/rangers-celtic-message-frank-lampard/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T19:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It remains to be seen who the next manager of the Rangers will be. The Ibrox club recently decided to part ways with Michael Beale after a bad start to the campaign that left them seven points behind Celtic in the league after just the first seven games. As a result, they now begin their […]
Rangers sent Celtic message amid Frank Lampard talk - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic youths lauded after impressing at elite Euro level]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176706</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/celtic-youths-lauded-after-impressing-at-elite-euro-level/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T19:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic B coach Darren O’Dea was left very impressed with his young Hoops team following their match against Lazio U19s on Wednesday. A late Mackenzie...
The post Celtic youths lauded after impressing at elite Euro level appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hollywood star spotted at Celtic Park as he shares picture]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44738</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/06/hollywood-star-celtic-park-picture/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T18:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is musicians who have grabbed most of the headlines in recent times when it comes to supporting Celtic. Of course, Rod Stewart is arguably the most famous fan that the Hoops have these days. Lewis Capaldi is well known for his support of the club as well. Recently, even Macklemore was seen performing on […]
Hollywood star spotted at Celtic Park as he shares picture - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Superb Celtic efforts recognised by FIFA and time is running out to get involved]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176701</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/superb-celtic-efforts-recognised-by-fifa-and-time-is-running-out-to-get-involved/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T17:12:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s treble success in 2022/23 is the basis for Ange Postecoglou’s nomination as the Best FIFA Men’s Coach Of The Year at their annual awards...
The post Superb Celtic efforts recognised by FIFA and time is running out to get involved appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton delivers grim Celtic Champions League verdict]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176697</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-delivers-grim-celtic-champions-league-verdict/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:17:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker Chris Sutton reckons the Bhoys will struggle to even make third position in Group E of the UEFA Champions League after losing...
The post Chris Sutton delivers grim Celtic Champions League verdict appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hearts explanation for shockingly low Celtic Tynecastle ticket allocation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176692</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-hearts-explanation-for-shockingly-low-celtic-tynecastle-ticket-allocation/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T15:21:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There will be just 576 Celtic supporters at Tynecastle for the upcoming Scottish Premiership match against Hearts, it was confirmed by the club today. The...
The post The Hearts explanation for shockingly low Celtic Tynecastle ticket allocation appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No surprises as Derek McInnes calls for 'aggressive' Kilmarnock at Celtic Park on Saturday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176688</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/no-surprises-as-derek-mcinnes-calls-for-aggressive-kilmarnock-at-celtic-park-on-saturday/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T14:55:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kilmarnock boss Derek McInnes reckons his team can pull off another shock victory against Celtic this weekend, after dumping the Bhoys out of the Scottish...
The post No surprises as Derek McInnes calls for 'aggressive' Kilmarnock at Celtic Park on Saturday appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO CRACKERJACK ACCOLADE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112875</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kyogo-crackerjack-accolade/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T13:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO FURUHASHI’S spectacular volley at Ibrox has won the Premiership Goal of the Month for September. The Japanese hitman was favourite for the accolade following his winner in Govan when he lashed a first-time drive away from the groping fingers of Jack Butland for the points-clincher just before the interval. It was Kyogo’s sixth goal against [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[International mention shows how far midfielder has come at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176680</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/international-mention-shows-how-far-matt-oriley-has-come-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder Matt O’Riley won’t be featuring for Denmark during the upcoming international break. The former MK Dons man has arguably been our best player...
The post International mention shows how far midfielder has come at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon confirms Leeds United’s interest in Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44735</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/06/neil-lennon-confirms-leeds-united-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T13:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a number of very talented players in their squad right now who have been linked with moves away from the club. It remains to be seen what the future holds for them. The Hoops did lose two regular starters over the summer in the form of Jota and Carl Starfelt. But other than […]
Neil Lennon confirms Leeds United’s interest in Celtic player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scotland's precarious UEFA coefficient position; a concern for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176668</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/scotlands-precarious-uefa-coefficient-position-a-concern-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scotland and Celtic find themselves in a precarious place in the UEFA coefficient standings after another disappointing week. The Hoops played their second European fixture...
The post Scotland's precarious UEFA coefficient position; a concern for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Much-loved Celtic stars set to face-off in tasty international clash next week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176653</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/much-loved-celtic-stars-set-to-face-off-in-tasty-international-clash-next-week/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a tasty-looking international clash next week that is set to have some current Celtic stars facing each other. The fixture between Japan and...
The post Much-loved Celtic stars set to face-off in tasty international clash next week appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Containing consequences]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112866</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/containing-consequences/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T11:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It still stings, but we need to park the pain of defeat and get back on the horse tomorrow.  Reversals can become infectious, they can drive confidence into a spiral. For my money, this phenomenon in part formed Brendan’s reaction after the game on Wednesday. He was relatively upbeat, containing the consequences by saying whatever [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio vlogger shares cool Celtic Park footage from the night that could have been]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176674</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/lazio-vlogger-shares-cool-celtic-park-footage-from-the-night-that-could-have-been/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seeing 58,000 Celtic fans going wild from the away end is a pretty cool sight. Okay, there’s a fair chance you don’t want to hear...
The post Lazio vlogger shares cool Celtic Park footage from the night that could have been appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston's referee theory that is making things difficult for Celtic in Europe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176644</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alistair-johnstons-referee-theory-that-is-making-things-difficult-for-celtic-in-europe/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston and Celtic are experiencing many difficulties when moving from domestic to European football. The Canadian is part of a Hoops side that have...
The post Alistair Johnston's referee theory that is making things difficult for Celtic in Europe appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss explains questionable decision vs Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44727</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/10/06/celtic-boss-explains-decision-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T10:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was the same old story for Celtic in Europe once again, as they lost 2-1 to Lazio at Parkhead despite being the better side in almost all departments for the majority of the game. The Hoops went ahead early through Kyogo Furuhashi, who ended his goal drought in the Champions League. But then, they […]
Celtic boss explains questionable decision vs Lazio - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PEDRO GOAL EXPLAINED: VAR TOO LATE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112856</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/pedro-goal-explained-var-too-late/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T09:36:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE questions over the legality of Pedro’s stoppage-time winner at Parkhead in midweek raged long after the final whistle and Celtic’s agonising 2-1 Champions League loss to Lazio. The header in the sixth minute of added-on time looked like a decidedly close call, but, curiously, there was no intervention from VAR. Live TV pictures were [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Friday October 6: Cheer Up Stevie D]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18515</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18515"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T08:35:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The disappointment in the result against Lazio might take a while to go away, and with a double header against group favourites Atletico Madrid ahead,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Malph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GREAT EXPECTATIONS: ‘I EXPECT HIM TO GET BETTER AND BETTER,’ BOSS VERDICT ON PALMA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112852</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/great-expectations-i-expect-him-to-get-better-and-better-boss-verdict-on-palma/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T07:35:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LUIS PALMA is standing by for his first start at Parkhead when Celtic take on Kilmarnock tomorrow afternoon. The 23-year-old winger is still settling in at the champions following his £3.5million switch from Greek outfit Aris Thessaloniki just before the September 1 transfer deadline. Brendan Rodgers predicts big things from the exciting raider who was [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers thinks the Celtic support showed something at the end of Lazio loss]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176630</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-thinks-the-celtic-support-showed-something-at-the-end-of-lazio-loss/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers thinks the Celtic support gave him a good indication of the team’s performance against Lazio. It was a tough midweek defeat for the...
The post Brendan Rodgers thinks the Celtic support showed something at the end of Lazio loss appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘WE’LL RECOVER,’ VOWS RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112847</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/well-recover-vows-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T06:44:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS insists Celtic have moved on from their Viaplay League Cup exit against Kilmarnock at Rugby Park in August. The Hoops boss saw the holders crash out of the competition in only the third game of his return to the club. Rodgers’ remarkable sequence of 24 successive knock-out wins during his seven consecutive trophy [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star shares the dressing room feeling after late Lazio sickener]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176637</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alistair-johnston-shares-the-celtic-dressing-room-feeling-after-late-lazio-sickener/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston has shared the feeling inside the Celtic dressing room after our late sickener against Lazio. The Canadian was one of the players closest...
The post Celtic star shares the dressing room feeling after late Lazio sickener appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC TRIO CALL-UP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112844</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-trio-call-up/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T05:51:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A TRIO of Celtic kids have been called into the Republic of Ireland squad for the European Under-21 Championship qualifier against Latvia a week today. Top prospects winger Rocco Vata, central defender Bosun Lawal and sriker Johnny Kenny will be involved in the 1pm kick-off as the Irish travel to Riga following back-to-back wins over [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers explains why Celtic supporters haven't seen more of summer signing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176621</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-explains-why-celtic-supporters-havent-seen-more-of-luis-palma-so-far/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has been speaking about Luis Palma since our UEFA Champions League loss to Lazio. The Honduran winger, signed from Aris Thessaloniki at the...
The post Brendan Rodgers explains why Celtic supporters haven't seen more of summer signing appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The media go down a very obvious route with Rodgers ahead of weekend Celtic clash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=176659</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/the-media-go-down-a-very-obvious-route-with-brendan-rodgers-ahead-of-celtic-vs-kilmarnock/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T05:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers won’t speak to the media on Friday ahead of Celtic vs Kilmarnock this weekend. Due to the short turnaround between the midweek loss...
The post The media go down a very obvious route with Rodgers ahead of weekend Celtic clash appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS’ UNWANTED HAT-TRICK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=112837</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-unwanted-hat-trick/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T04:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS completed an unwanted hat-trick in the Champions League Group E loss to Lazio in midweek. The 2-1 reverse against the Italians was the Celtic’s manager’s third consecutive defeat in European competition at Parkhead. The latest setback follows the 2-1 flop in front of the Hoops fans against RB Salzburg in the Europa League [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>