<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-09-06T18:12:29.329Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Japan picture is looking better for Celtic during this international break]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173507</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-positive-japan-picture-for-celtic-during-this-international-break/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The picture is positive for Celtic and our Japan stars during this international break. Things haven’t always been straightforward for our Japanese contingent over the...
The post The Japan picture is looking better for Celtic during this international break appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero already tips summer signing for future exit]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43957</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/06/celtic-hero-summer-signing-future-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T16:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic made nine additions over the course of the recently concluded summer transfer window. A lot of fans were not happy with the new arrivals though as the club mostly stuck to making ‘project’ signings rather than bringing in proven and experienced players who could make a positive impact on the team from the get-go. […]
Celtic hero already tips summer signing for future exit - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen McGinn wants Celtic to make a move in derby allocation mess; reality is different]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173554</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/stephen-mcginn-wants-celtic-to-make-a-move-in-derby-allocation-mess-reality-is-different/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen McGinn has shared some interesting thoughts on the ongoing derby allocation mess between Celtic and Rangers. The Hoops came out on top at Ibrox...
The post Stephen McGinn wants Celtic to make a move in derby allocation mess; reality is different appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wednesday UWCL joy as Celtic secure historic European result]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173598</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/wednesday-uwcl-joy-as-celtic-secure-historic-european-result/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T13:54:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic FC Women have picked up their first-ever win in the UEFA Women’s Champions League with a superb 1-0 result against Brondby this afternoon. Club...
The post Wednesday UWCL joy as Celtic secure historic European result appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Class Joe Hart interview clip emerges on Celtic social media]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173582</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/class-joe-hart-interview-clip-emerges-on-celtic-social-media/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A class clip from a recent interview with Joe Hart has emerged on Celtic social media. The Hoops goalkeeper has been a terrific presence ever...
The post Class Joe Hart interview clip emerges on Celtic social media appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Up against it; the number of tickets Celtic will receive for Feyenoord away clash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173584</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/up-against-it-the-number-of-tickets-celtic-will-receive-for-feyenoord-away-clash/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T11:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a little bit scary to think that Celtic will open their UEFA Champions League campaign against Feyenoord in less than two weeks. By the...
The post Up against it; the number of tickets Celtic will receive for Feyenoord away clash appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summer 23 Transfer Window assessment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111819</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/summer-23-transfer-window-assessment/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T11:02:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a busy transfer window, Celtic signed nine new players and sold four from the first team squad.  Central defence saw two planned arrivals: Maik Nawrocki (22) and Gustaf Lagerbielke (23), and the departure of Carl Starfelt (28).  Starfelt’s two-year partnership with Cameron Carter-Vickers was remarkably successful.  They only once experience defeat in a domestic [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some interesting takeaways as Sky Sports announce latest batch of Celtic fixtures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173539</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/some-interesting-takeaways-as-sky-sports-announce-latest-batch-of-celtic-fixtures/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There were a few interesting takeaways as Sky Sports announced their latest batch of Celtic fixtures on Tuesday. Brendan Rodgers‘ Hoops have been on the...
The post Some interesting takeaways as Sky Sports announce latest batch of Celtic fixtures appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["The status of Celtic is huge"; international boss confirms Hoops growth in far-flung country]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173524</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-status-of-celtic-is-huge-international-boss-confirms-pleasing-hoops-growth-in-far-flung-country/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jurgen Klinsmann says that Celtic have become a big deal in South Korea. The former Bayern Munich and Tottenham Hotspur forward is now in charge...
The post "The status of Celtic is huge"; international boss confirms Hoops growth in far-flung country appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Nothing': Rodgers compares Celtic-Rangers atmosphere to English football's biggest rivalry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173562</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/nothing-like-brendan-rodgers-compares-celtic-rangers-atmosphere-to-liverpool-manchester-united/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T08:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers says there is ‘nothing like’ the atmosphere in Celtic and Rangers games, as he compared it to Liverpool and Manchester United. Prior to...
The post 'Nothing': Rodgers compares Celtic-Rangers atmosphere to English football's biggest rivalry appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big day arrives for Celtic in UEFA Women's Champions League; format explained, how to watch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173545</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/big-day-arrives-for-celtic-in-uefa-womens-champions-league-format-explained-how-to-watch/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The big day has arrived for Celtic as they get their UEFA Women’s Champions League campaign underway on Wednesday. Fran Alonso‘s side are in Oslo...
The post Big day arrives for Celtic in UEFA Women's Champions League; format explained, how to watch appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I will always be very grateful"; star finally opens up on summer Celtic departure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173500</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/carl-starfelt-has-some-great-things-to-say-about-celtic-reaction-to-rodgers-jacynta-comments/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carl Starfelt has had some great things to say about Celtic as he finally opened up on his summer departure from the club. The Swedish...
The post "I will always be very grateful"; star finally opens up on summer Celtic departure appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic stance on controversial government proposals; strong Scottish football message sent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173531</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-celtic-stance-on-controversial-government-proposals-strong-scottish-football-message-sent/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic stance on some recent government proposals on supporters’ buses has become clear. On Tuesday, Scottish football fans were left incensed after a consultation...
The post The Celtic stance on controversial government proposals; strong Scottish football message sent appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jurgen Klinsmann shares what Brendan Rodgers told him about Celtic trio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173515</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/jurgen-klinsmann-shares-what-brendan-rodgers-told-him-about-celtic-trio/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jurgen Klinsmann has been speaking about his relationship with Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers. As current boss of South Korea, the former VfB Stuttgart and Tottenham...
The post Jurgen Klinsmann shares what Brendan Rodgers told him about Celtic trio appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC: DEAL OR NO DEAL? THE HILARIOUS AND THE HYSTERICAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111798</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-deal-or-no-deal-the-hilarious-and-the-hysterical/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T05:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THERE was speculation at the weekend that Kasper Schmeichel may emerge as a target for Brendan Rodgers. The link was that the Danish international, a free agent after being released by Nice, had played for the Irishman during their time together at Leicester City. CQN ignored the reports. Frankly, we didn’t believe them and saw [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS 32 RANGERS 7]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111794</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-32-rangers-7/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T04:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS reminded his Celtic players he knew how to win at Ibrox before Sunday’s confrontation. And the second time-around Hoops boss emphasised those words by sending out a determined bunch of Hoops stars who battled in front of a hostile 50,000 crowd to claim a 1-0 victory courtesy of a sensational volley from Kyogo [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IAN YOUNG: GREAT UNCAPPED CELTS (Part Two)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.cqnmagazine.com/?p=4760</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ian-young-great-uncapped-celts-part-two/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-06T04:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CQN is turning the spotlight again on the Celtic players who never had the honour of playing for their country. Ian Young, the solid, unspectacular right-back who sadly passed away in December 2019 at the age of 76, never got the nod to get into a Scotland squad. Young rarely hit the headlines with his [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon makes superb Champions League claim about Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43934</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/05/neil-lennon-champions-league-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T22:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the dust settles after Sunday’s away win for Celtic at Ibrox over the Rangers, there’s now a great set of opportunities ahead for the squad. One of those is to successfully navigate their way through the Champions League group stages. And Neil Lennon reckons that the team can do well in Europe. The immediate […]
Neil Lennon makes superb Champions League claim about Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou was offered chance to sign Celtic favourite]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43948</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/05/ange-postecoglou-sign-celtic-favourite/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T20:30:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Ange Postecoglou left Celtic in order to join Tottenham Hotspur just days after guiding the Hoops to a domestic treble, it was clearly a major blow for the club. The Australian was fantastic during his two seasons at Parkhead and won five trophies. Since leaving, he has already proven his mettle in London, as […]
Ange Postecoglou was offered chance to sign Celtic favourite - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Big mentality’: Andy Walker thinks Celtic have a player whose mindset is unmatched]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173484</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/big-mentality-andy-walker-thinks-celtic-have-a-player-whose-mindset-is-unmatched/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andy Walker has lauded the ‘big mentality’ of Celtic star Kyogo Furuhashi after he scored yet another goal against Rangers. Kyogo’s goalscoring record against Rangers...
The post ‘Big mentality’: Andy Walker thinks Celtic have a player whose mindset is unmatched appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Podence’s Olympiacos move raises Celtic questions]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43946</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/05/daniel-podence-olympiacos-move-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T19:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The mood around Celtic Park is very positive right now after a Glasgow Derby win away at Ibrox at the weekend. There is a long season ahead though and Brendan Rodgers’ side still need to improve a lot if they are to win the two remaining domestic competitions and make an impact in the Champions […]
Daniel Podence’s Olympiacos move raises Celtic questions - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ajeti and Soro exits leave just two pressing Celtic contract issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173443</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ajeti-and-soro-exits-leave-just-two-imminent-celtic-contract-issues/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Albian Ajeti and Ismaila Soro have now both departed Celtic after difficult spells in Scotland. The pair both arrived in 2020 — Soro in January,...
The post Ajeti and Soro exits leave just two pressing Celtic contract issues appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers contact manager as Michael Beale loses to Celtic again]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43942</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/05/rangers-contact-manager-beale-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T17:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Beale must be standing on shaky ground at Ibrox after losing another game to Celtic. The manager does not have a good record in Glasgow Derbies at all. On top of that, they were handed a 5-1 defeat by PSV in midweek, which saw them being knocked out of the Champions League qualifiers. As […]
Rangers contact manager as Michael Beale loses to Celtic again - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three reasons to feel very excited about Celtic after the international break]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173457</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/three-reasons-to-feel-very-excited-about-celtic-after-the-international-break/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s season was finally getting underway just as the first international break of the campaign arrived. As the team celebrated on the Ibrox pitch amid...
The post Three reasons to feel very excited about Celtic after the international break appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carl Starfelt admits he was taken aback by Celtic boss’ comments]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43938</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/05/carl-starfelt-celtic-boss-comments/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T16:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carl Starfelt was a stalwart in the heart of defence for Celtic during Ange Postecoglou’s run as the manager of the club. It feels like he often did not get the credit that he deserved for his contributions to the team. They did not lose a single league game in which he and Cameron Carter-Vickers […]
Carl Starfelt admits he was taken aback by Celtic boss’ comments - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Champions League Tickets]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58365</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/champions-league-tickets/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T11:18:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A week is a long time in football and what a week it was finished off in style at Ibrox by Kyogo. What a goal and a performance from MOTM Liam Scales. Nothing hurts them more than a Fenian running the show. We also saw the transfer window closed and another 3 players added to […]
The post Champions League Tickets appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The superb moment Todd Cantwell was shown up by Celtic star]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173421</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/the-superb-moment-todd-cantwell-was-shown-up-by-celtic-star/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a rough afternoon for Todd Cantwell on Sunday against Celtic. The Rangers midfielder struggled badly to impact the game at Ibrox as Brendan...
The post The superb moment Todd Cantwell was shown up by Celtic star appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Football fans and fragile self-esteem]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111807</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/football-fans-and-fragile-self-esteem/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T11:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you can withhold pressure from the baying mob after poor football results, you are built from strong stuff. Looking in from the outside, it is easy to understand why sacking a manager should never be done on the back of one poor run of form, least of all a manager’s first poor run of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sead Haksabanovic makes international call after Celtic exit; manager doesn't seem happy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173472</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/sead-haksabanovic-makes-international-call-after-celtic-exit-manager-doesnt-seem-happy/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T10:43:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player Sead Haksabanovic won’t be featuring for Montenegro during the upcoming international break. The winger is still on our books but won’t be playing...
The post Sead Haksabanovic makes international call after Celtic exit; manager doesn't seem happy appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic announce UEFA Champions League package details; price, deadline, 2022 comparison]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173475</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-announce-uefa-champions-league-package-details-price-deadline-2022-comparison/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T10:14:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have announced details for the upcoming UEFA Champions League three-match package. The Hoops are back in the group stage of the Champions League for...
The post Celtic announce UEFA Champions League package details; price, deadline, 2022 comparison appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alan Shearer criticises Celtic despite Glasgow Derby win]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43931</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/05/alan-shearer-celtic-glasgow-derby/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T09:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans were delighted with the result at the weekend and understandably so. Going into the Glasgow Derby, there were not a lot of expectations as Brendan Rodgers’ team had made a stumbling start to the season and had not made any high-profile additions to their squad over the summer either. Thus. most would have […]
Alan Shearer criticises Celtic despite Glasgow Derby win - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alan Shearer has a negative take on Celtic derby win as Gary Lineker picks out eerie moment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173463</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/alan-shearer-has-a-negative-take-on-celtic-derby-win-as-gary-lineker-picks-out-eerie-moment/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T08:13:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Lineker and Alan Shearer spent a short amount of time on their latest podcast talking about Celtic’s win at Ibrox. It was a glorious...
The post Alan Shearer has a negative take on Celtic derby win as Gary Lineker picks out eerie moment appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["What a player"; stars flock to Instagram after former Celtic hero announces retirement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173412</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-power-of-charlie-mulgrew-clear-to-see-as-stars-react-to-celtic-heavy-retirement-post/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic favourite Charlie Mulgrew has announced his retirement from football at the age of 37. Mulgrew came through the Hoops youth academy before departing...
The post "What a player"; stars flock to Instagram after former Celtic hero announces retirement appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon piles the pressure on to Ibrox figure after yet another Celtic derby win]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173404</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/neil-lennon-increases-the-pressure-on-michael-beale-after-yet-another-celtic-derby-win/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon has increased the pressure on Michael Beale after yet another Celtic derby win. It proved to be another beautiful Sunday for Celtic in...
The post Neil Lennon piles the pressure on to Ibrox figure after yet another Celtic derby win appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kvistgaarden talks Celtic as Podence door closes for good after Monday developments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173434</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/mathias-kvistgaarden-talks-celtic-as-daniel-podence-door-closes-for-good-after-monday-developments/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brondby forward Mathias Kvistgaarden has been speaking about his recent links to Celtic. The Hoops bid around £4m for Kvistgaarden in the closing stages of...
The post Kvistgaarden talks Celtic as Podence door closes for good after Monday developments appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EX-CELT CALLS IT A DAY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111786</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ex-celt-calls-it-a-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T05:31:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic defender Charlie Mulgrew has brought his 18-year playing career to a halt. The 37-year-old one-time Scotland international has decided to quit after leaving his post as player-coach at relegated Dundee United in the summer. Mulgrew had two spells at Parkhead and played for eight clubs after originally coming through the Hoops’ youth system. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I WILL GIVE HIM A HEADACHE,’ SCALES IN RODGERS TARGET]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111784</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-will-give-him-a-headache-scales-in-rodgers-target/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T05:16:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIAM SCALES is hoping to give Brendan Rodgers a selection headache in the months to come. The Irish centre-back answered his manager’s SOS call on Sunday when he took his place in the middle of the Celtic rearguard alongside new Bhoy Gustaf Lagerbiekle at Ibrox. In truth, that would not have been Rodgers’ pairing if [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star details next steps after breakthrough performance at Ibrox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173427</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/a-struggle-ahead-but-liam-scales-details-next-celtic-steps-after-breakthrough-performance/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Liam Scales has been detailing his next steps after his breakthrough performance at Ibrox on Sunday. It seems a little strange to use...
The post Celtic star details next steps after breakthrough performance at Ibrox appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FAREWELL TO CELTIC’S MISFIT MARKSMAN WHO COST MORE THAN £500,000-PER-GOAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111777</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/farewell-to-celtics-misfit-marksman-who-cost-more-than-500000-per-goal/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T04:12:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ALBIAN AJETI, Celtic’s £5million misfit marksman, has finally left the champions after nine goals for the club following his costly and disastrous arrival from West Ham in the summer of 2020. The big-money recruit, who spent last season on loan at Sturm Graz, has signed a permanent deal with Turkish club Gaziantep. The Swiss flop [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EVAN WILLIAMS: GREAT UNCAPPED CELTS (Part One)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.cqnmagazine.com/?p=4718</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/evan-williams-great-uncapped-celts-part-one/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T04:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CQN is turning the spotlight again on the Celtic players who never had the honour of playing for their country. Evan Williams, the keeper with the Welsh name who was born in Dumbarton, never got the nod to get into a Scotland squad. He was constantly overlooked, but was good and consistent enough to satisfy [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£6 million striker breaks silence on failed Celtic move]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43909</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/04/6-million-striker-failed-celtic-move/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T22:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As is often the case when a transfer window has closed there is more information about deals that didn’t quite materialise. Celtic did not manage to sign all their targets either, even though the club ended up bringing nine new players to the club. There is one striker, who they appeared to miss out on. […]
£6 million striker breaks silence on failed Celtic move - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player completes permanent exit after Deadline Day]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43923</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/04/celtic-player-completes-permanent-exit-deadline-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T21:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a decent record when it comes to identifying talents in recent years. That reputation was built up mostly during the time of Ange Postecoglou as manager. One cannot forget the terrible summer transfer window that the club had in 2020, one of the main reasons why their quest to win 10IAR failed so […]
Celtic player completes permanent exit after Deadline Day - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers make SFA decision after losing to Celtic again]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43917</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/04/rangers-sfa-decision-losing-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T19:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Going into the Glasgow Derby at the weekend, the Rangers were considered as the favourites over Celtic. Michael Beale’s side were coming off a 5-1 defeat at the hands of PSV in midweek, but Celtic had not put in a single convincing performance yet and were winless and goalless in their previous two games, a […]
Rangers make SFA decision after losing to Celtic again - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kasper Schmeichel agrees move amid Celtic rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43913</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/04/kasper-schmeichel-agrees-move-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T18:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most fans expected Celtic to sign a goalkeeper this summer, with there being major question marks surrounding Joe Hart and his suitability for Brendan Rodgers’ team. There were rumours linking them with a move for Dominik Livakovic, who would have been a great signing, but that did not end up happening. And with Benjamin Siegrist […]
Kasper Schmeichel agrees move amid Celtic rumours - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deflection tactics get desperate after Celtic triumph]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173399</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/deflection-tactics-get-desperate-after-celtic-triumph/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T17:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear, oh, dear. It seems some people in Glasgow are struggling with the latest Celtic derby triumph on Sunday, with deflection tactics taking a new...
The post Deflection tactics get desperate after Celtic triumph appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic Bhoy gets milestone international call-up weeks after signing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173394</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/new-celtic-bhoy-gustaf-lagerbielke-gets-milestone-international-call-up-weeks-after-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T16:31:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic Bhoy Gustaf Lagerbielke has been called up for the Sweden national team for competitive matches for the very first time. Lagerbielke has one...
The post New Celtic Bhoy gets milestone international call-up weeks after signing appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sevilla centre-back rejected chance to sign for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43905</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/04/sevilla-centre-back-chance-sign-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T12:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were very active this summer when it came to the centre-back position. Carl Starfelt departed the club in order to join Celta Vigo, freeing up a spot in the starting XI as a result. On the other hand, the Hoops signed three new centre-backs this summer in the form of Maik Nawrocki, Gustaf Lagerbielke […]
Sevilla centre-back rejected chance to sign for Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘What a Bhoy’: Trevor Sinclair says it’s ‘difficult not to love’ one Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173376</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-a-bhoy-trevor-sinclair-says-its-difficult-not-to-love-one-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trevor Sinclair has lauded the popular Kyogo Furuhashi, as he proved to be the game-changer once again for Celtic against Rangers. The 28-year-old ripped the...
The post ‘What a Bhoy’: Trevor Sinclair says it’s ‘difficult not to love’ one Celtic player  appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ibrox shaken to red brick core]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111766</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ibrox-shaken-to-red-brick-core/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T11:09:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Within the first minute at Ibrox yesterday, Newco sent a long ball forward that tempted Liam Scales into a challenge he missed.  Seconds later the ball ended in the net, only for the assistant to correctly flag offside.  It looked like a portent of doom to come, however, Liam was undeterred.  He threw himself at [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IMAGES: CELTIC DENIED STONEWALL PENALTY-KICK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111744</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/images-celtic-denied-stonewall-penalty-kick/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T10:33:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC should have been awarded a stonewall penalty-kick at Ibrox yesterday – but, amazingly, there has been absolutely no mention of the incident. CQN watched the replay of the entire match and spotted the infringement that should have seen Brendan Rodgers’ side awarded an undeniable spot-kick. In the 25th minute, eventual matchwinner Kyogo Furuhashi raced [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moussa Dembele makes superb claim after Celtic win vs Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43900</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/04/moussa-dembele-celtic-win-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T10:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moussa Dembele is one of the best players that Celtic have had in recent memory. The Frenc striker was superb during his time at Parkhead and he has had an interesting career since leaving for Lyon. He had some great seasons in Ligue 1, which saw him being linked with the likes of Chelsea and […]
Moussa Dembele makes superb claim after Celtic win vs Rangers - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Class': Ally McCoist hails 2 Bhoys, but says Rangers-Celtic 'might be worst I have seen']]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173359</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/class-ally-mccoist-hails-2-bhoys-but-says-rangers-celtic-might-be-worst-i-have-seen/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T08:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ally McCoist has hailed Callum McGregor and Kyogo Furuhashi for their performances following Celtic’s 1-0 against Rangers at Ibrox on Sunday. The former striker thinks...
The post 'Class': Ally McCoist hails 2 Bhoys, but says Rangers-Celtic 'might be worst I have seen' appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO AND THE JOY OF SIX]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111712</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kyogo-and-the-joy-of-six/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T08:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PACY hitman Kyogo Furuhashi is making up for lost time against Ibrox opposition after volleying in a spectacular winner in Govan in the champions’ 1-0 triumph to romp four points clear of their Glasgow rivals after the same amount of Premiership outings. Amazingly, the prolific Japanese striker had never scored against the city neighbours until [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The cold Celtic reality Michael Beale and Rangers are waking up to]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173354</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-cold-celtic-reality-michael-beale-and-rangers-are-waking-up-to/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T07:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s main title rivals Rangers are waking up to a four-point gap and the realisation that even at almost full strength, against a weakened Bhoys...
The post The cold Celtic reality Michael Beale and Rangers are waking up to appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘THEY THREW THEIR BODIES ON THE LINE,’ RODGERS HAILS HIS WINNERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111702</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/they-threw-their-bodies-on-the-line-rodgers-hails-his-winners/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T07:33:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS celebrated a bunch of fives as Kyogo Furuhashi fired Celtic to an exhausting 1-0 triumph at Ibrox on an afternoon many of the visiting players stood up to be counted. The Irishman was taking charge of the Hoops for the sixth time in enemy territory and has now succeeded in five of that [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers explains Celtic Ibrox absences; new Bhoy set to jet off again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173345</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-explains-paulo-bernardo-and-nat-phillips-situations-after-celtic-derby-absence/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T06:57:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was never in the plan to include Paulo Bernardo and Nat Phillips in yesterday’s Celtic squad at Ibrox, Brendan Rodgers revealed on the day....
The post Brendan Rodgers explains Celtic Ibrox absences; new Bhoy set to jet off again appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Left in awe; Callum McGregor's superb dressing room message to Celtic teammate at Ibrox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173347</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/left-in-awe-callum-mcgregors-superb-dressing-room-message-to-kyogo-after-celtic-derby-winner/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-04T06:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic captain Callum McGregor told Kyogo Furuhashi he might be one of the best strikers he’s ever seen after his glorious winner against Rangers at...
The post Left in awe; Callum McGregor's superb dressing room message to Celtic teammate at Ibrox appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James Tavernier reacts to Ibrox boos after losing to Celtic again]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43891</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/03/james-tavernier-reacts-ibrox-boos-losing-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T22:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be interesting to find out where James Tavernier ranks in terms of Rangers captains when it comes to his record against Celtic. The right-back was on the losing side in the Glasgow Derby once again, as the Hoops walked out of Ibrox with a 1-0 victory. Kyogo Furuhashi scored the winner on the […]
James Tavernier reacts to Ibrox boos after losing to Celtic again - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo explains why he did not celebrate Celtic’s goal vs Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43876</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/03/kyogo-celebrate-celtic-goal-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T20:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a stunning and surreal moment when Kyogo Furuhashi scored for Celtic at Ibrox on Sunday. When the ball found the back of the net the reactions all around were very unusual for the normal maelstrom that is the Glasgow Derby. Now, the Japanese forward has himself explained why he was hesitant to celebrate. […]
Kyogo explains why he did not celebrate Celtic’s goal vs Rangers - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss explains why Nat Phillips was dropped vs Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43884</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/03/celtic-boss-nat-phillips-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T19:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Perhaps it speaks more about the other moves made, but in many ways, Nat Phillips was Celtic’s marquee signing of the summer. The Liverpool centre-back has been brought in on a season-long loan amidst the long list of injury problems that Brendan Rodgers’ team are facing at this point in time. That did not stop […]
Celtic boss explains why Nat Phillips was dropped vs Rangers - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo: Two stars celebrate Celtic win from within Ibrox dressing room on Instagram]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173340</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/photo-matt-oriley-and-liel-abada-celebrate-celtic-win-from-within-ibrox-dressing-room-on-instagram/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T18:38:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There can’t be many things sweeter in football than celebrating a win in the away dressing room of your fiercest rivals, but that’s exactly what...
The post Photo: Two stars celebrate Celtic win from within Ibrox dressing room on Instagram appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Fans No Problem Lets Party]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58359</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/bad-week-for-the-bears/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T17:38:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All good things come in 3’s as they say so this weekend couldn’t be any better and today completed my ‘treble’. My only daughter got married on Friday and we were back in sunny Donegal for the nuptials as they head to New York for the honeymoon. Now it really couldn’t get much better but […]
The post No Fans No Problem Lets Party appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero takes dig at Todd Cantwell after Glasgow Derby]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43881</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/03/celtic-hero-todd-cantwell-glasgow-derby/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T17:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a match that most Celtic fans did not expect to win, which makes the result even sweeter. The Hoops had struggled for form at the start of this season, winning just two of their four games till now. On the other hand, the Rangers were coming off a 5-1 defeat at the hands […]
Celtic hero takes dig at Todd Cantwell after Glasgow Derby - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers fans meltdown after another loss to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43870</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/03/rangers-fans-another-loss-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T14:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans were worried going into the game away at Ibrox. They had not looked convincing the entire season and were winless in their previous two matches. On the other hand, the Rangers were coming off of a 5-1 defeat at the hands of PSV in midweek but overall, their supporters seemed to be more […]
Rangers fans meltdown after another loss to Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers reacts with superb BBC interview as Celtic leave Ibrox fans booing Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173325</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-reacts-with-superb-bbc-interview-as-below-strength-celtic-leave-ibrox-fans-booing-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T13:52:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers was a happy man after watching his Celtic team beat Rangers 1-0 at Ibrox today, fully satisfied with the efforts of his players....
The post Brendan Rodgers reacts with superb BBC interview as Celtic leave Ibrox fans booing Rangers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['World class': Neil Lennon blown away by 3 Celtic players after win over Rangers at Ibrox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173311</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/world-class-neil-lennon-blown-away-by-3-celtic-players-after-win-over-rangers-at-ibrox/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon waxed lyrical about Kyogo Furuhashi, Callum McGregor and Liam Scales after Celtic beat Rangers 1-0 at Ibrox on Sunday. Celtic’s main man up...
The post 'World class': Neil Lennon blown away by 3 Celtic players after win over Rangers at Ibrox appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘He enjoys playing against Rangers’: Chris Sutton hails Celtic player today at Ibrox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173291</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/he-enjoys-playing-against-rangers-chris-sutton-hails-celtic-player-today-at-ibrox/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton has hailed Kyogo Furuhashi for his ‘brilliant’ goal as Celtic beat Rangers 1-0 at Ibrox on Sunday. What a way to answer the...
The post ‘He enjoys playing against Rangers’: Chris Sutton hails Celtic player today at Ibrox appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RANGERS 0 CELTIC 1: TRUE GRIT CELTS AS KYOGO CRACKS IT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111693</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rangers-0-celtic-1-true-grit-celts-as-kyogo-cracks-it/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T13:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RANGERS 0 CELTIC 1   JUST CHAMPION! Celtic showed the true grit of title winners to claim a precious victory at Ibrox in the dramatic High Noon shoot-out. Kyogo Furuhashi was the man who claimed the glory goal just before the break, but this was an overall performance from a collection of players who did [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Criticised star turns it round, Kyogo class; 3 things we learned as weakened Celtic beat Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173286</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/priceless-class-captain-turns-it-up-3-things-we-learned-as-weakened-celtic-show-up-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T12:58:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crisis, what crisis? Celtic’s injury-ravaged and depleted squad have shown up rivals Rangers with a massive 1-0 victory at Ibrox. Brendan Rodgers and his team...
The post Criticised star turns it round, Kyogo class; 3 things we learned as weakened Celtic beat Rangers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BROONY AXED]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111690</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/broony-axed/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T10:12:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic skipper Scott Brown has been sacked by Fleetwood Town. The English third-tier side relieved the Hoops legend of his managerial duties following “a difficult run of results”. The team languish 23rd in League One after six matches with just one point. Brown’s team last picked up a point in the draw with Carlisle [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Rangers’ v Celtic, Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111686</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rangers-v-celtic-live-updates-21/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T10:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 12:00.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: ABADA STARTS, PALMA ON STAND-BY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111657</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-abada-starts-palma-on-stand-by/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T09:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIEL ABADA returns to the Celtic line-up for the first Glasgow derby of the season at Ibrox this afternoon. The Israeli winger, who comes in for South Korean Yang Hyun-jun, is the only change from the side that drew 0-0 with St Johnstone last weekend. Abada will be hoping to stage an action replay of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No new Bhoys: Celtic XI confirmed, one change, global TV details, instant reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173281</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-vs-rangers-confirmed-one-change-no-debuts-global-tv-details-instant-reaction/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T09:51:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manager Brendan Rodgers has named his Celtic team vs Rangers for today’s Scottish Premiership match at Ibrox. The full match squad is as follows: Starting...
The post No new Bhoys: Celtic XI confirmed, one change, global TV details, instant reaction appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend Scott Brown sacked from first management job; statement released]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173274</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-legend-scott-brown-sacked-from-first-management-job-statement-released/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T09:28:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend Scott Brown has been sacked as Fleetwood Town manager just a few weeks into the new season. A statement on the club’s official...
The post Celtic legend Scott Brown sacked from first management job; statement released appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[the rangers V CELTIC Matchday Minizine]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58352</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/the-rangers-v-celtic-matchday-minizine/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T09:13:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Click into image to download the rangers v CELTIC Match day Mini-zine. Hit subscribe to get match day edition in your inbox every time.
The post the rangers V CELTIC Matchday Minizine appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers fans make Michael Beale U-turn before facing Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43796</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/03/rangers-fans-michael-beale-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T09:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic announced their seventh summer signing in Luis Palma on Wednesday evening, the Rangers were sent packing from the Champions League qualifiers. Michael Beale wasn’t able to guide his team to the main stage of the competition, as they were defeated 5 -1 by PSV in the second leg of their matchup. As the […]
Rangers fans make Michael Beale U-turn before facing Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["We're really excited"; Brendan Rodgers talks up new Celtic signings ahead of Ibrox trip]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173271</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/were-really-excited-brendan-rodgers-talks-up-new-celtic-signings-ahead-of-ibrox-trip/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T08:50:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers called for Celtic signings in the last week of the summer transfer window and he got three of them – Luis Palma, Nat...
The post "We're really excited"; Brendan Rodgers talks up new Celtic signings ahead of Ibrox trip appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers sends clear message to Celtic dressing room ahead of Rangers test]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173268</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-sends-clear-message-to-celtic-dressing-room-ahead-of-rangers-test/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T08:16:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers will be making firm judgments on his Celtic players at Ibrox today, feeling that this is the kind of game where he can...
The post Brendan Rodgers sends clear message to Celtic dressing room ahead of Rangers test appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Champions League Draw Player Reactions]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58330</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/champions-league-draw-player-reactions/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T07:59:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After galloping towards the Scottish premier league title last season, Celtic were rewarded with direct rout into the group stages of the worlds premier club competition.  Celtic fans were in a fortunate position of watching on as clubs battled it out across Europe for the final few places at the top table of European football. […]
The post Champions League Draw Player Reactions appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘THIS IS WHERE YOU GET JUDGED AS A CELTIC PLAYER,’ RODGERS’ RALLYING CALL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111680</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/this-is-where-you-get-judged-as-a-celtic-player-rodgers-rallying-call/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T07:48:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has told his Celtic players to prepare for Judgement Day at Ibrox this afternoon. It’s an occasion when the Hoops will have to stand up to be counted in a partisan arena where there will not be a solitary Hoops supporter to add encouragement. On the last occasion at the same ground, Ange [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenny Dalglish makes Celtic derby scoreline prediction; thinks new signing can thrive vs Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173265</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kenny-dalglish-makes-celtic-derby-scoreline-prediction-thinks-new-signing-can-thrive-vs-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T07:47:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Liverpool legend Kenny Dalglish has given a big thumbs up to the signing of Nat Phillips from the Anfield side, believing he can...
The post Kenny Dalglish makes Celtic derby scoreline prediction; thinks new signing can thrive vs Rangers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big debut, Palma and Bernardo decisions; Celtic team news and Predicted XI vs Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173261</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/big-debut-palma-and-bernardo-decisions-celtic-predicted-xi-vs-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T07:25:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today’s a major test for Brendan Rodgers and Celtic, travelling away to rivals Rangers for the first derby of the Scottish Premiership season. After two...
The post Big debut, Palma and Bernardo decisions; Celtic team news and Predicted XI vs Rangers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Raving’: Tam McManus shares exciting info Greek source told him about Celtic new boy Palma]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173241</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/raving-tam-mcmanus-shares-exciting-info-greek-source-told-him-about-celtic-new-boy-luis-palma/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tam McManus has shared that he has been told by a former teammate in Greece that Celtic new boy, Luis Palma is a ‘top, top’...
The post ‘Raving’: Tam McManus shares exciting info Greek source told him about Celtic new boy Palma appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A YEAR AGO TODAY: CELTIC 4 RANGERS 0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111678</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/a-year-ago-today-celtic-4-rangers-0/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T06:57:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EXACTLY a year ago today, Celtic went on the goal rampage as they thumped Giovanni van Bronckhorst’s Ibrox visitors by four clear goals. Liel Abada, who has just signed a new deal at the champions, walloped in two efforts and Filipe Jota added the other after a spectacular solo sprint as the Hoops roared their [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: HITTING THE BOOS WITH BRENDAN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111675</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-hitting-the-boos-with-brendan/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T06:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BOOS and jeers bouncing around a stadium on the south side of Glasgow around two o’clock this afternoon would be a sweet cacophony to the ears of Brendan Rodgers. Not so welcoming was the noise that emanated from a section of Celtic Park last weekend when there was the predictable and pitiful reaction from so-called [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘There is absolutely': Peter Grant states if Nat Phillips will start for Celtic v Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173225</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/there-is-absolutely-peter-grant-states-if-nat-phillips-will-start-for-celtic-v-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T05:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant has backed on-loan Liverpool star Nat Phillips to make his Celtic debut against Rangers on Sunday at Ibrox. The Bhoys landed Nat Phillips’...
The post ‘There is absolutely': Peter Grant states if Nat Phillips will start for Celtic v Rangers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RANGERS v CELTIC: 5-MINUTE QUIZ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111620</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rangers-v-celtic-5-minute-quiz-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T04:15:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC take on Michael Beale’s team in the first derby of the season at Ibrox at noon today. As ever, no quarter will be asked or given in the rarefied atmosphere of this fixture. How much can you remember about recent encounters against the Govan club? Have a go on CQN’s fun five-minute quiz to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS v RANGERS (Part Six): MIGHTY MOUSSA TOP OF THE HIT PARADE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111659</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-v-rangers-part-six-mighty-moussa-top-of-the-hit-parade/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-03T04:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS resumes hostilities with Ibrox opposition in the High Noon showdown in enemy territory today. The returning Celtic manager has not figured in the derby fixture for four years and nine months. Rodgers has already been involved in 13 of the no-holds-barred encounters after first arriving at Parkhead in May 2016. The Irishman has enjoyed [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers calls out media over Celtic rumour]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43861</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/02/brendan-rodgers-media-celtic-rumour/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T22:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have done quite a bit of business over the course of the summer transfer window, bringing in nine new players in total. Seven have arrived on a permanent basis while two have been brought in one loan. Out of them, only one is more than 23 years of age, Nat Phillips of Liverpool, who […]
Brendan Rodgers calls out media over Celtic rumour - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Champions League Watch: Lazio deliver big statement win to turn around poor Serie A start]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173214</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-champions-league-watch-lazio-deliver-big-statement-win-to-turn-around-poor-serie-a-start/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T20:45:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that we know Celtic’s opponents for the upcoming UEFA Champions League group stage, it’s time to keep up with the goings on at all...
The post Celtic Champions League Watch: Lazio deliver big statement win to turn around poor Serie A start appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers wants Celtic to sign another Liverpool player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43857</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/02/brendan-rodgers-celtic-sign-liverpool/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T20:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic pulled off a late loan move for Nat Phillips this summer and there are high expectations that the Liverpool centre-back will be able to improve the Hoops’ defence. He has not gotten a lot of chances with the Reds but when he has been on the pitch, he has not looked out of place […]
Brendan Rodgers wants Celtic to sign another Liverpool player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic secure dream draw ahead of Champions League Group Stage]]></title>
        <id>http://celticunderground.net/?p=6630</id>
        <link href="http://celticunderground.net/celtic-secure-dream-draw-ahead-of-champions-league-group-stage/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T20:28:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will face Atletico Madrid, Lazio, and Feyenoord in Group E, In a somewhat surprising draw in comparison to previous Champions League seasons, where Celtic faced the likes of Real Madrid, Bayern Munich, Barcelona, and Manchester City in the group stages. Celtic centre-back Gustaf Lagerbielke spoke of the task facing Celtic against respected Champions League […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Alternative Glasgow Derby Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58339</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/the-alternative-glasgow-derby-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T19:31:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matt McGlone from the Alternative View joins More than 90 Minutes Editor, Andrew Milne to chat about all things Celtic. In this episode of the Celtic Soul Podcast they chat about the departure of Ange, the season so far, the second coming of Brendan Rodgers and the Glasgow Derby.
The post The Alternative Glasgow Derby Preview appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Brendan Rodgers identifies long-term Celtic replacement for Joe Hart; enquiry was made]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173207</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/report-brendan-rodgers-looking-at-liverpool-talent-as-celtics-long-term-joe-hart-replacement/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T19:27:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic didn’t sign a goalkeeper during the summer transfer window but a new report has stated that Brendan Rodgers is eyeing a Liverpool talent as...
The post Report: Brendan Rodgers identifies long-term Celtic replacement for Joe Hart; enquiry was made appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic turned down £7 million bid for important player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43853</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/02/celtic-7-million-bid-important-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T19:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were very busy over the course of the summer transfer window, both in terms of incomings and outgoings. Whether that has made any positive impact or not is a different discussion altogether. Brendan Rodgers’ team have not made the best start to the campaign and look like mere shells of Ange Postecoglou’s winning machine […]
Celtic turned down £7 million bid for important player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Net Spend summer transfer window 2023/24]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173201</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-net-spend-summer-transfer-window-2023-24/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T18:13:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s summer transfer window wasn’t without action, with lots of deals done in and out of the club. While some fans may feel the Bhoys...
The post Celtic Net Spend summer transfer window 2023/24 appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More than 90 Minutes Meets Luis Palma]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58332</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/more-than-90-minutes-meets-luis-palma/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T18:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 90 Minutes, Martin Donaldson and the Celtic Fan Media chat to Honduran international Luis Palma. Luis arrived in Glasgow on 30th August to sign a 5 year deal with the champions and immediately claimed he was ready to face our Glasgow rivals in the derby match on Sunday.  The 23 year old winger […]
The post More than 90 Minutes Meets Luis Palma appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Beale claims Rangers turned down new Celtic signing]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43849</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/02/michael-beale-rangers-celtic-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T17:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were busy in the last few days of the summer transfer window, trying to bring in players who could help the team after the Hoops stumbled out of the gates this season. It remains to be seen how successful they were in their quest. The club did make three late additions. Luis Palma was […]
Michael Beale claims Rangers turned down new Celtic signing - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Story created outside of the club"; Rodgers addresses Celtic spend & lack of big money players]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173203</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-addresses-celtics-summer-spend-and-lack-of-big-money-players/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T16:42:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has provided some candid thoughts on the way the summer transfer window went for Celtic, stating that the spending and approach was all...
The post "Story created outside of the club"; Rodgers addresses Celtic spend & lack of big money players appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 goals in 6 games for highly-rated Celtic youngster as B team pick up crucial Saturday win]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173196</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/superb-rocco-vata-form-continues-as-b-team-pick-up-crucial-saturday-win/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T15:54:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic prospect Rocco Vata has put all the recent transfer speculation behind him to score his seventh goal in six matches for the B team...
The post 7 goals in 6 games for highly-rated Celtic youngster as B team pick up crucial Saturday win appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["It's wasted it"; Lennon and McCulloch agree after Rangers pettiness damaged Celtic clash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173115</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/its-wasted-it-lennon-and-mcculloch-agree-that-rangers-pettiness-has-damaged-celtic-clash/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will have no fans in attendance for Sunday’s first derby of the season against Rangers. The allocation furore has been well covered ever since...
The post "It's wasted it"; Lennon and McCulloch agree after Rangers pettiness damaged Celtic clash appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have Champions League decisions to make as Monday deadline approaches]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173187</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-have-champions-league-squad-decisions-to-make-as-monday-deadline-approaches/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will have to name their ‘List A’ of Champions League players by Monday night. The Hoops are back in the group stage of European...
The post Celtic have Champions League decisions to make as Monday deadline approaches appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic linked with free transfer for Premier League winner]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43845</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/02/celtic-free-transfer-premier-league/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T12:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The summer transfer window is in the books and Celtic made nine additions to their squad. Despite that, many fans feel disappointed with the signings that the club made. There was a need for established and experienced players with the Champions League group stage coming up and a treble to defend. Instead, they stuck to […]
Celtic linked with free transfer for Premier League winner - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bernardo bang on plan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111658</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/bernardo-bang-on-plan/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T12:13:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paulo Bernardo’s signature on a loan-to-buy-option concluded Celtic’s business last night. It follows the same scouting, recruitment and commercial parth established with Jota two years earlier. At 21, he is bang on plan. If Celtic are to make a significant leap forward, we will not do it with mid-20s honest pros. Talent needs to be [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feyenoord boss shares his Celtic thoughts; indirect involvement in Rodgers return]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173180</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/feyenoord-boss-arne-slot-shares-his-celtic-thoughts-indirect-involvement-in-rodgers-return/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feyenoord boss Arne Slot has given his thoughts on Celtic and the rest of our Champions League group. Celtic were placed in to Group E...
The post Feyenoord boss shares his Celtic thoughts; indirect involvement in Rodgers return appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: McGREGOR, CONDUCTOR IN SEARCH OF AN ORCHESTRA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111655</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-mcgregor-conductor-in-search-of-an-orchestra/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T10:47:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WITH the clock ticking down all too quickly against St Johnstone, did you notice the selfless lung-bursting 50-yard sprint from Callum McGregor to recover the ball and attempt to set another Celtic attack in motion? In the fading moments, opposition keeper Dimitar Mitov rose to a right-wing corner-kick from Matt O’Riley to get both fists [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cause for optimism; the entire Celtic squad depth picture after frantic few days]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173171</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/cause-for-optimism-the-entire-celtic-squad-depth-picture-after-hectic-few-days/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been a hectic few days but the Celtic squad is now set for the challenges ahead. The club signed nine players over the course...
The post Cause for optimism; the entire Celtic squad depth picture after frantic few days appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton turns the heat up on Michael Beale ahead of Celtic clash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173144</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/chris-sutton-turns-the-heat-up-on-michael-beale-ahead-of-celtic-clash/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton has turned the heat up on Rangers manager Michael Beale ahead of Celtic’s visit to Ibrox on Sunday. It’s the first derby of...
The post Chris Sutton turns the heat up on Michael Beale ahead of Celtic clash appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic boost for Glasgow Derby]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43835</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/02/brendan-rodgers-celtic-glasgow-derby/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T09:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The summer transfer window is done and dusted. Celtic made nine signings over the course of it even though rumours of record-breaking offers and marquee signings proved to be well wide of the mark. Instead, the most high-profile addition that the club made was bringing in Nat Phillips on loan from Liverpool. And even that […]
Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic boost for Glasgow Derby - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£7m BID BOOTED AS CELTIC DEAL IN ABADA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111645</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/7m-bid-booted-as-celtic-deal-in-abada/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T08:56:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIEL ABADA signed an enhanced deal with Celtic just hours after the champions had knocked a £7million bid for the Israeli winger. Portuguese giants Sporting Lisbon were prepared to pay DOUBLE the fee the Hoops had shelled out for the Israeli international when he joined from Maccabi Petah Tikva in July 2021. However, the Parkhead [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic injury return for Ibrox; offers thoughts on potential debuts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173158</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-confirms-celtic-injury-return-for-ibrox-offers-thoughts-on-potential-debuts/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has confirmed that Hyeongyu Oh is available for Celtic at Ibrox on Sunday. The South Korean returned to training this week alongside the...
The post Brendan Rodgers confirms Celtic injury return for Ibrox; offers thoughts on potential debuts appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REVEALED: CELTIC CHAMPIONS LEAGUE FIXTURES]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111642</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/revealed-celtic-champions-league-fixtures/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T07:54:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC will kick off their Champions League Group E campaign with a game against Feyenoord in Rotterdam on Tuesday September 19. It will be an intriguing clash against the club that denied Jock Stein’s side a second European Cup triumph in 1970 when Ove Kindvall claimed the winner two minutes from the end of extra-time [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s Champions League fixtures confirmed; tasty match-ups, qualification verdict]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173152</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-champions-league-fixtures-confirmed-tasty-match-ups-qualification-verdict/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T07:05:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have found out their fixtures for the upcoming UEFA Champions League group stage campaign. On Thursday, the Hoops were placed in to Group E...
The post Celtic’s Champions League fixtures confirmed; tasty match-ups, qualification verdict appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£18.25m: RODGERS’ CASH SPLASH: ALL THE INS AND OUTS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111633</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/18-25m-rodgers-cash-splash-all-the-ins-and-outs/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T06:50:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS spent £18.25million in strengthening his Celtic squad this summer for the challenges that lie ahead at home and abroad. You can add £1million to that total which is the fee agreed for Japanese midfielder Tomoki Iwata when his initial loan move from Yokohama F Marinos became permanent. The highest outlay was the £4.3million [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rodgers has things to say about Ibrox allocation furore but all hope isn't lost for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173131</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/brendan-rodgers-has-things-to-say-about-ibrox-allocation-furore-but-all-hope-isnt-lost-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T06:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers had things to say about the Celtic and Rangers allocation furore at his Friday meeting with the print media. The Celtic manager is...
The post Rodgers has things to say about Ibrox allocation furore but all hope isn't lost for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic star makes definitive statement over debut at Ibrox; Rodgers has a decision to make]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173124</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/luis-palma-declares-himself-ready-for-celtic-debut-at-ibrox-now-rodgers-has-a-decision-to-make/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-02T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing Luis Palma says he is ready to make his debut at Ibrox on Sunday. It’s a huge weekend for the Hoops as...
The post New Celtic star makes definitive statement over debut at Ibrox; Rodgers has a decision to make  appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>