<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-09-16T14:08:05.502Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic v Dundee, GG Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111994</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-dundee-gg-live-updates/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T13:26:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates will appear below after 15.00.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed superb late-night news as club open talks]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44216</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/16/celtic-late-night-news-club-talks/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T13:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic made an unsteady start to the season but the win over the Rangers at Ibrox has lifted the mood around Parkhead and the future suddenly looks a lot brighter than it was a couple of weeks back. It is important for the club to build on their newfound momentum and string together some wins […]
Celtic handed superb late-night news as club open talks - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: DEBUT BHOY PHILLIPS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111957</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-debut-bhoy-phillips/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T13:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ON-LOAN Liverpool defender Nat Phillips makes his Celtic debut against Dundee at Parkhead this afternoon. The centre-back comes in to make his bow with £3million Swede Gustaf Lagerbiekle moving to the substitutes’ bench. South Korean winger Yang Hyun-jun comes in for the injured Liel Abada as the second change from the team that won 1-0 [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon offers a theory on Celtic European progress featuring Sevilla and Real Madrid]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174507</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/neil-lennon-offers-a-theory-on-celtic-european-progress-featuring-sevilla-and-real-madrid/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon has offered an interesting theory on some of the difficulties Celtic face in Europe. As a former Hoops manager and one of only...
The post Neil Lennon offers a theory on Celtic European progress featuring Sevilla and Real Madrid appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Much-hyped debuts expected as the Celtic faithful prepare for a big Saturday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174500</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/much-hyped-debuts-expected-as-the-celtic-faithful-prepare-for-a-big-saturday/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are back in action on Saturday and it should be a pretty fun afternoon. It’s our first home game in three weeks and a...
The post Much-hyped debuts expected as the Celtic faithful prepare for a big Saturday appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James McClean Interview]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58402</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/james-mcclean-interview/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T09:14:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James McClean  appeared on the Late Late Show last night for an interview with the new host Patrick Kielty It did not surprise me to learn that this was the Irish international football stars first appearance on the show. James’s view on the North of Ireland would not have sat well with the out going crew […]
The post James McClean Interview appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans will be introduced to a new referee on Saturday as SFA trend continues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174444</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-fans-will-be-introduced-to-a-new-referee-on-saturday-sfa-trend-continues/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic support will be introduced to a new referee against Dundee. It’s our big return to Celtic Park, three weeks on from our last...
The post Celtic fans will be introduced to a new referee on Saturday as SFA trend continues appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New footage shows real moment of Todd Cantwell injury as Celtic star shows no mercy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174494</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/new-footage-shows-real-moment-of-todd-cantwell-injury-as-celtic-star-shows-no-mercy/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers attacker Todd Cantwell will be out for weeks after picking up a costly injury in his side’s defeat to Celtic. The latest blow to...
The post New footage shows real moment of Todd Cantwell injury as Celtic star shows no mercy appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feyenoord have a major issue for Celtic clash and their manager knows it]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174486</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/feyenoord-have-a-major-issue-for-celtic-clash-and-their-manager-knows-it/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feyenoord have a major striking issue for their clash against Celtic next week. On Tuesday evening, the Scottish and Dutch champions will get their Champions...
The post Feyenoord have a major issue for Celtic clash and their manager knows it appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NO-HOPERS HOOPS? ‘THAT’S THE BEAUTY OF IT,’ INSISTS RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111979</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/no-hopers-hoops-thats-the-beauty-of-it-insists-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T07:40:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS insists his written-off Celts will be fearless when they commence their Champions League campaign against Feyenoord in Rotterdam on Tuesday night. The Hoops have already been branded as no-hopers by big-mouthed, dimwitted Dutch pundits as they prepare for their assault on Group E of Europe’s elite competition. Rodgers isn’t paying too much attention [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Beale reaching desperate stage; plucks out strange stat and overlooks Celtic dominance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174467</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/michael-beale-reaching-desperate-stage-plucks-out-strange-stat-and-overlooks-celtic-dominance/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers manager Michael Beale is reaching the desperate stage as pressure mounts following his recent defeat to Celtic. We’re the best part of two weeks...
The post Michael Beale reaching desperate stage; plucks out strange stat and overlooks Celtic dominance appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: SHUT IT, CELTIC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111969</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-shut-it-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T06:50:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EXCITING? Or excruciating? Adventurous? Or agonising? Praiseworthy? Or painful? I’m talking about Celtic’s forays into Europe over the past two years and, alas, to these tired old eyes, anyway, the experiences have been more of a plunging big dipper than a rollicking rollercoaster ride. Big Ange once famously stated he didn’t “pop any champagne corks [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic release important information for Feyenoord; fan meeting, alcohol, holdback decision]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174456</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-release-important-information-for-feyenoord-fan-meeting-holdback-alcohol-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have released some important information for Tuesday’s Champions League opener against Feyenoord. It’s an away game to kick off the campaign for Brendan Rodgers‘...
The post Celtic release important information for Feyenoord; fan meeting, alcohol, holdback decision appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple bits of good news for Celtic concerning Reo Hatate; weekend decision]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174437</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/multiple-bits-of-good-news-for-celtic-concerning-reo-hatate-weekend-decision/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are multiple bits of good news to report for Celtic concerning Reo Hatate. The Japanese midfielder is arguably our most talented player. Ever since...
The post Multiple bits of good news for Celtic concerning Reo Hatate; weekend decision appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mixed news for Celtic supporters as Motherwell make expected broadcasting announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174470</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/mixed-news-for-celtic-supporters-as-motherwell-make-expected-broadcasting-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The upcoming Premiership clash between Motherwell and Celtic will be available for supporters to buy on pay-per-view. The September 30 fixture, saw its kick-off time...
The post Mixed news for Celtic supporters as Motherwell make expected broadcasting announcement appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC v DUNDEE: 5-MINUTE QUIZ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111955</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-dundee-5-minute-quiz/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T04:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC take on Dundee at Parkhead this afternoon as the quest resumes for precious Premiership points. Kyogo Furuhashi was the man who made the difference with the only goal of the encounter at Ibrox before the international break. And the Japanese striker has happy memories of clashes against the Dens Park side in Glasgow. The [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE JOCK STEIN YEARS (Part Six)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=55171</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-jock-stein-years-part-six/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T04:15:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Jock Stein made an extraordinary immediate impact on the Parkhead club after his return as team boss in March 1965. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE,  author Alex Gordon, who has written fifteen publications on Celtic, has opened his book files on the Parkhead great for an absorbing twenty-one part series. Today, in Part Six of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GEORGE McCLUSKEY: GREAT UNCAPPED CELTS (Part Twelve)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=73055</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/george-mccluskey-great-uncapped-celts-part-twelve/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T04:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CQN is turning the spotlight once again on the Celtic players who never had the honour of playing for their country. George McCluskey was a scorer of important goals for the Hoops and played alongside such prolific marksmen as Frank McGarvey and Charlie Nicholas during Billy McNeill’s first stint as manager following his return to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur plot January move for Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44213</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/15/tottenham-hotspur-move-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T22:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Ange Postecoglou joining Tottenham Hotspur, Celtic fans were afraid that the Premier League club would try to sign some of their best players. Fortunately, it did not happen in the summer although the likes of Jota and Carl Starfelt did leave regardless. And now, it looks like another of their key stars is being […]
Tottenham Hotspur plot January move for Celtic player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC V Dundee Matchday Minizine]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58398</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-v-dundee-matchday-minizine/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T22:01:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post CELTIC V Dundee Matchday Minizine appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou makes classy Celtic claim after FIFA Best nomination]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44211</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/15/ange-postecoglou-celtic-fifa-best/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T21:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou left Celtic just days after winning the treble with them in order to join Tottenham Hotspur. It is a decision that did not go down too well with a lot of fans but as the days have passed and things have settled down, most recognise the choice the Australian made and why. He […]
Ange Postecoglou makes classy Celtic claim after FIFA Best nomination - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defiant Brendan Rodgers ready to prove Celtic doubters wrong in UEFA Champions League]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174434</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/defiant-brendan-rodgers-ready-to-prove-celtic-doubters-wrong-in-uefa-champions-league/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T20:49:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers reckons his team can spring a few surprises in the UEFA Champions League group stage, despite the Bhoys’ underdog status. The...
The post Defiant Brendan Rodgers ready to prove Celtic doubters wrong in UEFA Champions League appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rodgers, Injury Updates and Dundee Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58395</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/rodgers-injury-updates-and-dundee-preview/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T20:12:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic return to action against Dundee at another SOLD OUT Celtic Park. Liel Abada could be out for the next four months after picking up an injury away on international duty. Brendan Rodgers spoke highly of him in his pre-match press conference. Abada’s injury will now give someone else a chance to come in and […]
The post Rodgers, Injury Updates and Dundee Preview appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[West Ham teach Celtic harsh Friday night lesson in Premier League International Cup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174426</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/west-ham-teach-celtic-harsh-friday-night-lesson-in-premier-league-international-cup/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T19:58:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic B have suffered a heavy 5-0 defeat at the hands of the West Ham United U21s side in the Premier League International Cup on...
The post West Ham teach Celtic harsh Friday night lesson in Premier League International Cup appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers confirm another blow from loss against Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44208</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/15/rangers-confirm-another-loss-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T19:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Things just keep going from bad to worse for the Rangers at this point in time. They were knocked out from the Champions League qualifiers after losing 5-1 at the hands of PSV Eindhoven, a result that their fans were clearly not happy with. That was followed by a 1-0 defeat at Ibrox to Celtic. […]
Rangers confirm another blow from loss against Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitter Michael Beale can't hide the Celtic flashpoint running through his mind]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174422</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/bitter-michael-beale-cant-hide-the-celtic-flashpoint-running-through-his-mind/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T19:04:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Beale couldn’t resist taking a dig about an incident in the recent Celtic victory over Rangers, coming across very much as a man under...
The post Bitter Michael Beale can't hide the Celtic flashpoint running through his mind appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers refuses to bite on media stirring with firm response to Celtic transfer question]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174419</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-refuses-to-bite-on-media-stirring-with-firm-response-to-celtic-transfer-question/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T18:06:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has firmly closed the book on chat around Celtic’s summer transfer business, insisting that he’ll talk about the situation again in January. Celtic...
The post Brendan Rodgers refuses to bite on media stirring with firm response to Celtic transfer question appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic make superb announcement about investment]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44204</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/15/celtic-make-announcement-investment/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T18:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you look at the bigger picture, Celtic are in the middle of one of their most successful eras ever. The club have won the league title eleven out of the last twelve times and have clinched several cups to go with it. They have won five domestic trebles during that period of time as […]
Celtic make superb announcement about investment - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Celtic resurrection could be on the cards imminently; first appearance for 18 months]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174416</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/a-celtic-resurrection-could-be-on-the-cards-this-weekend-first-appearance-for-18-months/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T17:18:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Of all the players returning from injury during the international break, one of the most interesting is Mikey Johnston and his prospect of getting minutes...
The post A Celtic resurrection could be on the cards imminently; first appearance for 18 months appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Green Light for Celtic’s new training complex]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58391</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/green-light-for-celtics-fantastic-new-training-complex/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T17:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Football Club is delighted to announce that it has today approved significant investment into a state-of-the-art re-development of Celtic’s Barrowfield Training Centre, in the heart of the East End of Glasgow, as we aim to continue to create Celtic’s stars of the future. The development will deliver a fantastic new complex, hosting Celtic’s boys’ […]
The post Green Light for Celtic’s new training complex appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not Just Barrowfield: Lennoxtown training centre revamp also coming at Celtic, Rodgers speaks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174413</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/not-just-barrowfield-lennoxtown-training-centre-revamp-also-on-the-way-for-celtic-rodgers-speaks/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T16:37:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic confirmed that a large infrastructure project at the Barrowfield has been greenlit today, with the club believed to be spending millions of pounds on...
The post Not Just Barrowfield: Lennoxtown training centre revamp also coming at Celtic, Rodgers speaks appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lawwell, Nicholson and Rodgers react as Celtic confirm more details of £20m venture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174407</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/lawwell-nicholson-and-rodgers-react-as-celtic-confirm-more-details-of-20m-venture/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T16:07:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have officially announced they are funding the redevelopment of the Barrowfield training ground into a state-of-the-art complex that will include a full-size indoor pitch....
The post Lawwell, Nicholson and Rodgers react as Celtic confirm more details of £20m venture appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jota was open to Celtic return amid Al-Ittihad nightmare]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44200</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/15/jota-open-celtic-return-al-ittihad/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T15:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jota’s move to Al-Ittihad has clearly not gone as he would have envisioned. The Portuguese winger left Celtic in the summer in a £25 million move. He already seems to be on the fringes of the squad there and has been heavily linked with a move away, although nothing has materialised yet. Many Celtic fans […]
Jota was open to Celtic return amid Al-Ittihad nightmare - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Glad he's back"; box-office Rodgers praised by upcoming Celtic opponent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174383</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/glad-hes-back-rodgers-box-office-appeal-obvious-as-upcoming-opponent-of-celtic-speaks/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dundee manager Tony Docherty has been speaking about Brendan Rodgers ahead of his side’s game against Celtic this weekend. On Saturday afternoon, the Hoops will...
The post "Glad he's back"; box-office Rodgers praised by upcoming Celtic opponent appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Beale takes public dig about defeat to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44197</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/15/michael-beale-dig-defeat-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T13:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic did a tremendous job at Ibrox, getting a 1-0 win over the Rangers. They had gone into the game as underdogs, on the back of a defeat to Kilmarnock and a goalless draw against St Johnstone. But on the big occasion they delivered. The defence kept a clean sheet while Kyogo Furuhashi scored a […]
Michael Beale takes public dig about defeat to Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rodgers shares ambition for Celtic after watching Scotland vs England clash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174346</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-shares-scottish-ambition-for-celtic-after-watching-mcginn-and-more-at-hampden/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has shared his ambition to have a solid Scottish core of players at Celtic. It’s been a glorious period to be a Celtic...
The post Rodgers shares ambition for Celtic after watching Scotland vs England clash appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REVEALED: HATATE’S ‘ULTIMATE GOAL’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111961</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/revealed-hatates-ultimate-goal/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T11:53:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE has revealed he has an “ultimate goal in mind” while he stalls on a contract extension offer from Celtic. The Japanese midfielder has seen his compatriots Kyogo Furuhashi and Daizen Maeda sign enhanced terms in the summer, but he has yet to make a decision on his immediate future. Hatate signed until June [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic watch on as another European league secures a television deal we could only dream of]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174398</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-watch-on-as-the-eredivisie-secures-a-television-deal-scotland-could-only-dream-of/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic supporters may be aware of an impressive new television deal concerning the Eredivisie. The Dutch top flight has agreed a new five-year deal with...
The post Celtic watch on as another European league secures a television deal we could only dream of appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tight at top, Yang and Tilio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111822</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/tight-at-top-yang-and-tilio/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T11:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I know what you are thinking.  With our two nearest rivals for the title facing each other tomorrow, there is a chance we can open daylight between them and us at the top of the table – if we manage to overcome Dundee. Great, though this would be, I am less concerned about the threat [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I had this before"; Brendan Rodgers has a theory about Liel Abada Celtic injury]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174375</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-had-this-before-brendan-rodgers-has-a-theory-about-liel-abada-celtic-injury/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers has a theory about what caused the injury to Liel Abada. The Hoops attacker will be missing for a period of...
The post "I had this before"; Brendan Rodgers has a theory about Liel Abada Celtic injury appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic star already has his 'Palma 7' shirt as the hype gets real]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174390</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/emilio-izaguirre-shows-off-palma-7-celtic-shirt-and-it-looks-really-good/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emilio Izaguirre has shown off a new Celtic shirt with ‘Palma 7’ on the back. The former Hoops hero’s relationship with new signing Luis Palma...
The post Former Celtic star already has his 'Palma 7' shirt as the hype gets real appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘AMAZING,’ ADMITS AUSSIE NEW BHOY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111944</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/amazing-admits-aussie-new-bhoy/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T07:21:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AUSSIE teenager Liam Bonetig has signed a three-year deal at Celtic from Western Sydney. The defender will join the Parkhead side’s Academy after impressing during trials and the A-League outfit confirmed they will receive a transfer sum in training compensation for the 18-year-old prospect who has been at the club since 2016. The champions revealed [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘FITTER AND STRONGER,’ ABADA VOW]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111937</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/fitter-and-stronger-abada-vow/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T06:59:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIEL ABADA has vowed to come back “fitter and stronger” after his devastating injury blow. The Israeli winger faces “three to four months” on the sidelines after sustaining a thigh problem in training with the international squad, as CQN reported yesterday. Abada will miss the entire Champions League Group E campaign as well as the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic complete promising B team signing after confusing summer reports]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174367</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/celtic-complete-promising-b-team-signing-after-confusing-summer-reports/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have announced the signing of Australian centre-back Liam Bonetig on a three-year deal. The promising 18-year-old was last seen in action in the Western...
The post Celtic complete promising B team signing after confusing summer reports appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paulo Bernardo and Marco Tilio both share the images Celtic fans wanted to see]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174353</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/paulo-bernardo-and-marco-tilio-both-share-the-images-celtic-fans-wanted-to-see/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paulo Bernardo and Marco Tilio were both in Celtic training on Thursday. The pair, brought to the club this summer, are yet to make their...
The post Paulo Bernardo and Marco Tilio both share the images Celtic fans wanted to see appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liel Abada situation leads to UEFA frustration for Celtic boss]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174337</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/liel-abada-situation-leads-to-uefa-frustration-for-celtic-boss/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liel Abada could miss Celtic’s entire UEFA Champions League group stage campaign after suffering an injury on international duty. Abada will be out for a...
The post Liel Abada situation leads to UEFA frustration for Celtic boss appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upcoming Celtic clash moved for a reason that may not be immediately clear to all]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174361</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/upcoming-celtic-clash-moved-for-a-reason-that-may-not-be-immediately-clear-to-all/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s visit to Motherwell in a fortnight has been moved forward to a 12:30pm kick-off. The Hoops are due to visit the impressive Steelmen on...
The post Upcoming Celtic clash moved for a reason that may not be immediately clear to all appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THREE GOALS IN 13 MINUTES: BIG YOGI ON THE RAMPAGE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=82369</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/three-goals-in-13-minutes-big-yogi-on-the-rampage/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T05:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC great John ‘Yogi’ Hughes ran amok and scored a blistering 13-minute hat-trick in an 8-1 League Cup romp against Raith Rovers at Starks Park – EXACTLY 58 years ago today. The giant frontman, the Hoops’ eighth all-time leading scorer with 189 strikes, demolished the Fifers in the early months of the Jock Stein revolution. Big Yogi, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE JOCK STEIN YEARS (Part Five)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=55166</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-jock-stein-years-part-five/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T04:15:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Jock Stein made an extraordinary immediate impact on the Parkhead club when he returned as manager in March 1965. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE series, author Alex Gordon, who has written fifteen publications on Celtic, has opened his book files on the Parkhead great. Today, in Part Five of our fascinating look back at [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PETER LATCHFORD: GREAT UNCAPPED CELTS (Part Eleven)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.cqnmagazine.com/?p=5213</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/peter-latchford-great-uncapped-celts-part-ten/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T04:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CQN is turning the spotlight once again on the Celtic players who never had the honour of playing for their country. Peter Latchford was a Jock Stein signing in the legendary manager’s seemingly never-ending search for a replacement for Ronnie Simpson. He had bought the likes of Evan Williams, from Wolves, Ally Hunter (Kilmarnock) and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Hartson tips in-form Celtic player to be dropped]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44193</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/14/john-hartson-tips-celtic-player-dropped/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T22:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic made a questionable start to the season and many fans were left worried after their loss at the hands of Kilmarnock and then a goalless draw against a struggling St Johnstone side. Brendan Rodgers’ team appeared sluggish, uninspired and out of ideas. Yet, they turned up when it mattered the most, getting a win […]
John Hartson tips in-form Celtic player to be dropped - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss explains why he dropped €5 million signing]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44189</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/14/celtic-boss-explains-dropped-e5-million-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T20:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been dealing with a long list of injury problems at the very start of this season. A number of their important players are out on the sidelines for the foreseeable future and Brendan Rodgers will need to find a way to navigate through the upcoming fixtures. The win away at Ibrox might have […]
Celtic boss explains why he dropped €5 million signing - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers discusses late Luis Palma call with multiple Celtic debuts on the horizon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174315</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-discusses-late-luis-palma-call-with-multiple-celtic-debuts-on-the-horizon/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T20:30:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has confirmed Luis Palma won’t be returning to Celtic training until tomorrow, so it’ll be a late call on whether or not he...
The post Brendan Rodgers discusses late Luis Palma call with multiple Celtic debuts on the horizon appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Get him in’: John Hartson urges Rodgers to start 26-year-old for Celtic v Dundee]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174317</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/get-him-in-john-hartson-urges-brendan-rodgers-to-start-26-year-old-for-celtic-v-dundee/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Hartson wants to see Nat Phillips earn his first minutes in the colours of Celtic ahead of domestic football returning this weekend.  Many expected...
The post ‘Get him in’: John Hartson urges Rodgers to start 26-year-old for Celtic v Dundee appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boosted by 3 injury returns as Rodgers also provides Carter-Vickers and Nawrocki update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174312</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boosted-by-3-injury-returns-as-brendan-rodgers-also-provides-carter-vickers-and-nawrocki-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T19:26:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers says Reo Hatate, Marco Tilio and Yuki Kobayashi have all returned to Celtic training during the international break. The trio have been missing...
The post Celtic boosted by 3 injury returns as Rodgers also provides Carter-Vickers and Nawrocki update appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manager rejects Rangers job after loss to Celtic at Ibrox]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44186</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/14/manager-rangers-job-loss-celtic-ibrox/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T19:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Beale’s future at Ibrox is in serious doubt after he saw his side lose to Celtic at home. The team were booed at full-time and it looks like the manager might be on borrowed time now. It does seem like the Rangers might already be searching for his replacement but have already been turned […]
Manager rejects Rangers job after loss to Celtic at Ibrox - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pressure On: Celtic force Rangers into looking at manager change with approach reportedly made]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174309</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/pressure-on-celtic-force-rangers-into-looking-at-manager-change-with-approach-reportedly-made/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T18:01:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fallout of Celtic’s superb 1-0 win at Ibrox just before the international break continues to haunt Rangers, with reports indicating their hierarchy are strongly...
The post Pressure On: Celtic force Rangers into looking at manager change with approach reportedly made appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic confirm signing of defender on three-year deal]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44182</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/14/celtic-confirm-defender-three-year-deal/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T17:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The summer transfer window may have closed with Celtic making nine additions to their squad, seven on a permanent basis and two on loan. But the Hoops are continuing to strengthen the club as a whole, even if not the senior side. And they have added another defender to their B Team roster. Celtic signed […]
Celtic confirm signing of defender on three-year deal - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic stars react to their EA Sports FC 24 ratings; highest & lowest in squad, one is delighted]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174306</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-stars-react-to-their-ea-sports-fc-24-ratings-highest-and-lowest-in-squad/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T16:56:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of the Celtic squad have been taking part in a special challenge at Lennoxtown during the international break, in partnership with EA Sports and...
The post Celtic stars react to their EA Sports FC 24 ratings; highest & lowest in squad, one is delighted appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Longer period than expected"; Celtic star takes to Instagram after injury sickener]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174302</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/longer-period-than-expected-celtic-star-takes-to-instagram-after-injury-sickener/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T16:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic winger Liel Abada has updated supporters on his situation after picking up an injury on international duty with Israel earlier this month. Manager Brendan...
The post "Longer period than expected"; Celtic star takes to Instagram after injury sickener appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simon Donnelly says 'something special is brewing' with player Celtic sold under Postecoglou]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174285</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/simon-donnelly-says-something-special-is-brewing-with-player-celtic-sold-under-ange-postecoglou/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans wouldn’t be surprised to hear that Ben Doak is receiving rave reviews after his dazzling display for Scotland U21s recently. The Liverpool winger,...
The post Simon Donnelly says 'something special is brewing' with player Celtic sold under Postecoglou appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REVEALED: WHY BOSS SNUBBED FIVE STARS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111934</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/revealed-why-boss-snubbed-five-stars/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T14:57:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has revealed the reasoning behind three of his summer signings being left out of his Champions League squad. The Celtic boss omitted Polish defender Maik Nawrocki, Australian winger Marco Tilio and South Korean midfielder Kwon Hyeon-kyu from his 25-man pool for the forthcoming fixtures against Atletico Madrid, Lazio and Feyenoord. The champaign will [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Celtic stars we're expecting big things from in the UEFA Champions League]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174213</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/three-celtic-stars-were-expecting-big-things-from-in-the-uefa-champions-league/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re now a matter of days away from Celtic’s return to the UEFA Champions League. It’s just over 11 months since we last featured in...
The post Three Celtic stars we're expecting big things from in the UEFA Champions League appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: CELTIC KICK-OFF SWITCH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111927</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-celtic-kick-off-switch/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T14:21:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S Premiership game against Motherwell at Fir Park a fortnight on Saturday has had a kick-off switch. The match was due to commence at 3pm, but will now begin at 12.30pm at the request of both clubs. The earlier start for an encounter which is NOT being broadcast live by Sky Sports could aid recovery time for [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘SHAME,’ RODGERS CONFIRMS ABADA SETBACK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111926</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/shame-rodgers-confirms-abada-setback/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T14:07:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has confirmed that winger Liel Abada WILL be sidelined for the remainder of this year. It was originally feared the Israeli ace would be out for five months, as CQN reported earlier today, but it looks as though that may be too severe although his period in recuperation will be lengthy. Rodgers reckons [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rodgers in Confident Mood]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58384</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/rodgers-in-confident-mood/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T13:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The international break is over and Celtic get back to business this Saturday against Dundee. Media reports are suggesting that Liel Abada has picked up an injury while away on international duty with Israel and he could be ruled out for the next 5 months. Confidence should be high after our last outing at Ibrox […]
The post Rodgers in Confident Mood appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic sent blunt message by former Feyenoord player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44177</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/14/celtic-message-former-feyenoord-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T12:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will be kicking off their 2023/24 Champions League group stage campaign with a game against Feyenoord away at De Kuip. It will not be an easy task for the Hoops at all, as they have made an inconsistent start to the campaign and it is hard to predict which version of the Hoops will […]
Celtic sent blunt message by former Feyenoord player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Young Celtic stars about to embark on another UEFA adventure; TV arrangements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174234</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/young-celtic-stars-about-to-embark-on-another-vital-uefa-adventure-tv-arrangements/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While most of the UEFA-related Celtic talk at present is about the Champions League, there is another competition getting underway next Tuesday. The first-team’s involvement...
The post Young Celtic stars about to embark on another UEFA adventure; TV arrangements appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch: The outrageous Nat Phillips piece of skill that was brought up at Celtic press conference]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174206</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/watch-the-outrageous-nat-phillips-piece-of-skill-that-was-brought-up-at-celtic-press-conference/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nat Phillips almost certainly hasn’t been brought to Celtic to produce moments of extreme skill, yet he clearly has it in his locker. Back in...
The post Watch: The outrageous Nat Phillips piece of skill that was brought up at Celtic press conference appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The true cost of the Celtic squad; doesn't make great reading ahead of Champions League]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174226</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-true-cost-of-the-celtic-squad-reported-doesnt-make-great-reading-ahead-of-champions-league/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are inside the top 100 for the most expensive squads in world football. The information has been provided by CIES Football Observatory — a...
The post The true cost of the Celtic squad; doesn't make great reading ahead of Champions League appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Training Revision Loop urgently required]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111924</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/training-revision-loop-urgently-required/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T11:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If concerns are realised and Liel Abada’s injury, sustained on international duty with Israel, results in him missing five months of the season, it will be a huge blow to Celtic, as well as the player.  Liel was an instant hit when he arrived in Glasgow two years ago as a 19-year-old.  His goals and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ABADA FIVE-MONTH INJURY FEARS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111921</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/abada-five-month-injury-fears/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T10:46:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC winger Liel Abada faces a sickening FIVE-MONTH injury lay-off. The 21-year-old raider returned early from Israel’s international break after sustaining a muscle strain in training, as CQN stated at the weekend. Abada was checked out by the Hoops medical team and it appears the problem is a lot more serious than originally thought. Reports [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Absolutely, John McGinn': Andy Walker makes claim about Celtic 30-year-old fans will love]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174248</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/absolutely-john-mcginn-andy-walker-makes-bold-claim-about-celtic-30-year-old-fans-will-love/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andy Walker says Celtic midfielder Callum McGregor would start for England, alongside the likes of John McGinn, Andy Robertson and Kieran Tierney. All are either...
The post 'Absolutely, John McGinn': Andy Walker makes claim about Celtic 30-year-old fans will love appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laughter all well and good but Celtic star has hit upon a major safety concern at Ibrox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174191</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/laughter-all-well-and-good-but-nat-phillips-has-hit-upon-a-major-celtic-safety-concern-at-ibrox/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing Nat Phillips has revealed that he was at Ibrox for the team’s recent derby win over Rangers. The Liverpool loanee joined the...
The post Laughter all well and good but Celtic star has hit upon a major safety concern at Ibrox appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key Celtic player could be out for rest of 2023 with injury]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44173</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/14/key-celtic-player-rest-2023-injury/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T09:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have had terrible luck with injuries this season already. The likes of Cameron Carter-Vickers, Maik Nawrocki and Stephen Welsh are out for the foreseeable future with medium to long-term issues. And now, it looks like another key player could be set to join, in a major blow for Brendan Rodgers’ side. The Glasgow Derby […]
Key Celtic player could be out for rest of 2023 with injury - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘ITCHING TO GO,’ INSISTS NEW BHOY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111917</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/itching-to-go-insists-new-bhoy/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T08:10:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEW Bhoy Nat Phillips insists he can cope with the pressure at Celtic. The centre-back, who has signed a loan deal from Liverpool until January, missed out on a quickfire debut in the champions’ 1-0 win at Ibrox, but still caught the flavour of a hectic Glasgow derby. Phillips, whose dad Jimmy had a season [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Celtic stars who should have benefitted greatly from the international break]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174241</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/three-celtic-stars-who-should-have-benefitted-greatly-from-the-international-break/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s first team stars should all be back in training on Thursday as the team gears up for their next match. It’s the best part...
The post Three Celtic stars who should have benefitted greatly from the international break appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender shares fitness update after some Ibrox murmurings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174199</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-defender-nat-phillips-shares-fitness-update-after-some-ibrox-murmurings/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Nat Phillips has offered a reassuring fitness update as he closes in on his debut for the club. The Englishman was unable to...
The post Celtic defender shares fitness update after some Ibrox murmurings appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: The Rocco Vata hype continues but it may not be good news for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174220</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-rocco-vata-hype-continues-but-it-may-not-be-good-news-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hype around Celtic youngster Rocco Vata is continuing to grow. The 18-year-old is yet to feature competitively for Celtic this season, after getting some...
The post Report: The Rocco Vata hype continues but it may not be good news for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic plan for Nat Phillips is clear as defender addresses looming January decision]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174185</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-celtic-plan-for-nat-phillips-is-clear-as-defender-addresses-looming-january-decision/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent Celtic signing Nat Phillips was an impressive performer as he met the Scottish media for the first time on Wednesday. The English defender, signed...
The post The Celtic plan for Nat Phillips is clear as defender addresses looming January decision appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE JOCK STEIN YEARS (Part Four)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=55161</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-jock-stein-years-part-four/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T04:15:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Jock Stein made an extraordinary immediate impact on the Parkhead club when he returned as manager in March 1965. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE, author Alex Gordon, who has written fifteen publications on Celtic, has opened his book files on the Parkhead great for an absorbing twenty-one part series. Today, in Part Four of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JOHNNY DOYLE: GREAT UNCAPPED CELTS (Part Ten)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.cqnmagazine.com/?p=5623</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/johnny-doyle-great-uncapped-celts-part-eleven/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T04:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CQN is turning the spotlight again on the Celtic players who never had the honour of playing for their country. Johnny Doyle was a £90,000 signing for the Hoops in 1975 – the club’s record fee at the time – and he became a player who never gave less than 100 per cent for the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player makes superb Zlatan Ibrahimovic claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44168</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/13/celtic-player-zlatan-ibrahimovic-claim/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T23:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have certainly made quite a few additions to their squad over the summer. Mostly, they have stuck to bringing in highly-rated young talents from around the world. The results appear to be mixed till now. The likes of Odin Thiago Holm, Gustaf Lagerbielke and Yang Hyun-jun have made positive starts. On the other hand, […]
Celtic player makes superb Zlatan Ibrahimovic claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic summer signing’s father used to play for Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44165</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/13/celtic-summer-signing-father-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T21:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Very rarely have players represented both Celtic and the Rangers over the years. Also, there are very few who have signed for the Hoops, whose father used to play for the Ibrox club. And yet, there is one in Brendan Rodgers’ current squad. That is none other than Nat Phillips, who was brought in on […]
Celtic summer signing’s father used to play for Rangers - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nat Phillips explains why he left Liverpool to join Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44162</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/13/nat-phillips-liverpool-join-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T20:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nat Phillips is the most high-profile signing that Celtic made this summer. Even he arrived on loan for only the first half of the season and out of necessity more than anything else, as Cameron Carter-Vickers, Maik Nawrocki and Stephen Welsh are all out injured for the foreseeable future. Bringing in the Liverpool defender was […]
Nat Phillips explains why he left Liverpool to join Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic criticised for ignoring Scottish international player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44159</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/13/celtic-criticised-scottish-international/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T18:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have signed highly-rated young talents from all over the world in recent years and it has served them very well on the pitch. Just this summer, they brought in players from leagues in South Korea, Australia, Norway, Sweden, Greece, Poland, Portugal and England. They did not sign any Scottish player though. That does not […]
Celtic criticised for ignoring Scottish international player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022 Celtic summer signing now facing a struggle under Brendan Rodgers - opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174149</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/alexandro-bernabei-now-facing-a-struggle-under-brendan-rodgers-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Things are not looking good for Alexandro Bernabei after he was left out of Celtic’s UEFA Champions League squad. The Hoops ‘List A’ selection was...
The post 2022 Celtic summer signing now facing a struggle under Brendan Rodgers - opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gareth Bale mentions Celtic in Ange Postecoglou claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44155</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/13/gareth-bale-celtic-ange-postecoglou/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T15:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gareth Bale is the most decorated British footballer in history and he often does not get the credit that he deserves for what he achieved at Real Madrid. The Welshman scored in more than one Champions League final and won the competition five times, a record he shares with several of his former teammates. He […]
Gareth Bale mentions Celtic in Ange Postecoglou claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers sets a clear target for Celtic in the UEFA Champions League]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174142</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-sets-a-clear-target-for-celtic-in-the-uefa-champions-league/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has been speaking about the UEFA Champions League with less than a week to go before Celtic get this season’s campaign underway. It’s...
The post Brendan Rodgers sets a clear target for Celtic in the UEFA Champions League appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HEY, BIG SPENDER: £54.2m CELTIC IN CASH SPLASH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111913</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hey-big-spender-54-2m-celtic-in-cash-splash/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T14:43:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have spent £54.2million in assembling the squad currently at the disposal of Brendan Rodgers. That’s the total amount of cash the champions have splashed over the recent seasons which also takes in the likes of David Turnbull who arrived from Motherwell for £2.75million in the summer of 2020. The financial data has been released [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic man shares message after international efforts go under the radar; Hoops chances]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174157</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/hyeokkyu-kwon-shares-message-after-international-efforts-go-under-the-radar-celtic-chances/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player Hyeokkyu Kwon has shared a message after being away on international duty with the South Korea under-23 side. The holding midfielder, who joined...
The post Celtic man shares message after international efforts go under the radar; Hoops chances appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Injury consequence for Champions League squad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111912</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/injury-consequence-for-champions-league-squad/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T11:04:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The injury crisis in central defence had an interesting consequence for Celtic’s Champions League squad, announced yesterday.  As things stand, we have only two fit central defenders who have played for the club, Liam Scales and Gustaf Lagerbielke.  Nat Phillips is fit but has yet to make his debut. As recently as a month ago, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Pleasure': Jude Bellingham's verdict on Scotland's midfield after facing Celtic's McGregor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174164</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/pleasure-jude-bellinghams-verdict-on-scotlands-midfield-after-facing-celtics-callum-mcgregor/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic captain Callum McGregor faced one of his toughest tests on Tuesday night following Scotland’s 3-1 defeat to England at Hampden Park.  Jude Bellingham was...
The post 'Pleasure': Jude Bellingham's verdict on Scotland's midfield after facing Celtic's McGregor appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maik Nawrocki news doesn't appear to be good after Celtic squad announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174101</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/maik-nawrocki-news-doesnt-appear-to-be-good-after-celtic-squad-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic man Maik Nawrocki appears to be some way from making his return from injury, judging by developments on Tuesday. The Polish central defender, signed...
The post Maik Nawrocki news doesn't appear to be good after Celtic squad announcement appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers making a mistake not playing Celtic ace]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44152</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/13/brendan-rodgers-mistake-celtic-ace/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T10:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers’ return to Celtic Park has been up-and-down till now. The Hoops made a questionable start to the season for sure and are already out of the Scottish League Cup. But then, the win over the Rangers away at Ibrox has settled a lot of nerves and convinced the doubters that the Northern Irishman […]
Brendan Rodgers making a mistake not playing Celtic ace - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic round-up; Callum McGregor vs England verdict as Bernardo, Holm and Kyogo all feature]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174107</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-round-up-callum-mcgregor-vs-england-verdict-as-bernardo-holm-and-kyogo-all-feature/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tuesday was a busy day for some of Celtic’s stars as the international programme drew to a close. The first break of the season arrived...
The post Celtic round-up; Callum McGregor vs England verdict as Bernardo, Holm and Kyogo all feature appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GREEN LIGHT FOR HATATE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111883</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/green-light-for-hatate/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T08:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE is poised to make his return from injury against Dundee at Parkhead on Saturday as the champions continue their quest for Premiership points. The influential Japanese midfielder has been missing since a 25-minute second-half cameo in the 3-1 win over Aberdeen at Pittodrie exactly a month ago. Hatate suffered a muscular injury that [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers is bullish; thinks Celtic have already encountered major moment this season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174117</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-is-bullish-thinks-celtic-have-already-had-their-gibraltar-moment-this-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers had plenty of interesting things to say about Celtic on Tuesday. As we’ve already covered, the Hoops boss offered a pretty positive injury...
The post Brendan Rodgers is bullish; thinks Celtic have already encountered major moment this season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss shares great Reo Hatate news that extends beyond positive injury update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174083</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-shares-great-reo-hatate-news-that-extends-beyond-positive-injury-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers has shared some great news about Reo Hatate. The Japanese midfielder — arguably our most talented player — has endured a...
The post Celtic boss shares great Reo Hatate news that extends beyond positive injury update appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Irish outlet rave about Celtic youngster as he steals the show in midweek]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174135</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/irish-outlet-rave-about-rocco-vata-as-celtic-man-steals-the-show-in-midweek/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic youngster Rocco Vata was the standout performer for the Republic of Ireland’s under-21s on Tuesday evening. The young Irish side kept up their 100%...
The post Irish outlet rave about Celtic youngster as he steals the show in midweek appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers shares positive injury update but two Celtic stars not mentioned by name]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174090</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-shares-positive-injury-update-but-two-celtic-stars-not-mentioned-by-name/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers shared a largely positive injury update on Tuesday. It’s been a challenging few weeks for the Hoops with a number of...
The post Brendan Rodgers shares positive injury update but two Celtic stars not mentioned by name appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing produces in overnight international; Hoops debut soon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174125</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/luis-palma-produces-in-overnight-honduras-clash-celtic-are-next/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summer Celtic signing Luis Palma was among the goalscorers in an emphatic midweek win for Honduras. The Central American country were in CONCACAF Nations League...
The post New Celtic signing produces in overnight international; Hoops debut soon appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE JOCK STEIN YEARS (Part Three)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=55150</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-jock-stein-years-part-three/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T04:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Jock Stein made an extraordinary immediate impact on the Parkhead club when he returned as manager in March 1965. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE series, author Alex Gordon, who has written fifteen books on Celtic, has opened his publication files on the Parkhead great. Today, in Part Three of our fascinating look back at [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JOHNNY DIVERS: GREAT UNCAPPED CELTS (Part Nine)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.cqnmagazine.com/?p=5054</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/johnny-divers-great-uncapped-celts-part-nine/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-13T04:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CQN is turning the spotlight again on the Celtic players who never had the honour of playing for their country. Johnny Divers was a goalscoring phenomenon who netted the first goal in a 4-0 win over Dundee United at Tannadice in August 1965 that kicked off the historic first nine in row. He had been [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic tipped to sign another Liverpool player amid links]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44148</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/12/celtic-sign-another-liverpool-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T22:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already signed one player from Liverpool recently in the form of Nat Phillips, who arrived on loan for the first half of the season. It was a move made out of necessity more than anything else. Celtic have players like Cameron Carter-Vickers, Stephen Welsh and Maik Nawrocki out for the foreseeable future. So, […]
Celtic tipped to sign another Liverpool player amid links - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OFF NIGHT FOR SCOTS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111872</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/off-night-for-scots/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T21:13:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SCOTLAND were off colour, off target and off the pace as they lost 3-1 to England in the 150th Anniversary Match at Hampden this evening. There was also bad news from Norway where the hosts beat Georgia 2-1 in the Scots’ Euro group in the game in which a draw would have seen Steve Clarke’s [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou makes emotional claim about Celtic fans]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44144</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/12/ange-postecoglou-claim-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T20:31:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou is one of the most popular Celtic managers in recent memory. Not only did the Australian win over the fans with wins, trophies and the style of football that his team played but also with his conduct off the pitch as well. A cheeky one-liner was never far away and he seemed to […]
Ange Postecoglou makes emotional claim about Celtic fans - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou explains why he left Celtic for Tottenham]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44140</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/12/ange-postecoglou-left-celtic-tottenham/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T19:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were dealt a blow when Ange Postecoglou left the club, merely days after winning a domestic treble with the Hoops, in order to join Tottenham Hotspur. The lead-up to the Scottish Cup final had been dominated by rumours of his potential exit and the fans’ worst fears soon came true. Postecoglou had proven himself […]
Ange Postecoglou explains why he left Celtic for Tottenham - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms major Celtic injury boost]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44137</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/12/brendan-rodgers-celtic-injury-boost/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T17:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There has been very little good news for Celtic when it comes to the injury front. One player after another has gone down with fitness issues at the start of the season, leaving Brendan Rodgers with limited options to pick his team from. That contributed to the stumbling start they made to the campaign, even […]
Brendan Rodgers confirms major Celtic injury boost - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Paulo Bernardo state of play as Celtic debut comes in to focus]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174021</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-paulo-bernardo-state-of-play-as-celtic-debut-comes-in-to-focus/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paulo Bernardo could make his Celtic debut this weekend against Dundee. The midfielder joined us on a season-long loan from Benfica on the final day...
The post The Paulo Bernardo state of play as Celtic debut comes in to focus appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou signing must leave after Celtic decision]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44135</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/12/ange-postecoglou-signing-leave-celtic-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T15:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A change in managers is always an interesting time for a club and the players, and Celtic certainly are going through a transitional phase right now. Ange Postecoglou left at the end of last season in order to join Tottenham Hotspur while Brendan Rodgers has been brought in as the Australian’s replacement. Of course, Rodgers’ […]
Ange Postecoglou signing must leave after Celtic decision - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic set for big billing in Champions League opener as new television era begins]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173999</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-set-for-big-billing-in-champions-league-opener-as-the-tnt-sports-era-begins/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic get their UEFA Champions League campaign underway next Tuesday. It may not feel like it right now, with international football dominating the headlines, but...
The post Celtic set for big billing in Champions League opener as new television era begins appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: NAWROCKI OUT OF EURO SQUAD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111868</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-nawrocki-out-of-euro-squad/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T14:48:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS has been forced to leave crocked Maik Nawrocki out of Celtic’s 25-man Champions League squad . The £4.3million centre-back who arrived from Legia Warsaw in the summer suffered a hamstring problem during the Hoops’ 1-0 Viaplay League Cup loss to Kilmarnock at Rugby Park just over three weeks ago. It was announced Nawrocki [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[€5 million Celtic player left out of Champions League squad]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=44132</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/09/12/5-million-celtic-champions-league-squad/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T13:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will be kicking off their Champions League campaign in a week when they take on Feyenoord away in the Netherlands. The Hoops were not able to win a single game in Europe’s elite competition last season despite putting in a few impressive performances and finished bottom of their group as a result. They will […]
€5 million Celtic player left out of Champions League squad - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The potential for at least one Celtic debut this weekend; problem area looking better]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174006</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/the-potential-for-at-least-one-celtic-debut-this-weekend-centre-back-situation-improves/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic centre-back situation will already have improved by the time Saturday’s clash against Dundee rolls around. The Hoops are back in Premiership action against...
The post The potential for at least one Celtic debut this weekend; problem area looking better appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Right at the top': Ange Postecoglou shares what he 'tells everyone' about Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174056</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/right-at-the-top-ange-postecoglou-shares-what-he-tells-everyone-about-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has shared that he ‘keeps saying to everyone’ that Celtic should be ‘top’ of the bucket list of clubs you want to be...
The post 'Right at the top': Ange Postecoglou shares what he 'tells everyone' about Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Park's unlikely starring role the last time Scotland faced England in a friendly]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173990</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-parks-unlikely-starring-role-the-last-time-scotland-faced-england-in-a-friendly/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scotland face England in a friendly on Tuesday evening at Hampden Park. The match is uncompetitive by definition, yet it is sure to be a...
The post Celtic Park's unlikely starring role the last time Scotland faced England in a friendly appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor’s five mountains in five weeks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111867</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/callum-mcgregors-five-mountains-in-five-weeks/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T11:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If results to their way, Scotland will tonight become the first team to qualify for the Euro 2024 in Germany next summer.  Norway and Georgia are both on four points.  A draw would see them move to five, 10 behind Scotland with three games remaining. Either way, automatic qualification is inevitable, as, with Spain remaining [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I don't': Sutton mentions Callum McGregor & says England star doesn't get into Scotland XI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174035</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-dont-sutton-mentions-callum-mcgregor-says-england-star-doesnt-get-into-scotland-xi/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton name-dropped Celtic captain Callum McGregor whilst stating that England star Jordan Henderson doesn’t get into Scotland’s XI. Celtic’s main man in the middle...
The post 'I don't': Sutton mentions Callum McGregor & says England star doesn't get into Scotland XI appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic influence already clear to see as Luis Palma shares photo from Honduras]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174028</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-influence-already-clear-to-see-as-luis-palma-shares-photo-from-honduras/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T09:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic influence is already clear to see as Luis Palma shared a photograph from Honduras. The recent Hoops signing is back in his homeland...
The post Celtic influence already clear to see as Luis Palma shares photo from Honduras appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHEN HARRY MET BROONY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111858</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/when-harry-met-broony/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T08:22:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC hero Scott Brown came face to face with rival skipper Harry Kane before the Scotland v England Euro 2018 qualifier at a sunkissed Hampden on the afternoon of June 10 2017. It turned out to be an epic confrontation between the opposite onfield leaders during a thrilling 2-2 stalemate after the hosts had fought [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic youngster shares Rodgers hope for next season as surprise midfield talk emerges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=174014</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/bosun-lawal-shares-brendan-rodgers-hope-for-next-season-surprise-celtic-midfield-option-emerges/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bosun Lawal still seems to be hopeful about a future career at Celtic. The 20-year-old has played a handful of games for the Hoops since...
The post Celtic youngster shares Rodgers hope for next season as surprise midfield talk emerges appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HEARD THE ONE ABOUT HAMPDEN’S HEROES AND VILLAINS? CELTIC HERO REVEALS ALL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111839</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/heard-the-one-about-hampdens-heroes-and-villains-celtic-hero-reveals-all/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T07:39:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JUST over six years and three months ago, Leigh Griffiths sent two soaring long-range free-kicks beyond the grasping fingers of Joe Hart at Hampden Park in a crucial Euro 2018 qualifier. A late goal from Harry Kane gave England a 2-2 draw with Scotland, a loss of two points that went a long way to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic leave former Ibrox man feeling "a little bit silly" after glorious derby triumph]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173983</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-leave-former-ibrox-man-feeling-a-little-bit-silly-after-glorious-derby-triumph/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s over a week since Celtic silenced the doubters with a glorious derby win at Ibrox. With multiple injuries to contend with, and no supporters...
The post Celtic leave former Ibrox man feeling "a little bit silly" after glorious derby triumph appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo braced for big Japan chance after an injury that will interest Celtic fans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173976</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kyogo-furuhashi-braced-for-big-japan-chance-after-an-injury-that-will-interest-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Furuhashi could be set for his big opportunity to impress in a Japan shirt on Tuesday. The in-form Hoops forward was an unused substitute...
The post Kyogo braced for big Japan chance after an injury that will interest Celtic fans appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Joe Hart and Leigh Griffiths scenes that reached Celtic circles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173961</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-joe-hart-and-leigh-griffiths-banter-that-reached-celtic-circles/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart and Leigh Griffiths had plenty of chat to catch up on when they first met at Celtic in the summer of 2021. The...
The post The Joe Hart and Leigh Griffiths scenes that reached Celtic circles appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Hibernian boss credits Celtic move which opened doors to Scottish football]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=173968</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/new-hibernian-boss-credits-celtic-move-which-opened-doors-to-scottish-football/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Hibernian manager Nick Montgomery has credited a move Celtic made in 2021 with opening doors from Australian to Scottish football. The move in question...
The post New Hibernian boss credits Celtic move which opened doors to Scottish football appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamish Carton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE JOCK STEIN YEARS (Part Two)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=55147</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-jock-stein-years-part-two/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T04:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC legend Jock Stein made an extraordinary immediate impact on the Parkhead club when he returned as team boss in March 1965. The 38th anniversary of the passing of the Hoops great, at the age of 62, was marked by CQN on Sunday. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE,  author Alex Gordon, who has had fifteen Celtic works published, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TOM McADAM: GREAT UNCAPPED CELTS (Part Eight)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.cqnmagazine.com/?p=4982</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/tom-mcadam-great-uncapped-celts-part-eight/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-12T04:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CQN is turning the spotlight again on the Celtic players who never had the honour of playing for their country. Club legend Billy McNeill converted Tom McAdam from striker to centre-back – and the player was consistently immense following the dramatic career switch. He became a key man for the Hoops and a fans’ favourite [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>