<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2024-04-13T12:15:00.383Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘NO COINCIDENCE,’ KYOGO REACTION ANALYSED BY RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119563</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/no-coincidence-kyogo-reaction-analysed-by-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-13T09:21:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is convinced Kyogo Furuhashi has responded to the challenge from Adam Idah to lead the Celtic attack. The Hoops boss insists the Japanese striker has upped his game since the six-goal Norwich City loanee arrived at the champions in January. Rodgers is adamant it’s “no coincidence” Kyogo is sparking again after his striking [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers' big message to Celtic fans after being "taken aback" on derby weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194561</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-big-message-to-celtic-fans-after-being-taken-aback-on-derby-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-13T09:04:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers’ return to Celtic hasn’t always brought about the unity witnessed during his first spell at the club. He’d be the first to admit...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic favourite Chris Sutton goes in on the SFA after latest "fiasco"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194556</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-favourite-chris-sutton-goes-in-on-the-sfa-after-latest-fiasco/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-13T08:21:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Scottish FA have lurched from one refereeing crisis to another this season and, despite their best attempts, it’ll be hard to shake off the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adam Idah explains the difference between Celtic and Norwich City that is sparking his "best" form]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194546</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/adam-idah-explains-the-difference-between-celtic-and-norwich-city-that-is-sparking-his-best-form/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-13T07:29:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adam Idah wasn’t a wholly popular signing when his loan move from Norwich City to Celtic was announced in the winter transfer window. Some Celtic...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: DO US A FAVOUR, CALLUM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119560</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-do-us-a-favour-callum/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-13T07:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ONLY Callum McGregor had a clue what was going on in his thought process when he attempted to deliver a suicidal crossfield pass at Ibrox last weekend. Celtic were leading 2-1 in the 86th minutes when the comeback captain, on the pitch for a mere 21 minutes, accepted a short pass from Liam Scales midway [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic team news and Predicted XI vs St Mirren as 2 miss out on 4-point chance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194540</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-news-and-predicted-xi-vs-st-mirren-as-2-miss-out-on-4-point-chance/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-13T06:52:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are back in action in the Scottish Premiership later today knowing that victory would move them four points clear at the top of the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[McGREGOR: RODGERS IN NO RUSH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119558</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/mcgregor-rodgers-in-no-rush/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-13T05:52:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS preached caution in skipper Callum McGregor’s battle for fitness. After missing four games, the influential onfield leader made a return to first-team action as a second-half substitute in the 3-3 draw at Ibrox last weekend. Now all eyes are on the possibility of McGregor continuing his progress in this afternoon’s visit of St [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OH, WHAT CAN THE MATTER BE?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119551</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/oh-what-can-the-matter-be-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-13T05:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OH HYEON-GYU displayed impeccable timing when he fired in his first goal of the season. The South Korean powerhouse came off the substututes’ bench to thump in the 83rd-minute winner the last time today’s opponents St Mirren played at Parkhead. The champions toiled throughout the early November evening encounter and had to come from behind [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC v ST MIRREN: 5-MINUTE QUIZ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119543</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-v-st-mirren-5-minute-quiz-4/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-13T04:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC played St Mirren three times at Parkhead last season and thumped 11 goals into their net. This time around, they have had to be content with two after their 2-1 win over the Paisley club in November. Brendan Rodgers’ side had to respond from going a goal behind to come back and claim three [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The latest from Brendan Rodgers on Celtic's scouting and transfer revamp after Lawwell exit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194535</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-latest-from-brendan-rodgers-on-celtics-scouting-and-transfer-revamp-after-lawwell-exit/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T20:25:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time is ticking on Celtic’s quest to put in place a strong recruitment team ahead of the summer transfer window. It was announced in early...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers makes his feelings clear on loanee's future after dream spell elsewhere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194530</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-makes-his-feelings-clear-on-mikey-johnstons-future-after-dream-loan/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T19:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mikey Johnston’s loan from Celtic to West Bromwich Albion couldn’t be going any better than it is. Not only has he established himself as a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHEN SATURDAY COMES]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58770</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/when-saturday-comes-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T16:40:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The dust has settled on last weekend’s game v the rangers at Ibrox. With no ticket allocation for away fans, it was pubs and clubs around the globe that were packed with Celtic fans. Publicans everywhere rubbing their hands with plenty of hangovers to be nursed at work on Monday after overindulging on Sunday. […]
The post WHEN SATURDAY COMES appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers talks "integrity" in response to objects thrown at Celtic staff and players at Ibrox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194524</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-talks-integrity-in-response-to-objects-thrown-at-celtic-staff-and-players-at-ibrox/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T15:14:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers was asked about the unsavoury incidents at Ibrox last week involving objects being thrown at Celtic staff during the draw with Rangers. A...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers reacts to SPFL drama involving Dundee and Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194512</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-reacts-to-spfl-drama-involving-dundee-and-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T14:43:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has been discussing the issues around Dundee’s poor pitch at Dens Park and their recent postponement drama with Rangers. The Ibrox...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘CRAZY,’ IDAH OPENS UP ON CELTIC TRUST AND CONFIDENCE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119555</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/crazy-idah-opens-up-on-celtic-trust-and-confidence/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T14:27:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ADAM IDAH is revelling in the trust from manager Brendan Rodgers as he focuses on scoring the goals that will help take the title back to the east end of Glasgow for the third successive season. The champions face six crucial games as they bid fo their twelfth championship in 13 years and the countdown to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The class fan moment that left everyone in Celtic squad blown away and "amazed"]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194507</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-class-fan-moment-that-left-everyone-in-celtic-squad-blown-away-and-amazed/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T14:13:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That Celtic avoided defeat in a pressurised title race situation at Ibrox last weekend was made all the more impressive because no away fans were...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DAIZEN DESPAIR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119553</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/daizen-despair/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T13:47:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAIZEN MAEDA is on the brink of being ruled out of Celtic’s crucial league and Cup double bid. The Japanese speedster has suffered a hamstring injury and is already OUT off tomorrow’s vitally important Premiership game against St Mirren at Parkhead before the SPFL split. Brendan Rodgers admitted he was unsure if Maeda will return [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms double squad blow ahead of Celtic vs St Mirren]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194498</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-confirms-double-squad-blow-ahead-of-celtic-vs-st-mirren/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T13:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic haven’t had much luck with injuries this season. It’s been a key storyline throughout the campaign. Brendan Rodgers has been left frustrated by the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the Brazilian media are saying about Alexandro Bernabei's "electric" debut out on loan from Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194482</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-the-brazilian-media-are-saying-about-alexandro-bernabeis-electric-debut-out-on-loan-from-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Alexandro Bernabei has impressed on his debut for Brazilian club Internacional this week. The Argentinian made the loan move to South America last...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Putting fire in Dundee bellies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119544</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/putting-fire-in-dundee-bellies/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T11:01:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dundee really need to lawyer up over SPFL disciplinary procedures against them for problems with their pitch, leading to their game against Newco being postponed twice.  The game should have been scheduled for Wednesday 3 April, instead of the last midweek before the league split. Not scheduling a game until the last possible date before [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘ABSOLUTE STEAL’: SUTTON URGES £3m DEAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119531</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/absolute-steal-sutton-urges-3m-deal/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T07:02:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CHRIS SUTTON reckons Adam Idah would be “an absolute steal” if Brendan Rodgers can sign the striker for £3million from Norwich City. The on-loan 23-year-old Republic of Ireland international powerhouse hoisted his goal tally to six in as many starts when he rifled in the third at Ibrox on Sunday. Idah’s whiplash low effort eluded [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: ‘CELTIC’S WINNING DOUBLE-ACT,’ HOOPS ICON NAMES PRIZE GUYS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119522</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-celtics-winning-double-act-hoops-icon-names-prize-guys/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T05:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAVIE HAY insists Celtic WILL win their twelfth title in 13 years, but states his old club will have to perform at their highest standards to clear their remaining six league hurdles. The former Hoops player and manager is convinced his old club won’t falter as they focus on the main prize. Hay, speaking to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC EURO SETBACK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119528</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-euro-setback/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T05:29:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have received a Champions League setback with the news the title winners will NOT automatically qualify for the group stage of the 2025/26 Champions League. Scotland last night dropped out of the UEFA coefficient top 10 rankings following Viktoria Plzen’s goalless home stalemate against Fiorentina in the first leg of the Europa Conference League [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant on 'important' reason why Celtic are in better title-winning position than Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194479</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/peter-grant-on-important-reason-why-celtic-are-in-better-title-winning-position-than-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T05:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are in the thick of a straight shoot-out with Rangers for the Scottish Premiership title that could go down to the wire this season....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘AFRAID OF NO-ONE’: 57 YEARS AGO, WE’RE ON OUR WAY TO LISBON]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=78461</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/afraid-of-no-one-57-years-ago-were-on-our-way-to-lisbon/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T05:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC overcame Dukla Prague 3-1 in the unforgettable European Cup semi-final first leg at Parkhead exactly FIFTY-SEVEN YEARS ago today. The sensational victory edged Jock Stein’s heroes closer to history in Lisbon the following month. Bertie Auld, alongside his fellow-midfield mastermind Bobby Murdoch, helped orchestrate the downfall of extremely dangerous opponents on another evening of joy [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's Daizen Maeda earns glowing appraisal as Brendan Rodgers lauds his Glasgow Derby role]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194476</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-daizen-maeda-earns-glowing-appraisal-as-brendan-rodgers-lauds-his-glasgow-derby-role/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T20:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans will now be looking ahead to our clash against St Mirren this weekend following a pulsating Glasgow Derby clash against Rangers last Sunday...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I must admit’: Peter Grant shares an alternative view on Rangers’ penalty vs Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194449</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/peter-grant-has-an-alternative-argument-on-the-penalty-rangers-got-vs-celtic-on-sunday/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just when you think the Celtic penalty chat is all over, Peter Grant goes and throws in an alternative view that is sure to cause...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Celtic favourite announced as European giants prepare to descend upon Parkhead]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194473</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/another-celtic-favourite-announced-as-european-giants-prepare-to-descend-upon-parkhead/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans will have an additional opportunity to watch some of their heroes in action at Paradise once the Scottish Premiership season concludes. On the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Not concerned’: Peter Grant explains why he’s not worrying about Rangers’ upcoming visit to Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194458</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/peter-grant-explains-why-hes-not-concerned-about-rangers-upcoming-visit-to-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fallout of Celtic’s draw with Rangers continues this week as Peter Grant now weighs into the debate of the result. Later tonight Peter Grant...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton and Ian Ladyman engage in verbals involving Celtic over Dundee pitch issues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194462</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-and-ian-ladyman-engage-in-verbals-involving-celtic-over-dundee-pitch-issues/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been handed a psychological boost in their pursuit of the Scottish Premiership crown after Rangers’ match against Dundee was postponed again yesterday due...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three changes Brendan Rodgers could make vs St Mirren as Celtic continue title charge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194443</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/three-changes-brendan-rodgers-could-make-vs-st-mirren-as-celtic-continue-title-charge/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic continue their pursuit of the Scottish Premiership trophy this weekend when Stephen Robinson’s St Mirren travel to Parkhead. Last time out, the Bhoys were...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Keeping an eye’: Pundit says Celtic will be keeping tabs on winger with ‘a lovely left foot’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194433</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/pundit-says-celtic-will-be-keeping-an-eye-on-winger-with-a-lovely-left-foot/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I like a wee bit of Celtic transfer talk as it gives a welcome break from poring over the Glasgow Derby result which is now...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant thinks Celtic will 'definitely' look to complete permanent transfer this summer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194446</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/peter-grant-thinks-celtic-will-definitely-look-to-complete-permanent-transfer-this-summer/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will already be identifying summer transfer targets at Parkhead to strengthen Brendan Rodgers’ squad heading into 2024/25. With six Scottish Premiership matches left to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic now have Australian goalkeeper high on radar to replace Joe Hart]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194465</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-now-have-australian-goalkeeper-high-on-radar-to-replace-joe-hart/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T15:22:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers will already have a list of players on his radar to replace Joe Hart as his retirement date draws closer. Former...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers on why Celtic have found additional 'confidence' in last few weeks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194440</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-on-why-celtic-have-found-additional-confidence-in-last-few-weeks/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers has finally been able to enjoy a run of matches without major injury trouble in his second spell in charge at...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['A farce': Celtic fans are all saying the same thing after what Chris Sutton heard about Rangers last night]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194423</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-fans-are-all-saying-the-same-thing-after-what-chris-sutton-heard-about-rangers-last-night/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The title race took another turn for Celtic last night after Rangers’ game-in-hand against Dundee was postponed once again. Brendan Rodgers‘ side earned a draw...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aberdeen join VAR protests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119521</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/aberdeen-join-var-protests/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T11:17:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aberdeen issued a measured statement on the shortcomings of Video Assistant Referees yesterday, after their game at Livingston on Saturday ended in farce.  With the score at 0-0, Bojan Miovski scored in the 92nd minute.  Neither the referee nor his assistant raised an objection, and when the VAR checked the goal, they discovered their system [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans will love what John McGinn has said about Shunsuke Nakamura]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194430</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-fans-will-love-what-john-mcginn-has-said-about-shunsuke-nakamura/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are one of the most sizeable clubs in Europe, and their fanbase reflects that fact, reaching every corner of the world. If you are...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mikey Johnston's form earns further merited acknowledgement away from Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194425</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/mikey-johnstons-form-earns-further-merited-acknowledgement-away-from-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic loanee Mikey Johnston continues to shine at West Bromwich Albion despite previously being a bit-part player at Parkhead. Joining on deadline day, the Republic...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Shambles': Michael Stewart makes big VAR prediction after Celtic and Aberdeen errors this week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194419</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/michael-stewart-makes-big-var-prediction-after-celtic-and-aberdeen-errors-this-week/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VAR has been the big headline-grabber this week after Celtic were penalised at Ibrox by the refereeing technology. There is no point picking over the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC CONNECTION: DONS NAME NEW BOSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119493</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-connection-dons-name-new-boss/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T08:01:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JIMMY THELIN, the Elfsborg manager who sold Gustaf Lagerbielke to Celtic in the summer, has agreed to become Aberdeen’s new boss. However, the 46-year-old Swede will NOT be in the Hampden dug-out when the Dons face the holders a week on Saturday. Thelin will remain with his club side until their game against IFK Gothenburg on June [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘The reality is’: Michaele Beale makes Celtic admission after watching draw with Rangers at the weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194413</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/michaele-beale-makes-celtic-admission-after-watching-draw-with-rangers-at-the-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s point earned at Ibrox on Sunday sets the league title run-in up for an exciting end-of-season climax. With only one point separating Brendan Rodgers...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: ‘BRENDAN DESERVES MASSIVE CREDIT,’ INSISTS LEGEND]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119491</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-brendan-deserves-massive-credit-insists-legend/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T07:14:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAVIE HAY sees no reason to change his mind that Celtic will be crowned champions at the end of the season. The club legend insisted in CQN last week that his old club would not be running scared in a toxic atmospshere at Ibrox on Sunday. The former Parkhead player and manager stated he was [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers on lessons learned from Liverpool heartbreak amid Celtic title fight]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194406</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-on-lessons-learned-from-liverpool-heartbreak-amid-celtic-title-fight/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has plenty of experience in fighting for trophies as he leads the Bhoys into the final stretch of the campaign. With...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Sign him up’: Jim Duffy believes Celtic must sign talented youngster ‘everyone is talking about’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194410</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/jim-duffy-believes-celtic-must-sign-talented-youngster-everyone-is-talking-about/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T06:46:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that the madness of the weekend’s Glasgow Derby seems to be calming down, the Celtic fans will be looking forward to normal league business...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers issues exciting verdict on Reo Hatate's long-awaited Celtic return]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194403</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-issues-exciting-verdict-on-reo-hatates-return-and-hopes-for-future/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T20:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder Reo Hatate is now back in full flow after spending much of this season on the sidelines at Parkhead. Overall, the Japan international...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pundit reacts to surprise Celtic transfer theory involving 'terrific' in-form SPFL winger]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194400</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/pundit-reacts-to-surprise-celtic-transfer-theory-involving-terrific-in-form-spfl-winger/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will cast the net far and wide this summer in their attempts to recruit quality additions heading into the forthcoming 2024/25 campaign. Of course,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen Craigan explains how ‘sublime’ Celtic changed the ‘narrative’ after Rangers draw]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194367</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/stephen-craigan-explains-how-sublime-celtic-changed-the-narrative-after-rangers-draw/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That word ‘narrative’ is one that has been used all too often this season as Brendan Rodgers highlights the media perception of Celtic when their...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers on how he 'perfectly envisaged' striker competition at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194397</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-on-how-he-perfectly-envisaged-striker-competition-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers has managed to get a tune out of several attacking options at Parkhead as his side continue their title charge. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['I really do': Pundit makes bizarre Brendan Rodgers claim after Celtic’s Ibrox result]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194388</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/pundit-makes-bizarre-brendan-rodgers-claim-after-celtics-ibrox-result/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think many Celtic fans will agree that getting out of Ibrox with a draw against Rangers at this stage of the season is a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and the potential Eiran Cashin transfer option amid defensive dilemma]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194364</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/celtic-and-the-potential-eiran-cashin-transfer-option-amid-defensive-dilemma/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers will be identifying transfer targets this summer regardless of how the rest of the campaign unfolds. With six Scottish Premiership fixtures...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Absolutely devastated': Kieran Tierney says he's so upset after what happened at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194381</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kieran-tierney-shares-how-he-really-felt-about-celtics-draw-with-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there was ever a former player who had one eye on Celtic’s game with Rangers on Sunday, it’s Kieran Tierney. The Arsenal defender is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SIX APPEAL: KEEP CALM AND CARRY ON, URGES RODGERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119479</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/six-appeal-keep-calm-and-carry-on-urges-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T12:52:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS will order his Celtic players to remain calm amid the chaos as they embark on the six-game schedule that stands between them and a twelfth title in 13 years. The champions will take on St Mirren at Parkhead on Saturday afternoon before the league split and the manager reckons the Hoops are picking [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kieran Tierney makes a Callum McGregor claim that all Celtic fans would agree with]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194383</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kieran-tierney-makes-a-callum-mcgregor-claim-that-all-celtic-fans-would-agree-with/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans will be keen for Callum McGregor to play a starring role during the run-in after our club captain returned from injury at Ibrox....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['He's that good': Chris Sutton thinks 'important' Celtic player is heading for the Premier League]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194370</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/hes-that-good-chris-sutton-thinks-important-celtic-player-is-heading-for-the-premier-league/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s easy to forget that in the midst of a huge Glasgow Derby, there is other Celtic news out there to report on that can...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kieran Tierney directly answers whether he would ever come back to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194377</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kieran-tierney-directly-answers-whether-he-would-ever-come-back-to-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T11:40:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have had their fair share of fantastic players to have pulled on green and white over the years at Parkhead. Callum McGregor, Kyogo Furuhashi...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Hartson elaborates on why Daizen Maeda is undervalued at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194358</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/john-hartson-elaborates-on-why-daizen-maeda-is-undervalued-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic winger Daizen Maeda enjoyed another fruitful Glasgow Derby last weekend, netting the opener in the Bhoys’ 3-3 draw against Rangers at Ibrox. The Japan...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Curtail confidence, there remains a lot to do]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119478</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/curtail-confidence-there-remains-a-lot-to-do/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T11:01:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have no intention of encouraging anyone to place a bet, but if you think Celtic will be crowned champions in five weeks’ time, you can make a 40% return on your money.  Bookies do not give a 40% return on capital within five weeks often, so what’s going on? The confidence you feel after [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic eye Joe Hart replacement who wants to leave his current club]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194353</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-eye-joe-hart-replacement-who-wants-to-leave-his-current-club/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Away from the madness of the Glasgow Derby and onto some transfer news as Celtic look to build for next season. Brendan Rodgers‘ focus is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend Davie Hay explains why title race may now have swung in Bhoys favour]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194351</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-legend-davie-hay-explains-why-title-race-may-now-have-swung-in-bhoys-favour/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are well in the title race after securing a draw at Ibrox last weekend in a pulsating Scottish Premiership affair. The Bhoys will take...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gerry McCulloch's amusing dig at Rangers penalty decision vs Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194341</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/gerry-mccullochs-amusing-dig-at-rangers-penalty-decision-vs-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans will now be looking forward to our clash against St Mirren this weekend in the aftermath of our chaotic Glasgow Derby draw. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I’ve got to say’: Noel Gallagher shares who he thinks will win the league after watching Celtic vs Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194346</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/noel-gallagher-shares-who-he-thinks-will-win-the-league-after-watching-celtic-vs-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T08:15:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fallout of the Glasgow Derby between Celtic and Rangers has not only caused debate over the contentious VAR decisions, it has also thrown up...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALEX’S ANGLE: PROFESSOR PHIL, PREMATURE EXULTATION AND SILVA GUFF]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119475</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/alexs-angle-professor-phil-premature-exultation-and-silva-guff/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T08:05:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PHILIPPE CLEMENT appears eager to present himself as a studious type of guy. I had to smile when I read a newspaper reporter describe the Belgian as “an academic of the game”. Professor Phil? Forgive me, dear reader, but I am not subscribing to any of that drivel and especially not when this managerial egghead [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former SFA referee takes issue with Michael Stewart’s latest Celtic VAR comments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194339</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/former-sfa-referee-takes-issue-with-michael-stewarts-latest-celtic-var-comments/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The controversy over VAR is just not going to go away anytime soon now is it as the penalty awarded against Celtic at Ibrox continues...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon worried about key Celtic man after 'uncharacteristic' display vs Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194333</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/neil-lennon-worried-about-key-celtic-man-after-uncharacteristic-display-vs-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are still well in the title race courtesy of their spirited performance last weekend at Ibrox that resulted in a 3-3 draw. In truth,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Disgusted’: John Hartson believes Rangers should have had a player sent off against Celtic on Sunday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194336</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/john-hartson-disgusted-as-he-believes-rangers-should-have-had-a-player-sent-off-against-celtic-on-sunday/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T06:45:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s draw with Rangers was packed full of incidents and controversy as both clubs battled to come out victorious in the race for the title....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE CURIOUS FADE OF KYOGO FURUHASHI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119469</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-curious-fade-of-kyogo-furuhashi/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T05:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO FURUHASHI has seen an alarming contrast in his goalscoring fortunes at Celtic this season. The fans’ favourite was earning massive accolades from Ange Postecoglou this time last year after thumping in a double in the 3-2 Premiership victory over their Ibrox foes at Parkhead on April 8. Kyogo’s strikes hoisted his tally to a praiseworthy [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I have to say’: Neil Lennon shares how he really thought John Beaton handled the Rangers vs Celtic game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194320</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/neil-lennon-shares-how-he-really-thought-john-beaton-handled-the-rangers-vs-celtic-game/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The referee and VAR team have come under increasing scrutiny following Celtic’s 3-3 draw with Rangers at Ibrox on Sunday. Controversial VAR decisions once again...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton asks why experienced Celtic player wasn't involved in Glasgow Derby]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194330</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-asks-why-experienced-celtic-player-wasnt-involved-in-glasgow-derby/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic emerged last Sunday with their Scottish Premiership title aspirations unscathed following a dramatic 3-3 draw at Ibrox. Daizen Maeda, Matt O’Riley and Adam Idah...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘No doubt’: Simon Jordan delivers his verdict on how Celtic would perform in the English Premier League]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194307</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/simon-jordan-delivers-his-verdict-on-how-celtic-would-perform-in-the-english-premier-league/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taking a break from the Glasgow Derby coverage for a second, the discussion has now turned to how Celtic would perform if they ever made...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic title race reality as Neil Lennon gets honest over chances]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194322</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-celtic-title-race-reality-as-neil-lennon-gets-honest-over-chances/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are in a title race that could go down to the final stages of the season as they compete with Rangers for the Scottish...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Absolutely destroyed’: John Hartson says one Rangers player was ‘ripped to shreds’ in Celtic draw]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194315</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/john-hartson-says-one-rangers-player-was-absolutely-destroyed-in-celtic-draw/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There were many standout performers for Celtic in the draw with Rangers at Ibrox on Sunday. Cameron Carter-Vickers was a rock in the defence, Brendan...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton's surprising verdict on why Celtic's final Glasgow Derby won't decide league title]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194295</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-suttons-surprising-verdict-on-why-celtics-final-glasgow-derby-wont-decide-league-title/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have six vital league matches remaining as they aim to win the Scottish Premiership title following a dramatic draw at Ibrox last weekend. In...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I’ll be honest’: Pat Nevin makes Celtic title claim after watching the draw with Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194232</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/pat-nevin-makes-celtic-title-claim-after-watching-the-draw-with-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s draw with Rangers on Sunday has now opened up the debate on who is the favourite to win the Scottish Premiership now. With just...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero speaks after return to Parkhead confirmed for Borussia Dortmund Legends match]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194326</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-hero-speaks-after-return-to-parkhead-confirmed-for-borussia-dortmund-legends-match/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T14:40:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans are gearing up for a momentous end to the campaign that will hopefully conclude with a domestic double arriving at Paradise. Brendan Rodgers’...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REVEALED: REF NAMED FOR SAINTS CLASH]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119471</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/revealed-ref-named-for-saints-clash/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T14:03:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[STEVEN McLEAN will take charge of Celtic’s Premiership encounter with St Mirren at Parkhead on Saturday afternoon. After the repercussions concerning onfield official John Beaton and VAR colleague Nick Walsh following the controversial 3-3 draw at Ibrox on Sunday, the champions are gearing up for the first of six remaining games in their quest for [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Graeme Souness makes bizarre Celtic claim despite Brendan Rodgers' post-match Rangers comments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194301</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/graeme-souness-makes-bizarre-celtic-claim-despite-brendan-rodgers-post-match-rangers-comments/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fallout of the Glasgow Derby continues today as pundits and media people have their say on how Celtic and Rangers performed in the 3-3...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Officials and VAR confirmed as Celtic take on St Mirren in the Scottish Premiership]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194291</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/officials-and-var-confirmed-as-celtic-take-on-st-mirren-in-the-scottish-premiership/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic return to Scottish Premiership action this weekend against St Mirren as they continue their fight for a third successive title. Last time out, the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I must admit’: Peter Grant was ‘stunned’ at what Philippe Clement did at full-time after Celtic draw]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194270</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/peter-grant-admits-he-was-stunned-at-what-philippe-clement-did-at-full-time-after-celtic-draw/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Sunday Glasgow Derby is one that, for the Celtic fans at least, will be talked about for all the wrong reasons. From the VAR...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Stewart raises serious question about Nick Walsh's role in Celtic Rangers penalty incident]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194298</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/michael-stewart-raises-serious-question-about-nick-walshs-role-in-celtic-rangers-penalty-incident/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will now focus on upcoming fixtures following a powderkeg Glasgow Derby clash at Ibrox that ended all square. The Bhoys took the lead after...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Withdraw Ibrox safety licence as they withdraw moral hazard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119467</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/withdraw-ibrox-safety-licence-as-they-withdraw-moral-hazard/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T11:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What happens if you provide cover for a fan who threw shards of glass onto the Ibrox goalmouth before Joe Hart plays in goal?  It happens again.  When this occurred two years ago, Newco told Celtic their CCTV system did not cover the area the shards were thrown from.  The perpetrator was not identified and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton raises a big Ibrox VAR ‘problem’ after what he saw at Rangers vs Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194287</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-raises-a-big-ibrox-var-problem-after-what-he-saw-at-rangers-vs-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton has raised a serious concern over the VAR footage shown to John Beaton in Sunday’s 3-3 draw between Celtic and Rangers. Celtic were...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon refutes what Philippe Clement said after Glasgow Derby draw with Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194285</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/neil-lennon-refutes-what-philippe-clement-said-after-glasgow-derby-draw-with-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are now turning their focus elsewhere following a dramatic Glasgow Derby stalemate last weekend at Ibrox. We all now know the tale of the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QUESTION FOR Mr BEATON]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119464</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/question-for-mr-beaton/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T09:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NO-ONE mentioned a curious flashpoint moment involving referee John Beaton after he had awarded the Ibrox club a contentious penalty-kick in Sunday’s highly-charged 3-3 draw with Celtic. Ten minutes into the second-half, with the champions deservedly two goals ahead, the match official flashed a yellow card at serial diver Fabio Silva after he had once again [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic demand answers from SFA over key incident that occured at Ibrox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194282</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-demand-answers-from-sfa-over-key-incident-that-occured-at-ibrox/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans will now finally be settling down after a whirlwind clash against Rangers at Ibrox last weekend that ended in a 3-3 draw. Like...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[100% shot accuracy, six duels won: ‘Outstanding’ Celtic player was excellent vs Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194241</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/100-shot-accuracy-six-duels-won-outstanding-celtic-player-was-excellent-vs-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All the fallout and the controversy of the incidents in the 3-3 Glasgow Derby draw between Celtic and Rangers has actually overshadowed one thing. Just...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SILVA ‘EMBARRASSING’, SOUNESS ‘UTTER NONSENSE’: SUTTY FIRES BACK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119462</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/silva-embarrassing-souness-utter-nonsense-sutty-fires-back/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T07:34:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic goal hero Chris Sutton has waded into the Ibrox penalty-kick controversy by labelling the antics of Rangers striker Fabio Silva as “embarrassing”. The on-loan Wolves player appeared to have taken a theatrical dive to earn his side a penalty-kick shortly after the interval with the champions leading 2-0 in Sunday’s dramatic six-goal stalemate. Referee [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Callum McGregor delivers coy verdict on how injury issues will impact Celtic run-in]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194267</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/callum-mcgregor-delivers-coy-verdict-on-how-injury-issues-will-impact-celtic-run-in/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will be keen to shift the dial to preparations for our clash against St Mirren this weekend following the Glasgow Derby last Sunday. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Markus Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘It was unbelievable’: Peter Grant on the Rangers fans’ reaction when Fabio Silva won a penalty vs Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=194274</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/unbelievable-peter-grant-on-the-rangers-fans-reaction-when-fabio-silva-won-a-penalty-vs-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T06:41:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The furore over the decision to award Rangers a penalty in the 3-3 draw with Celtic is likely to continue for the rest of this...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SPOT OF BOTHER: CELTIC DEMAND SFA ANSWERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=119458</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/spot-of-bother-celtic-demand-sfa-answers/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T06:37:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC are awaiting answers from the SFA in the fall-out of Rangers’ controversial penalty-kick award in the 3-3 draw at Ibrox on Sunday. The Hoops hierarchy have written to Scottish football rulers for clarification over the flashpoint incident 10 minutes after the interval with the champions two goals ahead. The Parkhead bosses are convinced referee [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic want to sign £4 million-rated player in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45945</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-4-million-player-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T23:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The defeat at the hands of Lazio was further proof of Celtic’s need to strengthen in the January transfer window. The club might have brought in nine new faces in the summer but a lot of people feel that the team has taken a step back since last season, when they breezed past the competition […]
Celtic want to sign £4 million-rated player in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers sends clear message Celtic board must not ignore]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45941</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/brendan-rodgers-message-celtic-board/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T21:35:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s fate in Europe for this season is sealed after their 2-0 defeat at the hands of Lazio. The result means that the Hoops are guaranteed to finish bottom of their group in the UEFA Champions League. That also means that they will not be dropping down to the Europa League, something that should have […]
Brendan Rodgers sends clear message Celtic board must not ignore - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton publicly criticises Celtic after loss to Lazio]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45938</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/chris-sutton-celtic-loss-lazio/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T20:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic lost 2-0 away in Rome to Lazio. The Hoops were in the match for a long time before Ciro Immobile came off the bench to score a brace and put the game to bed. The result means that not only are Brendan Rodgers’ side out of the Champions League following the group stages but […]
Chris Sutton publicly criticises Celtic after loss to Lazio - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed £7 million Jeremie Frimpong windfall news]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45933</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-jeremie-frimpong-windfall-news/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremie Frimpong’s rise at Bayer Leverkusen has been fascinating, to say the least. The Dutchman had shown a lot of quality going forward at Celtic as well but not many could have foreseen him becoming one of the most prolific wingbacks in Europe just a few years later. That is exactly what has happened under […]
Celtic handed £7 million Jeremie Frimpong windfall news - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic told 29-goal striker is good enough amid links]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45930</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/celtic-told-29-goal-striker-good-enough/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T13:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to add to their options up top this January. Kyogo has done well once again but he is not scoring as frequently as he was last season. On the other hand, Oh Hyeon-gyu has been inconsistent as well and is not at the level required to start for the Hoops right now. There […]
Celtic told 29-goal striker is good enough amid links - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anderlecht consider making offer for Celtic standout in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45927</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/28/anderlecht-offer-celtic-standout-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T11:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have not had the greatest campaign till now. They were eliminated early from the Scottish League Cup and while they do lead the Premiership, their performances and results have been somewhat inconsistent. Almost half a season on, it feels like the Hoops are still finding their feet under the management of Brendan Rodgers and […]
Anderlecht consider making offer for Celtic standout in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serie A club want to sign Celtic player amid contract worry]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45907</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/serie-club-want-celtic-player-contract/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T22:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic fans hope for more quality players arriving there could be a problem with others heading for the exit door. It seems pretty clear that Brendan Rodgers wants to make the size of the squad more manageable over the next couple of transfer windows and departures are expected. But there is a risk of […]
Serie A club want to sign Celtic player amid contract worry - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur step up bid to sign Celtic-linked player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45918</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/tottenham-hotspur-bid-sign-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur made a fantastic start to the season under the management of Ange Postecoglou. With Harry Kane leaving the club in the summer for Bayern Munich, most expected them to struggle. Instead, they appeared to be putting up an unlikely title challenge and were sitting atop the Premier League table not too long ago. […]
Tottenham Hotspur step up bid to sign Celtic-linked player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boost in race to sign £11 million Real Madrid player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45914</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/celtic-boost-real-madrid-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T19:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to sign a goalkeeper in the near future. It is quite clear that Joe Hart is not the long-term solution between the posts. The Englishman’s performances have been criticised lately. Also, he is set to turn 37 years of age before this season comes to an end. So, while he has done a […]
Celtic boost in race to sign £11 million Real Madrid player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazio boss Maurizio Sarri makes fantastic Celtic claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45910</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/lazio-boss-maurizio-sarri-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T18:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By now, Celtic fans have accepted that Brendan Rodgers’ side are most probably not going through or even finishing third in their group in the UEFA Champions League. It would be a positive step to get a win in the competition though. It has been quite some time since the Hoops won at this level. […]
Lazio boss Maurizio Sarri makes fantastic Celtic claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic tipped to go for 28-year-old Premiership striker]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45904</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/celtic-tipped-go-premiership-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T12:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans breathed a sigh of relief as the Rangers dropped points at the weekend against Aberdeen. In fact, it took a late penalty for them to even come out with a draw from the game. That means that the Hoops will maintain their strong position at the top of the Scottish Premiership table. That […]
Celtic tipped to go for 28-year-old Premiership striker - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£7.5 million Mathias Kvistgaarden to Celtic transfer update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45900</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/27/mathias-kvistgaarden-celtic-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T10:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to sign a striker in January. On one hand, we have seen the club struggle for goals in some games this season. When the opposition puts up a resolute defence, the Hoops do not appear to have a lot of answers other than Kyogo, Matt O’Riley or Luis Palma. On the other hand, […]
£7.5 million Mathias Kvistgaarden to Celtic transfer update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur have been eyeing Celtic superstar]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45896</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/tottenham-hotspur-eyeing-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T23:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou made the move to Tottenham Hotspur in the summer and it was only a matter of time before the Australian was linked with a reunion with some Celtic players. The manager enjoyed a lot of success at Parkhead, even though he was at the club for just two seasons, and won five trophies […]
Tottenham Hotspur have been eyeing Celtic superstar - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John McGinn claims he spoke to Celtic players about manager]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45890</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/john-mcginn-spoke-celtic-players/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T21:35:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most Celtic fans will remember how the club missed out on the opportunity to sign John McGinn some years back. The Scot grew up supporting the Hoops but a move to Parkhead failed to materialise even though it had looked close and he ended up moving down south to join Aston Villa. McGinn has risen […]
John McGinn claims he spoke to Celtic players about manager - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic must consider signing striker from Premiership rivals]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45886</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-signing-striker-premiership-rivals/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T20:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there is one position where Celtic need to strengthen during the upcoming January transfer window, it is striker. The Hoops have been pretty inconsistent in front of goal this season so far. Of course, there are games when they can go out and score six times. But then, on days they are having a […]
Celtic must consider signing striker from Premiership rivals - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic legend takes dig at Rangers player for diving]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45884</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-legend-rangers-player-diving/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T18:35:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Celtic drew 1-1 against Motherwell, the Rangers were handed a major chance to get back into the title race. All they needed to do was win their games in hand and they would be just three points behind the Hoops in the league table. We have seen the Ibrox side not perform at their […]
Celtic legend takes dig at Rangers player for diving - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player criticised after draw against Motherwell]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45881</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/celtic-player-criticised-draw-motherwell/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T12:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Titles are not decided this early in the season. That has been proven once again. Not too long ago, Celtic were sitting seven points clear at the top of the Premiership table and most fans felt that the league was pretty much in the bag with the Rangers struggling for any kind of form.  It […]
Celtic player criticised after draw against Motherwell - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giorgio Chiellini makes superb claim about Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45874</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/26/giorgio-chiellini-claim-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T10:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Giorgio Chiellini is one of the best defenders of all time and he had some pretty positive comments about Celtic Park recently. The 39-year-old spent the majority of his career playing for Juventus and won more silverware there than one should try to count. Overall, he made more […]
Giorgio Chiellini makes superb claim about Celtic Park - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s problem is very clear and needs solving quick]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45870</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/celtic-problem-needs-solving-quick/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T19:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two more dropped points mean that Celtic have well and truly allowed the Rangers to get back into the title race. A lead which once stood at seven points, could be reduced to three if Philippe Clement’s side are able to win their games in hand. And the sad thing is that the Hoops have […]
Celtic’s problem is very clear and needs solving quick - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic problem after draw]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45866</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/brendan-rodgers-celtic-problem-draw/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T18:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was not the result Celtic were looking for, as they dropped two valuable points against Motherwell. David Turnbull’s goal appeared to have won it for the Hoops but the visitors equalised in the 90th minute and it ended 1-1. That means that if the Rangers win their games in hand, the gap will be […]
Brendan Rodgers addresses Celtic problem after draw - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hollywood superstar pictured wearing Celtic jersey]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45861</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/hollywood-pictured-wearing-celtic-jersey/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T12:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be safe to say that Celtic have their fair share of famous fans. Rod Stewart is the first name that comes to most people’s minds, one of the best-selling music artists in history. Lewis Capaldi is another popular musician known to support the Hoops. And several A-list celebrities like Gerard Butler, Snoop Dogg, […]
Hollywood superstar pictured wearing Celtic jersey - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic pushing for priority signing in January window]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45859</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/25/celtic-priority-signing-january-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T09:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s January transfer window is expected to be a busy one. The club might have made nine signings in the summer, seven arriving on a permanent basis and two on loan, but there are still holes in Brendan Rodgers’ squad that need to be filled. On the other hand, there are way too many players […]
Celtic pushing for priority signing in January window - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable source offers Sydney van Hooijdonk to Celtic update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45854</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/reliable-sydney-van-hooijdonk-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T22:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are believed to be on the lookout for a striker in the January transfer window. There might be a few reasons behind that. Firstly, both Kyogo and Oh Hyeon-gyu might be unavailable for a considerable length of time early next year due to the AFC Asian Cup. They are the club’s two options to […]
Reliable source offers Sydney van Hooijdonk to Celtic update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou claims Celtic success gets dismissed]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45852</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/24/ange-postecoglou-claims-celtic-success/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T21:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has proven to be a major success in the Premier League since swapping Celtic for Tottenham Hotspur. Of course, a lot of fans were not happy to see him depart after just two years at Parkhead. But he has been very respectful about the club even after leaving. And it is hard not […]
Ange Postecoglou claims Celtic success gets dismissed - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>