<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-11-22T18:13:29.357Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers makes Virgil van Dijk claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45794</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/22/celtic-brendan-rodgers-virgil-van-dijk/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T18:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will know the importance of the upcoming January transfer window. There is already a need to strengthen in some positions across the pitch. On the other hand, the AFC Asian Cup, which is scheduled to start in January of next year, makes things interesting as well. There are quite a few of the club’s […]
Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers makes Virgil van Dijk claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic scout highly-rated defender wanted by EPL clubs; likely to leave in January]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181147</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-scout-defender-sam-curtis-as-premier-league-clubs-show-interest-january-exit-likely/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T17:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with a move for St Patrick’s Athletic defender Sam Curtis. As reported by 90min, Celtic have recently scouted the right-back with...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key Celtic duo won't return to training until Friday with Motherwell test looming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181163</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/key-celtic-duo-wont-return-to-training-until-friday-with-motherwell-test-looming/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T17:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic stars Alistair Johnston and Luis Palma won’t be back at club training until Friday, giving them little time to prepare for the visit of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Shining light"; Celtic star barely used by Rodgers lauded by homeland media for int'l display]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181150</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-the-irish-media-are-saying-about-celtics-mikey-johnston-after-big-chance-to-impress/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T16:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mikey Johnston has found it difficult at Celtic this season after his return from a productive loan in Portugal last term. Finding himself injured during...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charlie Mulgrew names surprising Celtic player of the year contender]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181114</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/charlie-mulgrews-glowing-liam-scales-verdict-after-celtic-impact/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T16:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Charlie Mulgrew has praised Liam Scales for his performances at Celtic this season with the Republic of Ireland international cementing himself as a first-team regular....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The latest on Paulo Bernardo ahead of big Celtic push]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181084</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-latest-on-paulo-bernardo-ahead-of-big-celtic-push/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T15:57:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paulo Bernardo has continued his Portugal under-21 national team starting streak after featuring against Greece on Monday. Bernardo has now started in five consecutive games...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS IN ‘FINAL DECISION’ STANCE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114458</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-in-final-decision-stance/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T15:46:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS reinforced the need to add quality to his Celtic squad in the January transfer window when he spoke at the club’s AGM at Parkhead today. The Hoops boss has already admitted players will be coming and going after the turn of the year as he reshapes his pool for the second half of the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss drops potential Jota transfer return hint]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45786</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/22/celtic-boss-jota-transfer-return/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T15:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s most high-profile exit in the summer transfer window was that of Jota. The Portuguese winger had established himself as one of the club’s most important players over his two seasons at Parkhead. He would leave in a £25 million move to join Al-Ittihad. But things have not gone as he would have hoped. Jota […]
Celtic boss drops potential Jota transfer return hint - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Chief Financial Officer provides important new context on the club's £72m bank balance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181129</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-chief-financial-officer-provides-important-new-context-on-the-clubs-72m-bank-balance/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T15:26:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Chief Financial Officer Chris McKay has provided new details on why the club’s bank balance in year-end accounts was so high. In Celtic’s annual...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic publish rare new interviews with Peter Lawwell, Michael Nicholson and Chris McKay]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181123</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-publish-rare-new-interviews-with-peter-lawwell-michael-nicholson-and-chris-mckay/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T14:55:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have uploaded new video interviews with chairman Peter Lawwell and chief executive Michael Nicholson on the day the club held their 2023 AGM. Celtic...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers refutes Celtic transfer myth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181117</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-refutes-celtic-transfer-myth/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T14:24:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has stated no players have been pushed onto him during his second spell at the club after concerns were raised at...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Nicholson and Peter Lawwell take Rangers digs at Celtic AGM but a serious point is made]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181111</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/michael-nicholson-and-peter-lawwell-take-rangers-digs-at-celtic-agm-but-a-serious-point-is-made/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T13:53:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Chief Executive Michael Nicholson got a big laugh from the audience at today’s AGM with a quip about how many penalties Rangers win. Nicholson...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Lawwell defends significant increase in Celtic director salaries at AGM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181100</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/peter-lawwell-defends-significant-increase-in-celtic-director-salaries-at-agm/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T13:24:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic chairman Peter Lawwell has defended the increasing salaries paid to club directors in the last financial year. Celtic’s annual report for the financial year...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player ready to leave the club in January window]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45783</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/22/celtic-player-ready-leave-club-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T13:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic squad could undergo some changes in the upcoming January transfer window. Brendan Rodgers appears to have way too many players available to him right now and has not been able to give game time to a number of them. So, expect more to head out of Parkhead rather than arrive in the winter. […]
Celtic player ready to leave the club in January window - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers and Michael Nicholson pledge action on squad issues, investment at Celtic AGM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181093</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-and-michael-nicholson-pledge-action-on-squad-issues-january-investment-at-celtic-agm/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T12:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic 2023 AGM is underway and after a review of the last calendar year with video packages and the passage of routine resolutions, questions...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inevitable cull will see Mikey flourish elsewhere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114435</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/inevitable-cull-will-see-mikey-flourish-elsewhere/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T12:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You and I have talked about Mikey Johnston for over five years.  As a teenager, he was pivotal in a win at Ibrox early in our most recent nine-in-a-row season and seemed set for the top.  Just two days before that game we signed Mohamed Elyounoussi on loan, and the Norwegian international edged ahead of [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S UEFA FINES TOTAL OVER £65,000]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114456</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtics-uefa-fines-total-over-65000/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T11:57:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have been hit with £25,240.45 worth of fines by UEFA following fan misbehaviour in the Champions League 2-2 draw with Atletico Madrid at Parkhead. The latest penalty brings the club’s total financial punishment to a staggering £65,710.94 for their involvement in this season’s Champions League. The Hoops have been hit hard again after last [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star makes first start in over 5 months after fitness comeback]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181073</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/marco-tilio-takes-a-big-step-forward-after-celtic-concerns/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T11:53:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marco Tilio has provided Brendan Rodgers with a promising boost on the injury front by starting for the Australia under-23 national team.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Came up in recruitment meeting"; Pundits have their say on Celtic links with exciting striker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181060</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/peter-grant-delivers-verdict-on-what-hes-hearing-about-celtic-and-sydney-van-hooijdonk/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T10:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant and Stephen McGinn have weighed in on Sydney van Hooijdonk’s potential move to Celtic in January. Grant played with Sydney’s father, Pierre, at...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything you need to know about today's Celtic AGM; Euro ambition, Green Brigade ban]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181063</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/everything-you-need-to-know-about-todays-celtic-agm-euro-ambition-green-brigade-ban/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T10:23:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2023 edition of the Celtic Annual General Meeting (AGM) takes place on Wednesday and several important topics surrounding the club are sure to come...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GREEN LIGHT FOR YUKI EXIT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114433</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/green-light-for-yuki-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T09:48:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS is poised to give the green light to a loan move for Yuki Kobayashi, as CQN forecast last month. The Japanese centre-back has yet to make a competitive appearance since the Irishman took over from Spurs-bound Ange Postecoglou in June. The Greek-Australian gaffer signed Kobayashi in January after the 23-year-old defender came out [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘ON ANOTHER DAY, I GET MY LEG BROKEN,’ REFLECTIONS FROM O’RILEY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114431</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/on-another-day-i-get-my-leg-broken-reflections-from-oriley/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T08:37:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY celebrated his 23rd birthday yesterday in the aftermath of glowing tributes following his debut for Denmark senior team. The Celtic playmaker turned in his usual polished performance, but couldn’t prevent his adopted nation sliding to a 2-0 loss to Northern Ireland in Belfast, as CQN reported. The result was a mere hiccup for the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I HAD A BIT OF FUN,’ FORGOTTEN CELT SENDS RODGERS REMINDER]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114427</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-had-a-bit-of-fun-forgotten-celt-sends-rodgers-reminder/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T07:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MIKEY JOHNSTON won the Man of the Match award in the Republic of Ireland’s 1-1 draw with New Zealand at the Aviva Stadium in Dublin last night. However, the Celtic winger, who has figured in only 25 minutes for the champions in this campaign, admitted he is still off the pace as far as the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC STRIKER AT CROSSROADS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114422</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-striker-at-crossroads/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T06:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOHNNY KENNY is due to return to Celtic a week tomorrow when his loan deal at Shamrock Rovers expires. The Republic of Ireland Under-21 striker cost the champions £125,000 when they signed him from Sligo Rovers in January 2022, but is still awaiting his first-team debut. Kenny joined the Dublin outfit at the start of the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE BERTIE AULD: PART EIGHT: ‘CAESAR, DINO, OCEANS AND ME’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=86852</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-unforgettable-bertie-auld-part-eight-caesar-dino-oceans-and-me/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T05:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bertie Auld was the most irrepressible Celtic player of Jock Stein’s all-conquering team of the sixties. CQN are celebrating the life and incredible times of the club legend in an EXCLUSIVE series with extracts from his best-selling autobiography, ‘A Bhoy Called Bertie’, co-authored by his friend and writer Alex Gordon. The remarkable life story continues [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Struggling Celtic player sends message to Brendan Rodgers]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45778</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/21/struggling-celtic-player-message-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T23:05:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has a difficult job at Celtic right now. The squad size is not ideal and there are way too many players in certain positions. It would make sense for the club to part ways with some in the upcoming January transfer window. But at the same time, it is also important to make […]
Struggling Celtic player sends message to Brendan Rodgers - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic must try to sign Real Madrid superstar’s brother]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45774</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/21/celtic-must-sign-real-madrid-brother/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T21:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are always on the lookout for bright young talents. We saw the club sign nine players in the summer transfer window, all of them highly-rated youngsters, except for Nat Phillips, who was brought in on loan from Liverpool for just the first half of the season as a result of the number of injuries […]
Celtic must try to sign Real Madrid superstar’s brother - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic tipped to sign £4 million player in January window]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45771</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/21/celtic-tipped-sign-january-window/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T20:05:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic might have signed nine players in the summer transfer window, but the Hoops are expected to be pretty active in January as well. On one hand, there are a few positions in this current squad where they still need to improve. On the other hand, it feels like there are quite a few who […]
Celtic tipped to sign £4 million player in January window - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kristoffer Ajer makes fantastic admission about Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45769</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/21/kristoffer-ajer-makes-admission-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T18:35:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kristoffer Ajer had a very successful time at Celtic, enjoying a rise from being a young talent to a regular starter for the Hoops. He would leave the club in the summer of 2021 in order to make a move to the Premier League, as the Norwegian joined Brentford. He remains there to this day […]
Kristoffer Ajer makes fantastic admission about Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[English legend admits he has always wanted Celtic job]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45767</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/21/english-legend-wanted-celtic-job/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T17:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Ange Postecoglou decided to leave Celtic in the summer in order to take the Tottenham Hotspur job, the fans were certainly worried about the future. It would be a tough job to replace the Australian. The club did go out and bring in the best option available in the form of Brendan Rodgers. Rodgers […]
English legend admits he has always wanted Celtic job - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic want to sign striker also eyed by Leeds United]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45762</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/21/celtic-striker-eyed-leeds-united/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T13:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have spread their scouting network further and wider in recent years, especially following Ange Postecoglou’s appointment as manager in 2021. The Australian has left since then to join Tottenham Hotspur, but the Hoops have remained true to their transfer policy. And they are now being linked with a South African centre-forward. Celtic certainly need […]
Celtic want to sign striker also eyed by Leeds United - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PL Profit and Sustainability Rules, some window dressing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114420</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/pl-profit-and-sustainability-rules-some-window-dressing/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T12:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not buying the sense of aggrievement from Everton over their 10-point deduction for failing FA Premier League Profit and Sustainability Rules (PSR).  It is the harshest penalty yet given out by the League and puts Everton in the relegation zone, but they are just two points from safety and in sufficiently good form to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JINXED CELT’S REASONS TO BE CHEERFUL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114416</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/jinxed-celts-reasons-to-be-cheerful/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T07:40:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE at last has something to celebrate in the midst of an injury-hampered campaign. Celtic’s Japanese midfielder turns 26 today and is hoping for a change of fortune in the new year. Hatate was taken off early in the 2-2 Champions League draw with Atletico Madrid last month and extensive medical examinations highlighted hamstring [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC EYE WONDERBOY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114413</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-eye-wonderboy/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T07:17:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC are keeping tabs on South African teen sensation Luke Baartman. The eye-catching striker only made his first-team debut for Cape Town Spurs last month and already a host of admirers have been alerted to his talents. The South African Under-17 forward, who is still at school, netted his first goal against Kaiser Chiefs a [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STRIFE O’RILEY: EX-CELT RUINS DEBUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114408</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/strife-oriley-ex-celt-ruins-debut/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T06:40:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY suffered a shock defeat as Northern Ireland wrecked his Denmark debut in Belfast last night. The Celtic midfielder was praised for his performance, but couldn’t prevent a 2-0 loss in the final Euro 2024 qualifier with the Danes already among the countries who have already sealed their place in next summer’s soccer showpiece in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE BERTIE AULD: PART SEVEN: ‘BACK TO CELTIC – AND TAKING A WAGE CUT’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=86841</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-unforgettable-bertie-auld-part-seven-back-to-celtic-and-taking-a-wage-cut/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T05:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bertie Auld was the heartbeat of the Celtic side that conquered all in the sixties. CQN are celebrating the life and incredible times of the club legend in an EXCLUSIVE series with extracts from his best-selling autobiography, ‘A Bhoy Called Bertie’, co-authored by his friend and writer Alex Gordon. The remarkable story continues with [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Northern Irish legend claims Celtic player is like Frank Lampard]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45757</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/20/northern-irish-celtic-frank-lampard/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T23:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frank Lampard is one of the best midfielders in the history of the game. The Englishman enjoyed a tremendous career at Chelsea and made more than a hundred appearances for the England national team. He also played for teams like Manchester City, West Ham United, Swansea City and New York City FC. He was inducted […]
Northern Irish legend claims Celtic player is like Frank Lampard - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mohamed Elyounoussi makes Celtic claim after heroics]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45753</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/20/mohamed-elyounoussi-celtic-claim-heroics/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T21:05:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mohamed Elyounoussi probably does not get enough credit for how well he did at Celtic. A large reason behind that is that his first season with the club was filled with injuries and was also called off in the middle. The second one was the 2020/21 campaign. The Norwegian was one of the few shining […]
Mohamed Elyounoussi makes Celtic claim after heroics - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Son Heung-min sent clear message to Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45751</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/20/son-heung-min-message-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T19:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A number of Celtic players are away on international duty right now. Of course, there is always in the back of the fans’ minds that they could pick up an injury while representing their national teams. But at the same time, it is also a great opportunity for them to pick up experience and get […]
Son Heung-min sent clear message to Celtic player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star shines on international duty with man of the match honour in multi-goal thriller]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181043</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-captain-callum-mcgregor-earns-plaudits-for-international-display/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T19:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic captain Callum McGregor last night earned man of the match in Scotland’s 3-3 draw with Norway. McGregor played 89 minutes for Steve Clarke’s side,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[English Championship boss says Celtic have "every manager's dream" on their hands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181038</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/english-championship-boss-says-celtic-have-every-managers-dream-on-their-hands/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T18:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Southampton manager Russell Martin has hailed Celtic midfielder Matt O’Riley as a consummate professional for the time the pair spent together at MK Dons. Martin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mohamed Elyounoussi enjoys Celtic memories on return to Scotland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181031</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/mohamed-elyounoussi-enjoys-celtic-memories-on-return-to-scotland/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T18:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic winger Mohamed Elyounoussi has revealed that his success with Celtic at Hampden inspired him to score last night against Scotland for Norway.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player suffers injury concern on international duty]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45745</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/20/celtic-injury-concern-international-duty/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T18:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already dealt with and continue to deal with a number of fitness issues. Just at this moment, they have three key starters out of action for the foreseeable future in the form of Reo Hatate, Daizen Maeda and Liel Abada. Thus, Brendan Rodgers’ side deserve a lot of credit for continuing to produce […]
Celtic player suffers injury concern on international duty - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic make contact about crowd-pleasing January signing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181006</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/italian-newspaper-provides-more-on-celtic-and-sydney-van-hooijdonk-speculation/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T17:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have reportedly enquired about a move for Bologna striker Syndey van Hooijdonk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pundit compares Celtic squad to Rangers with firm verdict; two players who will worry Clement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180982</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/davie-provan-says-celtic-look-much-stronger-than-rangers-duo-noted-as-particular-problem-for-clement/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T17:31:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic winger Davie Provan has highlighted Celtic’s squad depth with Liel Abada and Daizen Maeda in particular catching the Scotsman’s eye. Provan, who played...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic left waiting on injury situation after international manager's comments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=181002</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-left-waiting-on-luis-palma-situation-as-honduras-boss-flags-up-concern/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T15:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic winger Luis Palma has picked up an injury whilst on international duty for Honduras.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic summer signing could play for another club before he makes Bhoys debut]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180987</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/marco-tilios-quest-to-play-for-celtic-could-take-a-detour/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic winger Marco Tilio has admitted that he would be open to a loan spell away from the Hoops if he can't break into the first team before January.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Grown a lot"; Hyeongyu Oh talks up the Celtic experience to South Korean media]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180994</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/hyeongyu-oh-talks-up-the-celtic-experience-to-south-korean-media/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T14:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic striker Hyengou Oh has spoken about how Scottish football has helped him become a more physical player. Oh is currently preparing for a World...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Shearer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC LEADER’S HECTIC SCHEDULE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114404</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-leaders-hectic-schedule/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T14:33:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC skipper Callum McGregor faces another hectic summer schedule as Scotland brought down the curtain on the Euro 2024 qualifying campaign in the 3-3 draw with Norway at Hampden last night. The influential Hoops midfield leader will be aiming to be involved in the Scottish Cup Final at Hampden on the iconic date of May [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic make first enquiries for £4 million-rated striker]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45741</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/20/celtic-make-first-enquiries-striker/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T14:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic might need to sign a striker in the upcoming January transfer window. Kyogo remains the first-choice and the Japanese forward continues to deliver the goods up top for the Hoops. On the other hand, after a slow start under the management of Brendan Rodgers, Oh Hyeon-gyu is starting to find the back of the […]
Celtic make first enquiries for £4 million-rated striker - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player considering leaving on loan in January]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45736</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/20/celtic-player-leaving-loan-january/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T12:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic might still have some areas where they need to improve but overall, Brendan Rodgers has a lot of options to pick his starting XI from. There are some players who are struggling to get into the team though and departing Parkhead, on loan or on a permanent basis, might be the right step for […]
Celtic player considering leaving on loan in January - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rationalising the wingers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114391</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rationalising-the-wingers/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T12:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the time, you and I talked about the hoard of wingers at the club after the summer’s transfer business.  James Forrest, Mikey Johnston, Liel Abada, Daizen Maeda, Luis Palma, Yang and Marco Tilio.  That’s seven players for two starting spots; it was always going to be a handful keeping everyone happy.  Marco got his [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEW BHOY POISED TO LEAD CELTIC CLEAR-OUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114384</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/new-bhoy-poised-to-lead-celtic-clear-out/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T07:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MARCO TILIO, who hasn’t figured in the Celtic first team since his June arrival, could be heading for the Hoops exit. The Australian winger, a £3million recruit on a five-year deal from Melbourne City, has been hampered with injury and his career has stalled at the champions. Now the 22-year-old forward, who played for 10 [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE BERTIE AULD: PART SIX: ‘WHY I SAID NO TO EVERTON AND YES TO BIRMINGHAM’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=86808</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-unforgettable-bertie-auld-part-six-why-i-said-no-to-everton-and-yes-to-birmingham/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-20T05:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bertie Auld was tailor-made for a Celtic team that played with a swashbuckling sense of adventure. CQN are celebrating the life and incredible times of the Hoops legend in an EXCLUSIVE series with extracts from his best-selling autobiography, ‘A Bhoy Called Bertie’, co-authored by his friend and writer Alex Gordon. The story continues with [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic appear to have pulled off absolute transfer masterstroke]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45689</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/19/celtic-absolute-transfer-masterstroke/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T22:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The international break can be quite mixed for Celtic fans. On one hand, it is pleasing to see the club’s players getting recognition with their national teams. But there is always a worry over them potentially getting injured while away. The Hoops already have enough fitness problems to deal with as it is. But one […]
Celtic appear to have pulled off absolute transfer masterstroke - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers compares Celtic duo with Liverpool icons]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45727</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/19/brendan-rodgers-celtic-duo-liverpool/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T21:05:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has been at some top clubs over the course of his career and has a result, he has gotten the opportunity to work with many world-class players. Of course, the Northern Irishman has won most of his silverware while at Celtic but that does not mean that he has not had success elsewhere. […]
Brendan Rodgers compares Celtic duo with Liverpool icons - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player told he will need to make Parkhead exit]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45723</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/19/celtic-player-told-parkhead-exit/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T19:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have a pretty deep roster at this point in time but there are quite a few players who did not seem to be a major part of Brendan Rodgers’ plans. It remains to be seen what the future holds for them. Of course, Liam Scales’ rise from the bottom of the centre-back pecking order […]
Celtic player told he will need to make Parkhead exit - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic keep SWPL pressure on Rangers with big Sunday win, surge clear of City]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180977</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-fc-women/celtic-keep-swpl-pressure-on-rangers-with-big-sunday-win-surge-clear-of-city/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T18:21:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SWPL increasingly looks like it could become a two-horse title race between Celtic and Rangers this season after a bad day for Glasgow City....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder admits uncertainty over Parkhead future]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45717</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/19/celtic-midfielder-admits-parkhead-future/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T18:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic already have a pretty big roster of players and one would expect them to part ways with some in the upcoming January transfer window. There are quite a few who are not getting enough chances right now and do not seem to have much hope of a better situation in the future either. For […]
Celtic midfielder admits uncertainty over Parkhead future - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers responds to class Kolo Toure comments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180972</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-responds-to-class-kolo-toure-comments/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T17:57:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has described Kolo Toure as one of the nicest people he has ever encountered in his life after glowing comments from...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Real signs of potential"; Chris Sutton is excited about the future of young Celtic duo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180965</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-sutton-delivers-verdict-on-celtic-progress-of-luis-palma-and-hyeongyu-oh/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton hasn’t hidden his feelings on the quality of the Celtic squad this season, nor his frustrations with recruitment during the summer transfer window....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers confirms "analytically brilliant" coach followed him to Celtic from Leicester]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180960</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-praises-analytically-brilliant-coach-who-followed-him-to-celtic-from-leicester/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T15:53:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers has been speaking about his backroom staff at Celtic this season, highlighting the hard work they put in to support him at Lennoxtown...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's 11 games in 38 days; full schedule, injuries, TV details, predictions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180953</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtics-11-games-in-38-days-full-schedule-injuries-tv-details-predictions/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T15:16:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re less than a week away from Celtic taking to the pitch again after the international break and it will be the start of a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic reportedly in the running to bring back former player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45713</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/19/celtic-bring-back-former-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T13:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already signed nine players since the arrival of Brendan Rodgers as the manager of the club, seven on a permanent basis and two on loan. Despite that, it does feel like there are some holes in the current squad which have not been filled. And hopefully, they will concentrate on those positions in […]
Celtic reportedly in the running to bring back former player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic interested in signing Tottenham Hotspur target]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45709</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/19/celtic-signing-tottenham-hotspur-target/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T10:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are always on the lookout for top young talents. In recent times, the club have spread their scouting network further and wider. Results have been somewhat mixed so far. Their signings in the first season under the management of Ange Postecoglou were spectacular. But since then, the success rate has been somewhat questionable. Many […]
Celtic interested in signing Tottenham Hotspur target - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SHOT-SHY CELT APOLOGISES TO BOSS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114375</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/shot-shy-celt-apologises-to-boss/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T09:53:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OH HYEON-GYU fired blanks in South Korea’s 5-0 win over Singapore in the World Cup qualifier – and insisted he was letting down coach Jurgen Klinsmann. The Celtic powerhouse is still awaiting his first goal at this level and missed out again after coming on as a 70th minute substitute in his country’s goal romp. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UNSEEN CELT EDGES CLOSER TO DEBUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114369</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/unseen-celt-edges-closer-to-debut/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T08:54:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MARCO TILIO edged closer to his long-awaited Celtic debut when he made a cameo appearance for Australia in their 2-1 win over Qatar last night. The winger, who cost £3million when he arrived from Melbourne City on a five-year deal in June, has been nowhere near a place in Brendan Rodgers’ matchday squad. Tilio has been [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MISERY FOR CELTIC DUO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114363</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/misery-for-celtic-duo/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T08:20:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LIAM SCALES and Mikey Johnston couldn’t prevent the Netherlands overcoming the Republic of Ireland 1-0 in Amsterdam last night. Stephen Kenny’s side’s dismal Euro 24 qualifying campaign came to a halt with Burnley’s on-loan Hoffenheim striker Wout Weghorst claiming the winner in the 12th minute. The Irish manager is under pressure after guiding his nation to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THE UNFORGETTABLE BERTIE AULD: PART FIVE: ‘SHATTERING BLOW AS CELTIC WANT TO SELL ME’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=86800</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/the-unforgettable-bertie-auld-part-five-shattering-blow-as-celtic-want-to-sell-me/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-19T05:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LISBON LION Bertie Auld was the most irrepressible Celtic player of Jock Stein’s all-conquering team of the sixties. CQN has been celebrating the life and incredible times of the Hoops legend in an EXCLUSIVE series with extracts from his best-selling autobiography, ‘A Bhoy Called Bertie’, co-authored by his friend and writer Alex Gordon. The story [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Liam Scales verdict as Celtic defender takes on difficult Dutch attack in Amsterdam]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180946</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-liam-scales-verdict-as-celtic-defender-takes-on-difficult-dutch-attack-in-amsterdam/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T21:46:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Liam Scales will be disappointed that his Republic of Ireland side suffered their latest defeat away to the Netherlands on Saturday night but...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Johnston international break bonus for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180941</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alistair-johnston-international-break-bonus-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T20:56:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star Alistair Johnston managed to avoid a gruelling short turnaround double-header against Jamaica after he was omitted from the Canada starting eleven on Saturday....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic 'keeping tabs' on breakthrough Premiership midfielder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180937</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-keeping-tabs-on-breakthrough-premiership-midfielder/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T20:18:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are one of the clubs credited with interest in Motherwell midfielder Lennon Miller after bursting onto the Scottish Premiership scene but there is a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cold water poured on £4m Celtic January transfer idea]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180934</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/chris-sutton-pours-cold-water-on-celtic-january-transfer-speculation/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T19:38:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker Chris Sutton doesn’t think the Bhoys will be spending significant amounts of cash on a forward in the January transfer window. Brendan...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two former Celtic players pictured back in Glasgow]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45705</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/18/two-former-celtic-players-glasgow/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T19:35:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are home to footballers from all around the world and it is always good to see former players back in town. On this occasion, a couple of them will be on the opposition side though. The Scotland national team are set to take on Norway soon in the UEFA EURO Qualifiers even though Steve […]
Two former Celtic players pictured back in Glasgow - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star confirmed for elite Saturday night test vs £35m Liverpool talent; how to watch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180930</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-defender-confirmed-for-elite-saturday-night-test-vs-netherlands-how-to-watch/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T18:57:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Liam Scales has been named in the Republic of Ireland team for a daunting away test against the Netherlands on Saturday night. Scales...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Brendan Rodgers told Kyogo to break through big Celtic barrier]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180927</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-brendan-rodgers-told-kyogo-to-break-through-big-celtic-barrier/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T18:18:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s fair to say Kyogo Furuhashi’s debut campaign in the UEFA Champions League with Celtic was a big disappointment for him. The Japanese star featured...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liam Scales makes superb claim about Celtic Park]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45699</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/18/liam-scales-makes-claim-celtic-park/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T18:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody at Celtic has enjoyed as meteoric a rise this season as Liam Scales. It is hard to believe that even a few months ago, most people believed that his Parkhead career was as good as over. He had spent the previous campaign out on loan at Aberdeen and even though he did well, there […]
Liam Scales makes superb claim about Celtic Park - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 duels won; Celtic star earns "excellent" verdict after first international start in a year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180921</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/reaction-and-verdict-as-celtic-star-cameron-carter-vickers-makes-first-usa-start-in-a-year/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T17:31:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[United States national team manager Gregg Berhalter was pleased with the performance of Celtic defender Cameron Carter-Vickers after his first international start in a year....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rising Celtic star now nominated for national overseas award alongside £100m man]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180917</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-liam-scales-now-nominated-for-national-award-alongside-two-top-premier-league-talents/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T16:43:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rise in status of Celtic defender Liam Scales continues apace this weekend after he was nominated for a national award in his native Ireland....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Funny Brendan Rodgers moment captures the spotlight in new Celtic video]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180914</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/funny-brendan-rodgers-moment-captures-the-spotlight-in-new-celtic-video/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T16:13:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic poked a bit of fun at Brendan Rodgers’ changing perception amongst supporters in the club’s new Christmas advert, with a moment that has become...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Celtic star qualifies for EURO 2024 and it could be huge for Bhoys form]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180908</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/another-celtic-star-qualifies-for-euro-2024-and-it-could-be-big-for-bhoys-form/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T15:25:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Scotland’s official qualification for next year’s European Championships booked a place for Callum McGregor and the rest of the Celtic contingent in the Scottish...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newcastle United in pole position for former Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45695</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/18/newcastle-united-pole-position-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T15:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have had a number top quality players over the years who have moved away after a few successful seasons at Parkhead. The grass is not always greener on the other side though. Of course, things have worked out for some. Just have a look at how Virgil van Dijk’s career has played out. He […]
Newcastle United in pole position for former Celtic player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero steals the show and makes headlines as he embarrasses Porto star on national duty]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=180902</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-hero-steals-the-show-and-makes-headlines-as-he-embarrasses-porto-star-on-international-duty/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T14:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star Luis Palma was one of the stars of the show for Honduras overnight as he produced an effective display to help beat Mexico...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton rules out Celtic signing £3 million Hearts player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=45687</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/11/18/chris-sutton-celtic-hearts-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T13:30:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are enjoying a decent run of form, at least domestically. But they might find themselves in a tough situation in January. The Hoops do not have a lot of squad depth in certain positions. On the other hand, the AFC Asian Cup is scheduled to start early next year. Both Kyogo Furuhashi and Oh […]
Chris Sutton rules out Celtic signing £3 million Hearts player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RODGERS’ SMILES BETTER – AT THE DOUBLE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114358</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rodgers-smiles-better-at-the-double/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T11:24:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KYOGO FURUHASHI and Matt O’Riley are on their way to becoming Celtic’s Dream Team double-act. The prolific striker and the stylish playmaker are dovetailing expertly in the champions’ line-up with the Japanese hitman now on the 62-goal mark after 101 appearances. O’Riley has added six strikes to his vast repertoire of talents, including next week’s opponents [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC STRIKER SEARCH: SHANKLAND? ‘FORGET ABOUT IT,’ INSISTS SUTTON]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=114348</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-striker-search-shankland-forget-about-it-insists-sutton/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-18T08:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS will be lumbered with a massive striking dilemma when three of his top frontmen are missing during the Asia Cup. The Hoops boss will almost certainly be without his top marksman Kyogo Furuhashi and his back-up Oh Hyeon-gyu when the forwards are called up by Japan and South Korea respectively, a predicament flagged up [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>