<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2022-07-22T09:22:38.146Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dylan Reid hailed for turning Celtic deal down as youngster tipped for St Mirren captaincy]]></title>
        <id>de9c701172c77df4a12d6d75ddf5ddc2</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20296938.dylan-reid-hailed-turning-celtic-deal-youngster-tipped-st-mirren-captaincy/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T08:42:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER St Mirren chief Tony Fitzpatrick has hailed Dylan Reid for making a "sensible decision" by turning down a transfer to Celtic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic youngster on trial with Forest Green Rovers]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/former-celtic-youngster-on-trial-with-forest-green-rovers/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/former-celtic-youngster-on-trial-with-forest-green-rovers/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T08:40:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic youngster Jonathan Afolabi is on trial with Forest Green Rovers as the Irishman searches for his next club following his release by The Scottish Champions. Afolabi, 22, joined Celtic in 2019 from Southampton but failed to make a first team appearance during that time. According to Gloucstershire Live, Afolabi has been training with the Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dublin Hoops Fan Home after Rovers Away Day Ordeal]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/dublin-hoops-fan-home/</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/dublin-hoops-fan-home/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T08:25:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dublin Hoops Fan Home. While Sligo Rovers fans were enjoying themselves in Glasgow’s Celtic bars before their Europa Conference clash with Motherwell. When the news broke that a Dublin Hoops fan was FREE, Daniel Fulham had been released from a Bulgarian Jail. https://celticfanzine.com/product/annual-magazine-subscription/ Daniel set on his long journey to the Bulgarian city, Razgard and […]
The post Dublin Hoops Fan Home after Rovers Away Day Ordeal appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Fran Alonso on Celtic FC Women’s Glasgow Cup debut on Sunday versus the Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/video-fran-alonso-on-celtic-fc-womens-glasgow-cup-debut-on-sunday-versus-the-rangers/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-fran-alonso-on-celtic-fc-womens-glasgow-cup-debut-on-sunday-versus-the-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T08:21:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Sunday afternoon a little piece of Scottish football history will be made in the Glasgow Cup when the Scottish Cup and League Cup double winners Celtic take on the current SWPL1 Champions, theRangers in the Glasgow Cup – the first time that this old and historic trophy will be played for in the women’s Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Fran Alonso on Celtic FC Women’s Glasgow Cup debut on Sunday versus the Rangers - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEMci70HDx8YB-FZWeojYkbQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-fran-alonso-on-celtic-fc-womens-glasgow-cup-debut-on-sunday-versus-the-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T08:21:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Fran Alonso on Celtic FC Women’s Glasgow Cup debut on Sunday versus the Rangers  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celt Leigh Griffiths training with Premiership club]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/former-celt-leigh-griffiths-training-with-premiership-club/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/former-celt-leigh-griffiths-training-with-premiership-club/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T08:11:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leigh Griffiths is training with Livingston as he attempts to get himself in a position to earn a contract with a club. The former Scotland Internationalist had been released by Celtic in January before sealing a deal until the end of the season with The Bairns. Unfortunately, he could not find the form to be Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Get him a club' - Ex-Celtic star Leigh Griffiths training with Premiership rivals]]></title>
        <id>3778049</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/get-him-a-club-ex-celtic-star-leigh-griffiths-training-with-premiership-rivals-3778049"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T07:59:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic star Leigh Griffiths is currently training with Livingston as he tries to find a new club ahead of the start of the season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Griffiths trains with Premiership Side]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/griffiths-trains-with-premiership-side/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/griffiths-trains-with-premiership-side/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T07:42:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker Leigh Griffiths has begun training with his old club Livingston in a bid to get his fitness up.  A move back to Almondvale has been completely ruled out by Livi gaffer David Martindale but he was happy to accommodate the former Scotland international. “Leigh was just scunnered with football and I had […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tony Fitzpatrick says St Mirren star Dylan Reid made 'sensible' decision to turn down Celtic - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEPyqlcOL_53xXssi9q_zisMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/in-your-area/renfrewshire/tony-fitzpatrick-says-st-mirren-27543587"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T07:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tony Fitzpatrick says St Mirren star Dylan Reid made 'sensible' decision to turn down Celtic  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘SCUNNERED’ GRIFF BATTLES BACK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/scunnered-griff-battles-back/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/scunnered-griff-battles-back/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T06:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LEIGH GRIFFITHS is back at former club Livingston in a bid to find a new club with the new league season kicking off next weekend. A year ago, the former Scotland international striker was only three weeks into a 12-month extension triggered by new Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou. However, Griffiths, who will be 32 next [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FEAR IS THE KEY FOR NEW BHOY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/fear-is-the-key-for-new-bhoy/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/fear-is-the-key-for-new-bhoy/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T06:23:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AARON MOOY admits he couldn’t turn down the opportunity to join Celtic – even if he finds Ange Postecoglou “intimidating”. The playmaker reunited with his former Australia international manager earlier this week after agreeing a two-year deal at the champions. The Hoops fans are hoping they may get their first glimpse of the 31-year-old new [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aberdeen boss Jim Goodwin ponders Liam Scales-Celtic dilemma as loan star shows importance]]></title>
        <id>3777668</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/aberdeen-boss-jim-goodwin-ponders-liam-scales-celtic-dilemma-as-loan-star-shows-importance-3777668"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aberdeen did not want to be participating in the Premier Sports group stage. It is the first time since League Cup reconstruction that they have experienced it due to European commitments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[French club target reported Celtic target Ryan Mmaee]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/french-club-target-reported-celtic-target-ryan-mmaee/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/french-club-target-reported-celtic-target-ryan-mmaee/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T05:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whilst we secured the double signing of Aaron Mooy and Moritz Jenz this week, many have been speculating over whether or not Ange Postecoglou and Celtic are finished in the transfer market. Sky Sports journalist Anthony Joseph even teased the supporters by posting an update on Twitter to confirm that the big man has gotten Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘SHAMBLES’: EX-CELTS IN SHOCK EXIT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/shambles-ex-celts-in-shock-exit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/shambles-ex-celts-in-shock-exit/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T05:23:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE plight of former Celtic trio Aiden McGeady, David Marshall and Ewan Henderson has taken another dramatic downturn with Hibs’ interest in the League Cup over. The ex-Hoops stars were already involved in a nightmare scenario with last season’s beaten finalists on the verge of a sensational exit after missing three consecutive penalty-kicks in the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connor Barron in Aberdeen injury blow as Jim Goodwin reveals star set to miss Celtic league opener - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEJkoDFE7T9Ok5epoxT4a9KgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/connor-barron-aberdeen-injury-blow-27546183"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Connor Barron in Aberdeen injury blow as Jim Goodwin reveals star set to miss Celtic league opener  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: CUP CRACKER AND DERBY DEADLOCKS: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Eleven)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-cup-cracker-and-derby-deadlocks-the-tommy-burns-story-part-eleven/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-cup-cracker-and-derby-deadlocks-the-tommy-burns-story-part-eleven/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-22T04:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS had won the Scottish Cup in his first season as Celtic manager after his appointment on July 12 1994. The league title, though, was his priority target and the legendary Celt came so tantalisingly and frustratingly close to achieving his aim during his second campaign. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE series, we chart Tommy [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fall behind in four-horse race for Premier League defender, according to reports]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-fall-behind-in-four-horse-race-for-premier-league-defender-according-to-reports/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-fall-behind-in-four-horse-race-for-premier-league-defender-according-to-reports/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T22:37:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have reportedly been dealt a blow in their attempts to land Tottenham Hotspur defender Japhet Tanganga after AC Milan ‘stole a march’ in their bid to bring the starlet to San Siro on a permanent deal. Tanganga burst onto the scene in 2019/20, where he was tasked with marking Liverpool’s rampant stars and put Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy - first Celtic press conference]]></title>
        <id>https://www.jerseydoesntshrink.com/2022/7/21/23273517/aaron-mooy-first-celtic-press-conference</id>
        <link href="https://www.jerseydoesntshrink.com/2022/7/21/23273517/aaron-mooy-first-celtic-press-conference"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T22:26:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Rob Casey/SNS Group via Getty Images
  

 Traditional and fan media had press conferences with new signing Aaron Mooy earlier at Celtic Park this afternoon.

Hamish also asked a question in the fan media conference, among the other outlets.


New Celtic signing Aaron Mooy speaking to @67HailHail, and other fan media, earlier today pic.twitter.com/scYhtpcyVE— Hamish Carton (@hamishcarton) July 21, 2022



And our very own Reidzo was there too, managing to take a non blurry picture of our new bhoy in the process. Well done John!!


Reidzo managed to take a photo that wasn’t blurry or contained a crap band pic.twitter.com/rWPIxc8oEV— GIGPOD ⚪️ (@gigpod) July 21, 2022



Good luck to the quietest guy ever to play for the club, and there’s another one tomorrow with Moritz ‘Mercedes’ Jenz, which we’ll be covering in the afternoon as well!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Rangers make transfer policy count for Champions League?]]></title>
        <id>6139658d71be0cbdc3ec9ce23dddd780</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20295834.can-rangers-make-transfer-policy-count-champions-league/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ON a recent trip to the supermarket, I heard an unusual, high-pitched noise periodically emanating from one of the adjacent aisles during the 10 minutes I spent inside the freezer door in the fish fingers section trying to recover from the inferno outside.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy insists Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou commands 'automatic respect']]></title>
        <id>0c3a59a830703b0eb9a2b3bf3d391407</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20296099.aaron-mooy-insists-celtic-manager-ange-postecoglou-commands-automatic-respect/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEW Celtic signing Aaron Mooy is no stranger to Ange Postecoglou’s managerial methods. The central midfielder was in and out of the Australia squad coached by the Parkhead boss between 2013 and 2017 and has accompanied the Greek-Australian on many a long-distance flight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing Aaron Mooy reveals Tom Rogic's advice after sealing move]]></title>
        <id>dd5f82b1899211a50948fdea3d696dfe</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20296067.new-celtic-signing-aaron-mooy-reveals-tom-rogics-advice-sealing-move/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC midfielder Aaron Mooy admits that the lure of challenging for titles and winning medals was a big pull when deciding to move to the cinch Premiership champions – and he is determined to follow in the footsteps of his countryman Tom Rogic by winning silverware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing Aaron Mooy trained in park ahead of World Cup play-offs]]></title>
        <id>e26799d5865462cdb073993d37840543</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20296085.new-celtic-signing-aaron-mooy-trained-park-ahead-world-cup-play-offs/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FOR most of us, a run around the local park is little more than an attempt to keep in shape. Maybe we would do it to train for a 10k, perhaps even a marathon. Between negotiating your way past other joggers and dodging errant dogs, it is about as far removed from the life of a top professional athlete as can be imagined. Well, most of them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Hello – Etims Podcast]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=17845</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=17845"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T21:29:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Hello! Its that time again, already! Desi, Hector, Monty and Ralph welcome back the glorious Glasgow Celtic with the first Podcast of Season 22-23.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer state of play as striker search speculation circulates - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEFkzX7AZ6-ZLH5KPiKMoAjEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPLfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/celtic-transfer-state-play-striker-24557613"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T21:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer state of play as striker search speculation circulates  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Holy Goalie’ Artur Boruc opens up on ‘scary letters’ received in the post after Old Firm antics]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/holy-goalie-artur-boruc-opens-up-on-scary-letters-received-in-the-post-after-old-firm-antics/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/holy-goalie-artur-boruc-opens-up-on-scary-letters-received-in-the-post-after-old-firm-antics/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T20:38:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic star Artur Boruc has opened up on ‘scary’ threats he received in the post after he blessed himself as Ibrox and ran around on away turf with a Champions flag after taking the league title – and the mick – in Govan. Police were involved, tempers flared and bonds were strengthened as Boruc Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aussie national team coaches believes Ange will ‘get the best’ out of Aaron Mooy]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/aussie-national-team-coaches-believes-ange-will-get-the-best-out-of-aaron-mooy/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/aussie-national-team-coaches-believes-ange-will-get-the-best-out-of-aaron-mooy/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T20:13:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australian national team coach Graham Arnold has told Celtic fans exactly what they want to hear ahead of the new cinch Premiership season; claiming that loveable boss Ange Postecoglou will be able to extract the best out of new signing Aaron Mooy as the Hoops embark on another trophy-laden season. The star, 31, joined Celtic Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed time update on new SPFL initiative; Bhoys investing six figure fee]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-handed-timeline-update-on-var-with-bhoys-shelling-out-six-figure-fee/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-handed-timeline-update-on-var-with-bhoys-shelling-out-six-figure-fee/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T20:11:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SPFL are looking to bring in a Video Assistant Referee (VAR) system by October, well ahead of the previously proposed start date in December. It was determined that VAR would be introduced to the Scottish Premiership after the upcoming World Cup. However, The Scottish Daily Mail reports that officials are now eyeing the weekend ...
The post Celtic handed time update on new SPFL initiative; Bhoys investing six figure fee appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Rangers go under the microscope - what pre-season has told us about impending title battle]]></title>
        <id>3777905</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-and-rangers-go-under-the-microscope-what-pre-season-has-told-us-about-impending-title-battle-3777905"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T19:48:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A comparative analysis of Celtic and Rangers in the here and now requires to come with more caveats than you would find at a caveats’ convention (there surely must be one somewhere in the multiverse).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Viaplay CEO promises value for Celtic and Scottish football fans after broadcast deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/viaplay-ceo-promises-value-for-celtic-and-scottish-football-supporters-after-broadcast-move/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/viaplay-ceo-promises-value-for-celtic-and-scottish-football-supporters-after-broadcast-move/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T19:42:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Viaplay CEO Anders Jensen has promised they will bring ‘added value’ to the households of Scottish football fans after the broadcaster announced its intention to acquire Premier Sports. Celtic’s matches in the Scottish Cup and Scottish League Cup currently air on Premier, but a rebranding is set to follow with new ownership of the TV ...
The post Viaplay CEO promises value for Celtic and Scottish football fans after broadcast deal appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham star draws interest from Celtic and two other clubs despite Milan transfer talks - Express]]></title>
        <id>CBMigQFodHRwczovL3d3dy5leHByZXNzLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsLzE2NDQwOTYvVG90dGVuaGFtLVNwdXJzLUphcGhldC1UYW5nYW5nYS1DZWx0aWMtQUMtTWlsYW4tTW9uYWNvLUJvdXJuZW1vdXRoLXRyYW5zZmVyLW5ld3PSAYUBaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZXhwcmVzcy5jby51ay9zcG9ydC9mb290YmFsbC8xNjQ0MDk2L1RvdHRlbmhhbS1TcHVycy1KYXBoZXQtVGFuZ2FuZ2EtQ2VsdGljLUFDLU1pbGFuLU1vbmFjby1Cb3VybmVtb3V0aC10cmFuc2Zlci1uZXdzL2FtcA</id>
        <link href="https://www.express.co.uk/sport/football/1644096/Tottenham-Spurs-Japhet-Tanganga-Celtic-AC-Milan-Monaco-Bournemouth-transfer-news"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T19:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham star draws interest from Celtic and two other clubs despite Milan transfer talks  Express]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["What a great place to go"; Dean Smith relishing Celtic Park visit with Norwich this weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-a-great-place-to-go-dean-smith-relishing-celtic-park-visit-with-norwich-this-weekend/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-a-great-place-to-go-dean-smith-relishing-celtic-park-visit-with-norwich-this-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T19:14:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Norwich City manager Dean Smith is looking forward to facing Celtic on Saturday, with the English side arriving as the Bhoys’ final pre-season opponents. Like Celtic, the Canaries kick off their league campaign next weekend. But they’ve chosen a somewhat different route in their preparations with an unusual double-header in Scotland coming up. Smith will ...
The post "What a great place to go"; Dean Smith relishing Celtic Park visit with Norwich this weekend appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Young Celtic talent scores first professional goal out on loan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/young-celtic-talent-scores-first-professional-goal-out-on-loan/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/young-celtic-talent-scores-first-professional-goal-out-on-loan/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T18:40:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic youngster Adam Montgomery had a storming mid-week out on loan at St Johnstone, scoring his first professional goal and creating two assists in a Scottish League Cup win. The Perth side badly needed a win away to Elgin City on Tuesday night after poor early draws, with no penalty extra points, against Annan Athletic ...
The post Young Celtic talent scores first professional goal out on loan appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Young Celtic talent scores first professional goal out on loan - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CBMiZ2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LjY3aGFpbGhhaWwuY29tL2NlbHRpYy15b3V0aC95b3VuZy1jZWx0aWMtdGFsZW50LXNjb3Jlcy1maXJzdC1wcm9mZXNzaW9uYWwtZ29hbC1vdXQtb24tbG9hbi_SAWtodHRwczovL3d3dy42N2hhaWxoYWlsLmNvbS9jZWx0aWMteW91dGgveW91bmctY2VsdGljLXRhbGVudC1zY29yZXMtZmlyc3QtcHJvZmVzc2lvbmFsLWdvYWwtb3V0LW9uLWxvYW4vP2FtcA</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/young-celtic-talent-scores-first-professional-goal-out-on-loan/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T18:40:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Young Celtic talent scores first professional goal out on loan  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic&#039;s League Cup rivals last season already out in July after SPFL punish shambolic blunder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-league-cup-rivals-last-season-already-out-in-july-after-spfl-punish-shambolic-blunder/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-league-cup-rivals-last-season-already-out-in-july-after-spfl-punish-shambolic-blunder/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T18:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The team Celtic faced in last year’s Scottish League Cup final, Hibernian, are already out of this year’s tournament after a shambolic July group stage that ended with the SPFL taking disciplinary action. Hibs were already facing a sharp exit following poor results versus Falkirk and Greenock Morton, with matches elsewhere this weekend threatening to ...
The post Celtic&#039;s League Cup rivals last season already out in July after SPFL punish shambolic blunder appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s League Cup rivals last season already out in July after SPFL punish shambolic blunder - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEBp1GUA4FB9JmFp6pfhzDOAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMLbFpgY</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-league-cup-rivals-last-season-already-out-in-july-after-spfl-punish-shambolic-blunder/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T18:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s League Cup rivals last season already out in July after SPFL punish shambolic blunder  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player quietly completes transfer move to Burnley - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEJSOblM5O686tOGq90OFIyQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4KKJCzCv9JoDMICkoAY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2022/07/21/celtic-player-completes-move-burnley/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T18:03:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player quietly completes transfer move to Burnley  The Celtic Bhoys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic vs Everton Down Under; Ticket Update]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-vs-everton-down-under-ticket-update/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-vs-everton-down-under-ticket-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T17:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everton were announced as the final team which Celtic would take on during the Sydney Super Cup alongside Sydney FC in November and ticket sales appear to be going well.   The Toffees will be hoping for a much better result than there most recent friendly outing where they were thrashed 4-0 by Minnesota United. The […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic new boy Aaron Mooy on Ange Postecoglou's 'intimidating' aura]]></title>
        <id>1396e42007b129a137cdb06a3a5ae1b6</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20296063.celtic-new-boy-aaron-mooy-ange-postecoglous-intimidating-aura/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T16:48:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AARON MOOY admits Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou still has an "intimidating" presence about him.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange&#039;s latest move is bad news for one of his first Celtic signings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/james-mccarthys-celtic-future-isnt-looking-great/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/james-mccarthys-celtic-future-isnt-looking-great/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic almost certainly rounded off their midfield options for the foreseeable on Tuesday with the signing of Australia internationalist Aaron Mooy. The former St Mirren midfielder put pen to paper on a two-year deal to reunite with his former national team manager Ange Postecoglou. The move was welcomed by current Socceroos boss Graham Arnold, with ...
The post Ange&#039;s latest move is bad news for one of his first Celtic signings appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KID’S STUFF FOR GEARED-UP GIAKOUMAKIS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kids-stuff-for-geared-up-giakoumakis/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/kids-stuff-for-geared-up-giakoumakis/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T16:38:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GIORGOS GIAKOUMAKIS welcomed the birth of his daughter – wearing CELTIC shorts. The Greek striker, who has missed the last two Hoops friendly games against Blackburn Rovers and Legia Warsaw on compassionate leave, was with his partner as she went into labour. His baby girl arrived this morning and Giakoumakis shared the news on social [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic set to miss out on long-term target as star chooses Napoli move]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-set-to-miss-out-on-long-term-target-as-star-chooses-napoli-move/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-set-to-miss-out-on-long-term-target-as-star-chooses-napoli-move/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T16:32:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic look set to miss out on long-term transfer target Ola Solbakken of Bodo/Glimt; with the Norwegian star being heavily linked with a move to Serie A giants and Champions League outfit Napoli ahead of the new season. Solbakken joined Bodo/Glimt back in 2020 from Ranheim, and has since scored 17 goals and registered 19 assists Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[&#039;Now I’m hearing...&#039; - Journalist shares last 48 hr transfer update for Celtic supporters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-transfer-rumours/celtic-news-ange-summer-plans-update/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-transfer-rumours/celtic-news-ange-summer-plans-update/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T16:15:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Journalist Mark Hendry, sharing news in the last 48 hours, has an update for Celtic supporters on the club’s transfer plans for the rest of this summer window. The Lowdown: Ange backed… The Hoops, after sealing a 2021/2022 SPFL crown over an impressive debut campaign in charge for Ange Postecoglou, have seriously backed their boss […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Rogic latest as he turns down more clubs after Celtic exit; Socceroos saga cleared up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/tom-rogic-latest-as-he-turns-down-more-clubs-following-celtic-exit-socceroos-saga-cleared-up/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/tom-rogic-latest-as-he-turns-down-more-clubs-following-celtic-exit-socceroos-saga-cleared-up/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Australia national team boss has joined Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou in cooling fears over former Hoops star Tom Rogic’s future. The Socceroos manager Graham Arnold had initially raised alarm about the Rogic’s wellbeing, having not heard from the midfielder after he pulled out of a national team squad, but the coach has now alleviated ...
The post Tom Rogic latest as he turns down more clubs after Celtic exit; Socceroos saga cleared up appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artur Boruc speaks out about his ‘blessing’, religious profile and hilarious nickname]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/artur-boruc-speaks-out-about-his-blessing-religious-profile-and-hilarious-nickname/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/artur-boruc-speaks-out-about-his-blessing-religious-profile-and-hilarious-nickname/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T16:09:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Holy Goalie. Honestly, whoever came up with that nickname – so simple, yet so hilarious – deserves a medal. The nickname, of course, belongs to Artur Boruc; the former Celtic goalkeeper who made 221 appearances in the famous goalkeeping jersey across Scotland, Europe and beyond in one of the most successful eras in the Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Rogic’s Brilliant Celtic Dressing Room Advice to Mooy]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/tom-rogics-brilliant-celtic-dressing-room-advice-to-mooy/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/tom-rogics-brilliant-celtic-dressing-room-advice-to-mooy/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T15:53:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy was in front of the media and fan media on Thursday afternoon has he gears up to begin his Celtic career. The Australian signed for the hoops earlier this week and has trained at Lennoxtown while the bhoys have been away in Poland. The Celtic manager was delighted to get the deal over […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy talks about his likely Celtic role; Harry Kewell influence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/aaron-mooy-talks-about-his-likely-celtic-role-harry-kewell-influence/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/aaron-mooy-talks-about-his-likely-celtic-role-harry-kewell-influence/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T15:43:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s new signing Aaron Mooy has just completed his first fan media press conference since signing for the club. With a lack of obvious cover in the deepest midfield spot, 67 Hail Hail asked Mooy about where he sees himself playing for Celtic going forward. He said: “I’ve played in different positions throughout my career, ...
The post Aaron Mooy talks about his likely Celtic role; Harry Kewell influence appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exciting Celtic Trio Available for Saturday; Ange Confirms]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/exciting-celtic-trio-available-for-saturday-ange-confirms/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/exciting-celtic-trio-available-for-saturday-ange-confirms/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T15:43:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU delivered an update on the state of play before Celtic’s final game of pre-season. Celtic had most of the squad to choose from with some exceptions. One exception over the last week was Gorgios Giakoumakis who was given a leave of absence to go back to Greece in order to be at the […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exciting Celtic Trio Available for Saturday; Ange Confirms - CeltsAreHere]]></title>
        <id>CBMiU2h0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9leGNpdGluZy1jZWx0aWMtdHJpby1hdmFpbGFibGUtZm9yLXNhdHVyZGF5LWFuZ2UtY29uZmlybXMv0gFXaHR0cHM6Ly9jZWx0c2FyZWhlcmUuY29tL2V4Y2l0aW5nLWNlbHRpYy10cmlvLWF2YWlsYWJsZS1mb3Itc2F0dXJkYXktYW5nZS1jb25maXJtcy9hbXAv</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/exciting-celtic-trio-available-for-saturday-ange-confirms/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T15:43:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exciting Celtic Trio Available for Saturday; Ange Confirms  CeltsAreHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Rogic’s one-word answer to Australia manager as midfielder’s whereabouts still unsure]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/tom-rogics-one-word-answer-to-australia-manager-as-midfielders-whereabouts-still-unsure/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/tom-rogics-one-word-answer-to-australia-manager-as-midfielders-whereabouts-still-unsure/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T15:30:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australia manager Graham Arnold has given an update on Tom Rogic’s current AWOL situation – stating that he has given his star time to ‘be left alone’ before working on his situation with the Socceroos going forward. Rogic left Celtic in the summer after nine superb years at Parkhead, and it was thought by many Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy talks about Ange’s ‘intimidating aura’ after rekindling with Celtic boss]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/aaron-mooy-talks-about-anges-intimidating-aura-after-rekindling-with-celtic-boss/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/aaron-mooy-talks-about-anges-intimidating-aura-after-rekindling-with-celtic-boss/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T15:15:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfield signing Aaron Mooy cannot wait to reconcile with former Socceroos boss Ange Postecoglou at Paradise following a five-year hiatus from the manager in the national team setup – despite claiming that the lovable gaffer has an ‘intimidating aura’ about himself. Mooy signed on a permanent deal earlier this week in a double deal Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Celtic vs Norwich City on TV? Live stream and kick off details for Hoops' final pre season clash - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEH7jTE27foaJ5oL1RHMFkSEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/celtic-vs-norwich-city-tv-27543883"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T15:08:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is Celtic vs Norwich City on TV? Live stream and kick off details for Hoops' final pre season clash  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer move talked up abroad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/national-team-manager-gives-thumbs-up-to-celtic-move/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/national-team-manager-gives-thumbs-up-to-celtic-move/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The manager of the Australia national team has backed Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou to get the best out of Aaron Mooy following his move to Glasgow. Mooy starred for Postecoglou previously when his fellow Aussie managed the national side, and the current incumbent Graham Arnold believes the pair will have a productive relationship again at ...
The post Celtic transfer move talked up abroad appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic set for fixture oddity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-set-for-glasgow-fixture-oddity-this-weekend/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-set-for-glasgow-fixture-oddity-this-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will experience a 23-year first on Saturday as they play at home at the same time as Rangers. As reported by the Scotsman, Celtic’s friendly against Norwich will be the first time they’ve kicked off at the same time, and in the same city as Glasgow rivals Rangers, who are facing Tottenham Hotspur at ...
The post Celtic set for fixture oddity appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic set for Glasgow fixture oddity this weekend - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEJkMVMVHgEVYnegaMS74o3gqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMLbFpgY</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-set-for-glasgow-fixture-oddity-this-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic set for Glasgow fixture oddity this weekend  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scottish football TV shake-up as Premier Sports sold for £30m]]></title>
        <id>3777448</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/scottish-football-tv-shake-up-as-premier-sports-sold-for-ps30m-3777448"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T14:08:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Premier Sports, one of Scottish football's major broadcaster partners, has been taken over by Nordic streaming platform Viaplay in a deal worth £30million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Elder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange confirms Celtic star is back at Lennoxtown following absence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-confirms-giorgos-giakoumakis-celtic-training-status-after-family-joy/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ange-postecoglou-confirms-giorgos-giakoumakis-celtic-training-status-after-family-joy/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou delivered his verdict on Celtic’s latest pre-season game in Poland yesterday. The Australian spoke after Celtic’s 2-2 draw with Legia Warsaw, in which Celtic raced into a Reo Hatate-inspired 2-0 first-half lead before being pegged back by the Polish side early in the second half, the match being played to mark ...
The post Ange confirms Celtic star is back at Lennoxtown following absence appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Southampton and Celtic striker could make League One transfer after Portsmouth trial - Hampshire Live]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEAfXaNn3V_7MegTE-yYMYPoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_qSbCzDCr7MDMLGt3gY</id>
        <link href="https://www.hampshirelive.news/sport/football/football-news/southampton-celtic-striker-transfer-portsmouth-7363313"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T13:27:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Southampton and Celtic striker could make League One transfer after Portsmouth trial  Hampshire Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic tease new look ahead of Norwich friendly]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-tease-new-look-ahead-fo-norwich-friendly/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-tease-new-look-ahead-fo-norwich-friendly/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T13:10:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have teased a new look to Paradise ahead of this weekend’s game against Norwich. Fans had noticed last weekend that the banners which covered the Jock Stein & Lisbon Lions stands were down. These featured Celtic legends across the years along with the slogan “Paradise – Where Legends Are Made”. 👀 🟢⚪️ A new Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star seeing pre-season progress that could culminate in bad day for Norwich]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-defender-seeing-pre-season-progress-that-could-culminate-in-bad-day-for-norwich/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-defender-seeing-pre-season-progress-that-could-culminate-in-bad-day-for-norwich/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic defender Stephen Welsh has dubbed yesterday’s first-half performance in Warsaw the best of Celtic’s pre-season so far. The centre-half spoke following Celtic’s 2-2 draw with Legia, which saw the Hoops race into a 2-0 half time lead in the Polish capital before being pegged back in the second half, the game being played to ...
The post Celtic star seeing pre-season progress that could culminate in bad day for Norwich appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Tease New Parkhead Design]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-tease-new-parkhead-design/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-tease-new-parkhead-design/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T13:09:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic has teased a first look at the new Celtic Park banners as the club look to freshen up the stadium ahead of the new season. The previous banners around the stadium were taken down at the end of last season with Paradise being left bare until now. As the SPFL gets set to begin […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic striker Giakoumakis Welcomes Baby Girl into the World]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-striker-giakoumakis-welcomes-baby-girl-into-the-world/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-striker-giakoumakis-welcomes-baby-girl-into-the-world/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T12:57:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gorgios Giakoumakis has been missing from the Celtic squad for the last week or so. The striker was given special leave to head back to Greece where his partner was expecting. Ange Postecoglou gave the prolific frontman the green light to go back home and wait for the birth of his child. Today, the Celtic […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will not be selling anyone they don't need to sell. The sooner the hacks get that, the better - Read Celtic]]></title>
        <id>CBMihAFodHRwczovL3JlYWRjZWx0aWMuY29tLzIwMjIvMDcvMjEvY2VsdGljLXdpbGwtbm90LWJlLXNlbGxpbmctYW55b25lLXRoZXktZG9udC1uZWVkLXRvLXNlbGwtdGhlLXNvb25lci10aGUtaGFja3MtZ2V0LXRoYXQtdGhlLWJldHRlci_SAQA</id>
        <link href="https://readceltic.com/2022/07/21/celtic-will-not-be-selling-anyone-they-dont-need-to-sell-the-sooner-the-hacks-get-that-the-better/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T12:47:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will not be selling anyone they don't need to sell. The sooner the hacks get that, the better  Read Celtic]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Broadcast shake-up for Celtic as media company announces &#039;significant&#039; rights acquisition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/broadcast-shake-up-for-celtic-as-media-company-announces-significant-rights-acquisition/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/broadcast-shake-up-for-celtic-as-media-company-announces-significant-rights-acquisition/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nordic streaming company Viaplay has announced its intention to acquire Premier Sports and all their related UK broadcast rights ahead of a launch in this country later this year. That means, pending regulatory approval, Viaplay will own the rights to the Scottish Cup and Scottish League Cup moving forward, both of which will be expected ...
The post Broadcast shake-up for Celtic as media company announces &#039;significant&#039; rights acquisition appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The once forgotten man of Celtic FC]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/the-once-forgotten-man/</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/the-once-forgotten-man/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T12:05:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s pre-season continues and  Tony Ralston is going about his business with little fuss. The once forgotten man of Celtic FC is now a fans favourite. Ralston gives 100% every time he pulls on the Hoops. https://celticfanzine.com/product/annual-magazine-subscription/ His late winner against Ross County, midweek in Dingwall is still ingrained in every Celtic fans mind from […]
The post The once forgotten man of Celtic FC appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Celtic Manager Talked Straight On O’Riley. Still The Hacks Insist On Twisting His Words.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/this-celtic-manager-talked-straight-on-oriley-still-the-hacks-insist-on-twisting-his-words/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/this-celtic-manager-talked-straight-on-oriley-still-the-hacks-insist-on-twisting-his-words/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T12:04:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday Ange spoke to the media after the game with Legia Warsaw. Boy, oh boy, I bet he regrets that now. He was asked about the stories “linking” Matt O’Riley to Leicester. I read them earlier in the day and they were so tiresome that I skipped them and didn’t even bother to comment. Every […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple Celtic Park changes on the way; new matchday area]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-park-changes-on-the-way-ahead-of-the-new-season-new-matchday-area/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-park-changes-on-the-way-ahead-of-the-new-season-new-matchday-area/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T12:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Park is set for a number of updates ahead of the new season, including the replacement of the banners adorning the exterior stadium walls. The banners were removed last month, leading to speculation about whether they would be replaced with new ones for the commencement of the new season. The official Supporters Liaison Officer ...
The post Multiple Celtic Park changes on the way; new matchday area appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Announce New Matchday Facilities]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-announce-new-matchday-facilities/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-announce-new-matchday-facilities/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T11:42:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The club have today announced that a new Matchday Bar is expected to open at Celtic Park this October.  This facility is to be opened on matchdays giving supporters a chance to arrive early at the stadium and soak up the atmosphere before kick-off. The new bar is to be located in the South West […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has his say on new Celtic transfer speculation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-boss-ange-postecoglou-unfazed-by-recent-transfer-report/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-boss-ange-postecoglou-unfazed-by-recent-transfer-report/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou has said he encourages admirers in his Celtic stars following Leicester City’s reported interest in Matt O’Riley. [The Telegraph] The Australian spoke after Celtic’s 2-2 pre-season draw in Poland with Legia Warsaw, in which O’Riley stood out, as Celtic raced into a 2-0 half-time lead before being pegged back in the ...
The post Ange Postecoglou has his say on new Celtic transfer speculation appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are raiding the transfer bargain bucket as Rangers summer sales show who's boss - Hotline - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEArEwfq_0SRUzI8Wpu3Ax_sqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/celtic-raiding-transfer-bargain-bucket-27540308"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T11:25:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are raiding the transfer bargain bucket as Rangers summer sales show who's boss - Hotline  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic transfer problem Aaron Mooy solves for Ange Postecoglou - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEAQ7q7H9OAcOhhaw5j_2OzoqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/celtic-transfer-problem-aaron-mooy-27539039"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T11:01:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic transfer problem Aaron Mooy solves for Ange Postecoglou  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘WE WILL BE BETTER,’ INSISTS DETERMINED POSTECOGLOU]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/we-will-be-better-insists-determined-postecoglou/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/we-will-be-better-insists-determined-postecoglou/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T11:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU promises Celtic “will be better” by the time the Premiership kicks off with the visit of Aberdeen to Parkhead on Flag Day a week on Sunday. The Hoops boss watched the champions draw 2-2 with Legia Warsaw last night in the Artur Boruc farewell performance with the former fans’ favourite bringing down the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Rangers set for rare 23-year first as police put 'appropriate plan' in place]]></title>
        <id>3777024</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-and-rangers-set-for-rare-23-year-first-as-police-put-appropriate-plan-in-place-3777024"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T10:54:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Rangers will play at home on the same day at the same time for the first time in 23 years this weekend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Elder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Ange Postecoglou encourages transfer talk in Celtic stars amidst Leicester Matt O'Riley latest]]></title>
        <id>3777003</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/why-ange-postecoglou-encourages-transfer-talk-in-celtic-stars-amidst-leicester-matt-oriley-latest-3777003"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T10:44:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has shrugged off interest in his Celtic stars – and insists he enjoys seeing other clubs keen on his players as it’s a reflection of their progress.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Oliver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ola Solbakken on course for Serie A move as Celtic thorn looks bargain free transfer]]></title>
        <id>377147765aecd7c7d0306e3c8118e6b3</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20294461.ola-solbakken-set-serie-move-celtic-thorn-moves-free-transfer/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T10:42:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Italian side Napoli are closing in on the signing of Norwegian star Ola Solbakken.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“I encourage it. If big clubs want our players that’s great,” Ange Postecoglou]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/i-encourage-it-if-big-clubs-want-our-players-thats-great-ange-postecoglou/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/i-encourage-it-if-big-clubs-want-our-players-thats-great-ange-postecoglou/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T10:03:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday we reported on the news that Matt O’Riley has become a summer signing target for Brendan Rodgers at Leicester City although noting that the former Celtic manager has to sell players before he is in a position to buy anyone. Indeed Leicester remain the only Premier League side not to buy a new player Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boruc’s Celtic Park Plan]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/borucs-celtic-park-plan/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/borucs-celtic-park-plan/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T09:50:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many Celtic supporters have fond memories of Artur Boruc’s time at the club and it was fitting that the Hoops would provide opposition for his final game.  After weeks of controversy surrounding ticket prices, the 42-year old got a decent send off from two clubs which are close to the former Polish internationals heart. Boruc […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy tipped to 'be the leader we need' amid Celtic rave review]]></title>
        <id>cae1dca045ca7faafb891b0f5236684b</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20294235.aaron-mooy-tipped-be-leader-need-amid-celtic-rave-review/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T09:49:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australia boss Graham Arnold feels Celtic manager Ange Postecoglou can 'get the best' out of new signing Aaron Mooy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artur Boruc cheekily dodges saying 'Rangers' in Celtic interview as Hoops hero reflects on career]]></title>
        <id>b8796b32ef18fe2a5d43a2f8731dd7d9</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20294163.artur-boruc-cheekily-dodges-saying-rangers-celtic-interview-hoops-hero-reflects-career/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T09:34:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ARTUR BORUC has cheekily dodged mentioning Rangers as he reflected on a stellar 22-year career.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer update as Postecoglou makes 'big clubs' admission amid Juranovic and O'Riley rumours - Glasgow Live]]></title>
        <id>CBMibGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmdsYXNnb3dsaXZlLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLW5ld3MvY2VsdGljLXRyYW5zZmVyLXVwZGF0ZS1wb3N0ZWNvZ2xvdS1tYWtlcy0yNDU0ODI3MdIBAA</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowlive.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/celtic-transfer-update-postecoglou-makes-24548271"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T08:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer update as Postecoglou makes 'big clubs' admission amid Juranovic and O'Riley rumours  Glasgow Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boruc Opens Up On Famous Pope Shirt Celebration]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/boruc-opens-up-on-famous-pope-shirt-celebration/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/boruc-opens-up-on-famous-pope-shirt-celebration/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T08:52:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was fitting to see Celtic participate in Artur Boruc’s final competitive game last night in Poland with club Chief Executive Michael Nicholson presenting the former Hoops keeper with a commemorative Celtic cross to mark the occasion.  One of the most important fixtures in the calendar when Boruc spent his time in Glasgow was Old […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EX-HOOPS TRIO NIGHTMARE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ex-hoops-trio-nightmare/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ex-hoops-trio-nightmare/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T08:23:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A TRIO of former Celtic players – David Marshall, Aiden McGeady and Ewan Henderson – are in the middle of a Hibs nightmare. The ex-Scotland keeper, the Republic of Ireland winger and the Under-21 midfielder all played in the Edinburgh club’s 1-1 draw against Morton at Easter Road last night – and are now on [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Rogic future latest as Australia boss details communications with Celtic hero]]></title>
        <id>cf6d09f467d757f18bb71a48f73f4177</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20293856.tom-rogic-future-latest-australia-boss-details-communications-celtic-hero/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T08:13:07.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[International Boss Reveals Celtic Transfer ‘Relief’]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/international-boss-reveals-celtic-transfer-relief/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/international-boss-reveals-celtic-transfer-relief/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T07:57:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australian boss Graham Arnold is backing Aaron Mooy to be a success at Celtic and is hopeful that the midfielder will be completely up to speed by the time the World Cup rolls around in November – stating his relief at the move. The 31-year old will be hoping for more regular first team football […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[O’RILEY INTEREST? ‘I ENCOURAGE IT,’ INSISTS POSTECOGLOU]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/oriley-interest-i-encourage-it-insists-postecoglou/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/oriley-interest-i-encourage-it-insists-postecoglou/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T07:45:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU insists he WELCOMES interest in Matt O’Riley and his Celtic stars. The Celtic boss was reacting to speculation Brendan Rodgers was preparing a bid for the smooth midfielder to take him to Leicester City – just six months after the Danish Under-21 international arrived at Parkhead in a £1.5million switch from third-tier MK [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Delivers Celtic Squad Verdict]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/ange-delivers-celtic-squad-verdict/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/ange-delivers-celtic-squad-verdict/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T07:28:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a 2-2 draw with Legia Warsaw Ange Postecoglou was quick to dismiss the idea that the opening period of the game in Poland had been Celtic’s best showing in pre-season so far.  The game marked a special occasion for former Hoops keeper Artur Boruc who was paid homage to by both sides before and […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fausto Vera to Celtic transfer door narrows as midfielder's agent drops major next move clue - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEKsMgvLnlzbJAmROOkLmGHkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/fausto-vera-celtic-transfer-door-27537066"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T07:22:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fausto Vera to Celtic transfer door narrows as midfielder's agent drops major next move clue  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“The way we played and the way we were moving in the first 45 was the best we have shown,” Stephen Welsh]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/the-way-we-played-and-the-way-we-were-moving-in-the-first-45-was-the-best-we-have-shown-stephen-welsh/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/the-way-we-played-and-the-way-we-were-moving-in-the-first-45-was-the-best-we-have-shown-stephen-welsh/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T06:57:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday Celtic participated in a friendly match in Poland with Legia Warsaw for Artur Boruc’s farewell party after a glorious career in the game. The Hoops were on top in the first half, thanks to goals from Reo Hatate and Daizen Maeda. However, after the break and several changes later we lapsed back into that Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou Addresses Matt O’Riley Speculation]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/ange-postecoglou-addresses-matt-oriley-speculation/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/ange-postecoglou-addresses-matt-oriley-speculation/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T06:50:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has addressed speculation linking Matt O’Riley with a move away from the club. Matt only signed for Celtic in January, but he’s made a big impact in the green and white hoops already. As we get geared towards the new season, the midfielder could be a pivotal player for Ange’s side over the […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: SNUBBING THE SUMMIT: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (PART TEN)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-snubbing-the-summit-the-tommy-burns-story-part-ten/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-snubbing-the-summit-the-tommy-burns-story-part-ten/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-21T05:05:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS had won the Scottish Cup in his first season as Celtic manager after his appointment on July 12 1994. The league title, though, was his priority target and the legendary Celt came so tantalisingly and frustratingly close to achieving his aim during his second campaign. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE series, we chart Tommy [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange reflects on a “glass half full” performance against Legia Warsaw]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/ange-reflects-on-a-glass-half-full-performance-against-legia-warsaw/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/ange-reflects-on-a-glass-half-full-performance-against-legia-warsaw/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T22:26:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou admitted his side weren’t at their best despite a controlling first-half display against Legia Warsaw on Wednesday afternoon. The Bhoys in Green looked to be at their best following a generally underwhelming performance against Blackburn Rovers on Saturday afternoon as they raced into a 2-0 lead in the Polish capital thanks Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange 'encourages' interest in Celtic stars amid O'Riley and Leicester rumour - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEJdEROTee-3V41tTHlNwJYYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-transfer-news/matt-oriley-transfer-latest-celtic-27535412"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange 'encourages' interest in Celtic stars amid O'Riley and Leicester rumour  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen Welsh reflects on ‘excellent’ first half after Bhoys frustrating draw in Poland]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/stephen-welsh-reflects-on-excellent-first-half-after-bhoys-frustrating-draw-in-poland/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/stephen-welsh-reflects-on-excellent-first-half-after-bhoys-frustrating-draw-in-poland/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T21:25:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic centre-back Stephen Walsh has praised his team-mates for a superb first half in Artur Boruc’s testimonial this afternoon as they raced into a 2-0 lead against Legia Warsaw – although admitted there were still improvements to be made as they let their lead slip in the Polish capital. Goals from Reo Hatate and Daizen Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“This isn’t a gamble for Ange Postecoglou,” Billy Reid]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/this-isnt-a-gamble-for-ange-postecoglou-billy-reid/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/this-isnt-a-gamble-for-ange-postecoglou-billy-reid/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T21:10:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The signing of Aaron Mooy as a free agent has garnered mixed reviews amongst the Celtic faithful it’s fair to say. The Aussie has been brought in to the club to help beef up the midfield area and provide cover and rotation if and when required. Boasting an embarrassment of experience in the game at Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou sends Celtic 'we will be better' message as Hoops play out Legia Warsaw draw]]></title>
        <id>9fc9e0586342118738bd58a5014e0fd6</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20293072.ange-postecoglou-sends-celtic-we-will-better-message-hoops-play-legia-warsaw-draw/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T20:38:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“WE will be better” was the message from Ange Postecoglou after his Celtic side blew a two-goal lead against Legia Warsaw in pre-season last night.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen Welsh hails Celtic's 'best half yet' but urges teammates to keep intensity up]]></title>
        <id>44c9e87a1ac35213a10fbf2b7460523b</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20293061.stephen-welsh-hails-celtics-best-half-yet-urges-teammates-keep-intensity/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T20:13:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[STEPHEN WELSH insists Celtic are making positive progress as they continue their preparations for the start of the competitive league season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen Welsh reacts to Celtic’s draw in Poland]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/stephen-welsh-reacts-to-celtics-draw-in-poland/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/stephen-welsh-reacts-to-celtics-draw-in-poland/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T19:20:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen Welsh has given his reaction after Celtic’s 2-2 draw against Legia Warsaw in Artur Boruc’s final game of professional football.  The young defender has been given a lot of game time during pre-season due to Carl Starfelt’s injury which he sustained while on international duty with Sweden during the summer months. With Celtic having […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic publish emotional Artur Boruc and Stevie Woods photo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-publish-emotional-artur-boruc-and-stevie-woods-photo/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-publish-emotional-artur-boruc-and-stevie-woods-photo/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T19:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have published a photo of the embrace between an emotional Artur Boruc and Bhoys goalkeeping coach Stevie Woods after tonight’s game in Warsaw. Celtic played out a 2-2 draw with Legia but the night was really all about the goodbye to Boruc, who had stellar careers at both clubs. After the match, the Polish ...
The post Celtic publish emotional Artur Boruc and Stevie Woods photo appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic SLO Confirms Celtic Park Makeover]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-slo-confirms-celtic-park-makeover/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-slo-confirms-celtic-park-makeover/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T18:48:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was brilliant to return back to Celtic Park on Saturday but there was something missing about the dear old Paradise.  For the past seven years large banners which paid tribute to some of the clubs greatest ever players and events greeted fans as they arrived at the ground with ‘Paradise’ inscribed in block letters. […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What next for James McCarthy?]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/what-next-for-james-mccarthy/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/what-next-for-james-mccarthy/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T18:30:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having signed Aaron Mooy just over 24 hours ago, many will ask where does James McCarthy fit in at Celtic if at all.  The 31-year old midfielder arrived at Celtic last August alongside Joe Hart and both players careers under Ange Postecoglou have been contrastingly different. Hart has been an integral part of Postecoglou’s team […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s Second Half Pre-Season Slumps Are Easily Diagnosed And Not Worth Worrying Over.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/articles/celtics-second-half-pre-season-slumps-are-easily-diagnosed-and-not-worth-worrying-over/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/articles/celtics-second-half-pre-season-slumps-are-easily-diagnosed-and-not-worth-worrying-over/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T18:22:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So what’s the secret to Celtic’s schizophrenic pre-season, where we’ve combined beautiful, beautiful football with nerve shredding inconsistency, and why shouldn’t that be a cause for concern for us all as we go forward? Well, tonight gave us the reasons, as if we needed reminding of them. What Ange has done in the past couple […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Aaron Mooy questions amid exceptional Reo Hatate showing in ultimately sloppy Legia draw]]></title>
        <id>3776360</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-aaron-mooy-questions-amid-exceptional-reo-hatate-showing-in-ultimately-sloppy-legia-draw-3776360"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T18:17:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The benefits that can be derived from signings don’t always even require them to contribute on the pitch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate shines and second-half dip costs Celtic win in Artur Boruc farewell]]></title>
        <id>00bd43dd2a0dcf548d2d001337f5129e</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20292952.reo-hatate-shines-second-half-dip-costs-celtic-win-artur-boruc-farewell/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T18:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IT may have been Artur Boruc’s night, but from Celtic’s point of view, this was the Reo Hatate show.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LEGIA WARSAW 2 CELTIC 2: BORUC’S LAST HURRAH IN HOOPS STALEMATE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/legia-warsaw-2-celtic-2-borucs-last-hurrah-in-hoops-stalemate/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/legia-warsaw-2-celtic-2-borucs-last-hurrah-in-hoops-stalemate/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T17:56:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ARTUR BORIC was hit by a Celtic whirlwind in the Hoops fans’ favourite’s last hurrah at the age of 42 tonight. The veteran keeper was taking his final bow after a colourful career at club and country level – and Ange Postecoglou’s side made sure he was kept busy before his retirement. The champions swept [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Legia Warsaw 2 Celtic 2 LIVE reaction as tearful Artur Boruc leads full time singsong - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>1500906835</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/legia-warsaw-vs-celtic-live-27531197"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T17:56:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legia Warsaw 2 Celtic 2 LIVE reaction as tearful Artur Boruc leads full time singsong  Daily Record
Legia Warsaw 2 Celtic 2 LIVE reaction as Artur Boruc brings his career to a close  Football Scotland
Celtic XI v Legia Warsaw confirmed as decisions made on Boruc, Giakoumakis, Hatate, Jenz and Mooy  Glasgow Live
Legia Warsaw v Celtic: team news, KO time and where to watch  The Celtic Star
View Full coverage on Google News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Celtic pre-season talkers as Ange Postecoglou's side draw against Legia Warsaw in Artur Boruc farewell]]></title>
        <id>3c60471a3beef58b31a7d649a51afbcc</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20292942.3-celtic-pre-season-talkers-ange-postecoglous-side-draw-legia-warsaw-artur-boruc-farewell/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T17:55:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[STAR SHOWING FROM HATATE]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Has Ange Postecoglou Found His Celtic MVP?]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/has-ange-postecoglou-found-his-celtic-mvp/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/has-ange-postecoglou-found-his-celtic-mvp/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T17:53:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic concluded their final game on the road during pre-season tonight with a 2-2 draw against Legia Warsaw in Artur Boruc’s final game of professional football.  It was a great showing from the Hoops in the first half as Postecoglou’s side moved the ball around well having great intent all across the pitch. There wasn’t […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The hype is building around one player at Celtic after draw vs Legia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/match/the-reo-hatate-hype-is-building-at-celtic-after-another-classy-pre-season-showing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/the-reo-hatate-hype-is-building-at-celtic-after-another-classy-pre-season-showing/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T17:53:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The performance of Reo Hatate is one of the main talking points coming out Celtic’s 2-2 draw away to Legia tonight, as hype builds around what he can achieve in the new season. Hatate was only on the pitch for 45 minutes in Warsaw, but that was enough to see he is looking very sharp ...
The post The hype is building around one player at Celtic after draw vs Legia appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic locked in Legia stalement as Holy Goalie receives his wish]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/report-celtic-locked-in-legia-stalement-as-holy-goalie-receives-his-wish/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/report-celtic-locked-in-legia-stalement-as-holy-goalie-receives-his-wish/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T17:53:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic continued their topsy-turvy start to pre-season with another 2-2 draw to leave themselves feeling rather disappointed against an admittedly below par Legia Warsaw side on Wednesday afternoon in Artur Boruc’s testimonial. The Holy Goalie received a superb reception from both sets of supporters in the Polish capital as he took to the pitch for Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[&#039;Get somebody in&#039; - McAvennie tells Postecoglou to axe Celtic starlet for new signing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-frank-mcavennie-talks-up-new-midfielder-coming-in-transfer-spl-ange/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-frank-mcavennie-talks-up-new-midfielder-coming-in-transfer-spl-ange/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T17:40:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic need to replace another midfielder between now and the end of the summer transfer window, according to former Hoops striker Frank McAvennie. The Lowdown: Mooy in, Johnston out? The Scottish Premiership champions continued their productive summer on Tuesday, securing the services of Australia international Aaron Mooy. The 31-year-old joins Celtic on a two-year deal […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Superb volley draws Legia level as Celtic lead crumbles]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/video-superb-volley-draws-legia-level-as-celtic-lead-crumbles/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-superb-volley-draws-legia-level-as-celtic-lead-crumbles/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T17:33:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have thrown away a 2-0 lead in the Polish capital after a superb volley by Portugal star Josue drew Legia Warsaw level in Artur Boruc’s testimonial game. Maciej Rosolek had halved the deficit just 41 seconds into the second-half after some weak defending by Cameron Carter-Vickers, and the home side looked to be piling Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Sloppy defending halves Celtic’s lead within 30 seconds of the second half]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/video-sloppy-defending-halves-celtics-lead-within-30-seconds-of-the-second-half/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-sloppy-defending-halves-celtics-lead-within-30-seconds-of-the-second-half/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T17:15:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s unusually for Cameron Carter-Vickers to be sloppy at the back for Celtic, but his weak physical showing has allowed Legia Warsaw to half the deficit against the Hoops in Artur Boruc’s testimonial against Ange Postecoglou’s men. Celtic had raced into a 2-0 lead at half-time following some superb football which could and should have Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Japanese link-up as Hatate feeds Maeda to double the lead]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/video-japanese-link-up-as-hatate-feeds-maeda-to-double-the-lead/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-japanese-link-up-as-hatate-feeds-maeda-to-double-the-lead/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T16:53:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s Japanese duo have linked up superbly to give the Hoops a 2-0 lead going into the interval in Warsaw – with Reo Hatate sliding Daizen Maeda in to double their advantage in Artur Boruc’s testimonial game. Hatate had finished superbly from an Anthony Ralston cross on the 20th minute to leave Boruc 1-0 down Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Of The Day: Artur Boruc – The Holy Goalie]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/photo-of-the-day-artur-boruc-the-holy-goalie/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/photo-of-the-day-artur-boruc-the-holy-goalie/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T16:44:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today’s photo of the day is chosen to the honour the man who is currently holding his testimonial match against Celtic. That man is of course none other than Celtic and Legia Warsaw legend Artur Boruc. Boruc was among the world’s best goalkeeper for a few years, at a time when he was plying his Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Reo Hatate Scores Special Goal Against Artur Boruc]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/video-reo-hatate-scores-special-goal-against-artur-boruc/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/video-reo-hatate-scores-special-goal-against-artur-boruc/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T16:38:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE has scored a special pre-season goal against Legia Warsaw and Artur Boruc. The Japanese midfielder was back in the starting XI after the last week or so off due to injury and illness. He certainly made up for lost time with this outstanding goal. Celtic have looked great in the first half against […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate scores stunning Celtic opener vs Legia Warsaw but Hoops fans are all wondering the same thing]]></title>
        <id>8f1cc240dcc482a70cdcd7b966d2dd81</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20292738.reo-hatate-scores-stunning-celtic-opener-vs-legia-warsaw-hoops-fans-wondering-thing/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T16:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE has opened Celtic's scoring against Legia Warsaw with a stunning finish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Hatate puts Celtic 1-0 up in Warsaw with a stunning volley]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/video-hatate-puts-celtic-1-0-up-in-warsaw-with-a-stunning-volley/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-hatate-puts-celtic-1-0-up-in-warsaw-with-a-stunning-volley/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T16:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reo Hatate’s sumptuous volley has given Celtic a 1-0 lead against Legia Warsaw in Artur Boruc’s testimonial game in the Polish capital. Hatate has become known for scoring superb goals in his time at Celtic Park ever since his arrival last January, with the Japanese star famously scoring two howitzers against theRangers at Paradise back Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Chief Makes Rare Public Appearance]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-chief-makes-rare-public-appearance/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-chief-makes-rare-public-appearance/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T16:11:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic chief executive Michael Nicholson made a rare public appearance on Wednesday evening as Celtic took on Legia Warsaw in Poland. Nicholson made his way onto the pitch pre-match against the Polish side to hand over a Celtic cross as a gift to former Celtic hero Artur Boruc on his final match before retiring. The […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Artur Boruc in a Celtic jersey ahead of farewell fixture]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/video-artur-boruc-in-a-celtic-jersey-ahead-of-farewell-fixture/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-artur-boruc-in-a-celtic-jersey-ahead-of-farewell-fixture/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T16:01:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artur Boruc has warmed up in a Celtic jersey as the Polish keeper bows out of professional football with a friendly between Legia Warsaw and Ange Postecoglou’s Scottish Champions. Boruc would make 221 appearances for Celtic, earning a number of plaudits as well as winning three League titles, two league cups and one Scottish Cup. Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artur Boruc pulls on Celtic shirt again for Legia Warsaw farewell showdown and Hoops fans are loving it]]></title>
        <id>e3284c8907da48e380ee57ecad6415cc</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20292573.artur-boruc-pulls-celtic-shirt-legia-warsaw-farewell-showdown-hoops-fans-loving/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T15:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ARTUR BORUC has pulled on the Celtic colours for a final time ahead of his  farewell clash in Poland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Cheers Celtic, greetin noo”: Fans react to Artur Boruc donning a Celtic shirt for the last time…]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/cheers-celtic-greetin-noo-fans-react-to-artur-boruc-donning-a-celtic-shirt-for-the-last-time/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/cheers-celtic-greetin-noo-fans-react-to-artur-boruc-donning-a-celtic-shirt-for-the-last-time/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T15:48:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It had to happen one day, didn’t it? That’s right – Artur Boruc is lining up in a Celtic goalkeeper shirt for one last hurrah before he retires from football. Famous pictures have encapsulated the ‘Holy Goalie’ wearing a yellow jersey in some of Celtic’s most famous results – wins against theRangers, ties against AC Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: KYOGO OUT, MAEDA IN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-kyogo-out-maeda-in/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/confirmed-kyogo-out-maeda-in/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T15:29:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOP scorer Kyogo Furuhashi is out the Celtic starting line-up against Legia Watsaw in the Artur Boruc testimonial match in Poland tonight. The Japanese hitman, who fired in 20 goals last season despite missing 22 games through injury, is on the bench with his countryman Daizen Maeda leading the attack. Liel Abada and James Forrest [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EX-BOSS TIPS MOOY TO BE HOOPS HIT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ex-boss-tips-mooy-to-be-hoops-hit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ex-boss-tips-mooy-to-be-hoops-hit/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T15:13:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OWEN COYLE is backing new Bhoy Aaron Mooy to be a hit at Celtic – after allowing him to leave Bolton for free 12 years ago. The much-travelled team boss, currently in charge of Queen’s Park, worked with the 31-year-old Australian midfielder while he was gaffer of the Lancashire club. Mooy was determined to leave [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Names Celtic Starting XI; One Major Return]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/ange-names-celtic-starting-xi-one-major-return/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/ange-names-celtic-starting-xi-one-major-return/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T15:10:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic team is up for the penultimate game of pre-season in Poland! The Hoops are taking part in a farewell match for their iconic former goalkeeper Artur Boruc — taking on Legia Warsaw. Ange Postecoglou has named a strong side for the game. Anthony Ralston makes the team despite getting a couple of stitiches […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Legia Warsaw “L” v Celtic, Live updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/legia-warsaw-l-v-celtic-live-updates/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/legia-warsaw-l-v-celtic-live-updates/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T15:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Live updates from Artur Boruc’s last game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Team’s Up – 5 changes as the Bhoys pay one last farewell to Artur Boruc]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/teams-up-5-changes-as-the-bhoys-pay-one-last-farewell-to-artur-boruc/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/teams-up-5-changes-as-the-bhoys-pay-one-last-farewell-to-artur-boruc/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T14:56:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic take to the Stadion Wojska Polskiego in Warsaw on Wednesday afternoon in what is likely to be Hoops’ fans final farewell to shotstopper hero Artur Boruc – affectionately dubbed as the ‘Holy Goalie’ – as they take on Legia in Poland’s capital. Following a measly 2-2 draw with Blackburn Rovers on Saturday in the first Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange rotates: Celtic XI confirmed, big chance for new signing, TV details, instant reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-vs-legia-confirmed-rotated-xi-broadcast-details-instant-reaction/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/celtic-team-vs-legia-confirmed-rotated-xi-broadcast-details-instant-reaction/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T14:55:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has named his Celtic team vs Legia in Warsaw tonight, for Artur Boruc’s goodbye match. The full match squad is as follows: Starting XI – Hart, Ralston, Carter-Vickers, Welsh, Bernabei, McGregor, Hatate, O’Riley, Forrest, Abada, Maeda. Substitutes – Bain, Siegrist, Taylor, Jullien, Kyogo, Turnbull, McCarthy, Jota, Johnston, Ideguchi, Lawal, Juranovic. Boruc is a ...
The post Ange rotates: Celtic XI confirmed, big chance for new signing, TV details, instant reaction appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic team news vs Legia Warsaw as Ange Postecoglou's side set up for Artur Boruc farewell clash]]></title>
        <id>1360126d5cca73894bf848c96c24203a</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20292142.celtic-team-news-vs-legia-warsaw-ange-postecoglous-side-set-artur-boruc-farewell-clash/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T14:46:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECOGLOU has named his Celtic team to take on Legia Warsaw for tonight's farewell clash for Artur Boruc.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grant backs Jenz to be Celtic success]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/grant-backs-jenz-to-be-celtic-success/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/grant-backs-jenz-to-be-celtic-success/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T14:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic midfield general Peter Grant spent a good few years at Fulham working in various roles where he helped develop Patrick Roberts, Moussa Dembele and Matt O’Riley.  Yesterday saw a fourth be added to that impressive list in the from of German central defender Moritz Jenz on a season long loan from Lorient with […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton reacts as Rangers and BBC dispute ends amid Celtic legend's Ibrox ban - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEKNxrD45OVjgU7BZfGGoptQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPLfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/chris-sutton-reacts-rangers-bbc-24542873"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T14:31:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton reacts as Rangers and BBC dispute ends amid Celtic legend's Ibrox ban  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hero Chris Sutton reacts to Rangers allowing BBC back into Ibrox after BT Sport snub]]></title>
        <id>040e23560cc31496022d9fb69cecc870</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20291843.celtic-hero-chris-sutton-reacts-rangers-allowing-bbc-back-ibrox-bt-sport-snub/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T13:47:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC hero Chris Sutton has reacted to the news that Rangers and BBC Scotland have settled their long-standing dispute.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegraph report Leicester City interest in signing Matt O’Riley from Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/telegraph-report-leicester-city-interest-in-signing-matt-oriley-from-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/telegraph-report-leicester-city-interest-in-signing-matt-oriley-from-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T13:36:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O’Riley has only been at Celtic since January, but it’s fair to say the player has made a big impression already. Since joining the Hops for a mere £1.5m from MK Dons in the last transfer window, O’Riley has caught the eye as a scorer of great goals and few simple ones, but also Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Big Celtic Q&A and 2022/23 season preview with fan site CeltsAreHere - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEPAvA0EBgFsL3HDjYLKkR_UqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPPfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/big-celtic-qa-202223-season-24539581"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T13:23:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Big Celtic Q&A and 2022/23 season preview with fan site CeltsAreHere  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Legia Warsaw vs Celtic: TV channel, live stream & kick-off time for Artur Borucs tribute game]]></title>
        <id>7d927dd2a9461aa1ce805f56e7337318</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20291649.legia-warsaw-vs-celtic-tv-channel-live-stream-kick-off-time-artur-borucs-tribute-game/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T13:17:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC take on Legia Warsaw in their latest pre-season friendly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star Matt O’Riley ‘high’ on Leicester City’s transfer wishlist]]></title>
        <id>c6dad819f8573c350a5ffda8e4832a7b</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20291367.celtic-star-matt-oriley-high-leicester-citys-transfer-wishlist/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T12:47:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY is reportedly a target for Leicester City this summer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Face Value Ticket Resale]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-face-value-ticket/</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-face-value-ticket/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T12:43:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sold out signs were up for last Saturday’s game between Celtic and Blackburn. We need to now have a conversation about Celtic Face Value Ticket Resale. Celtic Park was not full against Blackburn yet some Celtic fans who wanted to attend had no option but to watch on TV. It could be the same this […]
The post Celtic Face Value Ticket Resale appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sadly for the Ibrox side, it looks like Celtic will retain the Transfer Record Trophy - Read Celtic]]></title>
        <id>CBMid2h0dHBzOi8vcmVhZGNlbHRpYy5jb20vMjAyMi8wNy8yMC9zYWRseS1mb3ItdGhlLWlicm94LXNpZGUtaXQtbG9va3MtbGlrZS1jZWx0aWMtd2lsbC1yZXRhaW4tdGhlLXRyYW5zZmVyLXJlY29yZC10cm9waHkv0gEA</id>
        <link href="https://readceltic.com/2022/07/20/sadly-for-the-ibrox-side-it-looks-like-celtic-will-retain-the-transfer-record-trophy/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T12:43:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sadly for the Ibrox side, it looks like Celtic will retain the Transfer Record Trophy  Read Celtic]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calvin Bassey Rangers to Ajax transfer fee confirmed and how Celtic's record Kieran Tierney sale compares - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiECrHnc595M5sQLPr1jLMlO8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPTfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/calvin-bassey-rangers-ajax-transfer-24540954"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T12:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Calvin Bassey Rangers to Ajax transfer fee confirmed and how Celtic's record Kieran Tierney sale compares  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: SPFL dig up new Celtic signing&#039;s class goal vs Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/video-spfl-dig-up-class-aaron-mooy-goal-vs-rivals-after-celtic-signing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/video-spfl-dig-up-class-aaron-mooy-goal-vs-rivals-after-celtic-signing/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T12:10:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy has joined Celtic on a two-year deal, and what some people may not realise he’s actually making a return to Scottish football. Mooy, before his rise through the A-League, English Championship and Premier League, was once on the books at St Mirren, spending two years in his early 20s at the club. His ...
The post Video: SPFL dig up new Celtic signing&#039;s class goal vs Rangers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liam’s Aberdeen form tipping the Scales in Celtic’s favour]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/liams-aberdeen-form-tipping-the-scales-in-celtics-favour/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/liams-aberdeen-form-tipping-the-scales-in-celtics-favour/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T11:49:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liam Scales appear to have already made a positive impression in the short time he’s been playing with Jim Goodwin’s rebuilt Aberdeen side. The Dons have been in completive action already this season, with League Cup group stage football against Stirling Albion, Dumbarton and Peterhead. And it appears Scales – who is operating as a Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Ange Postecoglou and Celtic have got their priorities,” Sky Sports reporter]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/ange-postecoglou-and-celtic-have-got-their-priorities-sky-sports-reporter/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/ange-postecoglou-and-celtic-have-got-their-priorities-sky-sports-reporter/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T11:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s an incredibly relaxing position to be in to think Celtic’s transfer business may have been concluded with an incredible 44 days of the transfer window remaining. Just as we did with the January window, Celtic have not only been busy in the transfer market, they have also got their business done early. Yet according Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artur Boruc expecting to cry vs Celtic; discusses recent controversy and next career steps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/artur-boruc-expecting-to-cry-vs-celtic-discusses-recent-controversy-and-next-career-steps/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/artur-boruc-expecting-to-cry-vs-celtic-discusses-recent-controversy-and-next-career-steps/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artur Boruc is expecting an emotional night in his farewell match between Legia and Celtic this evening, believing the event is taking place so he can “finally cry”. Legia are Boruc’s boyhood club and that long association will be emotional enough for the goalkeeper, without also adding in Celtic – a team he also adored ...
The post Artur Boruc expecting to cry vs Celtic; discusses recent controversy and next career steps appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O'Riley a Leicester 'target' as Celtic star high on Brendan Rodgers transfer wishlist - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEBuMZYu_IK6JOCs73ZyaJ0QqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/matt-oriley-leicester-target-celtic-27529392"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T11:16:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O'Riley a Leicester 'target' as Celtic star high on Brendan Rodgers transfer wishlist  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[&#039;Another...&#039; - Rangers pundit wowed by &#039;really good&#039; transfer news out of Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-alan-hutton-talks-up-aaron-mooy-signing-transfer-ange-spl/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-alan-hutton-talks-up-aaron-mooy-signing-transfer-ange-spl/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T11:15:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy could be a ‘really good’ signing for Celtic after the deal went through on Tuesday, says former Rangers star Alan Hutton. The Lowdown: Mooy signs The Hoops had been strongly linked with a move for the Australia international in recent weeks, as Ange Postecoglou has been seeking to improve his midfield options having […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scintillating Rangers have 20 point advantage over Celtic as Parkhead wind up merchant gets rinsed - Hotline - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEBxqhtqDM5hjB65qnXZ3MqMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-transfer-news/scintillating-rangers-20-point-advantage-27529224"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T11:10:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scintillating Rangers have 20 point advantage over Celtic as Parkhead wind up merchant gets rinsed - Hotline  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good and bad times to sign frees]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/good-and-bad-times-to-sign-frees/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/good-and-bad-times-to-sign-frees/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T10:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy (31) and Moritz Jenz (23) we’re added to the squad yesterday, one an experienced central midfielder Ange Postecoglou has known to years, the other an unknown to us but whom Celtic have watched for over a year. There are times to worry about free and low cost signings and times to be reassured.  [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["This will not be an ordinary match"; Legia hype up Celtic visit as ticket sales pick up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/this-will-not-be-an-ordinary-match-legia-hype-up-celtic-visit-as-ticket-sales-pick-up/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/this-will-not-be-an-ordinary-match-legia-hype-up-celtic-visit-as-ticket-sales-pick-up/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legia Warsaw are urging as many of their supporters as possible to attend tonight’s match against Celtic in honour of Artur Boruc. Controversy has surrounded the fixture in Poland after the club’s die-hard supporters considered they had made tickets far too expensive for the event. In a bid to boost dreadful ticket sales they eventually ...
The post "This will not be an ordinary match"; Legia hype up Celtic visit as ticket sales pick up appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Idiotic Anti-Celtic Loan Banner Appears on Social Media]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/idiotic-anti-celtic-loan-banner-appears-on-social-media/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/idiotic-anti-celtic-loan-banner-appears-on-social-media/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T10:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few Aberdeen fans have got together to get a banner made telling their chairman they don’t want any more Celtic loan players. Yes, you read that right! They paid money to get a banner made to state they don’t want to take any players on loan from Celtic anymore. It seems an extreme over […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The BBC’s Grovelling Apology To Ibrox Is A Staggering Humiliation For Its Journalists.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/blogs/the-bbcs-grovelling-apology-to-ibrox-is-a-staggering-humiliation-for-its-journalists/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/blogs/the-bbcs-grovelling-apology-to-ibrox-is-a-staggering-humiliation-for-its-journalists/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T10:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The BBC and Ibrox have “resolved their dispute” this morning, a dispute that has been going on for ages and which kept the broadcaster from working at the ground on match days. Not a single BBC listener has been materially inconvenienced by this, except for those who follow the club and most of them have […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The BBC’s Grovelling Apology To Ibrox Is A Staggering Humiliation For Its Journalists. - TheCelticBlog.com]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEOfwDlu397IBoGr_UYrRJ04qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowne-jCzDg-bsDMLnLhQc</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/the-bbcs-grovelling-apology-to-ibrox-is-a-staggering-humiliation-for-its-journalists/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The BBC’s Grovelling Apology To Ibrox Is A Staggering Humiliation For Its Journalists.  TheCelticBlog.com]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Rogic shares Celtic post as midfielder breaks silence after welfare 'concern' - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEEeNfpRzXt2TehmVL2k-wOwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPPfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/tom-rogic-shares-celtic-post-24539108"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T10:27:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Rogic shares Celtic post as midfielder breaks silence after welfare 'concern'  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star 'high' on Leicester City transfer wish list - Leicestershire Live]]></title>
        <id>CBMibmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmxlaWNlc3Rlcm1lcmN1cnkuY28udWsvc3BvcnQvZm9vdGJhbGwvdHJhbnNmZXItbmV3cy9sZWljZXN0ZXItY2l0eS10cmFuc2ZlcnMtY2VsdGljLW9yaWxleS03MzU2NDA30gEA</id>
        <link href="https://www.leicestermercury.co.uk/sport/football/transfer-news/leicester-city-transfers-celtic-oriley-7356407"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T10:22:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star 'high' on Leicester City transfer wish list  Leicestershire Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Football Ramble Podcast – Edouard Michut and the ‘Jota route’ to stardom]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/football-ramble-podcast-edouard-michut-and-the-jota-route-to-stardom/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/football-ramble-podcast-edouard-michut-and-the-jota-route-to-stardom/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T10:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Respected European football writer Andy Brassell has been talking to the excellent Football Ramble podcast this week, and has been talking up Celtic as a destination the young stars of European football, perhaps frustrated by the lack of first team gametime at some of Europe’s big clubs. Brassell used Celtic’s recent links to PSG youngster Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROGIC APPLAUDS NEW BHOY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rogic-applauds-new-bhoy/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rogic-applauds-new-bhoy/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T10:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOM ROGIC has congratulated his Australian international team-mate Aaron Mooy on his move to Celtic. The playmaker left the Hoops at the end of the season following nine-and-a-half years at Parkhead and has missed the opportunity of teaming up with his fellow-countryman. Rogic, 29, has not posted on his Instagram page since sharing a farewell [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic CEO Michael Nicholson – Timing Is Everything]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-ceo-michael-nicholson-timing-is-everything/</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-ceo-michael-nicholson-timing-is-everything/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T09:43:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Timing is Everything it would seem for Celtic CEO and SPFL board member Michael Nicholson. He always seemed to be the quiet man on the Celtic board.  In the shadow of Peter Lawell and out of limelight. https://celticfanzine.com/product-category/t-shirts/ If he had he been appointed to the Celtic CEO role straight after Peter Lawell, it would […]
The post Celtic CEO Michael Nicholson – Timing Is Everything appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: THE DAY BIG JOCK APOLOGISED: EVAN WILLIAMS REVEALS ALL (Part Six)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-the-day-big-jock-apologised-evan-williams-reveals-all-part-six/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-the-day-big-jock-apologised-evan-williams-reveals-all-part-six/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T09:29:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EVAN WILLIAMS was a massive fan of Ronnie Simpson, the legendary Lisbon Lion he had to follow in the Celtic first team. The keeper, who arrived from Wolves in October 1969, rated the Hoops veteran as “the cleverest goalie there was” and was eager to work with the man who made his Scotland international debut [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rogic breaks summer silence to applaud Mooy signing for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/rogic-breaks-summer-silence-to-applaud-mooy-signing-for-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/rogic-breaks-summer-silence-to-applaud-mooy-signing-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T09:15:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aussie national boss Graham Arnold has been desperate to hear from Tom Rogic, after his text messages to the former Celtic star, in light of the player’s absence from the Socceroo’s World Cup play-off squad apparently went unanswered. Yet Rogic, who was recently spotted training back home in Oz, relieving any fears regarding his well-being, Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quick-start for VAR in Scottish Premiership could help referees before World Cup in Qatar]]></title>
        <id>3775025</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/quick-start-for-var-in-scottish-premiership-could-help-referees-before-world-cup-in-qatar-3775025"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T09:12:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Video assistant referees could be in use across Scotland’s top flight earlier than anticipated this season as talks continued to expedite the introduction of the system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Oliver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic vs Legia Warsaw; How to watch]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-vs-legia-warsaw-how-to-watch/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-vs-legia-warsaw-how-to-watch/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T09:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will play their fifth pre-season friendly on Wednesday evening and will say farewell to a Celtic Legend in the process. The Hoops take on Legia Warsaw in Poland as they gear up for the new SPFL season which kicks off at the end of this month Artur played at Celtic from 2005 – 2010 […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QUIET MAN MOOY WANTS TO BE BIG NOISE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/quiet-man-mooy-wants-to-be-big-noise/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/quiet-man-mooy-wants-to-be-big-noise/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T08:54:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEW Bhoy Aaron Mooy doesn’t like talking about himself – but aims to be a roaring success at Celtic. The Australia international midfielder, 31, signed a two-year deal with the champions after being released from his contract by Chinese Superleague outfit Shanghai Port at the turn of the year. Former club Huddersfield Town were among [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanished Report claimed Ibrox boss left seven voice messages on Mooy’s mobile]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/vanished-report-claimed-ibrox-boss-left-seven-voice-messages-on-mooys-mobile/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/vanished-report-claimed-ibrox-boss-left-seven-voice-messages-on-mooys-mobile/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T08:45:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it came to competition in the chase for new Celtic signing Aaron Mooy, Newcastle United and Mooy’s former director of football at former club Brighton, Dan Ashworth, was seen as possible challenge. There were also a host of English Championship clubs said to be hopeful of enticing the Aussie international south of the border Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The last time Celtic and Rangers played home games at same time as Glasgow set for rare occasion - Glasgow Live]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEBg23EE160t4DhDGWIhUcEUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow96D9CjDOy_QCMPvp0wU</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowlive.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/last-time-celtic-rangers-played-24537717"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T08:32:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The last time Celtic and Rangers played home games at same time as Glasgow set for rare occasion  Glasgow Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic named as transfer hotspot for continent's rising stars aiming 'to take the Jota route' - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>1493502248</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-transfer-news/celtic-named-transfer-hotspot-continents-27526487"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T08:26:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic named as transfer hotspot for continent's rising stars aiming 'to take the Jota route'  Daily Record
Moritz Jenz close to Celtic loan transfer as defender is set to join Aaron Mooy  Football Scotland
Celtic target completes medical and move now close  The Celtic Bhoys
Jenz Deal Gets Green light; Celtic Closing in on Double Signing  CeltsAreHere
Double delight as Celtic confirm signings of Mooy and Jenz  The Celtic Star
View Full coverage on Google News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What channel is Legia Warsaw v Celtic on? Is it on TV? Pre-season friendly kick-off time and how to watch]]></title>
        <id>3774930</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/what-channel-is-legia-warsaw-v-celtic-on-is-it-on-tv-pre-season-friendly-kick-off-time-and-how-to-watch-3774930"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T08:23:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic continue their preparations for the new season with a trip to Poland for a friendly with Legia Warsaw.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘DESTINY’: ADMITS NEW BHOY JENZ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/destiny-admits-new-bhoy-jenz/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/destiny-admits-new-bhoy-jenz/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T08:08:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEW Bhoy Moritz Jenz believes it was his destiny to play for Celtic. The 23-year-old German centre-back agreed a season-long loan deal from French club Lorient  – a year after Ange Postecoglou made his initial move as he revamped his Hoops squad. Jenz, though, left Swiss outfit Lausanne-Sport for the Ligue 1 club, but now [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aberdeen fans in Celtic loan players protest as Dave Cormack's transfer policy questioned - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEJtPahbRktdm2LJbt8yEWdQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPLfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/aberdeen-fans-celtic-loan-players-24537101"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T07:28:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aberdeen fans in Celtic loan players protest as Dave Cormack's transfer policy questioned  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Legia Warsaw v Celtic: team news, KO time and where to watch]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/legia-warsaw-v-celtic-team-news-ko-time-and-where-to-watch/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/legia-warsaw-v-celtic-team-news-ko-time-and-where-to-watch/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T07:22:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are in Poland to provide the opposition for Legia Warsaw in the Artur Boruc testimonial match this afternoon. The sides last met in a competitive fixture at Murrayfield in August 2014 in a Champions League qualifier with the then Polish Champions winning the match 2-0 – or so it seemed. A late substitution involving Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: ‘GORAM BROKE MY HEART’: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Nine)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-goram-broke-my-heart-the-tommy-burns-story-part-nine/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-goram-broke-my-heart-the-tommy-burns-story-part-nine/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T07:13:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS had won the Scottish Cup in his first season as Celtic manager after his appointment on July 12 1994. The league title, though, was the legendary Celt’s priority target as his second campaign prepared to kick off. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE series, we chart Tommy Burns’ career as the Hoops gaffer during turbulent [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Legia To Stand On: The Full Story Of The Saga Involving Celtic &amp; Tonight’s Opposition]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/no-legia-to-stand-on-the-full-story-of-the-saga-involving-celtic-tonights-opposition/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/no-legia-to-stand-on-the-full-story-of-the-saga-involving-celtic-tonights-opposition/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T06:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic face Legia Warsaw in Poland this evening, in a testimonial match that has been organised for Artur Boruc. Beyond both clubs’ love for the player, the obvious stand out in many people’s minds was the saga involving both clubs back in 2014. It’s fair to say many Legia fans still harbour a grudge against Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artur Boruc The Holy Goalie]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/artur-boruc-the-holy-goalie/</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/artur-boruc-the-holy-goalie/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T06:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are back in action tonight v Legia Warsaw in a pre-season friendly to celebrate the career of former Hoops goalie, Artur Boruc. The former Celtic number one, Artur Boruc The Holy Goalie enjoyed many memorable moments at Celtic making over 200 appearances.  https://celticfanzine.com/product-category/monthly-print-subscription/ David Potter, Celtic historian and author looks back at his time at […]
The post Artur Boruc The Holy Goalie appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Rogic Shares Celtic Post]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/tom-rogic-shares-celtic-post/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/tom-rogic-shares-celtic-post/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Rogic has gone off the grid since leaving Celtic. The midfielder is yet to sign for a new club, but was spotted in Australia earlier this month. [Read More Here] The Celtic hero has always kept somewhat of a low profile. However, tonight he made sure to acknowledge Celtic’s latest transfer – his friend […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“My Dream Come True” – Moritz Jenz reacts to Celtic move on Instagram]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/my-dream-come-true-moritz-jenz-reacts-to-celtic-move-on-instagram/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/my-dream-come-true-moritz-jenz-reacts-to-celtic-move-on-instagram/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T05:39:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would accurate to assume our new central defender Moritz Jenz could not contain his delight at finally managing to get his perfect football club in Celtic. The big man had a near miss last summer and ended up heading to Ligue 1 with FC Lorient. He endured an underwhelming time in the French league Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Give it to them’ – BBC Journalist’s Brilliant Celtic Transfer Post]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/give-it-to-them-bbc-journalists-brilliant-celtic-transfer-post/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/give-it-to-them-bbc-journalists-brilliant-celtic-transfer-post/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T05:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aberdeen based BBC journalist Phil McDonald has declared the Dons must secure Celtic loan bhoy Liam Scales at all costs. The Irishman went out on loan to Aberdeen earlier this summer. Since the Pittodrie side kicked off their League Cup campaign, they’re yet to concede a goal with Scaled at the heart of defence. It’s […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Give it to them’ – BBC Journalist’s Brilliant Celtic Transfer Post - CeltsAreHere]]></title>
        <id>CBMiWGh0dHBzOi8vY2VsdHNhcmVoZXJlLmNvbS9naXZlLWl0LXRvLXRoZW0tYmJjLWpvdXJuYWxpc3RzLWJyaWxsaWFudC1jZWx0aWMtdHJhbnNmZXItcG9zdC_SAVxodHRwczovL2NlbHRzYXJlaGVyZS5jb20vZ2l2ZS1pdC10by10aGVtLWJiYy1qb3VybmFsaXN0cy1icmlsbGlhbnQtY2VsdGljLXRyYW5zZmVyLXBvc3QvYW1wLw</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/give-it-to-them-bbc-journalists-brilliant-celtic-transfer-post/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T05:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘Give it to them’ – BBC Journalist’s Brilliant Celtic Transfer Post  CeltsAreHere]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Wednesday July 20: We Know Where We’re Going]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=17842</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=17842"/>
        <updated>2022-07-20T04:36:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic welcomed two more players to the fold yesterday, with Moritz Jenz and Aaron Mooy putting pen to paper.     Mooy, an Australian international…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Verdict as Chester FC come from behind to beat Stalybridge Celtic 3-2 - Cheshire Live]]></title>
        <id>CAIiELzzMoN_XSVwaPVBOaMpfsUqMwgEKioIACIQEimq9M5mts6cb4BxHgQdYCoUCAoiEBIpqvTOZrbOnG-AcR4EHWAwstfkBg</id>
        <link href="https://www.cheshire-live.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/chester-fc-stalybridge-celtic-report-24536349"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T23:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Verdict as Chester FC come from behind to beat Stalybridge Celtic 3-2  Cheshire Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signings: Interviews]]></title>
        <id>https://www.jerseydoesntshrink.com/2022/7/19/23270704/new-celtic-signings-interviews</id>
        <link href="https://www.jerseydoesntshrink.com/2022/7/19/23270704/new-celtic-signings-interviews"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T23:01:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Alan Harvey/SNS Group via Getty Images
  

 Mortiz Jenz and Aaron Mooy, as widely expected a few days ago, officially put pen to paper for the club earlier today.
Australian internationalist, Mooy, is reunited with his former manager, having worked under Ange Postecoglou during his tenure with the national team, and he joins the club on a two-year deal. Moritz Jenz is a German central defender who has been playing in the French top flight with Lorient since 2021.
Prior to that, the 23-year-old spent five years with Fulham, after which time he had a season in Switzerland with Lausanne-Sport before moving to France. He joins Celtic on a season-long loan, with the club having an option to buy.


 Give our  Bhoys a follow on Instagram, Celts! #MooySigns!  | #WillkommenJenz  — Celtic Football Club (@CelticFC) July 19, 2022



The new bhoys gave exclusive interviews earlier today which you can tune into below:


We’ll have a reaction to them on GIGPOD very soon as we gear up for our preview podcast ahead of the Aberdeen game shortly, as well as news for the changes with the show for 22-23! 
As always you can subscribe on Spotify or iTunes!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video – New Bhoy Moritz Jenz sold on Celtic by old teammate Matt O’Riley]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/video-new-bhoy-moritz-jenz-sold-on-celtic-by-old-teammate-matt-oriley/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-new-bhoy-moritz-jenz-sold-on-celtic-by-old-teammate-matt-oriley/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T22:20:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of Celtic’s newest recruits has revealed that he was desperate to play in the green and white hoops after being sold on it by Matt O’Riley. Moritz Jenz has insisted he was always looking to sign for Ange Postecoglou’s side after interest in him last summer when he was playing in Switzerland with Lausanne-Sport. Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic-bound Aaron Mooy's attitude at St Mirren held him back, insists Hugh Murray]]></title>
        <id>bf5dfde5ab6c57fe89be43ad784252c6</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20289307.celtic-bound-aaron-mooys-attitude-st-mirren-held-back-insists-hugh-murray/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WHEN Aaron Mooy first arrived in Scottish football at St Mirren in October 2010, it didn’t take long for his new team-mate Hugh Murray to be convinced of his obvious talents. And yet, the long-serving Buddies midfielder couldn’t envisage the youngster going on to play in the English Premier League one day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic should make sensational swoop for Chelsea player - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEKn-yixRcD4Tww0wI_q4qbUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4KKJCzCv9JoDMICkoAY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2022/07/19/celtic-sensational-swoop-chelsea-player/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T21:07:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic should make sensational swoop for Chelsea player  The Celtic Bhoys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liam Scales defies anti Celtic loan message by angry Aberdeen fans - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiELpvEHWt7HktG8UqHtsPodAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-transfer-news/aberdeen-fans-demand-no-more-27524856"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T20:57:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liam Scales defies anti Celtic loan message by angry Aberdeen fans  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers’ Alfredo Morelos worry while Celtic get better - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEOX_953P02NxSb98w8v-mxcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4KKJCzCv9JoDMICkoAY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2022/07/19/rangers-alfredo-morelos-worry-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T20:10:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers’ Alfredo Morelos worry while Celtic get better  The Celtic Bhoys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic backed to sign holding midfielder amid Mikey Johnston exit claim – expert - Football Insider]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEN4r0Sszv9lYN-SXuWAQ99MqMwgEKioIACIQnJ4k3aT29tENAyPF0QESjSoUCAoiEJyeJN2k9vbRDQMjxdEBEo0w4IzKBg</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballinsider247.com/celtic-backed-to-sign-holding-midfielder-amid-mikey-johnston-exit-claim-expert/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic backed to sign holding midfielder amid Mikey Johnston exit claim – expert  Football Insider]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Legia Warsaw vs Celtic: Live stream, TV channel, PPV, team news and kick-off time - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiECYDtsBO_j7mQr5q-6BQSLYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPLfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/legia-warsaw-celtic-live-stream-24530852"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legia Warsaw vs Celtic: Live stream, TV channel, PPV, team news and kick-off time  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Nicholson Receives Major Praise From Celtic New Bhoy]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/michael-nicholson-receives-major-praise-from-celtic-new-bhoy/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/michael-nicholson-receives-major-praise-from-celtic-new-bhoy/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T18:47:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moritz Jenz has taken to Instagram after signing for Celtic and gave one man at Parkhead a special thank you. With a season long loan in the bag, Moritz made a point of thanking the current Celtic chief executive Michael Nicholson for making the deal happen. “A special thank you to the SEO Mr Nicholson […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SPFL transfer news LIVE: Rangers sign Davies and Celtic complete double deal - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEA8_Zs8w88DrckQTWB5TB04qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPPfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/spfl-transfer-news-live-rangers-24515217"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T18:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SPFL transfer news LIVE: Rangers sign Davies and Celtic complete double deal  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Celtic squad depth chart after Mooy and Jenz arrivals; what positions are next]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/full-celtic-squad-depth-chart-after-mooy-and-jenz-arrivals-what-positions-are-next/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/full-celtic-squad-depth-chart-after-mooy-and-jenz-arrivals-what-positions-are-next/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have announced the signings of Aaron Mooy in midfield and Moritz Jenz in defence, strengthening Ange Postecoglou’s squad ahead of the new season. The manager has now added Jenz, Mooy, Alexandro Bernabei and Ben Siegrist to his group of champions, also completing permanent deals for Jota and Cameron Carter-Vickers. It means Celtic now have ...
The post Full Celtic squad depth chart after Mooy and Jenz arrivals; what positions are next appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midfielder rejects Celtic move despite having bid accepted - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEDIMt9pCPMqHEBDL19rCmMgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4KKJCzCv9JoDMICkoAY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2022/07/19/midfielder-rejects-celtic-bid-accepted/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T18:05:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Midfielder rejects Celtic move despite having bid accepted  The Celtic Bhoys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Davies seals Rangers transfer as one-time Celtic target leaves Liverpool to replace Calvin Bassey - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiELVMmkeitylfRXyLxGF3GdIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPPfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/ben-davies-seals-rangers-transfer-24516779"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T18:01:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Davies seals Rangers transfer as one-time Celtic target leaves Liverpool to replace Calvin Bassey  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Timeline for Moritz Jenz and Aaron Mooy Celtic match involvement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/timeline-for-moritz-jenz-and-aaron-mooy-celtic-match-involvement/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/timeline-for-moritz-jenz-and-aaron-mooy-celtic-match-involvement/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neither Moritz Jenz nor Aaron Mooy will be involved during tomorrow night’s Celtic match away to Legia Warsaw after signing for the club today. Both players met their new teammates, manager and coaching staff at Lennoxtown earlier today as the squad prepared to fly out to Poland. However, the Legia fixture will come too early, ...
The post Timeline for Moritz Jenz and Aaron Mooy Celtic match involvement appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moritz Jenz Celtic destiny fulfilled as new signing reveals pal Matt O'Riley's transfer plea - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>1493502248</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/moritz-jenz-celtic-destiny-fulfilled-27524045"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T17:37:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moritz Jenz Celtic destiny fulfilled as new signing reveals pal Matt O'Riley's transfer plea  Daily Record
Celtic target completes medical and move now close  The Celtic Bhoys
Moritz Jenz close to Celtic loan transfer as defender is set to join Aaron Mooy  Football Scotland
Jenz Deal Gets Green light; Celtic Closing in on Double Signing  CeltsAreHere
Celtic: Aaron Mooy and Moritz Jenz join Scottish Premiership champions  Sky Sports
View Full coverage on Google News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy Celtic Deal Verdict]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/aaron-mooy-celtic-deal-verdict/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/aaron-mooy-celtic-deal-verdict/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy’s transfer to Celtic has been met with a lot of mixed feelings from supporters but I truly believe the 31-year old can be a success at the club.  During this window, Nir Bitton and Ismalia Soro departed meaning that Celtic had to find a new midfielder. During Australia’s World Cup Qualifier with Peru […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star Matt O'Riley helped to push through Moritz Jenz's Parkhead switch,  the defender reveals]]></title>
        <id>9b5a84ac8b49abe5a7fb8d22e52cc8fd</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20290505.celtic-star-matt-oriley-helped-push-moritz-jenzs-parkhead-switch-defender-reveals/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T17:27:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC star Matt O'Riley will help new boy Moritz Jenz settle into life at Parkhead, the German has revealed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lurgan No. 1 CSC World Golf Day for Kano]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/lurgan-no-1-csc-world-golf-day-for-kano/</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/lurgan-no-1-csc-world-golf-day-for-kano/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T17:26:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Kano World Golf day is being backed by Lurgan No. 1 CSC. The date is Friday September 02 at Maze Golf Club. A 4 Ball costs £200 includes a meal and a variety of prizes to be won on the day . https://celticfanzine.com/product-category/monthly-print-subscription/ Any Business or CSC who like to sponsor a hole for […]
The post Lurgan No. 1 CSC World Golf Day for Kano appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mortiz Jenz Confirms Year Long Celtic Rumour]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/mortiz-jenz-confirms-year-long-celtic-rumour/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/mortiz-jenz-confirms-year-long-celtic-rumour/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T17:20:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MORITZ JENZ has revealed he was desperate to sign for Celtic last season but the deal didn’t happen for whatever reason The German defender was announced as a Celtic player on Tuesday afternoon and in his first interview with the club, the player confirmed last season’s rumour that Celtic tried to sign him before Lorient […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tone Deaf Downing Street Celtic Plan Comes to Light]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/tone-deaf-downing-street-celtic-plan-comes-to-light/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/tone-deaf-downing-street-celtic-plan-comes-to-light/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T17:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes you don’t believe what you are reading with it being revealed through published cabinet papers that former Number 10 adviser Alistair Campbell proposed that Celtic took on Rangers to publicise the referendum on the Good Friday Agreement [Glasgow Times].  The story gets better as one of the central ideas to the game was that […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy’s First Celtic Interview]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/aaron-mooys-first-celtic-interview/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/aaron-mooys-first-celtic-interview/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T17:03:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic TV have put out a short interview with Celtic’s newest Australian bhoy Aaron Mooy after the midfielder penned a two-year deal. Aaron became Ange’s fifth summer signing and comes with a wealth of experience. Mooy also knows the Celtic boss very well from their time in the Socceroos camp – that can only be […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic complete double signing of Aaron Mooy, Moritz Jenz]]></title>
        <id>https://www.sportsmole.co.uk/football/celtic/transfer-talk/news/celtic-complete-double-signing-of-aaron-mooy-moritz-jenz_490475.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.sportsmole.co.uk/football/celtic/transfer-talk/news/celtic-complete-double-signing-of-aaron-mooy-moritz-jenz_490475.html"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T17:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic announce that they have completed the double signing of midfielder Aaron Mooy and centre-back Mortiz Jenz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic new boy Aaron Mooy on delight of reuniting with Ange Postecoglou]]></title>
        <id>870fb57719b0ae04a06c7b20c68dd08e</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20290402.celtic-new-boy-aaron-mooy-delight-reuniting-ange-postecoglou/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T16:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AARON MOOY admits the chance to work with Ange Postecoglou again was a major factor in signing for Celtic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Aaron Mooy’s first interview as a Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/video-aaron-mooys-first-interview-as-a-celtic-player/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-aaron-mooys-first-interview-as-a-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T16:34:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy has given his first interview as a Celtic player after the 31-year-old was unveiled today. Arriving on a free transfer from Shanghai Port, Mooy and Moritz Jens became the fifth and sixth arrivals of the summer. Mooy has had spells at St Mirren, Melbourne City, Huddersfield and Brighton and now arrives at Celtic Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Deal Looks Dead After Double Signing]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-deal-looks-dead-after-double-signing/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-deal-looks-dead-after-double-signing/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T16:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have cooled any interest in Argentine midfielder Fausto Vera after securing Aaron Mooy on Tuesday afternoon. Mark Hendry of Football Scotland has had a prolific summer when it comes to Celtic exclusives and he’s now reporting a deal for the Vera looks to be off the table for now. Mooy isn’t the traditional defensive […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Lambert: Postecoglou factor can help Aaron Mooy thrive at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/paul-lambert-postecoglou-factor-can-help-aaron-mooy-thrive-at-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/paul-lambert-postecoglou-factor-can-help-aaron-mooy-thrive-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T16:23:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy can thrive in Glasgow’s goldfish bowl just like the way the Hoops’ Japanese contingent have under Ange Postecoglou. That is the view of former Celtic midfielder Paul Lambert after the announcement of both Australian Mooy and German Moritz Jenz were confirmed today. Lambert himself is no stranger to the cut and thrust of Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[&#039;I’ve been told...&#039; - Journalist drops significant Celtic update on links to &#039;dangerous&#039; striker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-hoops-unlikely-sign-jordan-larsson-this-summer-transfer-ange-spl-henrik/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-hoops-unlikely-sign-jordan-larsson-this-summer-transfer-ange-spl-henrik/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T16:14:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are now ‘unlikely’ to sign striker Jordan Larsson in the summer transfer window, with reliable journalist Anthony Joseph downplaying the rumour. The Lowdown: Larsson linked with move The 24-year-old is the son of Hoops legend Henrik Larsson and is currently without a club after his deal at Spartak Moscow expired. Larsson, dubbed a ‘dangerous‘ […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou reacts to his double signing spree]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/ange-postecoglou-reacts-to-his-double-signing-spree/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/ange-postecoglou-reacts-to-his-double-signing-spree/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T16:13:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has spoken of his delight at the signings of both Aaron Mooy and Moritz Jenz respectively. The two men put pen-to-paper on deals that will keep them in Glasgow for at least a year, after Mooy signed a one-year contract and Jenz starts a season-long loan deal with the option to make it Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘GREAT ADDITIONS,’ ADMITS ANGE AFTER DOUBLE SWOOP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/great-additions-admits-ange-after-double-swoop/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/great-additions-admits-ange-after-double-swoop/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T16:12:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have completed the double swoop for Aaron Mooy and Moritz Jenz after moving swiftly for the players, as CQN reported earlier today. The Australia midfielder, 31, has agreed a two-year deal while the versatile German defender will join on a season-long loan from French outfit Lorient. Mooy arrives as a free agent after his [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Watch New Bhoy Aaron Mooy Score Against Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/video-watch-new-bhoy-aaron-mooy-score-against-rangers/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/video-watch-new-bhoy-aaron-mooy-score-against-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T15:27:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For those of us who can still remember, Aaron mooy has played in Scottish football before with Paisley side St Mirren. A young Aaron with a head full of hair played for the SPFL side between 2010 and 2012. During his time with the club, he managed to get a goal against Rangers, something the […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moritz Jenz Has Familiar Face in Celtic Dressing Room]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/moritz-jenz-has-familiar-face-in-celtic-dressing-room/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/moritz-jenz-has-familiar-face-in-celtic-dressing-room/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T15:19:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s new loan defender Moritz Jenz has joined up with the squad ahead of the new season. While it can be daunting for any new player walking into a squad, there’s a familiar face among the Celtic setup for the German who will most likely help him settle that little bit quicker. Hoops midfielder Matt […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic seal Mooy and Jenz transfers, but are more needed?]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-seal-mooy-and-jenz-transfers-but-are-more-needed/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-seal-mooy-and-jenz-transfers-but-are-more-needed/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T14:48:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Lubo98 has written today, Celtic have this afternoon completed a double deal for free agent Aaron Mooy and FC Lorient’s ball playing centre-back Moritz Jenz. The news comes after Mooy completed a medical yesterday and Michael Nicholson thrashed out the loan deal with an option-to-buy included for the German defender Jenz. Ange Postecoglou had Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou Reacts to Celtic Tuesday Double Signing]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/ange-postecoglou-reacts-to-celtic-tuesday-double-signing/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/ange-postecoglou-reacts-to-celtic-tuesday-double-signing/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T14:14:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have made it a double signing Tuesday by announcing deals for both Aaron Mooy and Moritz Jenz. The rumour mill has been abuzz since Saturday evening when Ange Postecoglou claimed Celtic were closing in on two new players. The Mooy story broke first, but late on Monday evening Moritz Jenz came to the forefront. […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Do The Double As They Announce Two Signings For Project Ange.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/celtic-do-the-double-as-they-announce-two-signings-for-project-ange/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/celtic-do-the-double-as-they-announce-two-signings-for-project-ange/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T14:12:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Always on my days off. Always. Having decided, late last week, that I needed some time off I cleared the calendar of three days. I should have known that Ange would announce that we were to sign two players before the week ended. I should have known they’d do it today. Actually, I’m buzzing here […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou speaks on Celtic moves for Aaron Mooy and Moritz Jenz]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/ange-postecoglou-speaks-on-celtic-moves-for-aaron-mooy-and-moritz-jenz/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/ange-postecoglou-speaks-on-celtic-moves-for-aaron-mooy-and-moritz-jenz/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T14:11:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou has reacted to the double Celtic signing of Aaron Mooy and Moritz Jenz this afternoon, after the club officially announced deals for both. The Bhoys have snapped free agent Mooy up on a two-year deal, while Jenz makes the switch from Ligue 1 side Lorient on a season-long loan with the option to ...
The post Ange Postecoglou speaks on Celtic moves for Aaron Mooy and Moritz Jenz appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic complete double signing as Ange Postecoglou hails arrival of Aaron Mooy and Moritz Jenz]]></title>
        <id>3774145</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-complete-double-signing-as-ange-postecoglou-hails-arrival-of-aaron-mooy-and-moritz-jenz-3774145"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T13:58:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have strengthened their squad ahead of the new season with a double signing after confirming the arrivals of midfielder Aaron Mooy and defender Moritz Jenz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Elder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Double delight as Celtic confirm signings of Mooy and Jenz]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/double-delight-as-celtic-confirm-signings-of-mooy-and-jenz/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/double-delight-as-celtic-confirm-signings-of-mooy-and-jenz/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T13:57:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have confirmed their fifth and sixth signings of the summer by confirming deals for Aaron Mooy and Moritz Jenz. 🆕✍️ #WillkommenJenz We are delighted to announce the signing of German defender Moritz Jenz 🇩🇪 Welcome to #CelticFC, Moritz! 🍀 pic.twitter.com/egyZqWljBL — Celtic Football Club (@CelticFC) July 19, 2022 Jenz arrives on a loan with Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confirmed: Moritz Jenz Signs Celtic Loan Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/confirmed-moritz-jenz-signs-celtic-loan-deal/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/confirmed-moritz-jenz-signs-celtic-loan-deal/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T13:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have confirmed the signing of Moritz Jenz just minutes after confirming the signing of Aaron Mooy. Ange Postecoglou told Celtic fans the Hoops were close to a double signing on Saturday and by Tuesday, both players are in the door. Moritz has been a long term target for the club, with Celtic making an […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic announce double signing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-announce-double-signing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-announce-double-signing/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T13:56:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have officially announced that Aaron Mooy and Moritz Jenz have joined the club. Both players have been heavily linked with a transfer over the last few days. Midfielder Mooy arrives as a free agent following his most recent spell in China, having played in the English Premier League previously with Huddersfield Town and Brighton. ...
The post Celtic announce double signing appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic confirm Moritz Jenz transfer as German defender looks to revive career in Scotland]]></title>
        <id>2e844fc5cdd0cae592bbc2e533031b85</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20289692.celtic-confirm-moritz-jenz-transfer-german-defender-looks-revive-career-scotland/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T13:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have confirmed their second capture of the day after announcing the signature of Moritz Jenz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic confirm Aaron Mooy signing as midfielder links up with Ange Postecoglou]]></title>
        <id>ec7e833f92ae295fd0315be448e59b3c</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20289626.celtic-confirm-aaron-mooy-signing-midfielder-links-ange-postecoglou/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T13:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have confirmed the signing of free agent Aaron Mooy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Done Deal: Aaron Mooy Signs Celtic Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/done-deal-aaron-mooy-signs-celtic-deal/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/done-deal-aaron-mooy-signs-celtic-deal/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T13:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AARON MOOY has become Celtic’s FIFTH summer signing after signing a deal with the Scottish Champions. [CELTICFC] The Australian has been without a club since he ripped up his contract with Shanghai port in China earlier this year. Celtic haven’t divulged contract length as of yet. Ange has decided to bring his former Socceroos star […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fan’s meltdown over £20m+ Rangers star Calvin Bassey goes viral - Rangers News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEOx2gAt-CKeH_oFP-5SJUHsqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow78WJCzD3zJsDML-u0gc</id>
        <link href="https://www.rangersnews.uk/transfer-news/celtic-fans-on-air-meltdown-over-ajax-bound-rangers-star-calvin-bassey-goes-viral/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T13:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fan’s meltdown over £20m+ Rangers star Calvin Bassey goes viral  Rangers News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rangers gum bumpers are suffering Celtic amnesia over their transfer fib to themselves - Hotline - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEHJIdz3vsnhEwUOj1FrGfkMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/rangers-gum-bumpers-suffering-celtic-27520268"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T12:58:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rangers gum bumpers are suffering Celtic amnesia over their transfer fib to themselves - Hotline  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moritz Jenz – His suitability for Angeball and his unlikely interest]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/moritz-jenz-his-suitability-for-angeball-and-his-unlikely-interest/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/moritz-jenz-his-suitability-for-angeball-and-his-unlikely-interest/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T12:57:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic close in on both Aaron Mooy and Moritz Jenz respectively, a report in the Daily Record has given an insight into not only what the big defender Jenz is like, but a deeper delve into his personality and the processes he goes through which help keep him on course and grounded in a Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fading Celtic target Fausto Vera “50/50” on Argentinos Juniors departure amidst Genk’s improved bid]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/fading-celtic-target-fausto-vera-50-50-on-argentinos-juniors-departure-amidst-genks-improved-bid/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/fading-celtic-target-fausto-vera-50-50-on-argentinos-juniors-departure-amidst-genks-improved-bid/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T12:52:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rumoured Celtic target Fausto Vera has revealed that a move a away from his current club Aregntinos Juniors is “50/50”, depending on how events pan out. The defensive midfielder was supposedly seen as an alternative to the highly sought after Vinicius Souza, once he decided to put the chase to bed and join Spanish side Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mooy completes medical ahead of Celtic announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/mooy-completes-medical-ahead-of-celtic-announcement/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/mooy-completes-medical-ahead-of-celtic-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T12:44:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy has completed his medical ahead of his signing for Celtic as a free agent. According to Scottish Sun, the player will sign on the dotted line for one-year with the option for a further year, which makes sense considering he is in his thirties now. He is seen as filling the defensive midfield Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moritz Jenz update – player’s agent expected in Glasgow]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/moritz-jenz-update-players-agent-expected-in-glasgow/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/moritz-jenz-update-players-agent-expected-in-glasgow/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T12:43:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moritz Jenz’s agent is expected to be in Glasgow today to continue discussions with Celtic over a move for the German defender. The Lorient defender has emerged as a target for the Scottish Champions in recent days and now, it appears that he will move closer to becoming Ange Postecoglou’s latest signing. According to Sky Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Celtic hammer Linfield in Champions League Qualifiers]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/video-celtic-hammer-linfield-in-champions-league-qualifiers/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-celtic-hammer-linfield-in-champions-league-qualifiers/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T12:20:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On This Day in 2017, Brendan Rodgers’ Celtic faced Linfield at Celtic Park. It was a charged atmosphere given the relationship of the visitors from Belfast with Rangers and their roots. As a result, the songbook was belted out in full force at a near-capacity Paradise as Rodgers’ side looked to book their place in the Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion – Billy Gilmour loan deal to Celtic makes perfect sense]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/opinion-billy-gilmour-loan-deal-to-celtic-makes-perfect-sense/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/opinion-billy-gilmour-loan-deal-to-celtic-makes-perfect-sense/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T11:43:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the news emerging from Chelsea that Billy Gilmour will be part of Chelsea’s development group rather than Thomas Tuchel’s first-team squad during the West London’s pre-season tour of the USA, it would appear Gilmour will be looking at yet another loan swap rather than first team EPL exposure in the season ahead. Chelsea have Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion – Billy Gilmour loan deal to Celtic makes perfect sense - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEKgLauQbZYbZdaZr06HkyVcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/opinion-billy-gilmour-loan-deal-to-celtic-makes-perfect-sense/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T11:43:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion – Billy Gilmour loan deal to Celtic makes perfect sense  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[&#039;In talks...&#039; - Anthony Joseph says Celtic are closing in on fresh transfer after Aaron Mooy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-hoops-working-on-loan-move-for-moritz-jenz-transfer-spl-ange/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-hoops-working-on-loan-move-for-moritz-jenz-transfer-spl-ange/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T11:40:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are working on sealing an imminent loan move for Lorient centre-back Moritz Jenz, reliable journalist Anthony Joseph has confirmed. The Lowdown: Ange looking for depth The Hoops are having a productive time of things this summer, nailing down Cameron Carter-Vickers and Jota to permanent moves, while they are also reportedly closing in on the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moritz Jenz – Plenty to work on but much to work with]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/moritz-jenz-plenty-to-work-on-but-much-to-work-with/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/moritz-jenz-plenty-to-work-on-but-much-to-work-with/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T11:26:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A year after initial links to Lorient defender Moritz Jenz first emerged it appears the 6ft 2 central defender may be about to head to Celtic on a loan deal with an option to buy attached as Lubo 98 informed us on The Celtic Star earlier today. This one seems something of strange move when Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers predicted XI against West Ham United as Malik Tillman set for debut and new boys prepare for Ibrox bow - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiELCziUasaqg14e9Q__VTFSAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/rangers-predicted-xi-against-west-27518975"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T11:15:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers predicted XI against West Ham United as Malik Tillman set for debut and new boys prepare for Ibrox bow  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Campbell’s ‘Rangers v Celtic, An idea’ 1998 letter, revealed]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/alistair-campbells-rangers-v-celtic-an-idea-1998-letter-revealed/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/alistair-campbells-rangers-v-celtic-an-idea-1998-letter-revealed/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T11:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alistair Campbell, one time Tony Blair’s spokesman, press secretary and director of communications and strategy has long been open to alcohol being something of a crutch during his time spent in a stressful political working environment. Given his admittance to this, you can only assume the ‘Rangers v Celtic, An Idea’ letter sent to then Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Burnley complete transfer of former Celtic midfielder as Clarets bolster Academy ranks - Lancs Live]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEETPWdVt1GywGgRRQLsROq8qMwgEKioIACIQH8iyXwR83wMQ5m6KELTlVCoUCAoiEB_Isl8EfN8DEOZuihC05VQwuuHgBg</id>
        <link href="https://www.lancs.live/sport/football/transfer-news/burnley-complete-transfer-former-celtic-24528535"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T10:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Burnley complete transfer of former Celtic midfielder as Clarets bolster Academy ranks  Lancs Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic v Rangers Belfast friendly proposal to mark Good Friday Agreement unearthed in unseen government papers]]></title>
        <id>3773599</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-v-rangers-belfast-friendly-proposal-to-mark-good-friday-agreement-unearthed-in-unseen-government-papers-3773599"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T10:26:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently released government papers have revealed that a proposal was made for Celtic and Rangers to meet in a friendly in Belfast to promote the Good Friday Agreement referendum in 1998.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Elder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Soul Tees Back In Stock]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-soul-tees-back-in-stock/</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-soul-tees-back-in-stock/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T09:37:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Soul Tees Back In Stock . All Celtic Soul Tees & Merchandise ordered over the weekend now dispatched. Thanks very much for the continued support. Lisbon 67, One Star, Rude Bhoys, Celtic Soul & More than 90 Minutes all back in stock to have you looking sharp during the hot weather. https://celticfanzine.com/product-category/t-shirts/ ﻿ https://celticfanzine.com/product-category/monthly-print-subscription/
The post Celtic Soul Tees Back In Stock appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scottish Football VAR Latest]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/scottish-football-var-latest/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/scottish-football-var-latest/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T09:10:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reports have suggested that VAR technology could be introduced into Scottish football quicker than expected [Daily Record].  Everything about season 2022/23 is all a bit different with the Champions kicking their league season off at 4.30pm on a Sunday afternoon. As well as that, clubs will also experience a first with the World Cup being […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Labour advisor Alastair Campbell wanted Celtic and Rangers to play match 'wearing each other's jerseys' - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiECFmSAKLkK9lVezk214DGwgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIbTtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/news/politics/labour-adviser-alistair-campbell-wanted-27516945"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T09:02:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Labour advisor Alastair Campbell wanted Celtic and Rangers to play match 'wearing each other's jerseys'  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic target completes medical and move now close - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>1493502248</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2022/07/19/celtic-target-completes-medical-close/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T09:02:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic target completes medical and move now close  The Celtic Bhoys
The two potential Celtic XIs as Moritz Jenz and Aaron Mooy to make Ange's transfer wish a reality  Daily Record
Moritz Jenz close to Celtic loan transfer as defender is set to join Aaron Mooy  Football Scotland
Jenz Deal Gets Green light; Celtic Closing in on Double Signing  CeltsAreHere
Transfer breakthrough as Aaron Mooy set to sign for Celtic  The Celtic Star
View Full coverage on Google News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE, KYOGO AND CO, CHAMPIONS LEAGUE – AND ARTUR BORUC: FORREST OPENS UP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ange-kyogo-and-co-champions-league-and-artur-boruc-forrest-opens-up/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ange-kyogo-and-co-champions-league-and-artur-boruc-forrest-opens-up/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T09:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JAMES FORREST, Celtic’s longest-serving player, is raring to go in the new season. The 31-year-old Scotland international wide Bhoy is now working his way through his thirteenth pre-season as a Hoops performer. Ange Postecoglou’s men are now due to face Legia Warsaw in Poland tomorrow night in the Testimonial Match for the club’s colourful former [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Throwback To Jungle Days, Five Years Since Linfield Visited Paradise]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/a-throwback-to-jungle-days-five-years-since-linfield-visited-paradise/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/a-throwback-to-jungle-days-five-years-since-linfield-visited-paradise/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like them or loathe them, think they’re appropriate at Celtic Park or think the opposite, Irish Nationalist and Republican songs have been sung by Celtic supporters since the Brake Club days immediately after Celtic’s inception. Over the years the politics and songbook of the faithful have adapted, along with the evolution of current affairs themselves. Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Players Agent Flies in for Celtic Talks]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/players-agent-flies-in-for-celtic-talks/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/players-agent-flies-in-for-celtic-talks/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T08:54:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic look set to sign two new players this week! Aaron Mooy has undergone his Celtic medical with a deal for the Australian well down the line. The free agent is set to reunite with Ange Postecoglou and pull on the famous hoops. While we await Celtic’s announcement on Aaron, the bhoys are deep in […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jenz parallels with Jota]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/jenz-parallels-with-jota/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/jenz-parallels-with-jota/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T08:44:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At 23, German central defender Moritz Jenz emerged from the Fulham youth setup two years ago.  A season in Switzerland with Lausanne, then one in France with Lorient, 45 games in total, is apparently enough to convince Celtic to move for the player. Interestingly, before leaving London, he was in the same Fulham youth team [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic suffer transfer rebuff as midfielder opts to stay with Premiership rival]]></title>
        <id>3773247</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-suffer-transfer-rebuff-as-midfielder-opts-to-stay-with-premiership-rival-3773247"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T08:41:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[St Mirren youngster Dylan Reid has rebuffed overtures from Celtic to stay at the Paisley club.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Elder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The two potential Celtic XIs as Moritz Jenz and Aaron Mooy to make Ange's transfer wish a reality - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>1493502248</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-transfer-news/two-potential-celtic-xis-moritz-27512349"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T08:22:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The two potential Celtic XIs as Moritz Jenz and Aaron Mooy to make Ange's transfer wish a reality  Daily Record
Celtic target completes medical and move now close  The Celtic Bhoys
Moritz Jenz close to Celtic loan transfer as defender is set to join Aaron Mooy  Football Scotland
Jenz Deal Gets Green light; Celtic Closing in on Double Signing  CeltsAreHere
Transfer breakthrough as Aaron Mooy set to sign for Celtic  The Celtic Star
View Full coverage on Google News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Celtic and Rangers last kicked off at home at the same time as Glasgow set for bumper day of football - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEFvNiCEqg00pEG5vD9UpoYcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/celtic-rangers-last-kicked-home-27516034"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T08:02:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Celtic and Rangers last kicked off at home at the same time as Glasgow set for bumper day of football  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic hoping to secure loan-to-buy deal for German defender]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-hoping-to-secure-loan-to-buy-deal-for-german-defender/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtic-hoping-to-secure-loan-to-buy-deal-for-german-defender/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are working on a deal to bring Moritz Jenz to the club on a loan deal with an option to buy. L’Equipe reported initially that a deal was close but The Sun claim it will be a temporary switch initially. Ange Postecoglou is looking to add depth and quality to his defence and Jenz Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No10 adviser proposed Celtic vs Rangers Belfast clash 'with teams wearing each other's jerseys']]></title>
        <id>8ac62258152578429aed8a213b81aab6</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20288325.no10-adviser-proposed-celtic-vs-rangers-belfast-clash-with-teams-wearing-others-jerseys/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T07:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RECENTLY published British cabinet papers have revealed that No10 adviser Alastair Campbell proposed a special Celtic vs Rangers Belfast showdown to publicise the referendum on the Good Friday Agreement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou’s Transfer Success; Celtic Star Praises Boss]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/ange-postecoglous-transfer-success-celtic-star-praises-boss/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/ange-postecoglous-transfer-success-celtic-star-praises-boss/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T07:50:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic winger James Forrest has insisted that there is full belief behind Ange Postecoglou’s methods and transfer dealings.  The Australian arrived in Glasgow just over a year ago on his own and has overseen a huge job that was dubbed as a ‘rebuild’. Every player that the Australian brought to the club during the last […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NO-GO REID]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/no-go-reid/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/no-go-reid/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T07:41:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ST MIRREN teenage ace Dylan Reid has decided against a move to Celtic. The Scotland Under-17 midfielder was on Ange Postecoglou’s wanted list to join the Hoops B squad and the champions made a £125,000 bid over a week ago, as CQN reported. Reid has thought over the proposition, but will remain with the Paisley [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Medical Complete; Deal Imminent]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-medical-complete-deal-imminent/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-medical-complete-deal-imminent/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T07:35:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last 48 hours, Celtic have been on course to sign Aaron Mooy on a free transfer. It’s taken a massive step forward with the news Aaron has now come through his Celtic medical. [SunSport] The Australian is set to sign on with his former international manager at Celtic Park and get to work. […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Club to continue providing media access to Celtic Fan Media for new season]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/club-to-continue-providing-media-access-to-celtic-fan-media-for-new-season/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/club-to-continue-providing-media-access-to-celtic-fan-media-for-new-season/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T06:52:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have confirmed that the club’s working relationship with the Celtic fan media will continue this season, after declaring themselves very happy with the way in which the groundbreaking policy that started last summer has turned out. There were some concern inside the club about the plan to open up the media events to Celtic Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: ‘THE DAY I GOT TO PLAY WITH THE LIONS’: EVAN WILLIAMS TELLS ALL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-the-day-i-got-to-play-with-the-lions-evan-williams-tells-all/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-the-day-i-got-to-play-with-the-lions-evan-williams-tells-all/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T06:42:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EVAN WILLIAMS made history on May 1 1971 when he played in the final appearance of the Lisbon Lions. Jock Stein decided to look to the future as the European Cup-winning team of four years earlier was now breaking up. Ronnie Simpson, at the age of 41, would say farewell to the Celtic support in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: ‘THE DAY I GOT TO PLAY WITH THE LIONS’: EVAN WILLIAMS TELLS ALL (Part Five)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-the-day-i-got-to-play-with-the-lions-evan-williams-tells-all-part-five/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-the-day-i-got-to-play-with-the-lions-evan-williams-tells-all-part-five/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T06:42:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EVAN WILLIAMS made history on May 1 1971 when he played in the final appearance of the Lisbon Lions. Jock Stein decided to look to the future as the European Cup-winning team of four years earlier was now breaking up. Ronnie Simpson, at the age of 41, would say farewell to the Celtic support in [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GREEN LIGHT FOR JENZ – A YEAR LATE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/green-light-for-jenz-a-year-late/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/green-light-for-jenz-a-year-late/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T05:54:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MORITZ JENZ is heading for Celtic – a YEAR after CQN reported Ange Postecoglou’s initial interest in the versatile defender. The German, who can operate at right-back or in central defence, has been given the green light to finally join up with the Greek-Australian gaffer at Parkhead, according to a report in French sports journal [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Ange We Trust – His signings have all made an impact says James Forrest]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/in-ange-we-trust-his-signings-have-all-made-an-impact-says-james-forrest/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/in-ange-we-trust-his-signings-have-all-made-an-impact-says-james-forrest/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T05:49:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Forrest has been at Celtic for longer than any other player at the club – he even managed to share some time as a first team squad member with Polish goalkeeper Artur Boruc who left Celtic shortly afterwards, but the two players have that in common and will no doubt share a moment together Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luis Lopes to be unleashed by Aberdeen as Jim Goodwin gives Kelle Roos number one nod - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEAl8h-7ZqY80mph4krb7UtMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/luis-lopes-unleashed-aberdeen-jim-27512346"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Luis Lopes to be unleashed by Aberdeen as Jim Goodwin gives Kelle Roos number one nod  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: NEW £17m STAND, NEW ERA, NEW HOPE: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Eight)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-new-17m-stand-new-era-new-hope-the-tommy-burns-story-part-eight/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-new-17m-stand-new-era-new-hope-the-tommy-burns-story-part-eight/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T04:59:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS had won the Scottish Cup in his first season as Celtic manager after his appointment on July 12 1994. The league title, though, was the legendary Celt’s priority target as his second campaign prepared to kick off. In another CQN EXCLUSIVE series, we chart Tommy Burns’ career as the Hoops gaffer during turbulent [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Tuesday July 19: Business As Usual]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=17839</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=17839"/>
        <updated>2022-07-19T04:44:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It promises to be even hotter today than it was yesterday.   Don’t know what it’s like around your way, but round here, it was…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SPFL chiefs 'fast track VAR introduction to Scottish Premiership for before World Cup']]></title>
        <id>afe7817e9d47fb80ef4034a1dffa28c0</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20287991.spfl-chiefs-fast-track-var-introduction-scottish-premiership-world-cup/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T21:43:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SPFL chiefs are reportedly ready to fast track implementation of VAR in the Scottish Premiership.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rocco Vata given 'looks ready' Celtic assessment as veteran coos over starlet's quality]]></title>
        <id>01bcfc736f73398be1c40b275d53e418</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20287974.rocco-vata-given-looks-ready-celtic-assessment-veteran-coos-starlets-quality/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T21:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic starlet Rocco Vata has impressed Celtic's senior players with a top-class pre-season, according to impressed veteran winger James Forrest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artur Boruc 'right up there' with Celtic's greatest ever goalkeepers, says James Forrest]]></title>
        <id>15b43ac079d45dfacc5b4bde0779fabe</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20287607.artur-boruc-right-there-celtics-greatest-ever-goalkeepers-says-james-forrest/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ARTUR BORUC is a larger-than-life character.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou rightly deserves trust in handling transfers, insists James Forrest]]></title>
        <id>500bfc83ee98186738ca1a48e335a85b</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20287636.celtic-boss-ange-postecoglou-rightly-deserves-trust-handling-transfers-insists-james-forrest/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IN Ange we trust.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dylan Reid rejects Celtic B team offer to remain at St Mirren]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/dylan-reid-rejects-celtic-b-team-offer-to-remain-at-st-mirren/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/dylan-reid-rejects-celtic-b-team-offer-to-remain-at-st-mirren/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T20:29:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[St Mirren starlet has decided to remain at the Paisley club despite them accepting a @125k bid from Celtic. The news was confirmed by St Mirren this evening via a statement on their official website: ‘St Mirren Football Club can confirm that last week it allowed Dylan Reid permission to speak to a fellow cinch Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic 'agree deal' with French club to sign German centre-back]]></title>
        <id>3773061</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-agree-deal-with-french-club-to-sign-german-centre-back-3773061"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T20:28:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have agreed a deal to sign defender Moritz Jenz from Lorient, according to reports in France.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Elder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reid to Celtic Deal Off]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/reid-to-celtic-deal-off/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/reid-to-celtic-deal-off/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T20:16:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ST MIRREN youngster Dylan Reid will NOT be joining Celtic this summer after the club was given permission to talk to the player. Celtic wanted to bring Dylan into the B squad and had an offer accepted for him. [SunSport] Reid has decided to stay out and bide his time in Paisley. St Mirren confirmed […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Champions League plans are being worked on in Celtic training already]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/champions-league-plans-are-being-worked-on-in-celtic-training-already/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/champions-league-plans-are-being-worked-on-in-celtic-training-already/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T20:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic won’t play their first UEFA Champions League group fixture for another two months, but Ange Postecoglou has already been planning ahead this summer. The draw for the competition takes place on August 25th, with matchday one coming on the 6th or 7th of September. Until the names are pulled out of UEFA’s pots, Postecoglou ...
The post Champions League plans are being worked on in Celtic training already appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dylan Reid rejects Celtic transfer as St Mirren midfielder decides to stay in Paisley - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEBGFPGbB0aQEyRe5WUSaJZMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPTfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/dylan-reid-rejects-celtic-transfer-24525132"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T20:06:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dylan Reid rejects Celtic transfer as St Mirren midfielder decides to stay in Paisley  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dylan Reid turns down Celtic transfer option as St Mirren kid chooses to remain in Paisley after talks - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEJU2r73EVzPlos9Z4NM1ViUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/dylan-reid-turns-down-celtic-27514455"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T20:06:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dylan Reid turns down Celtic transfer option as St Mirren kid chooses to remain in Paisley after talks  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dylan Reid to stay at St Mirren as youngster turns down Celtic move]]></title>
        <id>293140983cb0ca7006bb68473b7bd867</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20287946.dylan-reid-stay-st-mirren-youngster-turns-celtic-move/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:59:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DYLAN REID will remain at St Mirren despite serious transfer interest from Celtic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Goodwin | Stirling Albion Preview - afc.co.uk]]></title>
        <id>CBMiQGh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmFmYy5jby51ay92aWRlby9qaW0tZ29vZHdpbi1zdGlybGluZy1hbGJpb24tcHJldmlldy_SAQA</id>
        <link href="https://www.afc.co.uk/video/jim-goodwin-stirling-albion-preview/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Goodwin | Stirling Albion Preview  afc.co.uk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Of The Day: The Moment We’ve Been Waiting For]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/photo-of-the-day-the-moment-weve-been-waiting-for/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/photo-of-the-day-the-moment-weve-been-waiting-for/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today’s photo of the day is rooted in excitement – the moment we’ve been waiting for, You’ll Never Walk Alone being sung, scarves aloft, ahead of a Champions League group stage match. It has been four and a half long years since Celtic Park last experienced such a scene, when the Hoops lost 1-0 to Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Of The Day: The Moment We’ve Been Waiting For - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEG5RoQTYZeEEisUOvl24ej0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/photo-of-the-day-the-moment-weve-been-waiting-for/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Of The Day: The Moment We’ve Been Waiting For  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is A German Defender Playing In France Celtic’s Other Signing Target This Week?]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/is-a-german-defender-playing-in-france-celtics-other-signing-target-this-week/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/is-a-german-defender-playing-in-france-celtics-other-signing-target-this-week/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:37:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reports tonight – unconfirmed – identify Celtic’s potential second signing this week as Moritz Jenz, who is a central defender who plays, currently, in France for Lorient. He’s been there for a year, but it’s fair to say that it’s not worked out for him. Celtic was allegedly – and I say allegedly – interested […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jenz Deal Gets Green light; Celtic Closing in on Double Signing]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/jenz-deal-gets-green-light-celtic-closing-in-on-double-signing/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/jenz-deal-gets-green-light-celtic-closing-in-on-double-signing/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:36:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It now looks very likely Moritz Jenz is on his way to Celtic after reports surfaced on Monday evening. French publication L’Equipe were first off the mark with the bit of transfer news and now Mark Hendry, who has been throwing out a number of Celtic’s exclusives lately, has revealed the Hoops are closing in […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Best Of Aaron Mooy This Year, A Glimpse At What To Expect From Celtic’s New Signing]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/video-best-of-aaron-mooy-this-year-a-glimpse-at-what-to-expect-from-celtics-new-signing/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-best-of-aaron-mooy-this-year-a-glimpse-at-what-to-expect-from-celtics-new-signing/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:30:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy is set to complete a short term move to Celtic, where he was reunite with Australian compatriot Ange Postecoglou, in the coming days. The deal is all but agreed, with just the paperwork to go through. Mooy is a name that many Celtic fans will be aware of, having seen his exploits in Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moritz Jenz 'close to' Celtic transfer as long term Parkhead target set for Lorient exit - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEH14fLx3wc5GSfgJrjmdGPQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/moritz-jenz-close-to-celtic-27514180"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:23:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moritz Jenz 'close to' Celtic transfer as long term Parkhead target set for Lorient exit  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton Caught On Camera: Former Celt Meets Disney Hero]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/chris-sutton-caught-on-camera-former-celt-meets-disney-hero/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/chris-sutton-caught-on-camera-former-celt-meets-disney-hero/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:18:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic striker Chris Sutton is known for being a wind up merchant, a joker with a dry sense of humour and for being eccentric at times. He is a hero to many Norwich, Blackburn and Celtic fans, but the man has heroes of his own and he was caught on camera meeting one of Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer latest as centre-back Moritz Jenz set for move to 'revive career in Scotland']]></title>
        <id>cfe9cf7740a0729010c7058139a0e8a9</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20287917.celtic-transfer-latest-centre-back-moritz-jenz-set-move-revive-career-scotland/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:14:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC are set to sign German centre-back Moritz Jenz from FC Lorient, according to French reports.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moritz Jenz close to Celtic loan transfer as defender is set to join Aaron Mooy - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>1493502248</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/moritz-jenz-close-celtic-transfer-24524868"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:14:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moritz Jenz close to Celtic loan transfer as defender is set to join Aaron Mooy  Football Scotland
Moritz Jenz 'close to' Celtic transfer as long term Parkhead target set for Lorient exit  Daily Record
‘Agreed’ – Sky Sports man provides brilliant Celtic transfer update  The Celtic Bhoys
Jenz Deal Gets Green light; Celtic Closing in on Double Signing  CeltsAreHere
Transfer breakthrough as Aaron Mooy set to sign for Celtic  The Celtic Star
View Full coverage on Google News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moritz Jenz, second time lucky as Celtic look likely to sign German defender]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/moritz-jenz-second-time-lucky-as-celtic-look-likely-to-sign-german-defender/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/moritz-jenz-second-time-lucky-as-celtic-look-likely-to-sign-german-defender/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T19:11:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moritz Jenz could finally make the move to Celtic one year after we reported on initial interest on the defender on The Celtic Star. And reports this evening emerging from France is that the deal is done and the player will be joining Celtic shorty. “After a short season in Lorient where he never managed Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moritz Jenz En Route to Celtic; Report]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/moritz-jenz-en-route-to-celtic-report/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/moritz-jenz-en-route-to-celtic-report/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T18:49:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[French publications L’Equipe claim German defender Moritz Jenz is on his way to Celtic. The defender who currently plays for Ligue 1 side FC Lorient didn’t have the best debut season with the club and could be looking for a move elsewhere in a bid to improve and progress. Celtic are in the market for […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic in for German defender Moritz Jenz]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/report-celtic-in-for-german-defender-moritz-jenz/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/report-celtic-in-for-german-defender-moritz-jenz/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T18:34:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lorient defender Moritz Jenz is likely to sign for Celtic this summer, French outlet L’Equipe has reported this evening. Jenz is a long-term target of the Bhoys and was heavily linked with a move from Swiss side Lausanne-Sport last year before joining up with the Ligue 1 outfit. It’s understood Celtic have been tracking Jenz’s ...
The post Report: Celtic in for German defender Moritz Jenz appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Turkish Side Want Celtic Outcast – Report]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/turkish-side-want-celtic-outcast-report/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/turkish-side-want-celtic-outcast-report/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T17:56:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Turkish side Trabzonspor is being credited with a major interest in Celtic outcast Christopher Jullien ahead of the new season. Record Sport claim the Turkish side is looking into a move for the French defender who looks set to make his Parkhead exit sooner rather than later. Chris looked all set to move out to […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic&#039;s global outlook now paying off for the rest of Scottish football]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-global-outlook-now-paying-off-for-the-rest-of-scottish-football/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-global-outlook-now-paying-off-for-the-rest-of-scottish-football/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SPFL have signed a new TV deal with Japanese streaming company SPOTV Japan for the coming season, which plans to emphasise Celtic matches, it was announced over the weekend. SPOTV also hold Japanese rights to the English Premier League and Major League Baseball, with the Scottish Premiership now added to an increasingly robust portfolio. ...
The post Celtic&#039;s global outlook now paying off for the rest of Scottish football appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo: North Curve Concourse Given A Brilliant New Paint Job]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/photo-north-curve-concourse-given-a-brilliant-new-paint-job/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/photo-north-curve-concourse-given-a-brilliant-new-paint-job/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T17:39:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The North Curve standing section at Celtic Park has been given more than a lick of paint this summer as the Green Brigade have been busy decorating the area ahead of the new season. An artistic nod was given to refugees, amid the ongoing Rwanda scandal at present and the arrival of many displaced from Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[&#039;Don’t think he’s good enough...&#039; - Ex-Celtic man urges potential &#039;star&#039; to consider Hoops exit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/mikey-johnston-celtic-future-mcavennie-claim/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/mikey-johnston-celtic-future-mcavennie-claim/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T17:05:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder Mikey Johnston should leave Parkhead this summer in order to become a ‘star’ man elsewhere, according to former Hoops striker Frank McAvennie. The Lowdown: Johnston struggles for game-time Ange Postecoglou’s side enjoyed a triumphant 2021/22 season, reclaiming the Premiership title, with a number of players making telling contributions. Johnston wasn’t one of those, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keevin’s Goram Piece Reeked Of Attitudes Scotland Should Have Left Behind.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/keevins-goram-piece-reeked-of-attitudes-scotland-should-have-left-behind/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/keevins-goram-piece-reeked-of-attitudes-scotland-should-have-left-behind/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T16:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This time last year, Hugh Keevins was forced to make a grovelling apology for utterly idiotic remarks he uttered in the aftermath of Kyogo being racially abused by Ibrox fans. His comment was that things are worse on that front than they were 60 years ago when the issue was “virtually non-existent.” He was slammed […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nohan Kenneh in Hibs transfer admission as Easter Road recruit eyes up Rangers and Celtic in European dream - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEFguFf0FVnGjZCmguUZnUDYqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/nohan-kenneh-hibs-transfer-admission-27512864"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T16:14:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nohan Kenneh in Hibs transfer admission as Easter Road recruit eyes up Rangers and Celtic in European dream  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Pirie’s Piece On Ange And Mooy Is Pathetic Anti-Celtic Stirring For The Sake Of It.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/mark-piries-piece-on-ange-and-mooy-is-pathetic-anti-celtic-stirring-for-the-sake-of-it/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/mark-piries-piece-on-ange-and-mooy-is-pathetic-anti-celtic-stirring-for-the-sake-of-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T15:33:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What a dire writer is Mark Pirie of The Daily Record. His article today, dredging up a five year old story, about how Aaron Mooy and Ange fell out over the latter subbing the former whilst manager of Australia is barrel scrapped gunk. It is gossip not news. “Aaron Mooy’s Celtic transfer olive branch as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic Hero Admits He Turned Down Arsenal to Stay at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/former-celtic-hero-admits-he-turned-down-arsenal-to-stay-at-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/former-celtic-hero-admits-he-turned-down-arsenal-to-stay-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T15:32:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC are heading to Poland on Wednesday to play in Artur Boruc’s farewell match against Legia Warsaw. Once upon a time, the hoops signed Artur from the Polish club. Under Gordon Strachan, Artur was a stalwart of the Celtic team. The goalkeeper was fantastic and his eccentric personality also endeared him to supporters. As he […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linfield boss David Healy makes "front foot" vow ahead of daunting date with Celtic's conquerors - Belfast Live]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEPizJLtjSotyuOEgnFrKNMcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowpM37CjCKx_QCMJXO0wU</id>
        <link href="https://www.belfastlive.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/linfield-boss-david-healy-makes-24521974"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T15:22:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linfield boss David Healy makes "front foot" vow ahead of daunting date with Celtic's conquerors  Belfast Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James Forrest praises "under the radar" Celtic teammate who is set to shine this season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/match/james-forrest-praises-under-the-radar-celtic-teammate-who-is-set-to-shine-this-season/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/james-forrest-praises-under-the-radar-celtic-teammate-who-is-set-to-shine-this-season/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T15:10:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Forrest was on media duties at Celtic Park today after the squad’s open training session in front of supporters. Season ticket holders got the opportunity to see Ange Postecoglou and his staff put the players through their pre-season paces ahead of a trip to Legia Warsaw. Forrest was asked about competition for places and ...
The post James Forrest praises "under the radar" Celtic teammate who is set to shine this season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James Forrest praises “under the radar” Celtic teammate who is set to shine this season - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEAUxEBGWWFxNHsl_aiJsxuMqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMI7NpgY</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/james-forrest-praises-under-the-radar-celtic-teammate-who-is-set-to-shine-this-season/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T15:10:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Forrest praises “under the radar” Celtic teammate who is set to shine this season  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James Forrest hails Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou's high expectations as winger 'buzzing' for Champions League - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEOzKC7dCis383YPyOmO-NQ8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/james-forrest-hails-celtic-boss-27512084"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T15:08:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Forrest hails Celtic boss Ange Postecoglou's high expectations as winger 'buzzing' for Champions League  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fausto Vera drops Celtic transfer clue as in demand star erases his socials amid Argentinos Juniors absence - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>1496351407</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/fausto-vera-drops-celtic-transfer-27511612"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T14:33:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fausto Vera drops Celtic transfer clue as in demand star erases his socials amid Argentinos Juniors absence  Daily Record
Celtic have chance to sign Barcelona midfield maestro  The Celtic Bhoys
The next candidate for Celtic departure after pleasing Tuesday announcement  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News
Postecoglou Plays It Coy On The Rumoured Celtic Target: Why The Manager Must Make The Call  The 4th Official
View Full coverage on Google News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The second signing – Chelsea’s Levi Colwill could be our man]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/the-second-signing-chelseas-levi-colwill-could-be-our-man/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/the-second-signing-chelseas-levi-colwill-could-be-our-man/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T14:19:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With excitement building up surrounding the possible signing of Australian international Aaron Mooy, it is also worth remembering Ange Postecoglou hinted heavily that two signings may arrive at the club this week, as Paul Gillespie informed us in The Celtic Star just yesterday. With Mooy looking like the midfielder Postecoglou was looking to target, and Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free agent Aaron Mooy edges out PSG youngster Edouard Michut for now]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/free-agent-aaron-mooy-edges-out-psg-youngster-edouard-michut-for-now/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/free-agent-aaron-mooy-edges-out-psg-youngster-edouard-michut-for-now/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T14:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It may seem a strange decision to choose between the 31-year-old in the twilight of their career and the up-and-coming PSG starlet, but according to Scottish Sun Football editor Derek McGregor that was the choice Ange Postecoglou made when picking Aaron Mooy over Edouard Michut.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time For Celtic’s CEO TO Step Up And Stop Being The Invisible Man.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/time-for-celtics-ceo-to-step-up-and-stop-being-the-invisible-man/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/time-for-celtics-ceo-to-step-up-and-stop-being-the-invisible-man/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T13:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The news today that Michael Nicholson has been “voted” onto the SPFL board is interesting, but not surprising. There was no real election here. Due to a grubby, scandalous backstage deal our club and the one at Ibrox swap places on that board every couple of years, a seedy practice the rest of the game […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The clubs Aaron Mooy is turning down to sign for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/the-clubs-aaron-mooy-is-turning-down-to-sign-for-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/the-clubs-aaron-mooy-is-turning-down-to-sign-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy is widely expected to sign for Celtic this week, with a deal even potentially being announced as early as today. Multiple outlets and journalists, including Mike McGrath at The Telegraph, Derek McGregor at The Scottish Sun, Mark Hendry at Football Scotland and Fabrizio Romano, are all reporting that the move is likely following ...
The post The clubs Aaron Mooy is turning down to sign for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SPFL roles for Celtic and Hibs chief executives in league boardroom re-shuffle]]></title>
        <id>3772391</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/spfl-roles-for-celtic-and-hibs-chief-executives-in-league-boardroom-re-shuffle-3772391"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T12:47:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic and Hibs chief executives will sit on the new-look board of the SPFL following the recent re-shuffle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Oliver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calvin Bassey is kicking off Rangers megabucks transfer era that will leave Celtic reeling - Hotline - Sports Hotline - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEMBZ4FF4AQLgV-yyA2DTeM0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/calvin-bassey-kicking-rangers-megabucks-27510068"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T12:43:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Calvin Bassey is kicking off Rangers megabucks transfer era that will leave Celtic reeling - Hotline - Sports Hotline  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Nicholson Replaces Ibrox Chief on SPFL Board]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/michael-nicholson-replaces-ibrox-chief-on-spfl-board/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/michael-nicholson-replaces-ibrox-chief-on-spfl-board/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T12:39:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC’S CHIEF EXECUTIVE Michael Nicholson has been appointed to the SPFL board this afternoon, replacing Ibrox chief Stewart Robertson. The SPFL board for the new season has been appointed this afternoon and here is the full run down: Michael Nicholson, Ron Gordon, James MacDonald, Les Gray, Graeme Mathie, Alastair Donald and Paul Hetherington The board […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Nicholson replaces Rangers MD Stewart Robertson on SPFL board as Celtic chief leads shake up - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEMIAGhs3g1qUSY0E54_iDYgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/michael-nicholson-replaces-rangers-md-27510136"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T12:21:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Nicholson replaces Rangers MD Stewart Robertson on SPFL board as Celtic chief leads shake up  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Chief Executive Michael Nicholson appointed to SPFL board]]></title>
        <id>990bf6e65c312dd2bba10c06c742377d</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20286639.celtic-chief-executive-michael-nicholson-appointed-spfl-board/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T12:16:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE 42 member clubs of the Scottish Professional Football League have today elected the seven club representatives who will serve on the SPFL Board for the forthcoming season at the league’s Annual General Meeting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers chief Stewart Robertson replaced by Celtic SEO Michael Nicholson on SPFL board - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEDwaRg_cCjdG5eC_ac5DIdgqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPPfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/rangers-chief-stewart-robertson-replaced-24519781"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T12:15:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers chief Stewart Robertson replaced by Celtic SEO Michael Nicholson on SPFL board  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Injury Boost]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-injury-boost/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/celtic-injury-boost/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T11:39:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC got their open training day underway at Celtic Park on a very hot Monday afternoon in Glasgow. The club had promised season tickets holders over a yer ago the even would take place as an extra thank you for loyalty during the pandemic season. They came good on the promise on Monday as a […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic inspired Union Bhoys nickname as Rangers prepare for red-hot welcome from Saint-Gilloise ultras - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEANNI263-mh4zw0VqghR848qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPLfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/scottish-premiership/celtic-inspired-union-bhoys-nickname-24518841"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T11:17:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic inspired Union Bhoys nickname as Rangers prepare for red-hot welcome from Saint-Gilloise ultras  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Joseph drops Celtic transfer claim as Hoops eye up move for &#039;top class&#039; 53-cap stalwart]]></title>
        <id>https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-transfer-talks-aaron-mooy-over-summer-move-transfer-ange-rogic-spl/</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballtransfertavern.com/celtic-news/celtic-transfer-talks-aaron-mooy-over-summer-move-transfer-ange-rogic-spl/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T11:10:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are ‘in talks’ with free agent Aaron Mooy over a move to Parkhead in the summer transfer window, according to reliable journalist Anthony Joseph. The Lowdown: Mooy without a club The 31-year-old made a name for himself at Huddersfield Town, helping them to reach the Premier League, before moving to Shanghai Port in 2020 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saint Gilloise Celtic link explained as Union Bhoys gear up for Rangers Champions League clash - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEDgv5bdKzWq6y1X9V4PqABEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/saint-galloise-celtic-link-explained-27508995"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T11:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Saint Gilloise Celtic link explained as Union Bhoys gear up for Rangers Champions League clash  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mooy feels like a pivotal decision for season ahead]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/mooy-feels-like-a-pivotal-decision-for-season-ahead/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/mooy-feels-like-a-pivotal-decision-for-season-ahead/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T11:04:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My knowledge of Chinese football since 1979 is limited, and I don’t watch a lot of Brighton or Huddersfield, so I’ll need to bow to Ange Postecoglou’s judgement when it comes to Australian international midfielder, Aaron Mooy. Mooy was a mainstay in the Huddersfield team that won promotion to the English Premier League, stayed there, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Waiter – a new nickname for Josip Juranovic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/the-waiter-a-new-nickname-for-josip-juranovic/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/the-waiter-a-new-nickname-for-josip-juranovic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T11:02:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who Knows – perhaps the Daily Record is trying to make amends for playing fast and loose with a previous interpretation of Josip Juranovic’s words as was highlighted over the weekend by Joe McHugh at Video Celts, but whatever the reason today has seen the Record produce an article altogether more positive when it comes Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stoke City take on Celtic in double header - Stoke-on-Trent Live]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEOB64RUAoEoszNy37Po1McAqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow6L2hCTDb05YCMNzZkAM</id>
        <link href="https://www.stokesentinel.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/stoke-city-celtic-pre-season-7345766"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T10:58:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stoke City take on Celtic in double header  Stoke-on-Trent Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy for Celtic could well be two players for the price of one]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/aaron-mooy-for-celtic-could-well-be-two-players-for-the-price-of-one/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/aaron-mooy-for-celtic-could-well-be-two-players-for-the-price-of-one/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T10:35:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is there really anyone out there with any doubts regarding Celtic signing Aaron Mooy? If there is, there is little to worry about and much more to delight in. Okay let’s get the limited negatives out the way. He doesn’t have pace over distance, and probably lacks that burst of acceleration, but when you can Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Josip Juranovic Talks Family, Football and Celtic Fans]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/josip-juranovic-talks-family-football-and-celtic-fans/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/josip-juranovic-talks-family-football-and-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T09:31:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JOSIP JURANOVIC has been talking about Celtic’s potential and their inclusion in the Champions League this season. The Croatian revealed he knew all about Celtic and their European exploits before joining the club and he wants to make his own lasting memories on those crazy nights at Celtic Park. Josip told SunSport: “We all know […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy Might Not Be The Universal Choice, But For Celtic He’s The Right One.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/blogs/aaron-mooy-might-not-be-the-universal-choice-but-for-celtic-hes-the-right-one/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/blogs/aaron-mooy-might-not-be-the-universal-choice-but-for-celtic-hes-the-right-one/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T09:30:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[About a fortnight ago, I wrote about the prospect of this club moving for Jordan Larsson and Aaron Mooy. I thought Mooy was the more likely of the two and that there was probably a deal to be done. I wasn’t in the least bit surprised last night when it was his name who emerged […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Josip Juranovic admits Celtic fortune as he reveals the Callum McGregor photo that makes him giggle - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEH56LxFuy6YhP158eMeZ5qkqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/josip-juranovic-admits-celtic-fortune-27507051"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T09:06:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Josip Juranovic admits Celtic fortune as he reveals the Callum McGregor photo that makes him giggle  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Rogic’s Aaron Mooy Comments Come to Light]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/tom-rogics-aaron-mooy-comments-come-to-light/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/tom-rogics-aaron-mooy-comments-come-to-light/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T09:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Celtic’s pursuit of Aaron Mooy looks set to end in success, a quote from ex-Celtic midfielder Tom Rogic has come to light. The Hoops Icon left the club this summer after ten years of brilliant service where he helped the bhoys make history. Tom has played with a lot of great footballers in his […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artur Boruc reveals Celtic love that led to him turning down Arsenal after Arsene Wenger phone call - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEJeJD7SLC8uXCLcWempczW4qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-transfer-news/artur-boruc-reveals-celtic-love-27506900"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T08:54:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artur Boruc reveals Celtic love that led to him turning down Arsenal after Arsene Wenger phone call  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maeda running on empty and the reason he doesn’t watch football on TV]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/maeda-running-on-empty-and-the-reason-he-doesnt-watch-football-on-tv/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/maeda-running-on-empty-and-the-reason-he-doesnt-watch-football-on-tv/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T08:47:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gradually Daizen Maeda is building up towards full fitness after just two weeks break after a season and a half of football in the J-League then immediately after it’s conclusion in the Scottish Premiership for the second half of last season. That was then followed by an international call-up for Japan so his long run Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic learning lessons as Aaron Mooy contract factor sweetens the deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-learning-lessons-as-aaron-mooy-contract-details-sweeten-the-deal/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-learning-lessons-as-aaron-mooy-contract-details-sweeten-the-deal/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ll have heard by now that Aaron Mooy is on the brink of joining Celtic and reuniting with his former national team boss Ange Postecoglou. As reported by multiple outlets, Mooy will become the Bhoys’ latest summer signing as early as today after talks progressed between the two parties over the weekend. A further update ...
The post Celtic learning lessons as Aaron Mooy contract factor sweetens the deal appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou’s Major Transfer Decision]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/ange-postecoglous-major-transfer-decision/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/ange-postecoglous-major-transfer-decision/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T08:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ANGE POSTECGOLOU has been given a lot more rope than many other Celtic managers when it comes to player recruitment. The Hoops gaffer’s involvement in the recruitment last season resulted in a double winning season. He has earned the right to be trusted when it comes to deals. Twitter can give you a gauge of […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I’M WORKING WITH MY TEMPO,’ BHOY RACER MAEDA’S WARNING]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/im-working-with-my-tempo-bhoy-racer-maedas-warning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/im-working-with-my-tempo-bhoy-racer-maedas-warning/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T08:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAIZEN MAEDA certainly hit the ground running in his Celtic career. The Japan international striker scored within four minutes of his Hoops debut as Ange Postecoglou’s side beat Hibs 2-0 at Parkhead on January 17. Maeda had arrived on Hogmanay as part of the ambitious triple swoop on the J-League with midfielders Reo Hatate and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic set to sign ex-St Mirren star - one-time £8million recruit could be Tom Rogic replacement]]></title>
        <id>3771681</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotsman.com/sport/football/celtic/celtic-set-to-sign-ex-st-mirren-star-one-time-ps8million-recruit-could-be-tom-rogic-replacement-3771681"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T08:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are understood to be closing in on a deal for former St Mirren midfielder Aaron Mooy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Sked</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy closing in on Celtic move after turning down English Championship interest]]></title>
        <id>2ace477e5e82104c516b28d14c617436</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowtimes.co.uk/sport/20285664.aaron-mooy-closing-celtic-move-turning-english-championship-interest/?ref=rss"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T07:34:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AARON MOOY is closing in on a move to Celtic after turning down options in the English Championship.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glasgow Times | Celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Aaron Mooy. Ange Postecoglou. Harry Kewell. Massive,’ Optus Sport]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/aaron-mooy-ange-postecoglou-harry-kewell-massive-optus-sport/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/aaron-mooy-ange-postecoglou-harry-kewell-massive-optus-sport/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T07:25:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The news that Ange Postecoglou is about to sign Australian international midfielder Aaron Mooy on a free transfer after his departure from Chinese club Shanghai Port – where he was on huge money incidentally – will deliver on half of the promise that the Celtic manager made on Saturday afternoon after the 2-2 draw with Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: BIG JOCK v THE DOC: EVAN WILLIAMS REVEALS ALL (Part Four)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-big-jock-v-the-doc-evan-williams-reveals-all-part-four/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-big-jock-v-the-doc-evan-williams-reveals-all-part-four/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T07:14:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EVAN WILLIAMS was a worthy successor to the legendary Ronnie Simpson at Celtic after signing for his boyhood favourites in October 1969. However, the keeper, who celebrated his 79th birthday last week, did not emulate the achievements of the veteran shotsopper with the Scotland international team. Simpson made his debut at the highest level at [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda Makes Unusual Champions League Admission]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/daizen-maeda-makes-unusual-champions-league-admission/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/daizen-maeda-makes-unusual-champions-league-admission/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T07:13:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda has revealed he has never watched a Champions League game as he gets prepared to take the plunge in the competition. Celtic won the league last season, earning the right to be in the elite European competition. Daizen came into the club in January and made a big difference to Celtic’s title tilt. […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch ex-Celtic star Karamoko Dembele score first goal and last minute winner for Stade Brestois 29 - Glasgow Live]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEL1vyo5msNzlugfshW2dLRwqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow96D9CjDOy_QCMPvp0wU</id>
        <link href="https://www.glasgowlive.co.uk/sport/watch-ex-celtic-star-karamoko-24516039"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T07:08:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Watch ex-Celtic star Karamoko Dembele score first goal and last minute winner for Stade Brestois 29  Glasgow Live]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: NEW-LOOK CELTIC – AND MISSING OUT ON LENNY: THE TOMMY BURNS STORY (Part Seven)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-new-look-celtic-and-missing-out-on-lenny-the-tommy-burns-story-part-seven/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/exclusive-new-look-celtic-and-missing-out-on-lenny-the-tommy-burns-story-part-seven/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T06:12:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOMMY BURNS celebrated his return to Celtic as manager on July 12 1994 by winning the Scottish Cup with the club’s 1-0 win over Airdrie. The league title, though, was the iconic Celt’s main target as he prepared for his second term in charge of the team that was always closest to his heart. In [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NEW BHOY MOOY SEALS DEAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/new-bhoy-mooy-seals-deal/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/new-bhoy-mooy-seals-deal/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T05:28:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AARON MOOY will seal a dream move to Celtic this week. The Australian midfielder will join his former international manager Ange Postecoglou at the champions after being released from his contract at Shanghai Port. The 31-year-old former Huddersfield and Brighton star, who had a two-year spell in Scotland with St Mirren after joining in 2012, and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer news LIVE as Celtic and Rangers plus Aberdeen, Hearts and Hibs eye signings - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CBMibmh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmRhaWx5cmVjb3JkLmNvLnVrL3Nwb3J0L2Zvb3RiYWxsL2Zvb3RiYWxsLXRyYW5zZmVyLW5ld3MvdHJhbnNmZXItbmV3cy1saXZlLWNlbHRpYy1yYW5nZXJzLTI3NTA1NzE20gFyaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZGFpbHlyZWNvcmQuY28udWsvc3BvcnQvZm9vdGJhbGwvZm9vdGJhbGwtdHJhbnNmZXItbmV3cy90cmFuc2Zlci1uZXdzLWxpdmUtY2VsdGljLXJhbmdlcnMtMjc1MDU3MTYuYW1w</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-transfer-news/transfer-news-live-celtic-rangers-27505716"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T05:25:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transfer news LIVE as Celtic and Rangers plus Aberdeen, Hearts and Hibs eye signings  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy’s Celtic Contract; Transfer Latest]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/aaron-mooys-celtic-contract-transfer-latest/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/aaron-mooys-celtic-contract-transfer-latest/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Sunday evening, Celtic transfer talk burst into life with the news the club were closing in on a deal for Australian midfielder Aaron Mooy. The former Premier League midfielder ripped up his contract with Shanghai Port earlier this year and has been mulling over his options for quite some time. Mooy and the current […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda sets Celtic Champions League targets as he reveals he swerved showpiece final for baseball - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEPZnvTixEhwveEpNNTcyo-0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/daizen-maeda-sets-celtic-champions-27503973"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daizen Maeda sets Celtic Champions League targets as he reveals he swerved showpiece final for baseball  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Calvin Bassey transfer cash give Rangers boss Gio van Bronckhorst greater spending power? Monday Jury - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEANr7W9Q3VkXHw_kDWF_AAcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/calvin-bassey-cash-give-rangers-27502474"/>
        <updated>2022-07-18T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will Calvin Bassey transfer cash give Rangers boss Gio van Bronckhorst greater spending power? Monday Jury  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mooy set for Celtic // Blackburn reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.jerseydoesntshrink.com/2022/7/17/23266911/mooy-set-for-celtic-blackburn-reaction</id>
        <link href="https://www.jerseydoesntshrink.com/2022/7/17/23266911/mooy-set-for-celtic-blackburn-reaction"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T22:57:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Matthew Ashton - AMA/Getty Images
  

 Many have said it should happen, and probably would have at some point, now it’s practically confirmed - Aaron Mooy is all but set to sign for Celtic. 


Celtic are set to sign Aaron Mooy on free transfer. Full agreement in place, been told contract will be valid until June 2023 with an option to extend for further season. ⚪️  #CelticFC Deal will be completed this week after he left Shanghai. pic.twitter.com/9FqfQpkIrK— Fabrizio Romano (@FabrizioRomano) July 17, 2022



The tap in merchant of confirmed transfers has tweeted it, and we should expect to see Mooy confirmed by the club in the next few days.
We’ll have more of an opinion on Mooy on the podcast as well and discuss it thoroughly rather than shooting at this time on a Sunday night when rational emotions are nowhere to be seen!
We’re sure 67HailHail will have one of the Aussie pundits on to chat about him too.
And speaking of 67HailHail, there was a reaction to the 2-2 draw with Blackburn at the weekend: 

And if you missed the game on Saturday, here’s the highlights:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On This Day: Wins over Sarajevo, Cliftonville and QPR]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/on-this-day-wins-over-sarajevo-cliftonville-and-qpr/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/on-this-day-wins-over-sarajevo-cliftonville-and-qpr/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T22:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On This Day, Celtic have recorded two Champions League Qualifier wins as well as a pre-season friendly victory over London side QPR. In 2019, Neil Lennon, having been appointed Celtic manager for a second time, saw out the second leg of the Champions League First Round Qualifying against FK Sarajevo at Parkhead. Ryan Christie opened Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano’s Mooy update, contract until 2023 with one year option]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/fabrizio-romanos-mooy-update-contract-until-2023-with-one-year-option/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/fabrizio-romanos-mooy-update-contract-until-2023-with-one-year-option/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T22:38:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano has updated Celtic supporters in relation to the club’s pursuit of Aaron Mooy. The 31-year-old midfielder is a free agent following his departure from Shanghai Port earlier this summer. The Italian journalist and transfer specialist has taken to Twitter to state that the Scottish Champions are set to seal a deal to sign Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy Closing in on ‘Dream Move’ to Celtic – Report]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/aaron-mooy-closing-in-on-dream-move-to-celtic-report/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/aaron-mooy-closing-in-on-dream-move-to-celtic-report/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T21:38:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SKY SPORTS is claiming tonight Celtic are now in talks with Australian midfielder Aaron Mooy over a deal to bring him to the Scottish Champions. Anthony Joseph has wrote on Sunday evening the Hoops are in talks with the former English Premier League star after he ripped up his contract with Shanghai Port. Joseph wrote: […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy to 'secure' Celtic transfer as Ange Postecoglou talks progress with in demand free agent - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEPm1TxrnR00fXrwyko8zafQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/aaron-mooy-secure-celtic-transfer-27505215"/>
        <updated>2022-07-17T21:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Mooy to 'secure' Celtic transfer as Ange Postecoglou talks progress with in demand free agent  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>