<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::newsfeed</title>
    <updated>2023-08-18T18:11:51.884Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://hooperman67.github.io/Reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The overlooked positive of today's Celtic update on Cameron Carter-Vickers and Reo Hatate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171369</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-overlooked-positive-of-todays-celtic-update-on-cameron-carter-vickers-and-reo-hatate/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T16:12:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While most of the headlines surrounding Cameron Carter-Vickers and Reo Hatate focused on their lack of availability for this weekend’s Scottish League Cup clash, a...
The post The overlooked positive of today's Celtic update on Cameron Carter-Vickers and Reo Hatate appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GREEN LIGHT FOR GUSTAF DEBUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111169</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/green-light-for-gustaf-debut/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T15:29:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEW Bhoy Gustaf Lagerbiekle is on course for a quickfire Celtic, as CQN forecast at the beginning of the week. Brendan Rodgers is poised to give the green light for the 23-year-old centre-back to face Kilmarnock in the Viaplay League Cup at Rugby Park on Sunday. Lagerbiekle was officially unveiled as the club’s sixth summer [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers provides update on transfer work at Celtic with 'pipeline' talked up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171360</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-provides-update-on-transfer-work-at-celtic-with-pipeline-talked-up/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T14:23:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers was asked about the recruitment process at the Bhoys this summer and how much involvement he has in that, at a...
The post Brendan Rodgers provides update on transfer work at Celtic with 'pipeline' talked up appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rodgers confirms new Bhoy is fit and available for testing Celtic debut after more injury blows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171357</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/rodgers-confirms-new-bhoy-is-fit-and-available-for-testing-celtic-debut-after-more-injury-blows/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T13:45:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers says new signing Gustaf Lagerbielke is fit and available for this weekend’s Celtic match against Kilmarnock, and he may be needed after another...
The post Rodgers confirms new Bhoy is fit and available for testing Celtic debut after more injury blows appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers takes firm stance as another Celtic summer exit looms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171350</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-takes-firm-stance-as-another-celtic-summer-exit-looms/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T13:27:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic prospect Rocco Vata looks destined for a permanent exit from the club before the end of the summer transfer window. Sky Sports journalist Anthony...
The post Brendan Rodgers takes firm stance as another Celtic summer exit looms appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘RELENTLESS,’ O’RILEY FIRES OUT WARNING]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111158</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/relentless-oriley-fires-out-warning/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T13:22:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY joined Celtic a month after Ange Postecoglou had won his first piece of silverware as Hoops manager following the 2-1 triumph over Hibs in the League Cup Final on December 19 2021. Four other trophies were claimed in the Greek-Australian gaffer’s two years in charge of the Hoops – and the stylish midfielder [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘MASSIVE FOR ME,’ WELSH HAILS RODGERS AS HE SIGNS NEW DEAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111146</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/massive-for-me-welsh-hails-rodgers-as-he-signs-new-deal/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T12:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[STEPHEN WELSH insists he will repay Brendan Rodgers for his faith in his ability after signing a new four-year contract at the champions. The versatile defender didn’t hesitate in penning the deal which will keep him at Celtic until 2027, at least, and he is determined to “kick on now” in his Hoops career after [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports man delivers worrying Celtic exit update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43495</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/18/sky-sports-man-celtic-exit-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T12:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already witnessed plenty of exits this summer. Jota departed the club in order to join Al-Ittihad in a £25 million move. Carl Starfelt has signed with Celta Vigo. Both of them were starters and their departures were headline-grabbers as a result. Other than that, Vasilias Barkas, Conor Hazard and Osaze Urhoghide have left […]
Sky Sports man delivers worrying Celtic exit update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big boost for Celtic as key injured star spotted back in Friday training after surgery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171346</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/alistair-johnston-injury-update-big-boost-for-celtic-after-friday-pictures/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T11:29:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic right-back Alistair Johnston is closing in on a return to action after missing the entire pre-season period, pictured back in training at Lennoxtown this...
The post Big boost for Celtic as key injured star spotted back in Friday training after surgery appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Faux grievances, summer shocks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111145</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/faux-grievances-summer-shocks/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T11:06:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[European football forever shocks, never more so that when Hibs and Hearts eliminate two teams you have heard of.  Rosenborg’s star rises and fades with the clock, but they are still vastly more experienced in Europe than Hearts.  Coming from two goals down in the tie to win last night was an heroic result. The [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bizarre bitter outburst from Kilmarnock man ahead of Celtic cup clash this weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171341</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/bizarre-bitter-outburst-from-kilmarnock-boss-derek-mcinnes-ahead-of-celtic-cup-clash/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T10:53:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kilmarnock manager Derek McInnes has decided to step back in time seven months to complain about an incident in a match against Celtic, despite saying...
The post Bizarre bitter outburst from Kilmarnock man ahead of Celtic cup clash this weekend appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Podence transfer twist amid heavy Celtic links]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43489</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/18/daniel-podence-transfer-celtic-links/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T09:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been linked with plenty of players in recent days. One name that has managed to capture the imagination of the supporters is Daniel Podence. The Wolves winger did not participate in pre-season games and was left out of their matchday 1 squad against Manchester United as well. Thus, his exit from the Molineux […]
Daniel Podence transfer twist amid heavy Celtic links - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers – Lets Go Round Again]]></title>
        <id>http://celticunderground.net/?p=6626</id>
        <link href="http://celticunderground.net/brendan-rodgers-lets-go-round-again/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T09:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Brendan Rodgers left us in 2019, my abiding memory of that week was a video posted on social media.  Put together by Tam Sellic’s Son, it was video of Rodgers with the music to the “Wedding March” but with the lyrics changed to “You are a c***!!”.  I was genuinely shocked by how many […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Critical Bill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JUST VAR-CICAL: WEE DEREK’S CELTIC BLEATINGS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111138</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/just-var-cical-wee-dereks-celtic-bleatings/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T08:02:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DEREK McINNES is obviously game for a laugh after his bleatings over a penalty call that didn’t go Kilmarnock’s way in their 2-0 loss to Celtic in the Viaplay League Cup semi-final in April. The Ayrshire club’s boss is preparing for Sunday’s tie against the holders at Rugby Park by pathetically harping on about an [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scotland get UEFA coefficient boost; how it can help Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171338</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/scotland-get-uefa-coefficient-boost-how-it-can-help-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T06:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scottish football is earning its place in the UEFA coefficient listing this week with Premiership clubs beating outfits from countries that are direct rivals to...
The post Scotland get UEFA coefficient boost; how it can help Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC KID AGREES DOUBLE DEAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111134</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-kid-agrees-double-deal/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T06:28:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BOSUN LAWAL has agreed a season-long loan at Scott Brown’s Fleetwood Town – on the same day he extended his Celtic contract to June 2026. The Republic of Ireland Under-21 centre-back will be given game-time in the English third tier and the move south was forecast by CQN almost a MONTH ago. Brendan Rodgers was [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IT’S WAR: CELTIC DERBY TICKET ROW RAGES]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111130</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/its-war-celtic-derby-ticket-row-rages/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T06:01:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC are ready to go to war with the SPFL as the club’s hierarchy insist they will REFUSE tickets to their Ibrox counterparts for the December 30 derby at Parkhead. The Hoops bosses have formally rejected the offer of 708 briefs for the match in Govan on September 3. The Celtic board took this decision [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coach’s Odin Thiago Holm claim should excite Celtic fans]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43442</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/17/coach-odin-thiago-holm-celtic-fans/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T22:32:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we have already seen this season, Brendan Rodgers is keen to give players on form the chance to start for Celtic. And following Reo Hatate’s injury against Aberdeen and his own positive displays in recent weeks, one of this summer’s signings could now be set to get an opportunity to shine. Rodgers has already […]
Coach’s Odin Thiago Holm claim should excite Celtic fans - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carl Starfelt sends emotional message to Celtic fans]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43482</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/17/carl-starfelt-emotional-message-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T21:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is hard not to feel that Carl Starfelt did not get the proper recognition that he deserved for his contributions to Celtic over the past two seasons. He was a nailed-on starter throughout Ange Postecoglou’s run at Parkhead. The only others who can say that are Kyogo, Jota, Cameron Carter-Vickers, Joe Hart and Callum […]
Carl Starfelt sends emotional message to Celtic fans - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Hart, Cameron Carter-Vickers and more respond to Celtic Instagram goodbye]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171333</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/joe-hart-cameron-carter-vickers-and-more-respond-to-carl-starfelt-celtic-goodbye/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T20:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carl Starfelt has said his goodbyes to Celtic in an Instagram post this evening, with his former teammates responding with well wishes. Starfelt has made...
The post Joe Hart, Cameron Carter-Vickers and more respond to Celtic Instagram goodbye appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exciting Champions League comments emerge from the Celtic camp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171330</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-promising-champions-league-ambition-within-the-celtic-camp-becomes-clear/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T20:17:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Matt O’Riley’s comments are anything to go by, the Celtic squad is feeling very positive about their ability to make a mark in Europe...
The post Exciting Champions League comments emerge from the Celtic camp appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic rumoured to be closing in on high-profile signing]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43479</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/17/celtic-rumoured-closing-profile-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T19:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been pretty active in the ongoing summer window. They have brought in six new players to the club in the form of Odin Thiago Holm, Marco Tilio, Yang Hyun-jun, Kwon Hyeok-kyu, Maik Nawrocki and the latest to arrive, Gustaf Lagerbielke. At the same time, some fans have been left a bit underwhelmed by […]
Celtic rumoured to be closing in on high-profile signing - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moussa Dembele sends brilliant message to Celtic fans after impressive debut for Al-Ettifaq]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171325</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/moussa-dembele-sends-message-to-celtic-fans-after-impressive-debut-for-al-ettifaq/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T19:28:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moussa Dembele is finding Celtic fans wherever he goes in the world, something made clear again after his goalscoring debut for Al-Ettifaq in the Saudi...
The post Moussa Dembele sends brilliant message to Celtic fans after impressive debut for Al-Ettifaq appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic find themselves in strong negotiating position to land attacker once worth £16.6m]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171320</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-find-themselves-in-strong-negotiating-position-to-land-attacker-once-worth-16-6m/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Celtic pursuit of Wolves attacker Daniel Podence looks viable despite the English Premier League side putting a high valuation on any transfer move away...
The post Celtic find themselves in strong negotiating position to land attacker once worth £16.6m appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic make double announcement about defender]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43476</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/17/celtic-make-double-announcement-defender/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T18:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have made quite a few additions in the ongoing summer transfer window. One area of the pitch that has been in particular focus is central defence due to a combination of reasons. Carl Starfelt’s exit, the unconvincing performances of Yuki Kobayashi and the question marks over the future of players like Stephen Welsh and […]
Celtic make double announcement about defender - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic make it clear they see a big Bhoys future for 20-year-old talent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171315</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/celtic-make-it-clear-they-see-a-big-bhoys-future-for-bosun-lawal-as-scott-brown-talks-up-qualities/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T17:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have announced that 20-year-old defender Bosun Lawal has committed his next three years to the Bhoys and will now spend a season out on...
The post Celtic make it clear they see a big Bhoys future for 20-year-old talent appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic take pleasing strong stance after yet more nonsense from Rangers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171309</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-take-pleasing-strong-stance-after-yet-more-nonsense-from-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T16:53:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic aren’t going to back down in the ongoing ticket furore surrounding derby matches, insisting that no Rangers fans will be allowed into Celtic Park...
The post Celtic take pleasing strong stance after yet more nonsense from Rangers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More reasons to look forward to the season ahead; 8 ex-Celtic players currently in management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171283</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/more-reasons-to-look-forward-to-the-season-ahead-8-ex-celtic-players-currently-in-management/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T16:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The start of a new football season always brings a new excited feeling to not only Celtic fans but football fans in general. For us...
The post More reasons to look forward to the season ahead; 8 ex-Celtic players currently in management appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["There was interest from other clubs"; Gustaf Lagerbielke explains why he chose Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171299</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/there-was-interest-from-other-clubs-gustaf-lagerbielke-explains-why-he-chose-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gustaf Lagerbielke has revealed that there was interest from other clubs for his services as he opens up on why he chose to sign for...
The post "There was interest from other clubs"; Gustaf Lagerbielke explains why he chose Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s final decision on Ibrox ticket allocation; Rangers make next move]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171292</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtics-final-decision-on-ibrox-ticket-allocation-rangers-make-next-move/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have made their final decision on the ticket allocation offered to them by Rangers for the first Glasgow Derby of the season at Ibrox....
The post Celtic’s final decision on Ibrox ticket allocation; Rangers make next move appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WAIT FOR IT: WHEN CELTIC WILL LEARN RIVALS IN VIAPLAY CUP DRAW]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111122</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/wait-for-it-when-celtic-will-learn-rivals-in-viaplay-cup-draw/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T14:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC will discover their Viaplay League Cup quarter-final opponents on Sunday night – if, of course, they do not falter against Kilmarnock in their opening tie with a 3pm kick-off at Rugby Park earlier in the day. The last-eight draw will be broadcast live on Viaplay immediately after the satellite broadcasters’ coverage of the holders’ [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris McCart responds as Celtic Youth Academy continues important development strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171277</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/chris-mccart-responds-as-celtic-youth-academy-continues-important-development-strategy/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have announced that they are continuing an important partnership to help secure some of the best young talents of the future. For many of...
The post Chris McCart responds as Celtic Youth Academy continues important development strategy appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lagerbielke arrives not a minute too soon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111113</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/lagerbielke-arrives-not-a-minute-too-soon/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T12:47:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s summer spend continued yesterday with the arrival of 23-year-old Swedish central defender Gustaf Lagerbielke from Elfsborg for a reported £3m fee.  At 1.93m, Gustav is tall, 8cm taller than Cameron Carter-Vickers and Maik Nawrocki, only Christopher Jullien (1.96m) was taller in recent times. Across the squad Celtic are a small team.  Purists who still [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leeds United transfer target urged to make Celtic move]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43473</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/17/leeds-united-target-celtic-move/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T12:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Things appear to be picking up pace for Celtic in the transfer market over the past few days. They have been linked with some high-profile names like Eric Dier and Daniel Podence lately, either of whom would be great additions to this team and a statement of intent on the part of the club. Quentin […]
Leeds United transfer target urged to make Celtic move - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elfsborg Sporting Director's classy message to Celtic and Gustaf Lagerbielke]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171247</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/elfsborg-sporting-directors-classy-message-to-celtic-and-gustaf-lagerbielke/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic eventually sealed the deal to bring Gustaf Lagerbielke to Glasgow this week after the club officially announced the move yesterday. The announcement brought an...
The post Elfsborg Sporting Director's classy message to Celtic and Gustaf Lagerbielke appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘That quality’: Peter Grant backs Celtic to sign player with 'great power' amid rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171250</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-transfer-news-peter-grant-delivers-verdict-on-daniel-podence-rumours/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant has backed Celtic to possibly secure a loan deal for Wolves winger, Daniel Podence.  Brendan Rodgers is keen to implement his own fingerprints...
The post ‘That quality’: Peter Grant backs Celtic to sign player with 'great power' amid rumours appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amir Mir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GUSTAF THE SIXTH – NOW FOR No.7]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111114</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/gustaf-the-sixth-now-for-no-7/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T11:14:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GUSTAF LAGERBIEKLE sealed his five-year deal to Celtic from Elsborg yesterday, as CQN reported. The 23-year-old Swedish international centre-back became Brendan Rodgers’ sixth signing ahead of the August 31 transfer deadline. Lagerbiekle, who cost something in the region of £3million, is the latest in the second time-around Hoops manager’s rebuilding of the treble-winning squad which [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic star's interesting comments on how the players feel about recent transfer rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171242</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/matt-orileys-interesting-comments-on-how-the-celtic-players-feel-about-recent-transfer-rumours/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the transfer rumours now in full swing, Celtic have found themselves linked to a variety of players over the last few days. Names like...
The post Celtic star's interesting comments on how the players feel about recent transfer rumours appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic handed £12 million Daniel Podence transfer boost]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43468</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/17/celtic-daniel-podence-transfer-boost/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T10:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Jota left Celtic earlier this summer in order to join Al-Ittihad, he left a massive gap in the squad as well. It is something that the Hoops need to fill as soon as possible. If the performances over the first few weeks of the league season have shown anything, it is that the club […]
Celtic handed £12 million Daniel Podence transfer boost - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Young Celtic talent speaks for the first time after sealing season-long loan move]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171235</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ben-summers-speaks-for-the-first-time-after-loan-move-celtic-youngster-sets-immediate-target/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Summers has spoken for the first time after sealing his season-long loan move to Scottish Championship side, Dunfermline Athletic. The move ends a year-long...
The post Young Celtic talent speaks for the first time after sealing season-long loan move appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O'Riley delivers verdict on Celtic's performance vs Aberdeen; states one obvious fact]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171230</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/matt-oriley-delivers-verdict-on-celtics-performance-vs-aberdeen-states-one-obvious-fact/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s performance against Aberdeen, despite getting off to a slow start, was one that still delivered a huge result. Going to Pittodrie is always a...
The post  Matt O'Riley delivers verdict on Celtic's performance vs Aberdeen; states one obvious fact appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I'm a real fan"; Peter Grant pinpoints one Celtic star the club must hold onto]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171221</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/im-a-real-fan-peter-grant-pinpoints-one-celtic-star-the-club-must-hold-onto/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T08:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Grant has reacted to the news reports that Celtic are about to open talks with Liel Abada and Reo Hatate in a bid to...
The post "I'm a real fan"; Peter Grant pinpoints one Celtic star the club must hold onto appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I REALLY BELIEVE WE CAN BEAT ANYBODY,’ O’RILEY EURO BOAST]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111109</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-really-believe-we-can-beat-anybody-oriley-euro-boast/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T08:10:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE nearest Matt O’Riley got to Champions League action two years ago was to switch on his television. Now the gifted playmaker, who was signed for a modest £1.5million from English third-tier outfit MK Dons in January 2022, insists Celtic can make an impact among Europe’s elite this season. London-born O’Riley is looking forward to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers backroom reshuffle ongoing at Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171207</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/brendan-rodgers-backroom-reshuffle-ongoing-at-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic coach, Scott Breddy, leaves the club this week after nine years of service. Breddy was the first-team Strength and Conditioning coach. Breddy made the...
The post Brendan Rodgers backroom reshuffle ongoing at Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC IN DOUBLE DEAL BID]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111105</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-in-double-deal-bid/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T07:17:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC are preparing to thrash out new deals with Reo Hatate and Liel Abada. The Japanese midfielder and the Israeli winger, both under contract until June 2026, will be offered lucrative extensions, according to a report in the Daily Record. Hatate and Abada have been been involved in transfer speculation this summer and Brendan Rodgers [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing set to make very quick debut after strong preparation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171202</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/new-celtic-signing-declares-himself-ready-for-quick-debut-after-strong-preparation/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T07:15:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing Gustaf Lagerbielke has declared himself ready to compete for the Bhoys immediately after a summer of strong preparation in Sweden. The Swedish...
The post New Celtic signing set to make very quick debut after strong preparation appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic board make exciting moves to secure future of top talents]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171197</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/big-contract-moves-on-the-way-from-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T05:49:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic will open contract talks with two of the club’s most important and exciting players in Reo Hatate and Liel Abada before the end of...
The post The Celtic board make exciting moves to secure future of top talents appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I LOOKED DOWN, MY ANKLE WAS TWICE THE SIZE IT WAS AT KICK-OFF,’ BOBBY MURDOCH, MAN OF THE MATCH IN LISBON]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=35538</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/i-looked-down-my-ankle-was-twice-the-size-it-was-at-kick-off-bobby-murdoch-man-of-the-match-in-lisbon/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T04:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BOBBY MURDOCH went through all sorts of agonies as Celtic gatecrashed the European big-time in Lisbon. The painful experience was highlighted in author Alex Gordon’s tribute book, ‘The Lisbon Lions: The 40th Anniversary Celebration’, which was published in 2007. The club legend, who would have been 79 today, was a thoughtful midfielder with a delightful touch [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Belgian club want to sign highly-rated Celtic player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43464</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/16/belgian-club-want-sign-celtic-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T22:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have lost a couple of key players this summer in the form of Carl Starfelt and Jota. Both of them were starters for the past two seasons and played a major part in winning five trophies during that period of time. Thus, their exits have certainly weakened the squad. It is not just established […]
Belgian club want to sign highly-rated Celtic player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano offers important Celtic transfer update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43460</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/16/fabrizio-offers-celtic-transfer-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T21:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have had a mixed summer transfer window till now. Nobody can deny that the club have brought in some very talented youngsters to Parkhead, who have a ton of potential. Gustaf Lagerbielke recently became the sixth signing of the second Brendan Rodgers era, with the Swedish centre-back being signed from IF Elfsborg. The likes […]
Fabrizio Romano offers important Celtic transfer update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic ready to open contract talks with two players]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43457</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/16/celtic-ready-open-contract-talks-two/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T19:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many Celtic fans are dissatisfied with how the summer transfer window has gone for the club. There were rumours about them making headling-grabbing additions to the squad. That has not happened at all. Instead, they have stuck to bringing in highly-rated youngsters and let’s see if they develop into key players in the future or […]
Celtic ready to open contract talks with two players - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gustaf Lagerbielke shares his reaction when he first heard of Celtic's interest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171192</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/gustaf-lagerbielke-shares-his-reaction-when-he-first-heard-of-celtics-interest/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Celtic signing, Gustaf Lagerbielke has revealed the timeline of when he first heard about his new club’s interest in him. The Swedish defender joined...
The post Gustaf Lagerbielke shares his reaction when he first heard of Celtic's interest appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic finally make long-awaited transfer announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43452</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/16/celtic-make-long-awaited-announcement-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T18:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic might not have made any headline-grabbing signings in the ongoing summer transfer window, but that does not mean that the club have not been active in terms of incomings. They had already brought in five fresh faces in the form of Odin Thiago Holm, Marco Tilio, Yang Hyun-jun, Kwon Hyeok-kyu and Maik Nawrocki. And […]
Celtic finally make long-awaited transfer announcement - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REVEALED: ‘I WAS PUSHING FOR IT TO HAPPEN,’ NEW BHOY GUSTAF]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111096</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/revealed-i-was-pushing-for-it-to-happen-new-bhoy-gustaf/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:42:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NEW Bhoy Gustaf Lagerbielke revealed he was “pushing for it to happen” as soon as he heard Celtic were interested in signing him. The Swedish international centre-back saw his efforts rewarded today when he signed a five-year deal with the treble winners in a move from Elfsborg estimated to be in the £3million bracket. Ironically, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers speaks as Celtic announce Gustaf Lagerbielke]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171186</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-speaks-as-celtic-announce-gustaf-lagerbielke/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:13:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have announced the signing of Swedish defender, Gustaf Lagerbielke, as the club’s sixth summer signing for Brendan Rodgers. The 23-year-old joins the club on...
The post Brendan Rodgers speaks as Celtic announce Gustaf Lagerbielke appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three reasons why Eric Dier would be a great signing for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171181</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/three-reasons-why-eric-dier-would-be-a-great-signing-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With transfer rumours ramping up for Celtic over the past few days, the Hoops support will be all be discussing whether the names mentioned so...
The post Three reasons why Eric Dier would be a great signing for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O'Riley explains what he has done off the pitch to help improve his Celtic performances]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171175</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/matt-oriley-explains-what-he-has-done-off-the-pitch-to-help-improve-his-celtic-performances/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder, Matt O’Riley has spoken about the techniques he has used to help improve his mindset and how they are helping to improve his...
The post Matt O'Riley explains what he has done off the pitch to help improve his Celtic performances appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Belgian side named as 'long-term admirers' of highly-rated Celtic prospect]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171153</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/belgian-side-named-as-long-term-admirers-of-young-celtic-prospect-rocco-vata/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T13:31:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Club Brugge are said to be interested in young Celtic prospect, Rocco Vata, according to a report by the Daily Record. The report claims that...
The post Report: Belgian side named as 'long-term admirers' of highly-rated Celtic prospect appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CCV AND THE KILLIE CONUNDRUM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111093</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/ccv-and-the-killie-conundrum/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T12:18:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CAMERON CARTER-VICKERS is fighting to be fit to take his place in the heart of the Celtic defence against Kilmarnock at Rugby Park on Sunday. The £6million recruit from Spurs missed the entire second-half of the 3-1 success over Aberdeen at Pittodrie at the weekend with a hamstring injury. Now Brendan Rodgers could have a [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic player could miss Glasgow Derby due to injury]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43448</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/16/celtic-player-glasgow-derby-injury/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T12:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have won both their league games till now and sit at the top of the Premiership table. But it has not been all smooth sailing for Brendan Rodgers’ side. Their performances have left a lot to be desired and at the moment they do not look like the well-oiled winning machine that they were […]
Celtic player could miss Glasgow Derby due to injury - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Sutton's amusing tale of the Celtic legend who was the club's 'biggest moaner']]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171149</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/chris-suttons-amusing-tale-of-the-celtic-legend-who-was-the-clubs-biggest-moaner/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic supporters have seen a variety of different players and managers who have graced the Parkhead corridors over the decades. From the supremely talented...
The post Chris Sutton's amusing tale of the Celtic legend who was the club's 'biggest moaner' appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qualifiers, cash, mitigating fitness]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111081</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/qualifiers-cash-mitigating-fitness/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T11:09:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lots to consider after last night’s Champions League qualifiers.  Top surprise of the night was Marseille being eliminated by Panathinaikos on penalties.  The Greek side equalised in the 10th minute of added time at the Velodrome in what must have been a horrible way to lose for the home fans. Should Panathinaikos reach the group [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIRTHDAY BHOY FALLON AND THE MISSING LISBON MEDAL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=62740</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/birthday-bhoy-fallon-and-the-missing-lisbon-medal/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T11:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FORMER Celtic keeper John Fallon celebrates his 83rd birthday today. Hopefully, the Hoops legend will be showered with gifts, but none will be as precious as the one he received in April 2019. Fallon, who had been the faithful understudy to Ronnie Simpson all the way through the historic European Cup campaign in season 1966/67, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pundit thinks coming to Celtic would be 'a very wise move' for Premier League player]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171142</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/john-hartson-believes-coming-to-celtic-would-be-a-very-wise-move-for-premier-league-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reports this week claiming that Celtic are preparing to make a move for Newcastle United’s Ryan Fraser came as a bit of a surprise to...
The post Pundit thinks coming to Celtic would be 'a very wise move' for Premier League player appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fabrizio Romano drops double Celtic transfer update]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43441</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/16/fabrizio-romano-double-celtic-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T09:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have brought in a number of highly-rated youngsters this summer already. Odin Thiago Holm, Marco Tilio, Yang Hyun-jun, Kwon Hyeok-kyu and Maik Nawrocki, are all believed to have the potential to become important players for the club someday. But more reinforcements are needed if the Hoops are to defend their domestic treble and also […]
Fabrizio Romano drops double Celtic transfer update - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two obstacles Celtic must overcome to make Daniel Podence deal happen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171137</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/two-obstacles-celtic-must-overcome-to-make-daniel-podence-deal-happen/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With less than two weeks of the transfer window to go, the Celtic transfer rumours seem to be ramping up over the last couple of...
The post Two obstacles Celtic must overcome to make Daniel Podence deal happen appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James McPake explains Celtic's stance when he tried to sign Ben Summers on loan last season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171130</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/james-mcpake-explains-celtics-stance-when-he-tried-to-sign-ben-summers-on-loan-last-season/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Young Ben Summers is a player that has been in and around the Celtic first team over the course of this season and last. The...
The post James McPake explains Celtic's stance when he tried to sign Ben Summers on loan last season appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["I could see him come in"; Pundit believes Celtic's latest transfer rumour could be a goer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171122</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/i-could-see-him-come-in-john-hartson-thinks-celtics-latest-transfer-rumour-could-be-a-goer/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s latest transfer rumour sees the club linked to Wolverhampton Wanderers’ Portuguese winger, Daniel Podence. Tom Collomosse of The Daily Mail tweeted yesterday that the...
The post "I could see him come in"; Pundit believes Celtic's latest transfer rumour could be a goer appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HATATE DERBY SCARE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111077</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/hatate-derby-scare/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T07:39:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[REO HATATE is facing a month on the sidelines and could miss three games, including the first derby of the season at Ibrox. The influential Japanese midfielder suffered a calf tear only 25 minutes after coming on as a second-half substitute in the 3-1 win over Aberdeen at Pittodrie at the weekend, according to a report [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC EYE WINGER – THREE YEARS AFTER FIRST LINK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111072</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-eye-winger-three-years-after-first-link/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T07:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS may be poised to reignite Celtic’s interest in Wolves winger Daniel Podence – a target for Neil Lennon more than THREE years ago, as CQN reported at the time. The Portuguese ace first came to the notice of the Hoops’ former boss back in July 2020 when it looked as though the flanker’s [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC TAKE £1.85m HIT ON MISFIT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111071</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-take-1-85m-hit-on-misfit/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T06:27:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC will take a massive £1.85million loss to remove midfield misfit Ismaila Soro from the club. The Ivorian anchorman, who cost £2million when Neil Lennon bought him from Israeli outfit Bnei Yehuda in January 2020, is finally poised to seal a move to French side Valenciennes, a move CQN reported 11 days ago. Soro still [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[International coach excited by Celtic 20-year-old's potential under Brendan Rodgers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171115</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/international-coach-excited-by-odin-thiago-holms-celtic-potential-under-brendan-rodgers/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T06:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Odin Thiago Holm could soon be getting a call-up to the Norway U21s side with coach Jan Peder Jalland keeping a watchful eye on his...
The post International coach excited by Celtic 20-year-old's potential under Brendan Rodgers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Key Celtic star set to miss up to a month; major doubt for Ibrox trip]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171110</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/reo-hatate-celtic-injury-update/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic midfielder Reo Hatate is expected to be out of action for up to a month after limping off against Aberdeen in the Scottish Premiership...
The post Report: Key Celtic star set to miss up to a month; major doubt for Ibrox trip appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sky Sports man confirms Celtic interest in £12m player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43437</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/15/sky-sports-celtic-12-million-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T22:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already brought in five new players this summer and are believed to be closing in on a move for Gustaf Lagerbielke of IF Elfsborg as well. The club are expected to make further additions to their squad before the ongoing transfer window slams shut in a little over a couple of weeks. And […]
Sky Sports man confirms Celtic interest in £12m player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic announce new initiative in Australia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171102</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-soccer-academy-lay-new-foundations-in-australia-with-latest-partnership-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T21:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past two seasons, Celtic have been hard at work setting up football camps in Japan and America in a bid to boost their...
The post Celtic announce new initiative in Australia appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gustaf Lagerbielke's appraisal by Elfsborg captain bode well for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171099</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/gustaf-lagerbielkes-appraisal-by-elfsborg-captain-bode-well-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T20:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s pursuit of Gustaf Lagerbielke has been well-publicised over the last week or so. The Swedish defender looks set to become part of Brendan Rodgers’...
The post Gustaf Lagerbielke's appraisal by Elfsborg captain bode well for Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer move for £7 million left-back ruled out]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43434</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/15/celtic-transfer-move-left-back-ruled/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T20:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic could do with another left-back right now. Greg Taylor might have done a tremendous job under the management of Ange Postecoglou but there are serious doubts over whether he is best suited to Brendan Rodgers’ style of football. And his recent performances have done nothing to prove the doubters wrong. On the other hand, […]
Celtic transfer move for £7 million left-back ruled out - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Away Days – Aberdeen]]></title>
        <id>https://celticfanzine.com/?p=58257</id>
        <link href="https://celticfanzine.com/celtic-away-days-aberdeen/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T19:10:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s was an early start on Sunday morning for our away adventure to Aberdeen. Tickets are always the talking point for these games or should I say lack of tickets. Once again at kick off time there were plenty of empty seats in the home stands. The away end was packed with Celtic fans […]
The post Celtic Away Days – Aberdeen appeared first on Celtic Fanzine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>celtic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic linked with ambitious move for Wolves player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43431</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/15/celtic-linked-move-wolves-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T19:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jota left Celtic earlier in the summer in order to join Al-Ittihad in a £25 million move. Things have not quite gone the Portuguese winger’s way since then and there is already talk of him being sent out on loan. On the other hand, the Hoops have not brought in a proper replacement for him […]
Celtic linked with ambitious move for Wolves player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic finally manage to agree transfer deal for midfielder]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43428</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/15/celtic-agree-transfer-deal-midfielder/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T17:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have been very active in the summer transfer window. They have brought in five fresh faces to the club and it remains to be seen how things turn out for them at Parkhead. On the other hand, there have been quite a few who have headed in the opposite direction as well, including starters […]
Celtic finally manage to agree transfer deal for midfielder - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yosuke Ideguchi recognised in Japan as Celtic midfielder voted onto on-loan club's God 7 list]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171088</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/yosuke-ideguchi-recognised-in-japan-as-celtic-midfielder-voted-onto-on-loan-clubs-god-7-list/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forgotten Celtic midfielder, Yosuke Ideguchi, has been given some recognition in Japan from his on-loan club, Avispa Fukuoka’s, fans. The Japanese midfielder has been at...
The post Yosuke Ideguchi recognised in Japan as Celtic midfielder voted onto on-loan club's God 7 list appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Doak explains how what he experienced at Celtic has benefitted him at Liverpool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171082</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/ben-doak-explains-how-his-experience-at-celtic-has-benefitted-him-at-liverpool/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T16:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is absolutely no denying that Celtic lost a major talent the day Ben Doak left Glasgow for Liverpool. The 17-year-old winger was tipped as...
The post Ben Doak explains how what he experienced at Celtic has benefitted him at Liverpool appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic 'agree' to sell fringe player; fee reported as club set to take a financial hit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171093</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-agree-to-sell-ismaila-soro-fee-reported-as-club-set-to-take-a-financial-hit/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T15:50:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have agreed to sell fringe player, Ismaila Soro, according to a report from Footmercato. The club are set to take a big financial loss...
The post Report: Celtic 'agree' to sell fringe player; fee reported as club set to take a financial hit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MUIR IN CHARGE OF CELTIC CUP DEFENCE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111063</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/muir-in-charge-of-celtic-cup-defence/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T15:19:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ALAN MUIR will be in charge of Celtic’s first defence of their Viaplay League Cup against Kilmarnock at Rugby Park on Sunday. The match official will be seen as something of a lucky omen for the champions. Remarkably, he has been the man in the middle in 39 previous Hoops games – and the Parkhead [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confirmed: SFA announce match officials for Celtic's league cup tie vs Kilmarnock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171075</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/match/confirmed-sfa-announce-match-officials-for-celtics-league-cup-tie-vs-kilmarnock/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SFA has announced the officials that will undertake Celtic’s first attempt at defending the league cup against Kilmarnock at Rugby Park on Sunday afternoon....
The post Confirmed: SFA announce match officials for Celtic's league cup tie vs Kilmarnock appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The reason why ex-Celtic star Jota's future at Al-Ittihad could be in the balance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171069</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-reason-why-ex-celtic-star-jotas-future-at-al-ittihad-could-be-in-the-balance/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic star, Jota, could see his move to Al Ittihad cut short this season as his new boss Nuno Espirito Santo confirms that a...
The post The reason why ex-Celtic star Jota's future at Al-Ittihad could be in the balance appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur player linked with move to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43423</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/15/tottenham-hotspur-player-move-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T12:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic were handed a major blow earlier in the summer when Ange Postecoglou left the club to join Tottenham Hotspur just days after winning the treble. The Australian had done a fantastic job at Parkhead over the past couple of seasons, winning five trophies. Thus, his leaving was not ideal. The Hoops have replaced him […]
Tottenham Hotspur player linked with move to Celtic - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spending big money in France]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111062</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/spending-big-money-in-france/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T11:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Christopher Jullien was 26 years old when Celtic paid Toulouse €8m for him four years ago.  We paid PSG even more a year earlier for Odsonne Edouard, then 20.  It is France, not England or Japan, that Celtic feel confident enough to spend their highest transfer fees. Compared to England, Germany, Italy and Spain, Celtic [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic are 'admirers' of Premier League defender]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171062</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/new-name-enters-the-fray-as-celtic-said-to-be-admirers-of-spurs-defender/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T10:25:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are said to be ‘admirers’ of Tottenham Hotspur defender Eric Dier according to a report in 90min. The experienced England international (49 caps) is...
The post Report: Celtic are 'admirers' of Premier League defender appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch: ex-Celtic striker Moussa Dembele scores debut winner for Al-Ettifaq]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171054</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/watch-ex-celtic-striker-moussa-dembele-scores-debut-winner-for-al-ettifaq/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T09:13:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Celtic striker, Moussa Dembele, has gotten his Al-Ettifaq career off to a great start after the Frenchman made his goalscoring debut for his new club....
The post Watch: ex-Celtic striker Moussa Dembele scores debut winner for Al-Ettifaq appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic considering move for £7 million-plus left-back]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43419</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/15/celtic-7-million-plus-left-back/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T09:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic could be in need of a new left-back. They have plenty of options there already. Greg Taylor has been a consistent performer over the past couple of seasons. On the other hand, Alexandro Bernabei was brought in for a significant transfer fee last summer and has now had a year to settle into Scottish […]
Celtic considering move for £7 million-plus left-back - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Celtic boss delivers assessment on Kieran Tierney's return to Paradise rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171049</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/neil-lennon-delivers-his-assessment-on-kieran-tierney-to-celtic-rumours/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The return of Kieran Tierney to Celtic has been a rumour that has been circulating in the media for the duration of this summer. The...
The post Former Celtic boss delivers assessment on Kieran Tierney's return to Paradise rumours appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STRIKING OUT: RODGERS ADVICE FOR O’RILEY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111058</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/striking-out-rodgers-advice-for-oriley/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T07:42:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MATT O’RILEY knew the score following an early chat with new manager Brendan Rodgers. The smooth playmaker was told his figures just didn’t stack up after the Irishman had scrutinised his personal statistics in his 18 months at the Hoops after his bargain £1.5million arrival from third-tier MK Dons. O’Riley provided more goal assists than any [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Motherwell's Mika Biereth tells how Celtic star's touch of class helped him settle in Scotland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171044</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/motherwells-mika-biereth-tells-how-celtic-stars-touch-of-class-helped-him-settle-in-scotland/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matt O’Riley has certainly been grabbing the headlines over the last few weeks. His goalscoring performances for Celtic have earned him praise from all quarters...
The post Motherwell's Mika Biereth tells how Celtic star's touch of class helped him settle in Scotland appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's latest transfer target featured on 2023 UEFA 'players to watch out for' list]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171040</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtics-latest-transfer-target-featured-on-2023-uefa-players-to-watch-out-for-list/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s transfer interest in Quentin Merlin is one of the most promising rumours of the summer window, with the young Frenchman already attracting plenty of...
The post Celtic's latest transfer target featured on 2023 UEFA 'players to watch out for' list appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[£3m GUSTAF JETS IN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111056</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/3m-gustaf-jets-in/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T06:46:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GUSTAF LAGERBIELKE is jetting into Glasgow today and his £3million move from Elfsborg is likely to be sealed within 24 hours. The Swedish international centre-back is poised for a medical at Lennoxtown after the champions and the player’s club agreed on the financial package, according to The Scottish Sun. Lagerbielke arrives just a few days [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC IN FRENCH LINK – BUT NOT AT £7m]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111049</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-in-french-link-but-not-at-7m/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T06:18:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC have been linked with Nantes left-back Quentin Merlin – but the champions will baulk at the £7million asking fee. Brendan Rodgers will continue his search of the market place as he strengthens his squad before the August 31 midnight deadline. Twenty-one-year-old Merlin, who has represented France through the youth ranks up to Under-21 level, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Brendan Rodgers told "intelligent" 2022 Celtic arrival about taking his game to next level]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171035</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/what-brendan-rodgers-has-said-to-matt-oriley-about-taking-his-celtic-game-to-next-level/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T05:46:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has given midfielder Matt O’Riley express instructions to add more goals to his game after reviewing the numbers of his first...
The post What Brendan Rodgers told "intelligent" 2022 Celtic arrival about taking his game to next level appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Euro club aware of serious Celtic interest in £7m deal after multiple scouting missions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171030</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/strong-celtic-interest-in-7m-deal-after-multiple-scouting-missions/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T05:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are showing ‘strong interest’ in Nantes defender Quentin Merlin this summer after multiple scouting trips to watch him in action. The Scottish Daily Mail...
The post Report: Euro club aware of serious Celtic interest in £7m deal after multiple scouting missions appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic already handed €12m Quentin Merlin problem]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43413</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/14/celtic-already-quentin-merlin-problem/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T22:35:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is no secret that Celtic could do with another left-back right now. Greg Taylor did a tremendous job in Ange Postecoglou’s system but he might not be best suited to Brendan Rodgers’ style of football and how full-backs feature in it. On the other hand, Alexandro Bernabei has major defensive shortcomings and does not […]
Celtic already handed €12m Quentin Merlin problem - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major update on Ryan Fraser to Celtic transfer situation]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43409</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/14/update-ryan-fraser-celtic-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T21:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fans have been calling out for some experienced players to be brought in this summer but they might not be entirely happy with the rumours linking the club with one such player. That is none other than Newcastle United winger, Ryan Fraser, who is expected to depart St James’ Park this summer. Fraser was […]
Major update on Ryan Fraser to Celtic transfer situation - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic interest in French Ligue 1 left-back confirmed]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43405</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/14/celtic-french-left-back-confirmed/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T19:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are expected to remain active in the transfer window over the next few weeks. The club have both their league games this season till now but their performances have left a lot to be desired. This does not look or feel like the well-oiled engine that Ange Postecoglou’s team was. And there are certain […]
Celtic interest in French Ligue 1 left-back confirmed - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic considering multiple winger options; potential Ryan Fraser arrival hurdle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171025</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-considering-multiple-winger-options-potential-ryan-fraser-arrival-hurdle/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T19:26:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ryan Fraser isn’t the only wide option Celtic are considering in the final weeks of the transfer window, as Brendan Rodgers makes a new attacker...
The post Report: Celtic considering multiple winger options; potential Ryan Fraser arrival hurdle appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["He's a good technician"; Pat Bonner's verdict is forming on Celtic summer signing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171016</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/hes-a-good-technician-pat-bonners-verdict-is-forming-on-celtic-summer-signing/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have added five new faces to the squad since the arrival of Brendan Rodgers seven weeks ago. There will be more, but for now,...
The post "He's a good technician"; Pat Bonner's verdict is forming on Celtic summer signing appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic ready to make move for Newcastle United player]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43396</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/14/celtic-ready-newcastle-united-player/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T18:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a couple of weeks left in the summer transfer window, it appears that Celtic are about to make a move for a Newcastle United player. Losing Jota to Al-Ittihad was a major blow, but the early switch at least gave time for a quality replacement to be brought in. There is some cover available, […]
Celtic ready to make move for Newcastle United player - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>StevieMac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neil Lennon says Celtic must reinforce two key areas for the upcoming Champions League campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171018</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/neil-lennon-says-celtic-must-reinforce-two-key-areas-for-the-upcoming-champions-league-campaign/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T17:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are certainly going to add more new faces in the transfer window this summer. Brendan Rodgers has already stated that he intends to have...
The post Neil Lennon says Celtic must reinforce two key areas for the upcoming Champions League campaign appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic fend off Brighton and other English clubs to tie down two highly-rated young talents]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171009</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/celtic-youth/celtic-fend-off-brighton-and-other-english-clubs-to-tie-down-two-highly-rated-young-talents/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic made the announcement today that 13 players have put pen to paper on their first professional contracts at the club, and there were two...
The post Celtic fend off Brighton and other English clubs to tie down two highly-rated young talents appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtic star that has found a new spring in his step under Brendan Rodgers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=171000</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/brendan-rodgers-effect-in-full-view-as-celtic-star-finds-a-new-lease-of-life-under-new-boss/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager, Brendan Rodgers, swept into Paradise this summer in a blaze of publicity this summer. Whilst many fans were unsure of the move, there...
The post The Celtic star that has found a new spring in his step under Brendan Rodgers appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reported Celtic transfer target makes UEFA Super Cup squad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170996</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/reported-celtic-transfer-target-makes-uefa-super-cup-squad/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reported Celtic transfer target James McAtee is clearly highly thought of at Manchester City, with Pep Guardiola including him in first-team activities this week. McAtee...
The post Reported Celtic transfer target makes UEFA Super Cup squad appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UNIQUE ANGLE: KYOGO – 56 AND COUNTING]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111041</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/unique-angle-kyogo-56-and-counting/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T14:12:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CRACKSHOT Kyogo Furuhashi took his Celtic goal tally to 56 in just over two years with his whiplash right-foot effort in the 3-1 win over Aberdeen at Pittodrie yesterday, The Japanese international striker seized on a misdirected header from the unfortunate Nicky Devlin to drive a blistering shot wide of the helpless Kelle Roos to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic's next 9 fixtures and the big test ahead for Brendan Rodgers' squad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170991</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/the-next-nine-domestic-fixtures-are-set-to-test-brendan-rodgers-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic have already negotiated a tough away fixture this season. The away trip to Pittodrie is about as tough a challenge as you can get....
The post Celtic's next 9 fixtures and the big test ahead for Brendan Rodgers' squad appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[POLISH UP YOU ACT, MAIK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111038</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/polish-up-you-act-maik/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T12:48:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IF new Bhoy Maik Nawrocki had any doubts about what is required to perform in the Celtic defence before the weekend, he certainly knows now! The £4.3million recruit from Legia Warsaw played his first competitive 90 minutes for the champions in the hard-fought 3-1 win over Aberdeen at Pittodrie yesterday. Nawrocki, 22, was rushed into [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic ready to make their move for Premier League player and it could be a bargain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170971</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/celtic-ready-to-make-their-move-for-premier-league-player-and-it-could-be-a-bargain/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T12:06:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are preparing a move for Newcastle and Scotland winger Ryan Fraser, The Northern Echo has reported this afternoon. Fraser is surplus to requirements on...
The post Celtic ready to make their move for Premier League player and it could be a bargain appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dominik Livakovic final decision amid Celtic rumours]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43393</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/14/dominik-livakovic-final-celtic-rumours/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T12:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of Celtic fans have not been impressed by the performances of Joe Hart in recent times and have called for the club to add to their ranks between the posts. The Englishman has been the club’s number one for the past two seasons but seems to be struggling at the moment, as it […]
Dominik Livakovic final decision amid Celtic rumours - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Brendan Rodgers' assessment of Celtic's weekend win bodes well for this season - Opinion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170965</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/opinion/the-season-ahead-looks-exciting-after-brendan-rodgers-assessment-of-celtics-weekend-win/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T11:13:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now, before I start, I realise that there were aspects of our performance yesterday against Aberdeen that didn’t look pleasing on the eye. I’m well...
The post How Brendan Rodgers' assessment of Celtic's weekend win bodes well for this season - Opinion appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yang delivered after control slipped]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111029</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/yang-delivered-after-control-slipped/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T11:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many roles a winger has to fulfil in the modern game, but the most important part is to beat your man, get a cross in and find a teammate.  Yang delivered this yesterday.  With Celtic under pressure, defending a one-goal lead late in the game, he collected the ball on the left – [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul67</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GUSTAF IN LINE FOR QUICKFIRE DEBUT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=111030</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/gustaf-in-line-for-quickfire-debut/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T10:56:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GUSTAF LAGERBIEKLE is on his way to Celtic – and could be in Brendan Rodgers’ squad for the start of Celtic’s defence of the Viaplay League Cup on Sunday. The £3million-rated Swedish international centre-back looks to have said farewell to Elfsborg in his team’s 1-0 loss to Hamaraby at the weekend. And the 23-year-old stopper [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dominic Livakovic's future finally decided after summer long links to Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170961</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/dominic-livakovics-future-finally-decided-after-summer-long-links-to-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dominic Livakovic’s future has now been decided after a summer-long transfer saga. The Croatian goalkeeper had been linked with a summer move to Celtic. Reports...
The post Dominic Livakovic's future finally decided after summer long links to Celtic appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["He was really, really good"; Pat Bonner hails Celtic star's cameo performance vs Aberdeen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170957</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/he-was-really-really-good-pat-bonner-hails-celtic-stars-cameo-performance-vs-aberdeen/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pat Bonner has hailed Reo Hatate’s performance against Aberdeen as Celtic’s win took the three points back down to Glasgow yesterday afternoon. The former Celtic...
The post "He was really, really good"; Pat Bonner hails Celtic star's cameo performance vs Aberdeen appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Journalist makes Kieran Tierney Celtic return claim]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticbhoys.com/?p=43390</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2023/08/14/journalist-kieran-tierney-celtic-return/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T09:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kieran Tierney was one of the faces of Celtic before leaving in the summer of 2019, to join Premier League giants Arsenal. He has had an inconsistent time in London. Not too long ago, the Scot was considered a future captain of the club. But now, he cannot even get into Mikel Arteta’s matchday squads. […]
Journalist makes Kieran Tierney Celtic return claim - The Celtic Bhoys - The Celtic Bhoys - Celtic FC News, Transfer Rumours and Fan Community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sourav Mahanty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic Diary Monday August 14: We Feel Fine ?]]></title>
        <id>https://etims.net/?p=18455</id>
        <link href="https://etims.net/?p=18455"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T08:50:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s no pleasing some people.     A difficult game against a much improved Aberdeen at Pittodrie ended in a 3-1 win for the hoops,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Malph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stan Petrov delivers a transfer message that Celtic must heed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170945</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/stan-petrov-delivers-a-transfer-message-that-celtic-must-heed/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s hard-fought win over Aberdeen came at a cost to Brendan Rodgers. Injuries to Cameron Carter-Vickers and Reo Hatate will be a cause for concern...
The post Stan Petrov delivers a transfer message that Celtic must heed appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["It is a very big club"; Gustaf Lagerbiekle speaks as Celtic speculation ramps up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170947</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/gustaf-lagerbiekle-speaks-as-celtic-speculation-ramps-up/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s reported pursuit of Gustaf Lagerbiekle appears to be coming to an end after the player spoke out prior to Elfsborg’s defeat against Hammarby yesterday....
The post "It is a very big club"; Gustaf Lagerbiekle speaks as Celtic speculation ramps up appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Sinat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers clears up player discipline issue after Sutton was left fuming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170944</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/celtic-boss-brendan-rodgers-clears-up-alexandro-bernabei-situation/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic manager Brendan Rodgers has no ongoing concerns regarding Alexandro Bernabei, but did confirm that he was omitted from the squad last week after the...
The post Celtic boss Brendan Rodgers clears up player discipline issue after Sutton was left fuming appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BIG TWO’S VERDICT ON NEW BHOYS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/?p=110982</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/big-twos-verdict-on-new-bhoys/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T06:27:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRENDAN RODGERS and his skipper Callum McGregor were singing from the same hymn sheet after Celtic’s 3-1 win over Abereen at Pittodrie yesterday. The champions had to remain resolute to overcome a committed and determined Dons side who proved right from the start they had no intention of being bit-part players in the continuing Hoops [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CQN Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers brushes off Spurs Celtic transfer query after Harry Kane sale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/?p=170938</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/brendan-rodgers-brushes-off-spurs-celtic-transfer-concerns-after-harry-kane-sale/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T06:19:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Rodgers isn’t concerned in the slightest about Tottenham Hotspur coming in for any of Celtic’s big assets in the wake of selling Harry Kane...
The post Brendan Rodgers brushes off Spurs Celtic transfer query after Harry Kane sale appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John McGinley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>