<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-07-11T12:22:39.371Z</id>
    <title>ArmchairCelts::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-07-11T12:22:39.371Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC MISFIT CLEARS UP MYSTERY]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-misfit-clears-up-mystery/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/celtic-misfit-clears-up-mystery/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T11:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC loan flop Charly Musonda has moved to try to clear up his mysterious vanishing act only days after apparently agreeing a deal with Belgian club Zulte Waregem. The 25-year-old one-time wonder boy, who saw an 18-month switch to Parkhead cut short by a year as he was returned to Chelsea in 2018, has been [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contrast with Celtic and Newco preparations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/contrast-with-celtic-and-newco-preparations/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/contrast-with-celtic-and-newco-preparations/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T11:05:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are two games into their preseason preparations and have another four friendlies before their first competitive game, Flag Day against Aberdeen on 31 July.  That is six games to get an entire squad fit and ready for 90 minutes football.  As you know, players are rotated during these games, with large numbers of substitutes [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[English side stepping up interest in ex-Celtic youngster after Lennoxtown exit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/english-side-stepping-up-interest-in-ex-celtic-youngster-after-lennoxtown-exit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/english-side-stepping-up-interest-in-ex-celtic-youngster-after-lennoxtown-exit/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[English League One side Portsmouth are reportedly interested in signing former Celtic youngster Jonathan Afolabi. The 22-year-old striker joined the Hoops at the beginning of Neil Lennon’s second tenure in charge at Parkhead from English Premiership side Southampton. Afolabi was part of an influx of young Irish signings arriving from south of the border and ...
The post English side stepping up interest in ex-Celtic youngster after Lennoxtown exit appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jackson’s Latest Sycophantic Ibrox Piece Misses Crucial Bits Of The Jigsaw Out.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/jacksons-latest-sycophantic-ibrox-piece-misses-crucial-bits-of-the-jigsaw-out/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/jacksons-latest-sycophantic-ibrox-piece-misses-crucial-bits-of-the-jigsaw-out/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T10:36:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keith Jackson is back to his Ibrox boot licking best today with an article which is quite astonishing in its desire not to look at the back picture and its clear intent not to join the dots. Everyone who has looked at the situation over there clinically knows a few things which aren’t in his […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James Forrest talks up the early advantage Celtic hold over rivals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/james-forrest-talks-up-the-advantages-of-unique-celtic-pre-season-experience/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/james-forrest-talks-up-the-advantages-of-unique-celtic-pre-season-experience/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic winger James Forrest has talked up the advantages of a longer pre-season without the interruption of Champions League qualifiers. The 31-year-old is going into his 13th pre-season as a Celtic player, having come through the ranks at Lennoxtown and become a key contributor under several managers over the years. Having suffered a frustrating few ...
The post James Forrest talks up the early advantage Celtic hold over rivals appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“And Charlie Tully! Wonderful player, awfie man,” Sean Fallon]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/and-charlie-tully-wonderful-player-awfie-man-sean-fallon/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/and-charlie-tully-wonderful-player-awfie-man-sean-fallon/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T10:07:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Charlie Tully was born on this day in 1924 in Belfast. He played for Belfast Celtic for a few years – a club now making a very welcome return – and then Charlie traveled to Glasgow in the summer of 1948 to sign for Celtic. He starred in the Celtic side for eleven seasons and Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fausto Vera Celtic Transfer Link]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/fausto-vera-celtic-transfer-link/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/fausto-vera-celtic-transfer-link/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T09:38:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CELTIC has been linked with a move for another Argentine player weeks after signing Alexandro Bernabei. Ange Postecoglou signed Alexandro to the club and made the defender the first ever Argentine born player to dawn the famous hoops. Now, it’s claimed Celtic could be diving into the same market again, this time for midfielder Fausto […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ROGIC RIDDLE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rogic-riddle/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/rogic-riddle/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T09:19:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOM ROGIC has been spotted in Sydney sparking speculation he is about to return to the Australian A-League. The 29-year-old playmaker has been without a club since making his farewell appearance for Celtic in the 6-0 win over Motherwell in the final game of the season on May 14. Socceroos international boss Graham Arnold expressed [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo sends Celtic statement which should leave opposition defenders fearing what is to come]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kyogo-reveals-targets-for-the-season-as-celtic-star-eyes-exciting-improvement/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/kyogo-reveals-targets-for-the-season-as-celtic-star-eyes-exciting-improvement/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic striker Kyogo Furuhashi has targeted a minimum of 20 goals as he prepares to enter his second season at Parkhead. The 27-year-old joined the Hoops last summer and was seen as one of Ange Postecoglou’s key pieces of transfer business during the window. The Japanese internationalist became a talismanic figure, helping the Hoops to ...
The post Kyogo sends Celtic statement which should leave opposition defenders fearing what is to come appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo of Rogic back in Sydney, Mooy in Glasgow amid Celtic and Newcastle links]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/photo-of-rogic-back-in-sydney-mooy-in-glasgow-amid-celtic-and-newcastle-links/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/photo-of-rogic-back-in-sydney-mooy-in-glasgow-amid-celtic-and-newcastle-links/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T09:07:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the mystery surrounding the reasons for Tom Rogic pulling out of Australia’s World Cup play-off encounter with Peru remain unsolved, the player himself has been spotted exercising on Saturday morning in Sydney, at least putting paid to any concerns surrounding Rogic himself, whilst also ramping up the rumours regarding a potential return to the Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Review: The Tommy Burns Story]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/review-the-tommy-burns-story/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/review-the-tommy-burns-story/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T09:04:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Tommy Burns story which had a three day run at the Kings Theatre in Glasgow was hailed with praise as it captured the hearts of each audience it performed to.  After a successful run at Celtic Park, it was time for the play written by David Carswell to be performed in one of the […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Celtic set to hold signing talks after latest transfer development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/report-dylan-reid-latest-as-celtic-set-for-signing-talks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/transfers/report-dylan-reid-latest-as-celtic-set-for-signing-talks/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic are reportedly set to hold signing talks with young St Mirren midfielder Dylan Reid. The Hoops have been keeping track of the 17-year-old’s progress for some time, having come through the ranks at the SMiSA Stadium. Interest in Reid has arrived from across Europe. However, it was Celtic who appeared to make the first ...
The post Report: Celtic set to hold signing talks after latest transfer development appeared first on 67 Hail Hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHY CELTIC’S TOP MAN WON’T ‘PLOD ALONG’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/why-celtics-top-man-wont-plod-along/</id>
        <link href="https://www.celticquicknews.co.uk/why-celtics-top-man-wont-plod-along/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T08:37:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JAMES FORREST, the most decorated current Celtic player, insists he will not let his standards drop as the Hoops continue their countdown to the new campaign. The Scotland international winger has won an astonishing TWENTY honours since being introduced as a substitute to the first team on May 1 2010 when the debut Bhoy marked [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Rogic trains in Sydney as former Celtic star's situation remains a mystery - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEHIzWQS_9jVj27VyhDfLZMcqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/tom-rogic-trains-former-celtic-27448172"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T08:32:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Rogic trains in Sydney as former Celtic star's situation remains a mystery  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogoal; Japanese Striker Makes Exciting Statement]]></title>
        <id>https://celtsarehere.com/kyogoal-japanese-striker-makes-exciting-statement/</id>
        <link href="https://celtsarehere.com/kyogoal-japanese-striker-makes-exciting-statement/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T07:59:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyogo Furuhashi is hoping to have a greater impact on the Celtic side in his second season at the club and is vowing to be even better.  The Japanese international made a huge impression on Celtic supporters last season when he bagged a hat-trick in his first league start for the Hoops against Dundee at […]
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On This Day: Chris Sutton signs for Celtic]]></title>
        <id>https://thecelticstar.com/on-this-day-chris-sutton-signs-for-celtic/</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/on-this-day-chris-sutton-signs-for-celtic/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T07:44:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On This Day in 2000, Martin O’Neill signed Premier League winner Chris Sutton for Celtic. The ex-Norwich and Blackburn Rovers forward arrived from Chelsea in a deal worth £6m, then the club’s record transfer fee. Sutton made 199 appearances for the club, scoring 86 times. In this time he would be a roaring success winning Read More]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Latest imported feed items on ArmchairCelts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“We’ve not been there for a wee while,” James Forrest - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiECaFQKnTHCV3U-0x2XtFgM0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/weve-not-been-there-for-a-wee-while-james-forrest/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T06:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“We’ve not been there for a wee while,” James Forrest  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Record Sport team debate all the big topics on the Monday Jury - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiECC8tLBCI6g1wjH1VO54ovIqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-news/should-celtic-boss-ange-postecoglou-27443979"/>
        <updated>2022-07-11T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Record Sport team debate all the big topics on the Monday Jury  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On This Day: Happy Birthday David Turnbull and Euro wins - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEGZpe-aCC5gHAHhPdg_RUMQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/on-this-day-happy-birthday-david-turnbull-and-euro-wins/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T22:59:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On This Day: Happy Birthday David Turnbull and Euro wins  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[€3 million Celtic target now close to joining Rangers - The Celtic Bhoys]]></title>
        <id>CAIiECcPySewsTCfWJbR1xuBepEqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4KKJCzCv9JoDMICkoAY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticbhoys.com/2022/07/10/3-million-celtic-target-close-rangers/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T19:12:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[€3 million Celtic target now close to joining Rangers  The Celtic Bhoys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Cruise Appears At Wimbledon Sitting Next To Third Rate Football Crook. - TheCelticBlog.com]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEEQnetND2tFQmi2WjriHV2YqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowne-jCzDg-bsDMLnLhQc</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticblog.com/2022/07/articles-and-features/tom-cruise-appears-at-wimbledon-sitting-near-third-rate-football-crook/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T18:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Cruise Appears At Wimbledon Sitting Next To Third Rate Football Crook.  TheCelticBlog.com]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Osaze Urhoghide praised by Celtic boss after Austria shift - 67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEAV6AoJiiKOBj3uHGhn4EncqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowr5GNCzDFxJ4DMLbFpgY</id>
        <link href="https://www.67hailhail.com/news/osaze-urhoghide-praised-by-celtic-boss-after-austria-shift/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T16:48:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Osaze Urhoghide praised by Celtic boss after Austria shift  67 Hail Hail - Celtic FC News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Southampton 'chasing' former Celtic star Moussa Dembele as he's made available for bargain transfer - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>CAIiENbDOZYDorLLpHCWo3y2Q_AqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow_-CqCzD868IDMPTfoQc</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/transfer-news/southampton-chasing-former-celtic-star-24450282"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T14:58:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Southampton 'chasing' former Celtic star Moussa Dembele as he's made available for bargain transfer  Football Scotland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer news as Malick Thiaw pushed towards Schalke exit and Ismaila Soro breaks silence after move - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiENkyEglnpryrqXqv3aMT2VQqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMIfHtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/celtic-transfer-news-malick-thiaw-27442571"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T08:32:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic transfer news as Malick Thiaw pushed towards Schalke exit and Ismaila Soro breaks silence after move  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s Champions League challenge as Joe Hart says there’s no point moaning about money - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEBPTrLKgPO_3R57XFdVJ8-YqGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/celtics-champions-league-challenge-as-joe-hart-says-theres-no-pointing-moaning-about-money/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T07:55:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celtic’s Champions League challenge as Joe Hart says there’s no point moaning about money  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers and the transfer bravado is back in Celtic 'tenners' game - Hugh Keevins - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEH2vTT4YqiZ5mwO-W4RUJMUqGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMKXUtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/rangers-transfer-bravado-making-comeback-27439186"/>
        <updated>2022-07-10T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers and the transfer bravado is back in Celtic 'tenners' game - Hugh Keevins  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dylan Reid’s Celtic transfer offer confirmed as Ange Postecoglou urges patience over further moves - Football Scotland]]></title>
        <id>1488230735</id>
        <link href="https://www.footballscotland.co.uk/spfl/dylan-reids-celtic-transfer-offer-24447507"/>
        <updated>2022-07-09T21:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dylan Reid’s Celtic transfer offer confirmed as Ange Postecoglou urges patience over further moves  Football Scotland
Ange Postecoglou confirms Celtic interest in Premiership player  The Celtic Bhoys
Celtic transfer update as Dylan Reid to get Ange Postecoglou sell after Rangers have offer turned down  Daily Record
Celtic transfer update with Hoops interest in Premiership starlet confirmed and bid 'accepted'  Glasgow Live
Offer Accepted; Celtic Closing in On Midfield Signing  CeltsAreHere
View Full coverage on Google News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ismaila Soro seals Celtic transfer exit as FC Arouca announce loan with option to buy - Daily Record]]></title>
        <id>CAIiEE5PGvT7_DgU7rEcgUmtjZ0qGQgEKhAIACoHCAowrueiCTDmn7gCMOjNtwU</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/sport/football/football-transfer-news/ismaila-soro-seals-celtic-transfer-27441297"/>
        <updated>2022-07-09T20:37:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ismaila Soro seals Celtic transfer exit as FC Arouca announce loan with option to buy  Daily Record]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Davie Robb and 1976 - afc.co.uk]]></title>
        <id>CBMiNWh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmFmYy5jby51ay8yMDIyLzA3LzA5L2RhdmllLXJvYmItYW5kLTE5NzYv0gEA</id>
        <link href="https://www.afc.co.uk/2022/07/09/davie-robb-and-1976/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-09T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Davie Robb and 1976  afc.co.uk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Celtic’s midfield general and patter merchant mic’d up at training - The Celtic Star]]></title>
        <id>CAIiENWXgFIh2Ztzpvsh83E1ZO8qGQgEKhAIACoHCAow4rGVCzCzlasDMJyQxgY</id>
        <link href="https://thecelticstar.com/video-celtics-midfield-general-and-patter-merchant-micd-up-at-training/"/>
        <updated>2022-07-09T10:48:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Celtic’s midfield general and patter merchant mic’d up at training  The Celtic Star]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>"celtic fc" - Google News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>